[Episode 25]
Sure. Wait for me a second.
Sure.
Hey, what have you been up to lately?
I've been really busy lately.
Let's have a drink.
Sure, no problem. I'll wait.
Okay.
Where do you live?
I'll get someone to take you home.
Where are you going?
Excuse me, I want ten coins.
Okay.
Ten yuan.
What do you want, exactly?
Told you I'm lucky.
Are you leaving or not?
If not, I'm heading back.
Wait.
No, it's not even two hours yet.
Stay with me a little longer.
Did you break up with your boyfriend again?
You're just sulking here, aren't you?
What does that have to do with this?
Jing.
Did you like dolls like this as a kid?
I thought little girls liked these.
I don't remember.
Okay, I'll go now.
I'll be right over.
Come on, Jing.
I just had an emergency
and have to handle it now.
I can't take you home.
Use this to buy two orders of rice rolls.
Take one for Uncle Chen.
If Uncle Chen asks where I went,
you know what to say, right?
I'll say you went to Aunt Liu's.
Right. Say that. Be good and watch your step.
Take it slow on your way home. Careful now.
Hello?
Oh, come on.
Why can't I pick this up?
Are you done yet?
Almost, sweetie. I'm nearly done.
Just a second.
This is for you. See? My daughter is amazing.
Jing.
- This is for you.
- I don't want it.
Didn't you love these as a kid? Take it.
That was when I was a kid.
Let's go.
[Lorraine Flower Kitchen]
What did you want to see me about?
Didn't I promise you before
I'd buy you a gold bangle
for your wedding chest?
I was strapped for cash back then.
Now that I'm doing better,
I should make it up to you.
No need.
There's too much I never had.
You can't make up for all of it.
I went to see Chen Yi.
Why did you go to him?
I didn't know where you were.
Of course, I had to ask him.
I knew he had to know where you were.
All these years,
Yi has really been there for you.
Those texts I sent you were exactly how I felt.
I'm on my own now.
On your own?
You haven't found someone else to lean on?
Or are you trying to come back and lean on me?
I have my own place in Peng City.
Don't underestimate me.
If I really wanted someone to lean on,
I'd have plenty of people to care for me.
You're my daughter.
Of course, I know your temper.
I didn't expect this to make you forgive me.
You agreed to come see me.
That's already more than enough.
It's been two hours. I should get going.
There are no more buses back to Peng City now.
Which hotel are you staying at tonight?
Have you booked it?
The water is all in the fridge.
Call the front desk if you need anything.
Jing.
Do you still have work tonight?
If you're not busy,
maybe we could stay here a bit longer.
I go to bed early now that I'm working.
I'm leaving.
Jing.
There is one thing
I was hoping you could help me with.
Go ahead.
Lately,
I've been dreaming a lot.
It's always about the past.
It's about when you were little.
About your grandparents.
In a while,
it'll be the anniversary
of your grandma's passing.
Could you come with me to Jiang City?
I'm afraid to go see her alone.
You don't have to answer right away.
I can wait.
You have a sensitive stomach.
Don't eat too much greasy takeout.
If you can't get used to living away,
come home.
Save it like this.
What do you want for dinner?
All done?
Let's call it a day.
It's raining. I'll take you to your hotel.
No, I don't want to stay at the hotel tonight.
Then where are you going? I'll take you.
It's so late. Sorry to trouble you.
Is that how you talk to me now?
So polite it feels distant.
Which way?
Right.
You're back.
Where should I put the umbrella?
Just leave it by the door.
Why is he here?
Maybe we should go back.
We dropped by out of the blue.
We didn't even give you a heads-up.
Are we interrupting something?
Not we.
It's you.
How is she interrupting in her own home?
That's not what I meant.
I just don't think we should stay tonight.
What are you talking about?
Miao Jing, it isn't what you think.
I mean, Yi and I aren't what you think.
Then we...
It's getting late.
It won't be safe if you head back too late.
Dry your hair.
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
What's wrong? Come here. Let me hold you.
What happened?
Don't be scared.
Come here. Don't go over there. Come here.
Did you make dinner?
They got soaked and need something hot.
Otherwise, they'll catch a cold.
If you haven't cooked, order delivery.
We have a hot pot at home. It'll be ready soon.
Will you be staying for dinner too, Mr. Cen?
- Sure.
- Mr. Cen.
Be careful on the road.
See you at the office tomorrow.
Dry your hair.
Here.
Thanks.
I used to keep a first aid kit in my bedroom.
It was yours?
Yes.
You brought him every time you came?
When he came to my place and couldn't find me,
he'd go make trouble at the shop.
Sometimes, when I couldn't avoid him,
I'd come here to Yi's place.
Yi has clout, so he doesn't go too far.
All right.
He's just stubborn.
He doesn't really have any other flaws.
He's actually soft-hearted.
No matter who asks him for help,
he'll do it, even with a scowl.
That's just how he is.
Come here. I'll dry your hair.
Let me help.
You're hurt. You should rest.
Come here.
Is it too hot?
It isn't hot now.
It's so hot here.
No, it's so cold now.
It's okay.
- Tu Li!
- Don't be afraid.
Come out.
- Let me tell you,
you can run, but you can't hide.
You shameless jerk. I'll scream.
Come out.
Don't worry. It's safe here.
I'll scream.
It's you again.
Chen Yi.
You keep disrespecting me.
I'm telling you, push me too far,
and I'll bite back.
I've still got some boiling water. Want some?
Get lost.
Bao, your dad is right here.
Your mom raised you like a little brother.
She's not a good mother.
Your dad will find you a new mom.
Then you'll have a mom.
You'll be a kid with a mom.
Yang Da Jun, have you no shame?
What nonsense are you spewing?
Can you get out of here?
Nice going.
Neighbors, come judge this.
The little boy in there is my son.
They won't let me see him.
Is there no justice? Someone, judge this.
Aren't you embarrassed?
When have you ever treated Bao
like your own son?
Bao is my son. He's our son, right?
Chen Yi, don't touch me. I'll call the police.
Stop yelling nonsense out here.
Who are you?
You're drunk and making a scene at my door.
And you ask who I am?
Miao Jing, go inside.
Your door? I can still speak, can't I?
Everyone, look at this family.
Shameless. They're protecting this woman
and keeping me from my own son.
Did you marry her? Did you get a license?
Did you register? Why is he your son?
I held a wedding banquet. I paid for it.
What about the paternity test?
Otherwise, this is extortion.
Tu Li, I'm giving you two choices.
Either give me the money,
or I'm taking the kid. Got it?
If you take my child today,
I'll fight you to the death.
With what? Nail clippers?
Either give me the money,
or I'm taking the kid.
You're broke, right?
You gambled it all away.
Now you're here asking Tu Li for money.
Fine. I'll give you two choices today.
Either you leave right now,
or I call the police and have you arrested.
Who are you trying to scare?
Hello, is this the police?
This is the power bureau's housing block.
- I'm reporting someone for gambling.
- Fine.
He's right here now.
- Please get here quickly.
I've got something to do.
I'll come back another day.
- Right.
- Tu Li.
I'm telling you, Tu Li.
I'll come back for you another day.
Thank you.
Come here.
Let me hold you. Look at me. It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
Mommy's here.
Don't be scared.
How did you know he was a gambling addict?
I was bluffing.
That was amazing.
When I was little, no one helped me
when I got bullied.
So I learned how to scare them off myself.
Otherwise, the trouble never ends.
To solve a problem,
you don't always need strength or a loud voice.
You need the right approach.
That's how you learn to stand on your own.
After all, no one can protect someone forever.
Let's eat.
What do you mean?
It's all in the drink.
Come on, it's all in the drink.
Does this make us a family?
Bao, don't say that.
Why can't I?
Mom, Auntie, and me.
What about me?
You're Auntie's Bao.
Bao, drink your orange juice.
You can't just say things like that.
Then why is he my Bao?
Because you can protect him.
He's a boy. I'm a boy too.
I live with Mom. You live together, too.
Mom is amazing. Auntie is amazing, too.
Your mom is the most amazing.
Eat up, Bao.
You eat too, Bao.
Eat.
This beef ball is so hot.
Here, eat this.
Bao is a good kid.
He's always wanted to call me Mom.
But I wouldn't let him.
So he keeps holding it back.
You know I used to study dance.
I loved dancing.
But when I gave birth,
the delivery tore me badly.
Even walking was hard.
Later, I had to work hard to raise him.
How could I keep dancing?
But I don't regret having him at all.
It's just that
sometimes I can't help being scared.
He's still so little.
He doesn't understand any of this.
When he grows up, when he goes to school,
gets a job, and starts a family,
do you think...
he'll blame me?
You've done a great job.
At least, Bao has always known he's loved.
He'll have a happy childhood.
If my mom had been more like you
when I was a kid,
I probably would've been happier too.
What did you tell me to get me to Teng City?
You said you'd marry me and find me a job.
It's been four years.
So where's that job you found me?
We're just not talking about that now?
Look at the way you are.
When my daughter and I came here,
you couldn't do enough for us.
I cook every day. You cooked only one meal!
What am I to you, your maid?
You won't get me a job,
so I stay home and wait on you.
So loud.
Morning.
Have some breakfast.
This place makes pretty good soy milk.
Have some more since you like it.
- When did Tu Li leave?
- She left at dawn. She had to open the shop.
Why didn't you tell me about Wei Ming Zhen?
I didn't want to affect you.
- She--
- Next holiday,
I'll go back to Jiang City with her.
She wasn't there when I was little,
and I won't be there when she's old.
Neither of us owes the other anything.
I'll go with you.
We'll see.
Do you want to move back in?
Eat it.
[Haoyun Logistics]
We'll leave the rest to you.
Their files don't quite match the facts.
Word came from Lingang.
Baiyou's cash flow is in trouble.
Some minor shareholders are selling.
And you put your name down at the worst time.
They'll keep their eyes on you.
Liu Bin Bo.
What is it?
I saw him having dinner
with Zhang Bin at Haoting.
Baiyou and Haoyun have financial dealings.
It makes sense they'd meet in Teng City.
But we still need to confirm it.
Check if the third party's dealings
with the auditee are aboveboard.
If it's just business,
why did they invite Chen Yi
before he had even joined Haoyun?
We do need to go there.
Ma Yang and I should go.
You're drawing too much attention now.
It's not safe.
I'll go with you.
Fine, but Lingang takes three to five days.
- Is that okay with you?
- I'll have Xiao Yu book the tickets.
This isn't just about reporting to Hongshen.
It's important to me, too.
I hope this is the break we need
to end all this soon.
[Once I can take some annual leave,
let's go back to Jiang City together.]
[Lingang]
[Baiyou]
It also feels really nice to the touch.
Take a look. It'd be great for a child.
- Let's go over here and pick another one.
- Pick one.
That's 38 yuan in total.
The code is different.
Hi. Would you like me to show you around?
Hi. I have a question.
What does the code on this toy mean?
I'd like to know exactly what it's made of.
The first digit indicates the production line.
For example, the one you have is line four.
Our company currently operates
six production lines in Lingang and Teng City.
As for the materials,
they are all 3C-certified.
They're baby-grade and skin-friendly.
Okay, we'll look around a bit more.
Sure.
How's it going?
Any recent progress?
Since the last report,
we've completed due diligence
on every subsidiary under the group.
We found no risk of material misstatements
in the financial statements.
The report will be issued next week.
Only Haoyun still hasn't been fully reviewed.
We're waiting on some financial data.
They still need to submit it.
When do you expect the results?
We'll work overtime and push it through.
We expect it next month.
Okay.
Thanks for your hard work.
Don't forget to come to dinner tonight.
[Haoyun Logistics]
[Miao Jing's Coming Home]
Where's Yi?
Wasn't Yi with you in the office just now?
What's wrong?
Tell me.
Since Miao Jing left on her trip,
why has time been moving so slowly?
It's been dragging.
Seriously dragging.
No, I was...
I was asking whether you got
into her social media page.
Did you fight again?
You can ask me for advice!
Right now, you have a married man right here.
Go ahead.
If it were you,
what would you do if you and Li Qiao fought?
Make it up to her.
If that doesn't work, keep trying.
Buy her a bag, makeup, something like that.
Do whatever it takes to make it up to her.
Miao Jing doesn't care about that stuff.
Besides, my taste isn't exactly great.
Do you think it's about the money?
It's about you.
It's about
showing you're willing to grovel, right?
- Who's there?
- What are you teaching him now?
I'm not teaching him.
Yi, don't listen to his nonsense.
Come eat at my place. The food's ready.
- Yeah.
- Okay.