[Episode 26]
- Disgusting.
- Food's ready.
Food's ready!
- Coming!
- Let's go, Yi.
You put on the most serious face of your life
for your wedding photos, Bo.
Don't look at my photos. That's not me.
Is the soup ready?
Coming, coming! Here it is.
Quick! It's hot! Watch out!
- Be careful.
- Don't touch.
Are you two just going to drink?
- It's burning me!
- Knock it off.
- Qiao, beat him then.
- You really need a beating.
Don't go easy on him. Beat him senseless.
He's asking for it.
You're always teaching my wife how to bully me.
When are you going to find someone
to keep you in line?
Me?
I'll leave it to fate.
If I meet the right person, I'll date.
If not, being like this is fine.
Isn't that right?
Come on, eat up. This soup is excellent.
I've been stewing it all morning.
Hurry and eat.
The vegetables are good too.
So, tell us.
What's going on with you and Miao Jing?
Right now...
I just don't know what she's thinking.
That's simple. Let me teach you.
When they say "no," they actually mean "yes."
When they say they're "not mad" anymore,
it means they're still "mad".
Just assume the opposite of what they say.
Nonsense.
Absolute nonsense.
How can you assume the opposite?
Everything should be taken literally.
Are you married?
No.
Then, in this room,
who has the most successful experience?
The dog.
Silly dog.
Take this back.
Let them go.
Just eat your food.
Then...
what if she says, "We'll see,"
and tells me to figure it out myself?
Well... that is a bit harder.
But I think
you need to analyze the specific situation.
Is it possible for you
to try a different approach?
For example,
try acting cute with her or something.
- Get lost.
- Stop giving him bad advice.
You always use that method
to avoid the real issues.
You never admit your actual mistakes.
That's why I was so angry before
that I wanted us to live apart.
Yi.
I think first, you need to find out
the real problem between the two of you.
Dating and building a life together
are two different things.
Dating is all about romance.
If there's a little friction,
you can just let it slide.
You don't have to worry about the future.
But building a life together
is different after all.
You can't just leave things vague.
Exactly. You should listen to her. She's right.
Building a life together
is about mutual effort.
If one person is always giving,
and the other is always taking,
the relationship will eventually collapse.
So...
What should I do specifically?
I'm just speaking in general terms.
As for the specifics,
you'll have to figure it out, Yi.
Why don't you start with some simple things?
Call her tonight.
Say things like, "I miss you",
"Are you tired?"
or "You've been working hard."
What do you think?
What are you laughing at?
- Nothing.
- What she said was great.
She's a master of love.
A toast to Qiao.
- To her.
- To Qiao.
Eat. Have some food.
- Are you praising me?
- Yes, we are.
We really are. You're good.
Start with some simple things.
Call her tonight.
Say things like, "I miss you",
"Are you tired?"
or "You've been working hard."
Hello?
Are you off work?
What's wrong with your voice?
Nothing. I just caught a bit of a cold.
Have you eaten?
I have dinner with a client later.
What about you?
I ate at Bo's, but I didn't really eat my fill.
In a bit, I'll head home.
What?
You lost your appetite because I'm gone?
What are you laughing at?
I miss you.
Me too.
All right. Hearing you say that,
I suddenly have an appetite.
I'll eat more later.
You should eat something
to line your stomach, too.
Wait for me to come back.
Okay?
I'm hanging up.
[Miao Jing's Coming Home]
Hello?
Hello, Chen. It's Ma Yang.
It's so late. What's the matter?
Yu and I are at the hospital now.
Jing's mother just fainted at the hotel.
Which hospital?
We're at the Teng City First People's Hospital.
I'll be right there.
Hello, Yu. I reached Chen. He's on his way.
Yeah, I have to wait for him to fill this out.
He'll be here soon.
Okay.
- Ma Yang.
- Chen.
- Where is she?
- She's still in the Resuscitation Room.
She isn't out yet. Xiao Yu is with her.
How is she now? Why did she pass out like that?
I don't know either.
All I have is her identification card.
There is a lot I can't fill in.
So we had to wait for you.
Sorry to trouble you both.
No problem.
Have you reached Miao Jing?
I called, but Jing didn't answer.
She might be busy.
She's been completely swamped
these past two days.
Don't tell her yet.
I'm here to handle this.
Okay.
Yu.
You're here.
How long has she been in there?
Over half an hour.
The doctor hasn't come out yet.
[Resuscitation Room]
Wei Ming Zhen's family.
Doctor, how is she?
After emergency treatment,
she's out of immediate danger for now.
But our tests show
that the cancer cells have spread
to her lungs and liver.
It's stage four breast cancer.
How could this happen?
How much time does she have?
That depends on her treatment plan
and how well her body recovers.
If she recovers well,
she can choose chemotherapy.
If not, we can only offer palliative care.
And judging by her current condition,
I don't think this is news to her.
So you should be prepared.
Okay?
This is a big deal.
Shouldn't we discuss it with Jing?
I just don't know if she can get away.
I'll handle it.
Thanks for everything today.
Go home and get some rest.
It's fine, Yi.
We'll get going, then.
We'll head out.
By the way.
Please don't bring this up at the company.
Just act like you don't know.
All right.
We're off. Let's go.
The patient is still under anesthesia.
She should wake in about half an hour.
Her condition is critical,
so she must be watched at all times.
Don't leave her alone.
What about Jing?
She's still away on business.
And now her mother suddenly...
Who could have expected something like this?
Good thing she has a brother.
He may not be her real brother, but...
Xiao Yu, do you think
Aunt Wei could be Chen's stepmother?
I don't know.
Jing rarely tells me about her family.
But she once told me that when she was little,
she came to Teng City with her mother.
If Chen Yi really is her brother,
then that pretty much settles it.
No wonder Chen told me not to talk about it.
That was pretty thoughtful of him.
For a guy who's not even related to her,
he's gone above and beyond.
- Let's take a cab home. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Miao Jing is away on business.
Don't say anything yet.
I need to ask you something.
If I'm right, just nod.
You came back to see Miao Jing this time
for money, right?
You don't want money.
Then you want Jing to support you in old age?
I called Miao Jing.
She'll be back tonight.
Stay out of it.
Don't worry.
It's not that I want to get involved.
[Teng City First People's Hospital]
[Miao: I'll be there soon.]
How is she?
The doctor said it's a breast issue.
As for the details, I'll go ask with you later.
Let's go.
You should go home first.
I'll stay here tonight.
I'll stay with you.
Tomorrow, I'll find a caregiver.
That way, it'll be easier on you.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
I'm fine.
I can be discharged in a few days.
I'll find you a caregiver tomorrow.
I have work during the day.
No.
Either you do as I say, or I'm done helping.
Hey, Yi.
[Inpatient Department]
You asked me to ask Fat Dragon
about Wei Ming Zhen.
They just texted me.
They found out Wei Ming Zhen has remarried
in Peng City.
She's a stepmother now.
His family seems pretty well-off.
Come in.
Hello.
I'm a family member of Wei Ming Zhen,
the patient in bed 18.
What is your relation to her?
Her daughter.
Sounds like she's done all right
over the past few years.
Then why did she come back?
Not necessarily.
The man has a son at home, too.
He should be in middle school now.
My friend in Peng City sells insurance.
When he asked around,
he also found an inquiry form from Wei.
It was about cancer coverage.
But that plan was expensive,
so she never followed through.
Late-stage cancer.
Wasn't she just here for observation
for a few days?
Let me explain her condition first.
The patient has breast cancer, stage four.
In other words, it's late-stage.
The cancer has spread to her bones,
her skull, liver, and lungs,
as well as her pleura and other areas.
In other words, it's spread.
Her vital organs are already failing.
At this stage,
treatment is focused on
easing her pain and prolonging her life.
This is her pathology report.
You can take a look.
The results show signs of prior drug therapy.
But in the past year, it looks like
she hasn't continued with that treatment.
This caused the cancer cells to spread fast.
Then her condition got much worse.
Later, I heard Wei Ming Zhen
spent a long time in the hospital.
The man couldn't support
both a patient and a student.
So they split up.
Okay. I understand.
Get some rest.
Things were critical this afternoon.
At the time, she had
no immediate family there with her.
So we followed emergency protocol
and tried to save her.
As her family, you have no objection, right?
Good.
These are the informed consent form
and the surgery consent form.
They need to be signed by the next of kin.
[Miao Jing]
How much time does she have left?
It doesn't look good.
Given her current condition, a month at most.
Is there anything else we can do?
There are two options.
One is chemotherapy alone.
The other is chemotherapy with targeted drugs.
But that option would be extremely expensive.
Honestly, given her current condition,
both options may end up about the same.
As her family, you should prepare yourselves.
As for the next treatment plan,
think it over and let me know, all right?
[Convenience Store]
One yuan.
Don't pick up this habit.
It's bad for your lungs.
I put the blanket on her, and she's asleep.
I'll move her to a private room tomorrow.
Then I'll go home
and get her some clean clothes.
I'll hand off my work and take a few days off.
I've thought it through.
I still want to go ahead with the treatment.
Okay.
I'm not tired. Don't worry.
Is the little one out of school yet?
Put the little one on the phone.
Sweetie.
Do you miss Grandma?
I miss you so much.
Your teacher praised you today?
You're such a star.
Later, I will bring you a pink doll.
Okay.
Bye!
See you later.
No. Don't.
Call me. If you need anything, call me.
I'll do it. Want some water? Here.
Here.
Easy. Here.
Be careful.
I mean, you're this sick.
Why hasn't your daughter come to see you?
My daughter is at work.
They can't manage without her.
No matter how busy, when her mom is sick,
she should show up and take care of her mom.
What's the point of spending money
if she doesn't show she cares?
She'll be here soon.
Besides, I'm fine.
Your daughter is that busy with work.
Is she dating anyone?
If you ask me,
you may not be worried now,
but when you see other grandparents
holding their grandkids,
you'll start to panic.
So noisy.
The television's too loud, right?
I'll turn it off for you.
Eat a little.
Here.
Good. You need to eat more.
Mei, you can head back. I'll stay with her.
Your mom barely ate. Try to feed her some more.
Call me if anything comes up.
Okay.
What are you doing here now?
I asked for time off.
I won't go in for the next couple of days.
Why take time off? Go back to work.
Making money matters.
To you, money always comes first.
If a woman has no money, she has nothing.
What is it?
Does it hurt?
Feeling better?
Here.
Gently.
Lying down feels awful.
I want to go walk around.
Dr. Cui said you can't get out of bed.
The doctor said
you can still get some air in a wheelchair.
Mom.
Doctor, please save her!
Mom, please hang on.
Nothing can happen to you!
With a scene like this,
they must be fighting the Grim Reaper.
When I die, will you burn paper money for me?
How much do you want?
As much as possible.
With paper money,
a lot of things get easier to handle.
I'm leaving this money to you.
Use it to burn offerings for me.
You don't need to burn much each year.
Just remember to do it every year.
Go back and get some rest.
[Inpatient Department]
- Miao Jing.
- She's gone.
Don't panic.
I'll have a nurse check the cameras.
Let's look outside first.
Hi. Have you seen the patient in Bed 18?
- No.
- Okay, thank you.
Let's go back.
I don't want to be...
a pathetic failure
and an unclean woman.
Even at the very last second,
I still want
to look beautiful.
Don't be ridiculous.
Even if I die,
I don't want to die on that little bed.
Stinking and pathetic,
like a dirty old rag.
What is it?
Jing.
I promise you,
from now on,
I'll be... a better mom.
You lazy bum.
Oh my God, hurry up.
Does making a fire have to take this long?
I'm starving. Are you trying to starve me?
You lazy bum.
What did you say?
Get out of here.
Come here.
Is that how you talk to your cousin?
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean, "what are you doing"?
- Why are you hitting my son?
- Didn't you hear how he spoke?
- Move aside.
- Go inside and do your homework.
Go. Every single day with this.
Why isn't dinner ready yet? It's been ages.
You just can't do anything right.
- Ming Zhen. Why are you here?
- Sister.
I came back to see you.
- Where's Jing?
- Jing? She's inside.
Has she been behaving lately?
She's been very well-behaved.
You can rest easy with her here.
Actually, I came this time to take Jing home.
Leaving her here has been
too much trouble for you.
- I feel so bad about it.
- It's fine, really.
Right. I brought these
for you and your husband.
You don't have to bring anything.
I'll get you a glass of water.
Jing.
I'm here to pick you up.
I'm taking you home.
Of course.
From now on, I'll be with you every day.
And I'll take you to the amusement park.
We'll ride roller coasters, watch fireworks,
and eat big burgers. Okay?
- Okay.
- Whatever you want to do in the future,
I'll do it with you.
Whatever other kids have,
I'll make sure you have it too.
Here.
The morgue charges by the day.
The family should arrange the funeral soon.
Someone needs to handle the paperwork.
I'll go handle the paperwork.
Wait here for me.
I'll be right back.