[OVERDO]
[Episode 6]
[Spirit tablet of
the late respected father, Murong Feng]
Rebellious son!
Kneel!
Bringing those despicable things
into the ancestral hall is unfilial!
How did I give birth to such a bastard?
Even Huo Minxian knows
that you can't have a son,
neglect to raise him,
and then expect him to turn out perfect.
Get your head out of the clouds.
You...
Mother.
Mulan needs to go to the hospital.
We'll leave first.
Go now.
[Murong Residence]
You defended Qingyi so strongly today.
But you're not even close to him.
I can feel that
you care about him a lot.
But in front of your mother,
you are always in a dilemma.
You want to protect him,
yet you have to consider her.
And I can feel
that he cares about you too.
Since you two are so close as brothers,
as his sister-in-law,
I should help him out.
Thank you for being so thoughtful.
Actually, 3 years ago,
he was wronged.
At that time,
I really couldn't protect him.
I could only trade 3 years of his freedom
for the Huo family to spare his life.
Since then,
he has been distant from me.
Perhaps he suffered even more
than you have seen.
Come in.
What brings you here?
Sister-in-law saved me.
I'm here to thank her.
So say it.
I only want to thank
Sister-in-law.
Alright.
I'll go rest first.
Don't talk for too long.
Eat up.
It will wash away
the bitterness in your mouth.
I like eating candied fruit
after taking medicine.
Really?
But you used to
always leave the candied fruit for me.
The past is the past.
The past is the past?
In the past,
you left all the sweet things for me.
From now on,
I will give them all to you.
Help!
You can't bear to see it?
But who ever showed us
any mercy back then?
Don't forget what we went through
and where we came from.
Every breath we take now
is borrowed from the King of Hell.
I'll kill you!
What we need to do
must never be abandoned
due to a moment of pity.
[Murong Residence]
With me here,
don't be afraid.
I like eating candied fruit
after taking medicine.
In the past,
you left all the sweet things for me.
From now on, I will give them all to you.
Young Master Qingyi.
Bad news.
Huo Minxian is missing.
Zongqi,
I know we, a widow and her daughter,
are living under your roof.
But Minxian
is your cousin after all.
You can't just ignore
whether she's dead or alive.
Then you go find her.
But where is she?
Aunt,
I have already sent people
to look for her.
You have to wait for the news.
We shouldn't panic now, should we?
Madam, Young Master.
Someone told me
they saw Her Ladyship heading west.
I followed that direction
and found this on the riverbank in Luzhou.
This is...
This is the shoe Minxian was wearing
when she went out
on the day she disappeared.
Minxian...
Minxian!
She just went to the Murong family's
ancestral hall.
How could this...
Murong Qingyi.
What?
Huo Minxian is missing?
Yes.
After she came out
of the ancestral hall yesterday,
she didn't return to the Huo family.
Later, by the river,
remnants of her clothes were found.
The salvage team hasn't found a body yet.
Her fate...
is unknown.
I happen to be in charge of this case.
The Huo family said
if something really happened to her,
they will not only
break off the engagement,
but also...
sue our Murong family.
It must have been you!
You caused more trouble for the family.
Where exactly is Huo Minxian?
How would I know where she is?
How would you know?
Yesterday...
Yesterday,
what did you say in the ancestral hall?
You said you wanted to make her disappear.
What a coincidence.
She really disappeared.
Tell us the truth.
Where is she?
Is she alive or dead?
Didn't I tell you?
It wasn't me.
I don't know where she is.
If it wasn't you,
then who else?
Who else could it be?
My late father, of course!
He's trying to crawl out of the ground
and take away his stupid daughter-in-law!
You...
Mother!
Calm down!
Qingyi said it wasn't him!
Yesterday,
in the ancestral hall,
he threatened Huo Minxian in public.
Everyone heard it.
He also abducted
the people Huo Minxian brought.
Now you say it wasn't you?
Who would believe that?
I think
you're nothing
but the reincarnation of a jinx.
How could you do things
without considering our family at all?
Now,
not only have we failed to form
a marriage alliance with the Huo family,
but we've also made enemies of them.
Oh no.
The planes are out of the question too.
I believe Qingyi.
If, because of
Qingyi's impulsive words yesterday,
Huo Minxian happened to disappear,
it would be too much of a coincidence.
So there must be someone
pulling the strings behind it.
Where are you going now?
I'm going to summon Huo Minxian's soul
and bring her back
for a ghost wedding with me.
Then we'll get her dowry
of 5 planes, won't we?
Sister, let Mother rest first.
Mother.
Qingyi.
Qingyi!
I believe you
didn't hurt Miss Huo.
I promise you
I will find out the whole truth
of this matter.
Mother...
is just like this,
having a sharp tongue
but a soft heart.
Don't always contradict her.
You really think of yourself
as my older brother,
settling family disputes here?
If you want to play house so much,
go play with Qingyu.
I don't have time for that.
Food is ready at home.
Eat before you leave.
Home?
Are you a Murong or a Li?
Let me give you a piece of advice.
If you try to please both sides,
you'll fail both sides.
Sooner or later, you'll have to figure out
who you really are.
What about you?
Me?
Neither the Li family
nor the Murong family
is my home.
Murong Qingyi's men
are taking Butler Li to the pier.
They probably
want to let him return to Feng'an.
We can't keep Butler Li alive.
Have Yinwei find a chance to strike.
Understood.
But just killing Butler Li
won't eliminate
the future trouble completely.
Don't forget
who brought Butler Li here.
I know what to do.
Young Master Qingyi, I checked.
This person is the servant
in the Huo family who found
clues to Huo Minxian's disappearance.
But why did he meet Miss Fang?
Could this have something to do
with Miss Fang?
[Murong Residence]
You recognized it?
Miss Huo's dress
was designed by a British designer
and made by a French tailor.
Even the fabric is custom-made.
It's the only one in all of Nancheng.
With this amount of blood loss,
it's really hard to say
if she's dead or alive.
What a pity for this dress.
The disappearance of Huo Minxian
was your doing?
If you hadn't brought Butler Li
to Nancheng,
Huo Minxian wouldn't have disappeared.
You caused trouble for me first,
didn't you?
Now everyone thinks
you killed Huo Minxian.
Why?
Why did you do this?
You should have
kept Butler Li in your hands.
Then I would have to listen to you.
But you had to let him go.
Now,
he will never say one more word.
Butler Li—
you killed him too?
He did so many dirty deeds for Huo Mingxi.
He deserved to die long ago.
Don't think everything is fine
just because you killed Butler Li.
I know who you are.
I can go tell the Huo family right now.
Go ahead.
Go tell everyone I'm Ren Susu.
Anyway, today it's a bloody wedding dress.
Tomorrow, it might be her corpse
lying on the bed
in your room.
Tell me, when that time comes,
will the Huo family believe you,
or believe
that you killed Mr. Huo and his daughter
and then framed the eldest daughter
of the Fang family in Nanyang
for the murders?
I'm very curious.
Don't say things you shouldn't say.
Don't do things you shouldn't do.
Murong Qingyi,
if you keep standing in my way,
do you really think I won't fight back?
Ren Susu,
is there any truth
to what you've told me?
♪ Hate is the smoke left by dying flames ♪
♪ Love is the warmth
lingering after the wildfire ♪
♪ Love and hate collide in a blaze ♪
♪ Devour me all ♪
♪ Ahead lies
a tangle of joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Behind remain
the bitterness of unspoken feelings ♪
♪ The heart races with every thought ♪
♪ As long as we loved each other,
I don't care ♪
♪ If it's a blessing or a curse ♪
♪ This spark of wildfire
spreading across the plains ♪
♪ Stirs embers that refuse to fade ♪
♪ The love that refused to die ♪
♪ Has already consumed us both ♪
[Li Residence]
Father.
I read the telegram.
Murong Qingyu
really did set up the aviation school.
Yes.
With these planes,
the aviation school
finally has a solid foundation
for future development.
Listen to me.
You must
ruin the donation ceremony
of the aviation school.
Why?
You are a member of the Li family.
If the Li family can't get those planes,
we can't let the Murong family
have them either.
Father,
I can't do it.
The aviation school is a good thing
that benefits the country and the people.
-Moreover, for the aviation school, Qingyu...
-Have you forgotten your surname?
We've been fighting with the Murong family
for so many years.
Do you think we are playing house?
Family matters are family matters,
and political matters
are political matters.
Fate arranged for the Li family
and the Murong family
to raise each other's children.
As long as Qingyi and I are around,
the two families
should be as close as one.
As close as one?
Cheng Jinzhi still suspects me
of killing Murong Feng.
But it's a misunderstanding.
Seriously.
Cheng Jinzhi raised you
to be too naive.
Do as I said. I'm hanging up.
Father.
Fa—
[Linglong Cheongsam]
[Closed]
You're finally here.
Has Huo Minxian been properly settled?
Huo Minxian has arrived home safely.
Don't worry.
We were very cautious.
She still thinks
the ones who kidnapped her
were just a bunch of greedy thugs.
After Huo Minxian returns home,
the engagement between the two families
will continue.
Those 5 planes—
the Huo family won't be able to get out
of giving them.
It's a sure thing they will be donated
to the aviation school.
That's going to cost them a lot.
Just making them cost a lot
is not enough.
I gathered you here today
to tell you some good news.
Our old acquaintance
has finally returned.
The director of Renxin Orphanage,
Sun Rongci.
That old thing has always been cautious.
She's accompanied
by the Huo family's thugs.
Even if she's back,
she'll hide in the orphanage.
How do we make our move?
Once the Huo family's 5 planes arrive,
the aviation school will open.
The elites will gather then.
How could they pass up
such a good opportunity?
She will definitely
personally take the orphanage children
to do a charity performance
to raise funds.
That time
will be our best chance to strike.
Indeed,
only the opening of the aviation school
with such a grand scene
can lure out
this dark and cunning snake.
Sisters,
although we share the same goal,
I was the one who brought you together,
and you are under my command.
I will ask you one more time now.
Have you really thought this through?
Even knowing that what we're about to do
involves great risks?
We might get hurt,
or even...
even lose our lives.
We crawled out of that hellhole
and survived until now.
Isn't it all for this day?
As long as the wicked can be punished,
we will gladly face every outcome.
Good.
Then at the opening ceremony,
we will send Sun Rongci on her way.
[Murong Residence]
What the hell?
I thought someone
didn't like eating at our house.
The pickled cabbage today
isn't fermented enough.
It's not sour enough.
Pay more attention next time.
Hello, this is Murong residence.
Madam.
The Huo family called and said
they could no longer provide the planes.
What?
What's going on?
Isn't the Huo girl fine?
At a time like this,
what is the Huo family trying to pull?
The Huo family said
the supplier paused the transaction
for an unknown reason.
The planes
are still on the supplier's ship.
And the Huo family can't do anything
about it.
Someone intervened?
What exactly happened?
Without these 5 planes,
what should we do about
the aviation school's opening ceremony?
Qingyi, the planes
you tried so hard to get are gone.
Why don't you seem worried at all?
If the aviation school can't open,
I'm not the one who should be worried.
It was you.
Was it you who did this?
So I'm the one
who did all the bad things, right?
Are you out of your mind?
The Huo family's supplier
has worked with them for years.
If they suddenly made things difficult,
there must be something fishy.
Murong Qingyi.
Go to the Huo family and ask them.
Why do I remember
these 5 planes
being the price for selling me off?
Whether they are wanted or given,
shouldn't I be the one to decide?
Alright, alright.
Stop arguing.
I already know about the planes.
I am thinking of a way.
At worst,
we just won't hold the opening ceremony.
Also,
I'll say it again—
Qingyi's marriage
has nothing to do with the planes.
It seems
in this whole family,
Qingyu is the only reasonable one.
I think
even without these 5 planes,
you won't be short of people
to help you
make the opening ceremony happen.
Get lost.
Let's eat.
Qingyi.
Regarding the planes,
you must have a way, right?
This opening ceremony
is very important to you, right?
That's why you really want those 5 planes,
right?
Why would I want the planes?
I'm just worried about your brother.
You told me before
that I should have had Butler Li's life
in my hands.
I think you were right.
What about you?
Shouldn't you—
like this—
have had Huo Minxian's life
in your hands too?
Only in this way can you control me.
Am I wrong?
But now,
you let her go at this crucial moment.
I don't believe
you would do such a stupid thing.
So I guess
whatever you want to accomplish
must depend on my marriage
to Huo Minxian.
I don't know what it is yet.
But those 5 planes
must be indispensable.
Right?
Thank you.
No need to be polite with me.
The Huo family
was going to give you the planes anyway.
Now,
I'm just saving them the trouble
of being the middleman.
That still caused you trouble,
[Huang Aihua,
Chinese patriotic businessman]
didn't it,
Huang?
Stop it.
Seriously.
With our
so many years of friendship,
why didn't you contact me earlier
when you returned?
You made me wait until now
to have a chance
to repay you for saving my life.
Back then, I was just
an ordinary medical student.
If I had known
that the dying man on the street
would one day have a business
spanning 5 continents,
I wouldn't have dared to treat him
so casually.
I remember you were an excellent pilot
back then.
Are you quitting medicine
to become a pilot now?
Alert!
There's a boat approaching.
Miss Fang, you're really something,
being able to track me down here.
The five planes—
sell them to me at a price
higher than the market price.
No.
You were right last night.
I really do want these 5 planes.
I want to do my utmost to ensure
the opening ceremony happens.
The aviation school's opening
is too important to Qingyu.
Whether you believe it or not,
I am Qingyu's fiancée now.
We rise and fall together.
Naturally, I want to help him
achieve his goal.
Young Master Qingyi,
I hope you can make
these 5 planes happen.
I believe
I can definitely offer
terms that will satisfy you.
How
sincere and touching
you are.
You want those 5 planes, right?
Fine.
Kneel down and beg me.
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
Ren Susu!
♪ Together, we fall ♪
You would throw away your dignity
for Murong Qingyu?
Yes.
Not only would I kneel,
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
I'd even kowtow.
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
You know better than I do
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
that the aviation school
is of great importance.
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
It's not just about
one person or one family.
How much effort
your brother has put into this?
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
I will definitely help him.
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
Back when you used Huo Minxian
to threaten me,
did you ever think of today?
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
You acted pitiful
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
and sincere when you needed me,
but showed no mercy when you hurt me!
♪ We ♪
Today, I'd like to see whether,
♪ Must be together ♪
for those 5 planes,
♪ Forevermore ♪
you would put on a show
of or fake your own death again. me
or
fake your own death again.
♪ Let the tears fall,
let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
If you want to lie to me,
lie to the end.
Don't change your mind
and make yourself look foolish.
Don't you want to know
why I left without saying goodbye
3 years ago?
Don't you want to know the truth
about Huo Mingxi's death?
Give the planes to Qingyu,
and I'll tell you
what exactly happened 3 years ago.
Get lost!
Look!
Up there!
Something is flying over!
They look like planes!
Planes?
Is what happened 3 years ago
really that important to you?
Qingyi,
I remember
those planes
were originally your gift to your brother.
I just wanted to see her beg me,
admit defeat, and apologize to me.
The winner
hasn't been decided yet.
But now that she really has begged you,
I feel like
you're not that happy.
Alright.
Anyway, fools in love
are doomed to suffer.
[Closed]
The aviation school's planes
are in position.
Now we are just waiting for her.
I heard he's coming tomorrow.
That old dog from the Huo family
is coming too?
Is the news accurate?
The orphanage is using
the aviation school's opening
to make a big score.
His coming
won't just be for making money.
He must be planning some despicable acts.
Great.
We can kill them all at once.
No.
Our target this time is only Nanny Sun.
Don't cause any extra trouble.
What do you mean by extra trouble?
Have you forgotten what he has done?
Of course I haven't.
Targeting the Huo family
would be satisfying for a moment,
but what about the others?
Are we just going to let him go?
Susu is right.
The Huo family is too big a target.
If we rashly make a move
on the old dog Huo,
we might expose ourselves prematurely.
We haven't even found any evidence against
the people involved back then yet.
They would go into hiding again.
That would be the real trouble.
But he...
Listen to me.
If anyone
dares to act without authorization,
I will ask her to quit.