[OVERDO]
[Episode 7]
[Zhenhua No. 1 Aviation School]
Today is a big day—
the opening of the aviation school.
I heard that all the forces in Nancheng
will be coming to attend.
Even Master Huo,
who hasn't been out for a long time,
is coming in person to congratulate.
Master Huo is coming too?
Of course he is.
The Huo family spent so much money on it.
Amazing.
Welcome.
-Welcome!
-Welcome.
Welcome!
Is she the principal's wife?
She and Principal Qingyu
are a perfect match.
Yeah.
-Welcome.
Welcome.
Qingyu.
Congratulations.
Qingyi!
Qingyi.
You guys talk first.
I'll go over there to take a look.
Come to
the banquet hall with me later.
These 5 planes
are all thanks to you.
Why would I go to the banquet hall?
To give me a chance to show my face?
You are a Young Master
of the Murong family.
Only you give others a chance,
not the other way around.
This time,
you helped me,
and I'll remember it.
It's all thanks to Sister-in-law
going in person
to fight for the planes for you.
She even
bore the humiliation.
This is true love, Sister-in-law.
I just wanted to make a couple happy.
After all, in this world,
no one would betray true love.
Right,
Sister-in-law?
That's right.
It's the aviation school's opening today.
With so many people
on such a grand occasion,
I wonder
what will happen later.
Brother, Sister-in-law,
let's look forward to it together.
Boss Hai.
It's Boss Hai's car.
Boss Hai is also here.
Boss Hai.
Boss Hai!
Boss Hai, you look beautiful today.
Boss Hai, will you be performing today?
Watch out!
Watch out.
Thank you, Inspector Li.
How do you know my surname is Li?
Only after we parted at the train station
did I realize it was
Mr. Li who captured me.
I really regret
not being taken away by you.
Inspector Li.
If you keep spacing out here,
the tabloids will have something
to write about tomorrow.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
How do I go in if you don't let go?
Do you want to arrest me that much?
Please.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Principal.
Congratulations, Principal,
on the opening of the aviation school.
Thank you.
He's coming!
Today's VIP is here!
Master Huo has arrived.
Master Huo is here!
Master Huo is here.
He is Master Huo.
This is the real head of the Huo family.
For decades,
he's been a force in the military,
political, and business sectors.
Even the largest bank, Hongfang Bank,
is the Huo family's private property.
The old master is over 70 years old,
but he looks so young.
I wonder what magic potion he took.
Master Huo,
how is your health?
Thanks for your concern.
I'm doing well.
How is your father
doing?
Same as usual.
No one is as filial as you.
You will have good fortune.
Thank you, Master Huo.
[Head of the Huo family,
Huo Shaoxiong]
This is
the biggest banker
and philanthropist in Nancheng...
and the founder of Renxin Orphanage,
Mr. Huo.
Miss Fang,
nice to meet you.
Kid,
are you hungry?
Come.
Come over.
Come to Grandpa.
Master Huo.
There were some misunderstandings
between our two families before.
Now
Minxian is back,
we should keep in touch
and make up.
Of course.
We're in-laws after all.
You must be
the one who quietly
brought back the Huo family's planes
from the sea, Young Master Qingyi.
Master Huo.
Three years ago, I was sent to prison
by your Huo family.
You don't recognize me now?
Look at your memory—
take care of your health.
Minxian married
such a fearless tiger.
I wonder,
if Minxian's deceased father
knew about this in the underworld,
would he be gratified
or worried?
I don't know if he knows,
but if you want to know,
you can go down and ask him.
The Huo family's generous donation
of 5 planes
is truly a feat worth praising.
Today is the test flight.
Master Huo, please do us the honor.
Please proceed to the banquet hall.
The aviation school
has prepared excellent dishes.
Please enjoy.
Such fragrant pastries.
Let me try.
-I want to try it too.
I want to try too.
[Renxin Orphanage Director,
Sun Rongci]
Why are you biting your fingers again?
Babies,
biting your fingers
is very unhygienic.
Besides,
the people coming today
are all respectable masters and madams.
How much money we can raise
depends entirely on your performance.
Let me tell you,
whoever performs well today
can have an extra steamed bun.
The masters are here.
Smile, every one of you.
Smile.
Smile!
Greetings, Master Huo.
This is...
This is the director of Renxin Orphanage.
Everyone knows
the Huo family has been doing charity
for over 20 years.
Renxin Orphanage
is the fruit of our labor.
Nanny Sun has been dedicated
to taking care
of these children for over 20 years.
She has done her utmost,
and her hard work is highly appreciated.
I've long heard
Master Huo is a man of great love.
This is truly a great virtue.
I'm flattered.
I just want to repay
the kindness Master Huo gave
over 20 years ago.
I'm doing it willingly
for the sake of the children.
It's nothing worth mentioning.
What a group of good kids.
You've taught them well.
They are so quiet and sensible.
Today is the opening day
of Qingyu's aviation school.
Grandfather specially brought the children
to perform for you,
in order to help Qingyu
accumulate virtue.
I just want to let these children
go out more
and broaden their horizons.
There's nothing else.
Master Huo,
our Murong family
has served
in the military for generations,
so we have killed too much.
Today is a good opportunity
to raise funds for the children.
Good.
Very good.
They call it a fundraiser,
but doesn't it
all go into their pockets in the end?
Come on.
-Turn right.
-The Huo family suffered this time.
This little donation is nothing.
Let's go, Mother.
Wait.
Turn right, be good.
Don't fall.
Nanny Sun.
Miss Fang.
What brings you here?
The children are going to perform soon.
I came to take a look.
Don't get your hands dirty.
You really taught them well, Nanny Sun.
These young children
are as quiet as the living dead.
Miss Fang,
you're right.
They are like the living dead
indeed.
Don't you find these children pitiful?
They are either sick or disabled,
and none of them have a home.
If it weren't for Master Huo's kindness
to build this orphanage,
wouldn't they all
freeze to death
or starve to death on the streets?
Am I right?
For these children
to be where they are today,
Nanny Sun and Master Huo
really went to great lengths.
I wouldn't dare say so.
We need people like Miss Fang
to support us.
Nanny, go ahead with your work.
If you miss the donation,
that would be a real pity.
Thank you for the reminder, Miss Fang.
I'll go now.
I'll...
go right now.
Um...
Well,
may I ask, Miss Fang,
have we met somewhere before?
Perhaps you've mistaken me
for someone else, Nanny.
Mistaken?
Old people
do have a bad memory.
My apologies.
My apologies...
Come, children.
Let's go.
Go.
Slowly.
She has forgotten all about us.
But her face
has long been carved into my bones.
We stick to the plan.
Today is the day she dies.
You followed me?
Don't be so paranoid.
I just found these children a bit strange,
so I came to take a look.
What did you find?
Nothing much, actually.
It's just that
I can tell the difference between
being well-behaved and quiet naturally
and being so
from having to read the room.
After all,
I also grew up reading the room.
The performance just now
-was really touching.
-Grandfather.
-Don't worry.
-I won't keep it from you all...
-We've booked the goods.
-Miss Hai Tangqing, famous star of Nancheng, is also here.
She just told me backstage,
she was very moved
by Mr. Huo's kindness,
and decided to perform
for Renxin Orphanage,
to raise funds.
Her compassion for the world
is an example to us all.
I'll go on stage
and keep everyone under control.
I tampered with the food Nanny Sun ate.
When she goes out,
you follow her.
Where are you going, Miss Fang?
I'm going out for a bit.
Boss Hai.
Today is a big day
for my brother and sister-in-law.
I would like to
request a performance
for Miss Fang.
Which performance would you like?
The Peony Pavilion:
The Resurrection.
Quick,
hurry up.
Who is he to call the shots?
We aren't prepared at all.
Young Master Qingyi has a strange temper.
We can't afford to offend him.
Hurry up.
Did he notice something?
I hope I'm wrong.
♪ Old aunt ♪
♪ Arrived at the backyard ♪
♪ To see only a pavilion of rubble ♪
♪ With thorns and thistles on the ground ♪
Do you think
the dead can come back to life?
Ren Susu.
If you really cared about me,
how could you bear to
why did you leave without saying goodbye
3 years ago?
♪ The grass grows in spring ♪
♪ I remember the Taihu Lake stone ♪
♪ Is where I picked up the painting ♪
Murong Qingyi.
Trying to use a play with hidden meanings
♪ It felt like a fading dream,
leaving me in a daze ♪
to delay my actions—
how childish.
♪ How do I live? ♪
♪ Scholar, there is no need to rush ♪
♪ Just gather under the plum tree ♪
Where are you going, Miss Fang?
The play isn't over yet.
♪ Miss ♪
♪ It's so sad ♪
♪ Why are you crying? ♪
♪ It's time ♪
♪ Messenger patrolling the mountains ♪
♪ Local deity of this mountain ♪
♪ Manifest sacred power
and show divine presence ♪
♪ Local deity of this mountain ♪
♪ Manifest sacred power
and show divine presence ♪
♪ Aunt ♪
♪ Open the mountain today ♪
♪ To invite Du Liniang to rise ♪
♪ I don't want them dead ♪
♪ Only alive ♪
What exactly is it
that makes you insist on taking risks?
What's going on?
Tasia planted a bomb
on Master Huo's plane.
Did you know about that?
What did you say?
Our target this time is only Nanny Sun.
Don't cause any extra trouble.
The Huo family is too big a target.
If we rashly make a move
on the old dog Huo,
we might expose ourselves prematurely.
We haven't even found any evidence against
the people involved back then yet.
They would go into hiding again.
Are we just going to let him go?
Old dog Huo can't die yet.
Think of something, Susu.
[Teacher of Zhenhua Aviation School,
Ye Zhihong]
Grandfather,
she is Ye Zhihong,
a teacher at the aviation school.
She is also the school's
first female pilot.
During the test flight later,
she will fly the plane for you.
Master Huo.
Truly a heroine who outshines men.
I don't drink.
Know your place.
The Huo family donated the plane for free.
Can't you at least show some respect?
The aviation school has rules—
no drinking before flying.
Besides,
if I drink,
would Master Huo dare to fly with me?
I gave this order.
Mr. Huo is an important guest.
Ensuring your safety is our top priority,
isn't it?
Mr. Huo,
please.
Master Huo,
this plane just arrived
at the aviation school.
Ms. Ye might not be familiar
with its performance yet.
We should use an old model.
Qingyu,
what do you think?
This is the plane
donated by the Huo family.
Why can't I take it?
You can.
I will fly it.
Why are you messing around?
Do you even know how to fly?
My flying skills
were taught personally by my brother.
What,
doubting the principal
of the aviation school?
Even if you dare to fly it,
others might not dare to take it.
No one is familiar with this new plane.
If something happens up there,
no one would be able to control it.
You worry too much, Miss Fang.
Let's use this one.
Ms. Ye and I will take a spin.
Master Huo.
As long as I'm around today,
Ms. Ye is not flying.
Why don't you, Master Huo,
go up for a spin with me?
Miss Fang,
shall we go for a spin?
Threatening me?
Qingyi!
When will you stop this nonsense?
Come down!
If Miss Fang won't, Qingyu, you can.
If we brothers test fly together,
breaking through the clouds,
and dying together,
it would be a good story.
Did he find out something?
I'll go.
Go do your work.
You have so many VIPs to entertain,
and you need to appease Master Huo.
Don't worry.
Flying with me,
aren't you afraid
something might happen up there,
and nobody can control it?
Let's find out.
Taking off in such a short distance.
Amazing!
As expected of the Cheng Army.
That's Young Master Qingyi
up there, right?
Yes.
His flying skills are amazing.
Yeah.
Mother.
He's showing off again.
I really
despise him from the bottom of my heart.
Dundun.
Who is it?
Who is she calling?
Dundun.
-Come here.
-Whose nickname is Dundun?
The principal's nickname is Dundun?
Come.
Drink.
Sister.
There are so many outsiders here.
Don't call me by my childhood name.
Got it.
You are just like Dudu.
All right.
Today is a big day
for the aviation school.
How could you let him fly?
We are all Young Masters
of the Murong family.
It's the same whoever flies.
He doesn't even know his own limits.
He just loves to show off.
Though he has the Murong family blood,
he's different from us.
Exactly.
Remember,
you
are the one
who holds up the Murong family.
Why did you insist on flying this plane
and forcing me to join you?
What are you up to?
Didn't you promise to tell me
the truth about 3 years ago?
Speak.
It's just the two of us now.
You can say it freely.
Do you remember 3 years ago,
I told you
I had something very important
to do?
Have you seen this girl?
She has a mole on her left cheek.
She's easy to recognize.
No.
Lan is in Beicheng,
a place called Yu Estate.
That is the base camp
of the Huo family in Beicheng.
Hard work pays off.
We finally found traces of Lan.
We learned that
she was in the Huo Mansion in Beicheng.
Though I had never been to Beicheng,
I was not unfamiliar with it.
At that time, you and I had been
corresponding for a long time.
But I came to Beicheng
only to find Lan.
I never thought of using you.
But I overestimated myself.
The Huo Mansion was heavily guarded.
I tried many times to sneak in,
but failed every time,
covered in injuries.
Fortunately, my companion saved me.
Although we couldn't
sneak into the Huo Mansion,
at least we learned Lan's
location in Yu Estate.
I'll be gentler.
Don't worry.
Although I couldn't sneak in today,
I've roughly figured out
the layout of Yu Estate.
Lan
should be in
the courtyard behind the garden.
Wake up!
It's the landlord's alarm clock
for the night shift.
Not the alarm
from when the orphanage abused us.
It's all in the past.
I'm looking for an opportunity
for my senior to take me
to the inner courtyard to sing.
But I don't know how long that will take.
We will definitely find a way to get in.
It's snowing in Beicheng.
Just like that,
to wait for the right moment
to rescue Lan,
I stayed in Beicheng.
And then,
I unexpectedly met you.
The person from the letters
-appeared right in front of me.
-Is it you?
As for what happened next,
you already know.
Those were the happiest days of my life
since I grew up.
Until I found out
about your relationship
with the Huo family.
Susu.
A family friend, the Huo family,
is holding a banquet in Beicheng.
Qingyu asked me to attend on his behalf.
Come with me.
For Lan,
I had to use you to enter the Huo family.
This might be my only chance.
Go ahead and do your thing.
I want to go take a walk in the garden.
I'll go first.
After sending you away,
I started to carry out my plan.
That was the first time
since I came to Beicheng
that I was so close to Lan—
and also the last.
Lan.