[alarm beeps]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILDREN WERE FILMED SAFELY
GEN AI WAS USED FOR SOME SCENES
The thing is, the more I like you,
the smaller I become.
You know what I mean?
Tell me, how come I have to bear
the weight of your past too?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I'm not as strong
as you are.
[wistful music playing]
[Si-woo] I never tried
to stop anyone from leaving me.
I always respected their decision.
It was my way of being considerate,
while also protecting my pride.
But I can't do that this time.
[scanner beeps]
No matter how pathetic or broken I become…
I don't want to let this person go.
EPISODE 9
THERE'S AN ERROR, STILL CLOCKING IN!
[wistful music playing]
[sighs] I'm so all over the place.
If I can't process my own feelings…
[inhales deeply] …how can anyone else?
[gasps]
Be careful.
Don't you even resent me after all…
after all the terrible things
I said to you?
Yes, I do.
You said the most hurtful things to me.
And it's not like I'm a saint.
Then why are you following me?
Well, because I like you more
than I resent you.
And to make sure you get home safely.
I'm saying…
I'm not really sure
if I can keep on liking you.
I know.
Besides, I can't promise
something like this won't happen again.
So you're saying something like this
could happen again?
In the same way I can't change my past,
things can happen again
that are out of my control.
Still, I want to prove to you
that there was a good reason for it all.
I don't know
if I'll be able to trust you
no matter what.
Why did you arrive late today?
I was late because Choi Soo-jin's mother
suddenly collapsed.
-Is she all right?
-Yeah.
She recovered shortly
after getting to the hospital.
Whatever the reason,
I'm sorry for leaving you all alone today.
[sighs]
I need some time
to sort out my thoughts.
Whatever you need. I'll keep liking you
in the same way I've always liked you.
Mr. Kang.
Take all the time you need to think.
Just as I promised you before,
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll stay right by your side.
And what if I told you
we should end this anyway?
Then I'll try to do even better.
What if I still told you I can't do this?
Then there's nothing I can do.
I'll just have to give up.
[sighs]
But I won't make it easy for you…
because I plan on liking you
with everything that I have.
I'll stop following you now and head back.
It's cold, so hurry inside.
WE'RE A TEAM
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
[Si-woo] Good night.
[birds chirping]
[panting]
[pants] Hey, let's stop. Stop.
Stop. [sighs]
That happens for tagging along
when you never run.
Everyone's running nowadays.
I was curious.
But I'm done with this. It's way too hard.
-[exhales]
-[sighs]
It's the weekend.
Aren't you seeing Ji-yoon?
I'm waiting on her.
Sure.
-Everyone's got a date but me.
-[phone buzzes]
[Father] I moved yesterday.
What is it?
Did Ji-yoon say she can't see you today?
It's my father.
He said he moved yesterday.
[Seong-min] Oh, already? [chuckles]
His habit of telling you after the fact
hasn't changed.
Shouldn't you go and visit him?
[sighs] It's not that easy.
Do you still resent your father?
[scoffs] At my age? Please.
Your entire life hit a hard reset
because of him.
You're allowed to resent him a little.
I'm sure that's how I felt back then,
but now?
It's just numb.
It doesn't even hurt
or even itch either.
I think that might be worse though.
Yeah, maybe.
[server] Here's your chicken.
[Seong-min]
You ordering fried chicken? You?
And for lunch, no less?
Ji-yoon said she likes it,
so I thought I'd try it.
Of course you went for the chicken breast.
When someone tells you
that they need time,
how much space should you give 'em?
-Is that what Ji-yoon said?
-Mmm.
Oh, wow.
So the time has finally come
where I get to give you some advice.
I'll hear you out at least.
So,
just because she needs time to think,
it doesn't mean
you should leave her alone.
But you can't cling so much
that you get on her nerves either.
Whenever she casually turns around,
you just need to be there,
lingering nearby,
looking a little different from usual,
with soulful eyes.
-Don't stalkers do that?
-Ugh.
You're so dry.
So, you can't completely cut her off
because she needs some time.
You still have to check in
every morning and night.
And end your texts with a question mark.
-Question mark?
-Come on.
I mean, that's the only way
to keep the conversation going.
[sighs] Never mind.
I'll handle it my own way.
-Hold on. I've still got tons to tell you.
-Just eat.
[groans]
Hold on.
Why's everyone gathered there?
[chuckling]
[gasps]
-What are you doing?
-Well, Na-ri said she wanted to brag.
-About what?
-Mr. Kang!
Look at him.
Doesn't Mr. Kang look
totally handsome today?
I mean, he looks super young
with his hair down like that!
His outfit too.
He's rocking that boyfriend look today.
[squeals]
-He looks so handsome.
-He looks younger now.
I'm off now, girls. You can go inside
and continue enjoying the view.
[upbeat music playing]
[sighs]
Huh?
-[chattering]
-Oh. Hey there.
[Seong-min] So, you can't completely
cut her off because she needs some time.
You still have to check in
every morning and night.
And end your texts with a question mark.
[computer chimes]
KANG SI-WOO
[Si-woo] Good morning?
[sighs]
Yep. Wrong answer.
Ms. Cha.
Got a second?
Why aren't you saying anything
about this photo?
What about it?
Take a good look.
This means Mr. Kang and Ms. Choi Soo-jin
used to be married.
Yeah, and so what?
What does their past
have anything to do with you?
Hey, if this gets out,
the whole company will flip out.
It'll be its biggest scandal yet.
Yeah?
DELETE THIS IMAGE?
YES
Then just pretend you never saw it.
You knew, didn't you?
[sighs]
Hey, how did you find out anyway?
By chance.
If he gets put in a tight spot,
it won't do us any good either.
The demo is right around the corner.
There's no need to stir things up.
Are the brochures ready to go?
There were a few rounds of edits,
and now they're off to print.
-And the living appliances?
-No issues there.
-Are we done with the kitchen appliances?
-Yes.
How's the integration program?
It's completed,
but we're still running tests.
All right, so all that's left
is the most important part of Home-AI.
There's still something left?
Yes. Trust.
[gentle music playing]
Just like it happens between two people,
if there's no foundation of trust
between humans and AI,
then our project is bound to fail.
[sighs]
-Sir, are you talking about security?
-Yes.
What can we do?
There's not much time until the demo.
I've been looking for a security solution
for a pretty long time.
Is that what your secret meetings
with the president have been about?
Yes.
And so, have you found the answer?
I'm still looking for it.
But don't worry.
I'll have it solved before the demo.
All right, everyone.
Let's run our final checks.
-Yes, sir.
[high-pitched ringing]
[dramatic music playing]
S W - ENTER PIN
INCORRECT PIN
LONGLIVESAEUM
[inhales deeply]
Interesting taste he's got there.
Oh. Oh.
[laughs]
We did it, Mr. Kim!
The regulatory sandbox approval
came through!
Really?
Then let's start right away!
If we push hard, we can showcase it
at the task force's demo.
[chuckles]
You can work late tonight, right?
[breathing heavily] Yes.
[both chuckle]
[sighs]
Bad news.
I just got hit with overtime,
so I have to cancel tonight.
Sorry.
He must have been so excited
for our first date.
[Jae-in] You can't go on a date
because of work?
[sighs]
-That's super cool.
-[chuckles]
The things you find cool…
I'll call you after I'm done.
-[Jae-in] Okay. You got this, No-ah.
-[chuckles]
[mysterious music playing]
[groans]
[whispers] What's wrong?
Never mind AI.
My honor is completely shattered.
[gasps] Your loan interest?
You haven't taken care of that yet?
[groans]
This is way more complicated than that.
Oh, no. What on earth have I done?
-Are you clocking out?
-Yes.
-How about you?
-[elevator dings]
Come in.
Where are you going?
Well, I'm just going to see you off.
[gentle music playing]
Don't worry.
I'm only walking you to the first floor.
You really don't have to try this hard.
Thing is, I can't change the past,
but I can change the present, can't I?
I'll keep trying everything I can
until you can trust me.
[water running]
You know, it's your leg that's broken,
so why are you making me wash your hair?
Of all things, now I'm waiting
on my husband hand and foot.
Unbelievable.
What are you doing?
[Yeong-mook] Hey, sweetheart.
-[water stops]
-[Hye-gyeong groans]
Can you dry your dad's hair? Thank you.
[chuckles]
Come on.
You can't even wash your own hair?
Well, I could if I wanted.
Then why?
[whispers] 'Cause I'm just milking it.
[chuckles] Having fun?
-So much fun. [chuckles]
-[laughing]
-Stop peeling. It's too much work.
-Mmm. Exactly.
You should've just bought
the prepped ones to begin with.
They don't measure up.
They're wilted and not enough.
So, did you choose Dad
because he measured up from day one?
[clearing throat]
Where did it go?
I swear it was around here somewhere.
Well, of course.
Back then,
no other man could compare to your dad.
Really? What did you like about him, huh?
He always kept his word
and didn't make empty promises.
You think that's easy to do?
I just knew that
he was someone I could trust.
I see.
And now?
[whispers] There's no keeping his word.
He won't say anything at all now.
[chuckles] Come on, Mom.
Just give him a little time.
Then I'll grow old just waiting.
I was washing his hair earlier,
and there were so many gray patches.
When did he get so old?
Don't let your precious years
just slip by either, okay?
Mmm.
So, Mom,
what kind of man
do you want me to be with?
Well, as your mother,
I just want someone who will put up
with you, no matter the attitude.
Oh, when do I ever have an attitude?
I just mean I hope that it's someone
who loves you that much.
It should be overflowing,
so it's okay even if it spills a little.
[Si-woo]
Take all the time you need to think.
I'll keep liking you in the same way
I've always liked you.
Seriously, I told you not to come out.
I need to keep moving
so that it heals faster.
I'll just go this far. [chuckles]
Dad?
Mmm?
About the guy
who fixed my cassette player…
-What is he like?
-Why? It's not working?
No. I'm just grateful.
He fixed my stuff so well,
and he keeps you company sometimes.
-You even said he bought you a gift.
-[chuckles]
He's a good kid.
And also a lonely one.
Why?
See how your mother took the time
to wash my hair for me?
No matter how pathetic or broken you are,
in the end,
it's your family that sticks by your side.
But that kid?
He's all alone.
I don't know the exact details,
but his mother passed away,
and he barely sees his father.
I think he's even been divorced once.
-That's rough.
-[chuckles]
But still, he's a really solid guy.
He's grown into a fine man.
His parents would feel so proud
if they could see him now.
[chuckles]
What would you think
if I dated someone like him?
Hmm?
You heard what I said.
[sighs] I don't know.
You said he's a good guy. Why hesitate?
That's a different story.
No matter how great a guy you bring home,
in my eyes, you'll always be too good.
-[chuckles]
-[chuckles] Silly girl.
Just go back inside now. Mom's waiting.
Ah, right. I can't have your mom worrying.
Get home safe.
-Bye, Dad.
-Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
Mr. Jeon? You've been working until now?
-Working and a whole lot of thinking.
-Thinking about what?
Is Ji-yoon seeing anyone right now?
[chuckles] Why?
[sighs] I'm almost certain
it's somebody I know.
What? Hey, hey, hey. What? What? Whoa.
-How did you know?
-Well, they both have matching stickers.
[sighs]
You knew too?
I told her to be careful. Of course.
-Ow!
-You let on that you knew!
I did not. [breathes shakily]
But you see,
I think I made a mistake,
and now things are tense between them.
What should I do?
-And what kind of mistake?
-I can't tell you that.
[sighs] I don't know,
but at times like these…
I should apologize first?
Well, no. Just pretend you don't know.
Huh?
If she realizes you've caught on,
things could get worse.
Just let them deal with their own issues.
Oh.
-You sure?
-Yes. Let's go.
[sighs]
You guys lied to me.
Well, not exactly lied.
-[Jae-in] No-ah!
-[chuckles]
[nervous chuckle]
-Who's this?
-He's my… younger cousin.
Yeah. [chuckles]
It's late. I'll get going.
Good night.
How long have you been waiting for me?
You should have let me know you were here.
"Younger cousin"?
Are you embarrassed about dating me?
I'm not. It's just that…
talking about personal life at work
can get messy.
I'm sorry.
I tend to keep things to myself.
Hey, I know I was wrong. Hmm?
[synth-pop music playing]
One iced Americano
and one hot café latte, please.
It's on me.
Oh, come on. You're a student.
A slice of cheesecake as well, please.
Ahh!
Oh, you got some here.
One moment, please.
We could have stopped by your place first.
-Why? So you can pay for the cab too?
-Well, of course.
-No-ah.
-Hmm?
Don't treat me like a child.
What?
You wouldn't do this with a child.
Hey, I-I never…
I'll call you when I'm home.
GOOD NIGHT
[sighs]
What should I say?
[pop music playing]
MAY I HELP YOU?
I need a good-night message
for my girlfriend
that'll really show her
how much I like her.
In text form.
STAY BY MY SIDE
EVEN IN YOUR DREAMS!
SLEEP WELL, MY LOVE
We've lived together long enough,
and you still haven't figured me out?
YOU ARE ALWAYS THE PERSON
I THINK OF AT THE END OF MY DAY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
A PROFOUND GIFT YOU ARE TO ME.
SWEET DREAMS. HAVE A WONDERFUL
START OF THE DAY TOMORROW.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH, TRULY!
That is seriously the worst.
[phone buzzes]
MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
[Si-woo] I still like you so much today.
Good night.
This is so unlike him.
But I won't make it easy for you…
because I plan on liking you
with everything that I have.
[typing]
[computer chimes]
[Si-woo] Good morning.
[phone buzzes]
MS. CHA JI-YOON. CONFIRMING YOUR
RESERVATION AT "RESTAURANT OZ"
[sighs]
[Ji-yoon] Should I cancel
our restaurant reservation for to--
Yes, President Han.
We'll have to reschedule.
I have a commitment tonight.
Yes.
-[phone chimes]
-[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
[Young-sam]
Why haven't I heard back from you yet?
Are you even working on what I asked?
[tense music playing]
[Kee-tae]
I actually did find out something,
but it's such a personal
and private matter.
[Young-sam] What is it? Spit it out!
[Kee-tae] There's something suspicious
going on between these two.
You damn lunatic!
[comical music playing]
To think he saw me as a man of ambition.
He completely overestimated me.
You see,
I plan on stretching things out
and outlasting everyone at this company.
[sighs]
Here's the salad you ordered.
-Thank you. Enjoy your meal.
-Thank you. Yes.
Thank you.
Sir, we have set reservation times.
I'm sorry, but may I take your order now?
Sure. I'll have the dinner course, please.
[server] Would that be for one person?
No, for two, please.
Certainly, sir.
You came.
Yes.
I looked like someone
with a tragic backstory.
Thank you for saving me.
What would you do if I hadn't come?
I would have eaten alone.
And then I'd keep making reservations
until you showed up.
I came because
there's something I want to ask you.
Ask me anything, and I'll tell you.
So,
can you tell me
why you two got a divorce?
Where would you like me to start?
The very beginning to the end.
All of it.
[server] Excuse me.
How about we eat first?
Sure.
[gentle music playing]
[Si-woo] Our mothers had been
best friends since high school.
We saw each other often
since we were little,
and they frequently joked
about becoming in-laws one day.
Then…
we ended up at the same college
and naturally started dating.
We had a normal relationship,
and like everyone,
we pictured a future together.
So,
is that when you started
considering marriage?
Yes.
We planned to study abroad together,
so we married after graduation.
Oh.
But then my father's business
suddenly went under,
and then my mother became ill,
so I could no longer go anywhere.
And then when she said she'd go alone,
I couldn't bring myself to stop her.
Why not?
If you're married, aren't you supposed
to choose to stay together?
Well, I believed
that was the best decision for us.
So I decided to get a job and make money,
and Soo-jin went to the States to study.
We both got busy,
and living in opposite time zones,
we gradually talked less and less.
Then my mother passed away,
and when Soo-jin came back
to Korea for a bit,
she told me that she wanted a divorce.
It felt like the natural course of events.
I was too drained by my own life
that I had no room left
to tend to the loneliness
she must have been going through.
So I accepted things as they were.
It took less than a year for us
to go from marriage to divorce.
You went through all of that
in a period of just one year?
Yes.
I pictured it so many times.
How and where did these two meet?
Was it love at first sight?
Who fell for the other first?
I'd wonder over and over again.
Who was to blame for the split?
If it was Mr. Kang's fault…
would I be able to handle whatever it was?
But I…
I actually never imagined that you
were going through things like that.
The part of my past
that you find hard to handle
was the emptiest time of my entire life.
But I won't let it hold me back anymore.
So, every moment I spend liking you
feels too precious to waste.
Even now, every single second of this.
Well,
I don't want to repeat
the same mistake again.
I started this
because I had feelings for you,
but those feelings aren't enough now.
If I'm going to be with you,
I want to be sure that I do so
with a heart… that won't waver.
Is that okay?
Yes, absolutely.
[typing]
[computer chimes]
KANG SI-WOO
[Si-woo] Good morning.
[typing]
[computer chimes]
[Ji-yoon] Good morning.
[pop music playing]
SET THE COOKING TIME
STANDARD
MANAGE DETERGENT
My twin boys just won't listen to me.
Tell me, what should I do?
FIRST CHECK WHAT'S GOING ON
AND GIVE THEM YOUR ATTENTION.
Okay, and how do I give them attention?
No.
We can't push this back by even a day.
[music ends]
Oh.
[chuckles]
Where's Mr. Kang?
-He said he was going to the hospital.
-Why?
He's working too hard.
It took a toll on him, I guess.
MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
[classical music playing]
What's wrong?
Hmm?
You look like you have a lot on your mind.
Ah.
Mr. Kang's gone to the hospital.
Just wondering if he's okay.
Have you tried calling him?
No.
Why not? Call him.
I actually asked him
to give me some time
to think things through.
Did something happen?
Thing is,
I've lost all confidence in myself.
[sighs] You also have moments like that?
I thought I was the only one
who lacked confidence.
[scoffs]
An easy relationship doesn't exist.
At least at work,
you get better with experience, you know?
But why does dating have to be so hard?
Well, seeing someone as intelligent as you
become a fool when it comes to dating
is oddly comforting to me, you know?
-I'm a total failure at this. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
[sighs]
[gentle music playing]
KANG SI-WOO
[Si-woo] Did you enjoy your lunch?
[typing]
[computer chimes]
[Ji-yoon] Are you feeling okay?
[typing]
[Si-woo]
Yes, I feel much better after the IV.
[Ji-yoon] I thought you said
you take good care of yourself.
We can't have our team lead fall sick.
[Si-woo] This is kind of nice,
being sick once in a while.
[Ji-yoon]
Just take care of your health first.
[Si-woo] I even like hearing you nag.
[scoffs, chuckles]
[Na-ri] The brochures are out!
For you, Mr. Kang.
-This one's for you.
-Thank you.
They look really great. Really nice work.
Thank you. [chuckles]
Tomorrow's the big day.
So let's go ahead and showcase
all we've prepped without a hitch.
What do we do about that thing?
What thing?
The Demo Ghost.
-[sighing]
-[chuckles]
"The Demo Ghost"?
Right, you wouldn't know
since you were in the States.
So there's this ghost that ruins demos
even if you've rehearsed them
countless times.
It made the built-in water dispenser
stop dispensing,
caused the voice recognition to go dead
and stopped a robot vacuum
that was running smoothly.
That's the legendary Demo Ghost.
I've never seen it
with my own eyes though.
Errors happen so often during live demos
that we say it's the ghost's doing.
-Should we use a talisman or something?
-Yeah, I am the talisman.
Don't worry.
You can all go home early today.
-Yes, sir.
[phone buzzes]
[Si-woo] Get to bed early tonight.
That way, you'll be ready
to deal with the ghost if it shows up.
[Ji-yoon] You too.
For a long time,
we've been creating home appliances
that make people's lives more convenient.
However, today,
that technology evolves to the next level.
Home-AI is here.
Now, we invite you
to experience that future
and see for yourself.
[upbeat music playing]
So now we are going to take a look
at how Home-AI can transform your day
by following a typical busy day in Seoul.
The first thing you do in the morning
is check your schedule and the weather
on the built-in refrigerator screen
to pick an outfit that suits your day
and is appropriate for the weather.
But when you get to work,
you suddenly remember
that you left the induction cooktop on
with a pot still sitting on it.
In the past,
you would have had to go back home,
but now, you can turn it off remotely
from your phone.
COOKTOP
OFF
While you're working at the office,
you might wonder
how your dog is doing alone at home.
So just check the video
your robot vacuum sends you.
It's Sun-shim.
Sure enough,
Sun-shim is napping again today.
[laughing]
After a long day of work, you come home
and start preparing your meal.
Shall we try a new recipe
for dinner tonight?
CHICKEN, STEAK…
You look up a recipe that can be made
with ingredients in your fridge,
send it to the oven,
and then you just pop the prepped
ingredients into the oven, and done.
After having a nice meal,
it's now time to do one of the most
dreaded household chores, the laundry.
Washing machine, open the door.
[chimes]
-[buzzer sounding]
-[appliances chiming]
[ominous music playing]
Oh, would you look at that.
1 SELECTED
FRIDGE
It's the Demo Ghost.
[chuckles]
[murmuring]
What's that punk doing?
The age of Home-AI has arrived.
Devices have become smarter than ever,
learning our preferences, lifestyles,
medical information,
and they can even recognize our voices.
However,
if something like this were to happen,
people would no longer be able
to trust and use Home-AI.
-Mr. Lee Young-hun.
-Sir?
Did you hack the AI system?
Yes.
I hacked it and planted an error program
in the system.
Does that mean personal data
can be leaked too?
Yes,
it is entirely possible.
[attendees murmuring]
What's going on here?
Um, I don't know. I'm not sure.
-Was it Manager Ko and Director Noh?
-Yes.
They told me to do anything
to sabotage the demo.
-And in return?
-Your position, actually.
They promised I'd be
the task force team lead.
They plan to swallow the Future
Home Appliances task force whole.
They said ruining the demo
would put the task force
under the vice president,
and that Mr. Noh would manage it himself.
[scoffs]
That must have been
pretty tempting for you then.
[chuckles]
No, sir.
"May work speak for itself, not politics."
"You must work for yourself.
Don't do it for others."
You see, I have never forgotten
everything I learned from you.
[uplifting music playing]
So…
do what Mr. Noh has asked of you.
Sir?
If you attack the system,
I'll try to defend against it.
[chuckles]
That is exactly why we made security
the top priority of our Home-AI project.
So we built our new security program.
Neo Solution is finally here.
[pop music playing]
RESTORE
Neo Solution
doesn't just neutralize malware.
It uses blockchain technology,
allowing connected devices
to protect each other
from security threats.
If a single device has an issue,
it is automatically isolated,
keeping the rest
of your Home-AI network secure.
Sensitive information
is stored separately,
providing double,
even triple layers of protection,
creating a world tailored
to each user's unique lifestyle.
We have named it
the "Home-AI user experience."
[sighs] Geez.
[sighs] What on earth was all this?
Well, to put it in simple terms,
I was acting as a double agent.
What?
-[thuds]
-Oh, come on!
-Well done!
-[groans]
It's pretty clear
that Lee Young-hun has turned on us.
I know. I picked the wrong guy.
-Uh, for a month.
-[Kee-tae] A month?
I never thought
he'd do something like this.
I'm talking about you.
Geez. Useless idiot.
Get lost.
But-But-- But, Mr. Noh.
-Yes, this looks far neater.
-[alumnus] Choi Soo-jin.
[attendee chattering]
-Jeong Hyeon-u.
-That one looks good, right?
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Shall we go?
That's right, it's me,
your college classmate.
Hey. I heard you went abroad.
I'm surprised to see you here.
And I heard you two got married.
But I didn't know you and Si-woo
worked at the same company.
-You okay working with your husband?
-Well, about that…
Ms. Choi? President Han is asking for you.
Okay.
Let's talk later.
Sure. The three of us should grab a bite.
-[chuckles] See you.
-Yeah.
[chuckles] Talk about a stroke of luck.
Here's to our Future Home Appliances
task force after a successful demo!
-[all] Cheers!
-[lively music playing]
-Oh! Mr. Kang! Over here!
-Oh!
-Another draft beer here, please!
-Coming.
Wait, I thought that you were going
to the dinner with the clients.
I stopped to say hello and left.
I'm sure the Global Sales Team
can take it from there.
But still,
shouldn't you be with them there too?
Well, this is more important to me.
Everyone, you did a great job today.
Mr. Kang, that wasn't cool.
I mean, seriously,
you almost gave us all a heart attack.
It was the only way we'd be able
to fool the other side completely.
-I hope you understand.
-Of course.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Uh, truth is, I got an offer
from Mr. Ko some time ago.
If I handed over some dirt on you,
he'd make me senior associate.
-Really?
-So what is it that you gave him?
A juicy rumor…
about a workplace romance
between Mr. Kang and Mr. Lee.
-Something to get him off my back.
-[chuckling]
-[laughing]
-Oh, my! [giggling]
But to be honest with you all,
I was very much tempted, you know?
I've been an associate for ages,
and I have twins to feed.
[Si-woo] I understand.
The workplace is where your limits
are constantly tested.
But since you didn't give in,
it means you didn't give up on yourself
and kept your integrity.
Oh, my, you really do know
how to talk, Mr. Kang.
Whatever! I…
I guess I love the task force!
To this team, forever!
-Forever!
-Wait!
I'll be going back
to the Development Team.
What?
But I thought you were staying with us
until launch.
Well, my work here on the task force
is finished now.
Hmm. Time to move on
to the next assignment.
This company doesn't give us enough time
to catch our breath, does it?
We get paid, so we work.
[gasps] Mr. Kang!
You're supposed to take our side,
at least for today!
Here's to us, to being a team forever.
[all] Forever!
[chuckles] Have you been waiting long?
No. You're right on time.
Did you have a good day?
Mmm. I got so many compliments.
It's the first time I'm recognized
purely for my own hard work.
At this rate,
you'll be, like, promoted in no time.
No, not even close.
Let's go eat. I'm starving.
-[chuckling]
-No-ah!
[chuckles] Hi.
Who's this?
[upbeat music playing]
-He's my boyfriend.
-Really?
No way. [chuckling]
We're on the way to grab dinner,
so I'll call you later.
Mm-hmm.
Now that they know,
the news is practically out.
-Sure you can handle that?
-Then you better handle this too.
-Hmm?
-I'm Yoon No-ah's boyfriend!
I'm Yoon No-ah's boyfriend!
[whispers] Damn it.
Wait for me, girlfriend!
I really loved this task force.
We all worked so hard.
[chuckles]
-Where's Mr. Kang?
-He already left.
Huh?
You know, he seemed really exhausted.
[Young-hun sighs] He probably
hasn't been sleeping that much.
He was buried
in that security solution for months.
[phone buzzes]
Doesn't Mr. Kang live alone?
[Si-woo] I'm heading home first.
[Kee-tae] Being alone when you're sick
must be so miserable.
Hey, I think I'm going
to head out early too.
-So suddenly?
-Yeah, my mom…
No, I mean, my dad got injured, so…
Hey, listen! If your father's not well,
you should go there now.
Yes.
-I should.
-Huh.
-I'll be in touch, okay?
-Yes, go ahead then.
-All right, then.
-Bye.
-Good night, everyone.
-Yeah, get going.
-She's just leaving like that?
-Her father's injured.
-Come on, let's toast.
-[Young-hun] Oh, right.
[doorbell rings]
Is he not home?
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[doorbell rings]
[phone chimes]
Mr. Kang?
Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang! Mr. Kang!
Ji-yoon?
[sighs]
-Where were you?
-[coughs]
I was terrified that you passed out.
I think I'll pass out
from you hitting me so hard.
I was so worried.
How could I possibly
give up on someone like you?
[sighs]
[gentle music playing]
Have some tea.
-There's something I'd like to ask you.
-You still have more questions?
Why did you tell me
right from the beginning
that you're Ms. Choi's ex-husband?
I'm not really sure.
Because it's definitely not something
I would normally share.
Maybe it was a system error,
since you're the only variable
that changes me.
I'm not sure why I said it,
but once I fell in love with you,
I figured it was a good thing
I had already told you.
Pathetic, right?
Yes.
Anyway, let's think things through
and own up to them.
Let's do that.
Don't hide things from me,
saying it's for my sake.
-Tell me everything.
-Okay. I'll do that.
Then you can be honest with me.
Wasn't it difficult?
Being alone for such a long time?
Wasn't it painful?
Yes.
It was painful.
[panting]
When my father's business went under
and he left my mother as if to run away…
When Soo-jin left, insisting
that she'd go study abroad by herself…
And even when she
eventually asked for a divorce,
I couldn't bring myself to fight for us.
So I kept telling myself that letting her
go was the considerate thing to do.
But actually,
it was… just my pride,
not wanting to admit
how miserable and lonely I truly was.
Because I…
simply didn't know how
to share my grief back then.
I guess you were even younger
than I am now, back then.
And all alone like that.
How on earth
did you bear all of that pain?
[sighs] I feel so heartbroken
for the past you.
[Si-woo sighs]
[sighs]
You're in trouble.
Once you feel pity, it's game over.
Well, I truly don't care
about your past anymore.
No matter how temperamental
or how romantic you may be.
So,
I'm just going to focus
on my feelings for you right now.
You see?
I told you it wouldn't be easy
to turn down my feelings for you.
[chuckles quietly]
May I take back what I just said?
You may not.
I'll forget my pride, because now,
I won't let you go no matter what.
[sighs]
Do you want to go out for a walk?
What?
Well, I don't want to do it
just to decompress.
-Then…
-Then?
Buy me a steamed bun.
-A steamed bun?
-Yes.
I haven't had
my first steamed bun this year.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[ominous music playing]
Found it.
[exhales]
[sighs, exhales]
A COLLEGE COUPLE SUCCESS STORY!
YOU TWO HAPPY TO GET MARRIED?
-You should have some too.
-I don't really eat carbs this late.
Fine, fine.
I'll just pig out by myself then.
Your hands are all red.
Give it. I'll hold it.
[hisses]
Oh, that's hot! [chuckles]
-[exhales sharply]
-Hey, Ji-yoon?
Yes? [inhales sharply]
I love you.
[lighthearted music playing]
You're saying that
with a steamed bun in your hands?
I may be holding a bun,
but I really mean it.
I do too.
What was that?
I love you.
[chuckles]
Oh!
It's snowing.
Mr. Kang, it's snowing!
[Si-woo]
At long last, I found my joy again.
May this joy stay safe and sound
for a long time to come.
[music continues]
SPECIAL THANKS TO BAE YU-RAM
WE'RE A TEAM!
[Ji-yoon] Wait, is this a proposal?
I used to think
that marriage was the natural
next step after dating.
So why am I hesitating about it?
[Kee-tae] Fights between
husband and wife are inevitable.
I don't like having things
lying around like that.
[No-ah] What is all this?
[employee]
Those two were actually married?
What if someone
spreads this rumor with ill intent?
What happened?
[Young-sam]
I might not be able to pull you up,
but I sure as hell
can drag you straight to the bottom!