Here
Gorgeous
Cheers
The wine’s good and the service is excellent
Justin, you’ve made me very happy tonight
It's my greatest honor
Little Justin, you’re so good at taking care of people
from now on,I don’t want anyone else when I'm here
but you
whatever you need—
I’ll do my best to satisfy it
I just hope every time you come—
you can be as happy
Bring all the drinks! Tonight’s on me.
Thank you for your generous support
I promise tonight—
will be your most unforgettable one
Little Justin has really improved a lot
Looks like the special training wasn’t wasted
Not bad. Looks like tonight’s sales—
might break a record
Rourou, you finally came
It’s been 131 hours, 45 minutes, and 20 seconds.
I thought you were joking with me
Were you afraid I’d stand you up?
No, that’s not what I meant...
I’m really happy you're here again
Come
Rourou, you had champagne last time
want to try something different this time
or have some snacks first?
You’re being so aggressive —afraid I’ll run away?
because
I don't want to miss you again
this kid is normally kind of silly
didn’t expect him to get smart when he meets a beauty
People eventually grow up
This stupid woman
My dance moves are charming, right?
Have a seat, please
Don't forget your mission
What’s wrong, Rourou?
What happened?
Nothing, I might just be a little tired.
If you’re really tired—
maybe you should go home and rest tonight
Don’t force yourself to stay, okay?
I'm okay
I still want you to stay with me a bit longer.
Not a problem
As long as you say the word—
I’ll follow you to the ends of the earth.
"Ends of the earth"? That’s so cliché
Happy to see you smiling
now I’m relieved.
Pan Hao
Let’s meet outside next time.
I want us to be like normal friends.
I don’t want it to be like this—
like I’m paying to spend time with you.
that's no problem
didn't I just way
I’ll do anything as long as you ask
here
It's my turn after Lee Xun’s done showering, right?
We agreed yesterday it’d be my turn
Don’t sneak off to poop
You’re not allowed to either!
Did we say that yesterday?
Yes, we did.  Don't play dumb
OK
But seriously—
Today we finally met—
a VIP client who talks like a normal person
Clients like that should be treasured like family heirlooms.
That’s because you haven’t met true love
Let me tell you
I basically had the "love-you-forever combo meal" today
smiling the whole time—genuinely.
Not like you guys fake-smiling till your faces cramp.
hey, that rhymed.
You brought that on yourself
Hey, I didn't say I was tired.
I'm powered by love right now —double stamina
I’m a true-love warrior.
Oh, really?
why don't you just move into the VIP room
Fine—book it for me.
You exhausted pretty boys—
the youth-saving miracle is here!
Here comes dumber
Did you get a shot or take something? Why so hyped?
Neither
It’s all thanks to this
What's that?
Look
This is called black maca
Boosts stamina, boosts charm — and it’s all natural.
Even ladies can take it
Really?
This stuff is the real deal
this is Lutein
Like the stage downstairs—
spotlights flashing all night
If you don’t take this—
you'll be blind tomorrow
You should've shared this earlier
we've been hanging on whole night
whatever they are, give me some
Ladies can take this
Come on, here you go
I'm not kidding
black maca—
it's the last line of defense till dawn
for guys like us who need to stay sharp and stay strong
Seriously?
For real
Rourou’s not asleep yet
should I call her—
and arrange some “pure love” plans?
This won't work for you
why?
why what
what "pure love"? What are you up to?
pure love
making love
if possible
I said, if possible...
is there even such a saying?
Of course
So, are you going right now?
I kinda want to
Then, I'm going to shower
wait, shower
I was first yesterday
Let me tell you
Last one is a pig
Last one is...
I'm not a pig
I'm a person
idiot
I'm not
If Rourou cares that I work here—
should I tell her the truth
then run away with her?
but if she stays with me—
We’d have to live our whole lives
in hiding.
Wouldn’t that be too unfair to her?
Hello, feel free to take a look
He's our top star
Hunter is so handsome
This cooling sensation…
feels amazing.
Staying up late, acne breakouts, dry skin—
One bottle solves it all
What are you spraying?
You’ve been spraying nonstop
and moaning like that
well...
This is sprayable vitamin B complex—
commonly known as "all-nighter's savior"
Improves dullness,
fights acne, moisturizes and boosts energy.
Don’t you see my face glowing?
Glowing?
More like greasy, you idiot.
What are you even doing?
Moaning like that—
perfect timing
I can’t reach my back
help me spray it
on my back
yes
not there
Shoulders, shoulders
Shoulders, shoulders...
just the shoulders
yeah
a little lower
Didn’t sleep well last night?
Not really
Bro—
Easy, easy!
That’s way too much force
You should open a boxing gym
you’d knock out ten at once
Are you sure about that?
Once he sees blood—
What’s that supposed to mean?
Are you going to joke about that forever?
Hey, no...
Bro—
It wasn’t me
He said it
He did
wait
Cheng-Han, Bro
I’m just concerned about you.
Why aren’t you going on stage yet?
Didn’t a regular book you?
That regular specifically requested me
to enter as a VIP
Said she wants me to smell nice, look glowing
and full of energy.
No wonder you’re spraying the vitamin B stuff
I’m not joking
in this condition,
I can handle three-table guests in one night
do two dance sets,
and sing a Wu Bai's song.
Bro, I think you’ve been working hard lately
Look how dry your skin is.
Come here
Let me put some moisturizer on you
Nice—shiny and glossy.
Here too...
You spray here?
He did it
Fight! Fight!
Same old rules
Youth is wonderful
You’re just too beautiful.
Is Jin Chu-Yun inside?
Is Jin Chu-Yun in there?
I don’t know anything
You...
I ...
What does it mean for not answering the phone?
Your phone keeps ringing. Aren’t you going to answer it?
Is it urgent?
Ignore it
Should we do this first
I don't...
Go on
Hey, I...
Take good care of our Justin
He gets drunk easily
Gentlemen,
Sorry
This is a male companion club
If you’re looking for pretty ladies,
you might want to try the one next door.
I’m not here for male companions
I’m here for my wife.
Get her out to me.
Your wife is so beautiful
I wouldn’t have forgotten.
if I’d seen her before
How about —
you call her again to confirm?
I did
she didn’t answer
But GPS of her phone
show she’s here.
she must be here.
Search the place
Wait a second
what?
trying to stop me?
Sir
I understand you’re looking for someone
But shouting like this
is scaring other guests.
Our reputation
depends on these customers.
Right now all eyes are on you.
do you really want to find her
or do you want to be tonight’s main show?
Fine
Keep it low-key
Search
Sorry, not this room.
Back off
You’re finished
what are you doing?
Hurry, go get Hunter
and have him take her away
got the wrong person
Sorry
You can continue
Get out
I'm sorry
Wrong person?
What are you looking at?
Keep it down
Didn’t expect it to be guys
Ignore him. Let’s continue.
Miss Lin, your husband is here.
I’m dancing seaweed.
Super fast
Up
Down
Magical stage.
Where did you learn to dance?
Impressive
Jin Chu-Yun, stop hiding!
Get out of my way
Hey, first time here?
don't be shy
You’re new, right?
I’m here to find my wife.
I like this type — a little wild
Handsome, don’t be shy.
Come have fun with us.
Hold on
I’m not here to work
you’ve got it wrong
They are the male companions
I'm not
Drink up — let’s see who passes out first.
Drink up!
I don’t want to drink.
I really don't want to
What are you doing?
I’m just here to find my wi—
ve never been hit before.
you hit me
How can you slap me?
Help!
Help
Excuse us
Stop
This is the last private room
Jin Chu-Yun
Mister
My name is Pan Jinlian
Not Jin Chu-Yun.
now...
You've searched and checked
without finding your wife.
Wanna check out next door?
Let me tell you — this GPS tracking
isn’t always accurate.
let's not interrupting my business
How about this—
Send me her photo
I’ll share it to other clubs
We’ll all help look
it'll be faster
easy
What are you up to?
Don’t be impulsive.
We have surveillance cameras here
Make a move
the police will be here soon.
oh, right
You lied to me.
I’ll make you pay first
Do you know how tall the grass is
on the last person's grave who caused trouble here?
Fine
I won’t argue with you for now
but I won’t let him off
You brought guns into our place?
You’ve got some nerve.
Get him out.
Move
Tony
Help me!
To...
Sleeping with my wife behind my back — feels good, huh?
I’ll chop you up
Let’s see how you bang my wife again.
Wang Jian-Hai, come at me if you’ve got guts
Feeling sorry for him?
Have to chop you up
what are you doing
man
Intentional injury carries at least five years
and causing permanent disability—
Do you know how long you’d be imprisoned?
Who are you?
Sorry, I forgot to introduce myself
My name is Lee Xiao-Zhen
Azure Dragon Syndicate International Holdings Group
Azure Dragon Syndicate
The Azure Dragon Syndicate
If you dare hurt him,
I’ll make sure you never walk out of prison
Works perfectly for your wife
to have a good time here.
Zhen, what are you doing here?
I was passing by and wanted a drink.
Even lawyers come to the clubs?
You have a wide clientele
Officer, someone's here causing trouble with a knife
Please come over, thank you.
put it down
Put it down — you damn—
Wang Jian-Hai, have you made enough of a scene?
I’m making a scene?
You’re the one fooling around with men!
Do you respect our marriage at all?
Respect?
What about you?
Have you fulfilled your duties as a husband?
If you're capable, would I need to be here?
I’m not incapable.
Oh?
Wanna check how long it’s been since last time you touched me?
That's enough
Let’s talk at home. Let’s go.
I'm not going home with you
Let's make things clear here
Thank you
Hunter
Do your best
Miss Lee is our benefactor
Thank you so much
I might not have walked out that door,
if it weren’t for you
Do you know this behavior is an illness?
I do
Compulsive behavioral disorder
It’s a psychological imbalance.
you can’t live normally
if it’s severe
Have you noticed
that after doing that thing,
you feel empty inside specially?
I do feel empty
every time after it ends
But...
I just can't stop
I’ve tried really hard before
not to think about it
not to touch it
But whenever I’m alone,
the desire
is like an addicted beast
that I can’t control
However
last time,
when I went to the hotel with you,
it was the first time
I didn’t have that urge
I don’t know why either.
maybe it's you
You make me feel at ease.
it's like
the missing piece in my heart
has been fulfilled
Me too
That night
was the first time since my husband passed away
that I actually slept peacefully.
Could you sleep with me more often?
I mean
just sleep, nothing else.
Of course
You saved my life.
Whatever you need, I’m there.
or
we could level up the challenge a little
Let’s sleep our way through every hotel in Taipei.
I’m game
but can you keep up?
Bros
I almost died young today. No joke.
Then how’re you still alive?
you...
I'm serious
I almost became a eunuch today
Jin Chuyun’s husband
barged into the VIP room
and held a knife to my junk
Dude was about to separate head from body—if you know what I mean.
Bro.
After all the talks
is it still attached?
Yeah, wanna see?
Hard pass
So the guy who stormed in today
came to catch you in the act?
so,
Tony helped to resolve it?
Nope
My guardian angel showed up
Lee Xiaozhen
The one with the black card
who booked me whole night last time
She gave them a serious beatdown
and even called the cops
I must’ve done some serious good deeds in a past life—
helped old ladies cross the street or something—
to get this lucky
also
She’s an ace attorney of
Azure Dragon Syndicate International Holdings—
It's her
who?
what?
you know her
We’ve crossed paths a few times.
Lawyers are into male companions?
Crossed paths how?
in bed?
or fists?
In court
Didn’t I tell you not to come back?
Don't you understand?
Leave. Now.
Let's see
if you can hang on till the cops arrive
Don't touch her
I'll sign
See?  Just sign and nobody gets hurt
you have to make me come here in person
what are you doing?
No...
Help!
what are you doing?
well...
Lee Xiao-Zhen
you'd never think she's that kind of person
Killers don't exactly advertise it
After all these years,
you're still that fast
Otherwise how could I keep up with the heir to the best?
That’s all in the past
I just
want a quiet and normal life.
Back then,
you walked away without hesitation
because of Yuchuan… right?
Yu
Look who is this?
what a small world
Since we haven't settled anything last time
now you've delivered yourself right to my doorstep
great
we might as well settle it once for all
Haven't you learned the lesson yet
This time
I won't hold back
Hold back?
Who do you think you are, some savior?
hold back my ass
Go!
Go after him! What’re you looking at me for?
Mom told me to give these to you
she said you’d come looking for me.
Let's go
You don’t say it,
but I can tell
you care about him.
Otherwise
you wouldn’t have risked cutting ties with him
just to stop him from becoming a cop.
Did it even matter?
He became a cop anyway.
Nearly got himself killed more than once because of Lee Xun
After everything that’s happened,
he never says a word.
If I hadn’t had Hsu Chenghan watching him secretly,
you think he’d still be alive?
You two are
cut from the same cloth
stubborn as hell.
Uncle Ma
Tony
How's your sister?
She’s hanging in there.
The hospital called — they found a matching heart
and want to schedule the transplant ASAP.
That’s good news.
After the surgery,
she’ll finally get to live like a normal person, right?
Yeah… that’s true.
But I was thinking of telling the hospital maybe I should—
Don’t worry about the money.
Tony will handle it.
If money can fix it, it’s not a problem.
Just stay with your sister through the surgery
we’ll take care of everything else.
You go all out protecting Yuchuan every time,
I see all of it.
That’s just how Ma is — loyal to the core
You show him heart, he shows you loyalty.
Thank you, Ma
Thank you, Tony
By the way,
I actually came to give you an update
back in the dorm
Lee Xun and Yuchuan were talking about
the client who saved Chang Yihao today.
They already figured out
it was Lee Xiaozhen — the lawyer of Azure Dragon Syndicate
Do they have a plan?
Not yet
But they also mentioned
they know Azure Dragon Syndicate's rule:
no hurting the elderly, women or children.
Lee Xun’s been digging into it, too.
They really want to know
why the gang
has never dared mess with the club.
Got it
I'll head out then
Thanks, Ma
Thanks, Tony
Look like...
Lee Xun’s going to uncover your secrets
sooner than later
While Hsu Chenghan’s away,
I’ll need you to keep an eye on Yuchuan.
Bro.
do we really need to be this formal?
Don’t forget, I was the one looking after Yuchuan
before Hsu Chenghan came along
It's so pretty
I’ve imagined this moment a thousand times.
Standing here
looking out at the skyline…
with you by my side.
This exact scene
has appeared in my mind countless times
Pan Hao
We...
Let's be together