Thank you
Is going out for a late-night snack with me
embarrassing you or something?
Dressed like that—are you afraid of
being recognized, or kidnapped?
Rourou, you’ve got it all wrong
I’ve got all kinds of connections out there
and quite a few enemies too.
I’m worried someone might show up while we're eating
and smack me with a pig's head.
Relax, no one here knows you
except me
Sir, do you know him?
Keep it down
What was that about?
I told you—
no one here’s gonna recognize you.
Hurry up and eat
or I’m finishing it all.
Here
I remember you’ve always had a sensitive tongue.
That’s way too hot—how are you eating it?
Let me cool it down for you.
Pan Hao
Don’t be so nice to me.
If I’m not nice to you,
should I be nice to that old guy behind you?
Okay, perfect temperature now
Eat
There’s somewhere I’ve always wanted to go.
Let’s go after this.
Sure. Wherever you wanna go,
I'm in.
Here—your favorite.
Thanks
It’s so beautiful.
I’ve imagined this moment a thousand times.
Standing here
looking out at the skyline…
with you by my side.
This exact scene
has appeared in my mind countless times
Pan Hao
We...
Let's be together...
Are you serious?
Even after all these years apart…
I don't know if you're any different
than who you were
I still want to give it a shot.
Just so you know—
No refunds, no returns
and no trial period either.
Thanks for the ride,
my dear Mr. Pan
Just got yourself a handsome boyfriend…
already getting used to having the chauffeured service?
or else?
You're already mine
Isn’t this the least I should get?
Whatever you said
Off to work
I'm leaving
Hey, don't get too close to your clients
at work
Of course
See whose name’s written on me?
Sun Rourou
I've really gotta go
Bye
Time to catch up on sleep.
Guys
I’m up early for once—
wait...
Actually… I just haven’t slept yet.
Brought you all a protein-packed feast.
YuChuan
help me to get the table set up
Hurry, get moving!
Look who finally showed up.
Who drained you dry last night?
couldn't find you at all
I’m still full of energy, alright?
Come on, everyone
Thanks to you—
I’m officially with Rourou.
Nice
Where's Chenghan?
Seems like he took time off
to be with his sister for surgery.
He has a sister?
Weren’t you his middle school classmate?
How do you not know that?
Alright, guys
You’ve all eaten the food, right?
then you owe me one
When I go take a nap later,
no one’s allowed to wake me up.
Good night
I knew it—
nothing comes for free with you.
Even if he didn’t treat us, we wouldn’t have bothered with him.
Give me one more chance.
Asking for more chances?
I was this close to breaking even.
Please, please, please
I can still borrow some more
I can still borrow some more, please
Borrow again? With what?
Broke and still gambling?
Stop messing around here, get out
Please, please, please
Let me in again
Please, I can win
I will win
Get out
Please, please, please
Let me go in again
I can make it happen
I swear
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Biao
Brother Biao....
I heard you've been going to casino lately?
Where are the diamonds?
You see...
Look, hear me out
I could’ve gotten it—
But I… just had bad luck
Listen
Just give me more time.
I can nail it
Seriously
Give you some more time?
and who’s giving me time?
Hey
Three days
I'll give you three days
Okay
Three days later,
If I don’t see the diamonds—
You’ll be collecting your own corpse.
Okay, three days
Don't let me down
Let's drink together
Come on over
I’m in a great mood today.
Bring me your smoothest talker—
the hottest one to come and drink with me.
Hi, sorry to keep you waiting.
This is our top host at ACE—
Hunter
Come
Beautiful, what should I call you?
Just call me Yunru.
So you’re the smoothest talker?
That's right
Good
Strong drinker
Come
Slow down
no one’s competing with you.
Easy for you to say
If I drink slower—
or order less—
you’ll just
run off to some richer lady, right?
Why would I?
You hosts are all the same—just sweet talk.
Saying you love me—
saying I’m the only one—
and what happened?
I’m eight millions in debt
and being forced to drink and entertain men.
Lin Yunru
You used to be one of Leo’s regulars?
Right
I used to be a VIP here.
Now?
I'm broke
and drowning in debt.
Leo said he’d help me find a way to make money
That “way” was
to send me to a hostess club to drink with clients.
Otherwise, I’d get my limbs broken.
This is all your fault.
All because of you lowlife bastards
who scam women for money
Calm down
Calm down first
Calm down now
I had enough
I don’t want to do this anymore.
Chill out now
Tell me everything—
what happened?
At first,
I just wanted someone to treat me well.
Someone who could comfort me
and made me feel loved.
I thought I could buy
real love.
Turns out—
the more
I paid,
the less I was loved.
Leo said I could front it on credit
since my credit is solid
not like I wouldn't be able to pay it back
Leo
asked you to cover it upfront?
At first, just a few hundred thousand.
I figure it's okay
as long as I can pay it back
Then it snowballed to eight millions
from one million
Eight millions?!
Zhen
Leo really went too far,
scamming girls out of money is one thing,
but that's not all
The point is
he actually sent them to
the hostess bars
People like that should be chopped up
I didn't know
you were so righteous.
You bet
Even though I have compulsive behavioral disorder
I step up
when it matters.
just like you saved my life the other day
Zhen
didn't you say the other day
that you want to sleep through every hotel in Taipei with me?
Why did you invite me home today?
Sorry, I’ve been busy.
but I do miss you
I invited you over instead.
You don't like it?
How can I not like it
if I can see you?
Are all companions this cheesy?
Of course not...
If you don't like it
I can switch to my “dorky mode".
Hello, I am Hunter
So dorky, huh...
By the way, is Wang Jianhai
still bothering you?
No... no...
I've had you got my back.
Lin Yunru came by.
Didn't she stop going to the club a long time ago?
Why is she going back to support the club now?
She's not here to support
but to complain
She's tricked into signing some IOUs by you
The interest skyrocketed
and ended up being a hostess
Isn’t that normal?
That’s how this business works.
She wanted to do it herself, who forced her?
The problem is—
you made her advance the money
and had her signed some IOUs.
Working with loan sharks
is illegal
The police are investigating.
investigating?
What can they do?
No one dares mess with this food chain nowadays
This has blown up.
Lin Yunru isn't the only one
other girls have reported it too.
You should stop now.
Don't keep doing that.
Tony…
back when we hung out together
didn't you tell me that
making money fast is what matters.
Look at you now
How long will it take to make enough to live on
relying solely on services and chatting?
In our business, without lending
how do we keep the clients spending more?
Should you consider
bringing the Club into the system?
Give them credit lines,
they can enjoy more fun
and pay it off slowly
your sales revenue doubled
Everybody is happy
This is why you left?
Losing is gaining.
What do you think?
If you join--
I'll bring your ex-staff back to you
Otherwise,
can you afford them?
I'm here today to warn you
out of respect for
our past work relationship
If you thought
I would join you
Not a chance
Tony
You’re still this stubborn.
Take care of yourself
Morning
Want to freshen up first?
Let's have breakfast together.
You’re a grown man—afraid of getting tanned?
The UV here is brutal,
my face is my livelihood.
That’s why I cover up like this
It’s professional responsibility.
I brought this...
waterproof, sweat-proof, brightening, moisturizing—
I already applied some earlier
Not sticky, no tanning.
Come here, I’ll apply some on you too.
Come over here
Take your jacket off.
It's all natural
even suitable for sensitive skin.
Don't worry
I’ll protect that handsome face of yours.
You must be thirsty.
How did you know I like this?
and this, too
I made it just for you
this morning.
Finish everything
Then I’m digging in.
You’re an amazing cook
Such a great woman
I’d better marry her ASAP.
What?
Do you want to marry a wife—
or marry a housemaid
who can cook and do laundry for you?
Just kidding
I’d never make you work that hard.
You don’t have to do this anymore,
we’ll eat out.
You rarely get a day off.
Just relax
Let’s move to the next plan later
That’s my girlfriend,
so thoughtful.
You even have itinerary planned
Of course
Eat this first.
Have some more
Okay
Hotter than I thought.
That’s all it takes?
Thought you guys had thicker skin.
Sounds like you want to find out
how thick my skin really is?
You invited me to a hot spring—
aren’t you afraid I’ll eat you alive?
Since I've invited you here,
do I look scared?
Don’t regret it.
Wait, I’m changing.
Hurry up
I want to check out the essential oil one
This is a public bath area
aren’t you worried about being seen?
Let’s go somewhere else—
somewhere more private.
Police raided
the male host club “Church”yesterday
suspected ties to loan sharks
luring women into
paying on credit
forcing them to sign high-value IOUs
If unpaid...
forced into hostess or overseas work
The accounts have been
wiped clean.
Leo has people watching.
Police won’t reach us yet.
As for other stores
I told them
to stay low
Good work.
Sure
Also, according to police
Leo, head of the club "Church"
is missing
Police are making every effort to apprehend him
They are also clarifying if
there's possible linked to a bigger network
behind this incident
You rock!
Police got the evidences
and shut the club down
This is just warm-up.
Let’s celebrate?
Aren’t we tired enough?
By the way,
About the Gang rules—
“Don't hurt the elder, women, or children.”
"the Elder" here
might not mean actual old people
but refer to certain someone.
Why bring this up?
We keep hiding here is
because there's a rumor…
The gang won’t touch the club
for that rule
Lee Xun is investigating
"the Elder" is likely an assassin.
You're saying
the Boss might owe him,
"the Elder",
a huge favor
That’s why the rule exists.
But
what does that have to do with us?
Do you know if Ma had any tattoos?
I don't
He doesn't exactly strip,
beside, we’re not that close.
You’ve all worked hard lately.
Yuchuan suggested…
let's relax in the hot springs
and do skin care at the same time.
After all, we make a living off our "bodies".
I have a question
is this gonna be mixed-gender?
It’s my first time at a hot spring,
do we have to get completely naked?
No way, I just did this yesterday.
That would totally ruin my nice memory with Rou Rou
with a bunch of dudes around.
The point is to check someone’s tattoo...
Alright, everyone go in first.
Let's do this
hot spring
Hey, we don’t get out like this often
Don’t keep that sour face on.
I heard this place—
is great for improving muscle and joint mobility
Just enjoy it.
What are you so exciting about?
I've been doing the hot spring nonstop…
It’s hot spring!
Hot spring!
There you go yapping again.
Tony
Why aren’t you changing with us?
Why are you hiding in there?
Ma, why aren’t you changing?
Feeling shy?
yeah, why not?
My stomach suddenly feels off.
I’m going to the restroom first.
Go ahead without me.
Did he figure out our plan?
No rush
You can't be in the hot spring dressed.
We’ll get our chance.
YuChuan
will there be any issue if I do this two days in a row?
I don't know
Tony哥
Tony
Why is Ma taking so long?
I'll go check
What's the matter?
A little disappointed?
Were you expecting something?
way too guarded.
That’s not cool, man
We’re all guys here together—
and you’re in a tank top and swim trunks?
Isn’t that a bit distant?
It’s not about that.
My body is given by my parents
though we're in the hot spring
better stay covered to avoid catching a cold.
Or
do you have something in mind today?
Alright, alright
We hardly come out together
Don’t be so uptight.
Just relax
Enjoy the hot spring
then get back to work refreshed.
I’m so exhausted.
The hot spring felt amazing.
Nice and warm all over.
Rou rou
Ah-Jun
Hey...
My diamonds
What the heck...
This is real!
How much will these cost?
Talk!
Why did you steal from me?
I didn't do it on purpose
Biao forced me.
You're with Azure Dragon Syndicate?
it's a misunderstanding
I owe him gambling debts.
If I don't follow his instructions,
he’d make my life hell.
Since he knew I'm here
then why doesn’t he come himself?
Because
this place is off-limits.
The gang has rules,
No hurting the elder, women, or children.
Hey, we already knew it
Can you tell us something more useful?
I already told you
everything
I know
Please let me go
Okay...
Then choose
A finger…
or a toe?
Boss Hao, I'm sorry, I won't do it again
Please give me a break
Please...
Screw your begging
Pan Hao
Keep him alive
He can monitor the gang.
Jun
Yes?
Listen carefully…
If you touch my stuff again—
It's not gonna be just a finger
Yes
you won’t live to see tomorrow.
Got it?
Yes
Get lost.
Thanks, Boss Hao
How did you get the diamonds?
When I first
joined the gang—
they got me in
this big deal event
because I'm capable
Things went sideways in a shootout.
Everyone died.
I was the only survivor.
I figured
I took the diamonds as compensation
and they've been chasing me since
With their power…
you’re lucky to still be alive.
that's right, why are you with us
with so many diamonds?
I'd be gone if I were you
You think I didn’t try?
I run into the gang members
every time I tried to run away
Besides,
I met the love of my life here.
Are you going to run for life?
You need a plan
to handle these diamonds.
Exactly, the gang won't let go off you
That’s why I’m hiding here
in the club
Hey...
we’ve been through life and death together.
If anything goes wrong,
we've got each other's back.
OK
I gotta get back to work.
Dude,
funny how fast you run now.
David,
Casting just sent over more actor profiles
Want to take another look?
Let’s talk about it tomorrow
I’m tired today
What kind of male lead are you actually looking for?
How did it go?
Rou rou
Jay
Stop the car
Is he a new host?
He’s ridiculously handsome
No, sorry
Sir
Is this your first time here?
Would you like me to introduce
our hosts?
No need
I want him