Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional
and created for
entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
D*ck!
His d*ck, bro!
Watch his d*ck!
Why the hell are you yelling so loud?
You scared me!
I could've accidentally cut his d*ck.
Sorry.
I've never handled a case like this before.
Don't worry, Beer.
To is great with d*cks.
Whether it's ring cases,
or Benz's carving
that ended in a bloody mess.
Argh. Bee!
Now's really not the time
to go over my work history.
Help me hold him still.
I don't want to mess this up.
Hey!
Bro, no. Please.
No!
Please. Nooooo!
(If life is a journey, )
(my life is about charging forward.)
(So no matter what I do, )
(I'm meticulous every step of the way.)
Ouch! Be careful with my d*ck!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Ouch!
My d*ck!
My d*ck! Ah!
Be careful with my man's d*ck.
We still need it, you know.
Bro!
It's just lifting a bag.
Why can't you help?
I'm very sorry, but your bag looks heavy.
Would you like to check it in?
Why do I have to check it in?
I've never had to anywhere else.
You work in service, so you should help.
Do you think being a flight attendant
makes you so high and mighty?
All you do is dress up.
Let me handle this.
Ma'am, I can only help you this time.
Next time, if your bag is heavy,
please check it in.
Okay.
Is this yours?
Oh, my friend asked me to buy it for them.
This is exactly why cabin crew
shouldn't lift passengers' luggage.
We don't want to damage
their valuable belongings.
Enjoy the flight.
(I believe that if we work hard enough, )
(one day, we'll reach our destination.)
Ahhh!
Be careful with my d*ck!
Bro, no!
It finally came off.
Let's take him to the hospital.
How's that for wearing it to last longer?
You almost lost the
chance to ever last again.
Being a man is not about your d*ck.
It's about your heart.
Having a big d*ck doesn't mean anything.
If you have a big heart,
people will love you.
Come on. Let's take him to the hospital.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Excuse me.
Babe, are you okay?
Get up slowly.
(My life was going well, )
(but everything turned upside down)
(after I met this guy.)
Mr. Boiling Tofu.
Stray-Dog Scammer.
You're cunning, huh?
Hey, I'm calling the cops!
(A rescuer who came into my life)
(and changed it forever.)
"A Dog and A Plane"
(Episode 1)
BANGKOK
Thanks for saving me.
Otherwise, I would've lost it.
How am I supposed to help everyone
lift their luggage?
If I helped this one,
someone else would want me to help too.
I'm already in my 30s.
My back hurts.
I get it, but we work in customer service.
We have to do our job.
We can't just snap and lose our temper.
We have to keep our emotions in check.
All we can do is
give them a passive-aggressive smile.
But it's okay.
Just treat me to omakase and we're good.
Kanit! So you only helped
because you wanted something in return?
But okay.
Guess who this is.
Who is it?
Come on.
I could tell it was you
just from your perfume.
I thought you said you were flying today.
Yes, I am.
But I wanted to get my boyfriend fix first,
so I'd be fully recharged for work.
Oh, wow.
Why don't you just have my friend
sit next to you then?
Please. I don't sit next to him.
I only sit on top of him.
Oh, so you talk back now?
But let me tell you something,
you're doing more than
just sitting on top of me tonight.
Oh!
Have mercy on this single lady!
You two are making my imagination run wild.
Sorry, I've already
gotten my boyfriend fix.
I'll call you when I land.
Okay.
I'm going now.
Bye-bye.
Safe flight.
Thanks.
Wow! He's totally whipped for you.
What good deed did
you do in your past life?
Your boyfriend is handsome, rich,
and even works near you.
Still, he works for a different airline.
But it's okay. I'll get
into his airline one day.
Then we'll be known as
the flight attendant-and-captain couple.
I'll show him off all over the airport.
Sure.
Ow!
Are we almost at the hospital?
It hurts!
Hurry up, Ki!
His wiener is turning purple!
Yeah!
I am hurrying!
This is a mission to save his wiener.
You'll be in the doctor's hands soon.
You'll still be able to use it. Trust me.
MISS YOU ALREADY
Okay, okay.
I'm going.
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Damn it!
What the hell was that driving?
I'm going to deal with you!
What kind of driving was that?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
You almost killed
everyone in the rescue car!
How the hell were you driving?!
It's obviously an intersection,
and you still sped through it!
Are you crazy?
It shot forward on its own.
Nobody wanted to crash into you.
Damn it!
Did something happen to the car?
Let's call your insurance.
Give me the number.
What do you mean, call insurance?
The cars didn't even hit each other.
Aren't you going to compensate me
for the shock?
My heart already went to the underworld,
you know?
Are you some kind of scammer?
Waiting for someone to pull out
so you can crash into them?
I've seen those clips.
I'm not falling for your scam.
Come on, Mr. Tofu Face.
Watching too many vertical dramas?
Huh?
What did you just call me?
Tofu Face, of course.
Your angry face looks like boiling tofu.
Like tofu boiling in a sukiyaki pot.
Have you seen it?
Blub blub blub blub.
You've got some nerve criticizing
someone else when you look like that.
Why?
You look like a stray dog.
The kind that barks at modified cars
blowing black exhaust smoke.
What kind of job do you even do
dressed like that?
A magician?
I'm a flight attendant.
Ever heard of it?
Yeah.
So, are you going to compensate me
for the shock or not, flight attendant?
I can pay,
but only through the proper legal process.
Not here.
You're cunning.
Huh?
Hey, what are you doing?
You're cunning, huh?
I'm calling the cops!
Are you paying or not?
Don't come any closer.
I'm calling the cops.
Go ahead. Do it.
Don't come any closer.
So what's it going to be?
No!
Are you paying or not?
Let's go, To!
We need to hurry.
The injured guy can't take it anymore.
If I weren't worried about his d*ck,
I'd deal with you.
I don't even want to see you again.
Uncivilized.
Barbarian.
Barbarian, my ass!
What do you think?
He's just my type.
Hey.
Hmm?
This bag is pretty.
Hmm? Let me see.
It'll make a good carry-on.
Yeah.
Hey, but it's expensive.
I'm not going to get it.
Up to you.
But it's pretty.
Let's check out other things.
Excuse me.
You're holding the bag I'm interested in.
Could you please give it back?
Give it back?
I don't think so.
I happen to be buying this bag too.
Damn.
This scene looks familiar.
I feel like I've seen it before.
Excuse me.
Can I get a new one and the bill, please?
I'm sorry.
That's the last one we have in stock.
Oops. Sorry.
Looks like this bag is coming home with me.
I may have come later,
but you were the one who let go first.
I was just taking time to think about it.
You took too long.
You're not the only one with good taste.
Other people do too.
You know what to do, right?
Please take my card.
I have cash.
Then I'll take this
one, this one, this one,
and this one too.
It's up to you
who you want to sell it to.
Thank god that guy gave in,
but why the hell did you buy four bags?
Now I'm the one suffering!
You talked me into it.
I'm Kanit.
I can handle getting hurt,
but losing face would kill me.
It's just your pride, not your man.
You don't have to be
so afraid of losing it.
I'm dying here.
Why are we even dragging four bags anyway?
Ahhh!
Shit!
I almost died.
Wait for me!
Ah!
Relaxing, right?
Your muscles are so tight.
Yeah.
Now that I'm in my 30s,
my body's really falling apart.
Are you already 39?
You're the same age as my dad!
Shut up, I'm only 31!
You already want me to be your dad?
Daddy.
Hello, Daddy.
Don't let me see you guys getting old.
Thanks for asking me
to work with you, Daddy.
I'm only making you struggle.
It's all blood and tears in our lives.
Hey.
Who's crying this late at night?
Did a ghost come to haunt us, To?
Beer!
It's not some damn ghost.
It's me crying.
Oh?
Ki!
What's wrong?
Kae texted me to break up.
She dumped me!
I knew it.
Long-distance relationships never work.
She lives in Phang Nga
and you're out here
living like a dog in Bangkok.
I'm going to go beg her
to get back with me.
I know I've been working hard lately,
but isn't breaking up over text too harsh?
It's okay.
She said she wants to be alone.
She doesn't want a relationship anymore.
She's definitely cheating on me!
Why do you think that?
I heard another guy's
voice when I called her.
She said her gay friend came over.
That's bullshit.
I have gay friends.
I know what they sound like.
That bitch!
If you're sure she's cheating on you,
then let's prove it.
Prove what?
Prove that his girlfriend's
cheating on him.
If she wants to break up with him,
at least give him a good reason.
I'm not letting my bro get played.
It's okay.
Hey, that's enough.
Hey.
Hmm?
That's enough.
I'm going to take a shower.
No, don't go yet.
I like your scent on me.
It smells nice.
Enough. I feel so sticky.
Don't go yet.
We rarely get to spend time together.
Tonight,
I'm taking you on a
long flight with no transit.
Enough.
Tomorrow morning, I have to leave early
for a wedding in Phang Nga.
I haven't even bought anything yet.
I might…
not be able to go with you anymore.
Oh? Why not?
I've had this planned with you
since last month.
I know I promised you,
but my friend Meng needs help.
His wife has to have surgery on her uterus.
He needs to stay with her,
so he asked to swap flights with me.
I have to cover his flight.
But why you?
Is there really no one else he can ask?
There really is no one else.
Remember your birthday?
Meng agreed to swap
flights with me for that.
But I already told my parents
you're coming with me.
I want to show off to my family
that my boyfriend is a captain.
I'm sorry,
but my friend really needs help.
It's not that I don't
want to meet your family.
I really do want to meet them,
so I can try the Southern curry
and see if the original flavor is as spicy
as what you just gave me.
I won't break any more promises.
Mm. Don't ditch me again next time.
I won't.
Wow, To.
You bought an expensive bag
just for this trip?
Expensive?
I got this from in front of the foundation.
It only cost a thousand baht.
What?
Mm.
Hold on.
Wow, but this is a designer bag.
Really?
This must be a premium knockoff.
I just thought the print looked nice,
so I bought it.
To, you're handsome
and you have good taste.
The only problem is
you're a little too broke.
(Screw you.)
Thank god I'm handsome.
Yeah, yeah, you're handsome.
Enough with the compliments.
I need to take a shit.
Alright, let's go.
Shithead.
Okay.
I'll call you when I get there.
(Safe trip.)
(Next time, I promise I'll properly
introduce myself to your parents in person.)
Hey, shouldn't you be
asking for my hand next time?
(I just might.)
(Talk later. I have to work now.)
Okay. Safe flight.
(Bye-bye.)
Hey!
Oh!
Whoa.
Mr. Boiling Tofu.
Another hit-and-run, huh?
Look who it is.
It's the Stray-Dog Scammer.
Don't you ever watch where you're going?
Or did your brakes
fail again like last time?
I was walking straight ahead.
You're the one rushing off to
who knows where.
What are you, a high-speed grandma?
Look, I know it was an accident,
but do you even know how to apologize?
It's basic manners.
Didn't you learn proper manners in school?
Seriously?
Excuse me. Back in high school,
I won the Lower Southern Thailand.
Good Manners Award.
But I save my manners
for people with manners.
Are you sure you actually
competed in that contest?
Fine, I'm sorry.
An apology like that? Just keep it.
Then what do you want, huh?
You wanna go one-on-one?
Wanna go at it?
Huh?
Solving problems with violence?
Barbaric.
Barbaric or not, you'll see.
You're gonna cry.
Whoa.
Looks like we gotta charge in, bro.
You wanna go?
Charge?
Oh, I'm definitely about to
let something charge out.
Hurry up. I need to take a shit!
Oh?
Alright.
Come on!
Help!
Help! Is anyone there?
My door's broken!
What's wrong with your door?
It's broken.
It won't open.
Could you get someone to help?
Hey, it's okay.
I'm a rescuer. I'll help you.
But how are you going to do that?
If the door's broken,
then I'll just break it down.
What? No!
Please just get someone else to help.
I don't want the door
slamming into my face.
It's okay. I can save you.
Step all the way back.
No!
Step back.
Trust me.
I deal with this kind
of thing all the time.
The door's going to hit my face. No!
Step back, okay?
Hey!
Step back!
Sorry, I couldn't stop.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
The lock's broken. It's all rusty.
We should tell them to replace it.
I'll make a complaint myself.
I have to go.
Occupied!
Not you again.
Didn't you see it was occupied?
Why did you keep knocking?
You have no manners.
I saw it, but you were taking forever.
I thought you died in the toilet
and turned into poop particles in the air.
I waited until the plane almost landed.
Were you planning to never let anyone else
take a shit?
Don't be dramatic. I
wasn't in there that long.
You're messing with me on purpose.
Don't flatter yourself.
How did it even take you that long to poop?
Did you eat an elephant or something?
I have to use the bathroom after you.
Is my nose going to stop working?
Am I going to die?
Gross.
I only went in there to pee.
There's no smell.
If there's any smell,
it's my expensive perfume.
Mm.
That smells more like funeral perfume.
What are you talking about?
It's amber wood.
It smells seductively good.
I bet all you smell every day is
roadside exhaust fumes.
You should get your nose cleaned sometimes,
so you can smell
something expensive like this.
Mm, then let me smell it.
I'm going to sniff your neck
and see how good it is.
Hey!
Pretty tempting.
Tempting my temper!
Move!
I'm going to take a shit!
PHANG NGA
I've arrived, Mom. I'm at the hotel.
Sure, I'm coming right over.
Mm.
No f*cking way.
Mom, I have to go.
See you at the wedding.
What is this?
This must belong to that punk.
Ew!
When did we swap bags?
Shit!
This must belong to
that tofu-faced flight attendant.
Wow.
These clothes and this watch.
This is all good stuff, bro.
Yeah, he's right.
These are all authentic.
Not premium knockoffs like yours.
How am I supposed to return this to him?
I don't even have his number.
Then there's no need to rush.
Can we borrow these?
No way!
That's basically stealing his stuff.
After all that public service,
don't you have any conscience?
What the hell, Ki?
Hey!
We're trying to go undercover
and catch Kae cheating.
I just need this for a quick disguise.
It'll be fine.
Hell no!
Take it off.
Listen. Do you have money to buy us
the stuff we need for our disguise?
Yeah.
Can I borrow 1,000?
I forgot to bring my wallet.
Let me borrow 1,500.
Alright, idiots.
Fine.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Just get this over with
and return the clothes ASAP.
Nice.
We've been watching for a while.
Nothing's going on.
She's just working like normal.
He's right.
We've been spying on her for a while now.
It's probably nothing.
Hey, keep it low-key.
What do you think, bro?
Do we keep going or stop here?
Let's wait a little longer
and follow her back to her room.
I'm going to talk things out with her.
I'm wearing fancy clothes, after all.
I might as well make the most of them.
Okay.
Come on.
She finishes work and goes straight home.
There's nothing suspicious.
You should go talk
things out with her nicely.
Whatever you do, keep it down.
Be considerate of the neighbors.
Yeah.
Mm.
Go.
Who are you?
And who are you?
Who is it?
Kae!
Ki.
What's the meaning of this?
Who's this guy?
This is Yak. He's my new boyfriend.
New boyfriend?
But you said you were living
with your gay friend.
You bitch!
You bastard!
Are you calling me gay?
This is not a gay friend.
This is a side piece!
It's your fault you
didn't have time for me.
You were busy with
your rescue work at ungodly hours.
I've been earning money
so we could be together!
Why didn't you wait for me?
You took too long.
Just leave.
No, I'm going to talk to you.
Hey!
You got dumped and you still don't get it?
Dumbass!
Get the f*ck out of here
and don't ever come back!
What's your problem?
Hey, Ki!
Ki!
No fighting!
Let's go!
Kae, don't leave me!
- Ki!
- Kae!
Don't leave me!
CHALOR &amp; YUWADEE
25 FEBRUARY 2026
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Thank you so much.
Of course. You're so sweet.
Stay in love, you two.
Thank you so much.
They're so cute.
What are you wearing?
Why aren't you in a suit?
Honey, look at how he's dressed.
It's a long story, Dad.
It's okay.
Let him do whatever he's comfortable with.
Our son is handsome
no matter what he wears.
You two sure love praising each other.
Hey, I thought you were
bringing your boyfriend to meet me.
The one who's a captain.
Something urgent came up.
He couldn't make it.
Again?
I don't believe
you really have a boyfriend anymore.
Of course I do, Dad.
He's a captain.
He's really handsome and rich too.
Always bragging.
When will I ever get to meet him?
Calm down.
Good thing Kana brought a partner
and saved us some face.
Don't mind your dad.
It's fine that your
boyfriend couldn't come.
I'm glad you're here.
You never do anything like other people.
You're from the South
and you can't even speak Southern.
Come on. It's okay.
I can speak it, I just don't like to.
Why? Just why, Kae?
Keep it down.
I tried so hard,
but in the end,
she chose someone
with bigger muscles than me.
I can build more muscle, you know?
I can do it.
Listen to me, bro.
Even if you inject
steroids into your muscles
and they get as big as a baby's head,
she still wouldn't choose you.
It hurts.
Hang in there.
Hey, Ki.
I think you should
get back up and move on.
Yeah.
I want to die!
Then jump into the sea.
I'm going to jump into the sea.
Okay, go ahead.
It's salty.
That's amazing.
Congrats. Wow.
Cheers!
Again?
Yeah, I'm on my way.
Talk later.
You scammers!
Hey!
How could you?
How dare you guys wear my clothes?
Huh?
That watch too!
You guys stole my bag on purpose,
didn't you?
I'm reporting all of you!
Hey, calm down.
Our bags got mixed up.
No one meant for this to happen.
I didn't have anything to wear,
so I just borrowed your clothes, okay?
You're wearing my clothes too.
Let's call it even.
Come on.
Call it even?
These shabby shirts and boxers?
You wanna call it even?
Which brain cell came up with that idea?
My boxers are expensive, you know?
Expensive or just moldy?
Do you even know how many
hundreds of thousands this all costs?
Can you even afford to pay me back?
You're looking down on me.
Poor people have dignity too, you know?
Poor people don't have to be thieves!
I'm taking this all the way.
Fine!
Let's just take everything off right here!
Yeah!
Show him we have no bad intentions.
Are you serious?
I agree!
I don't like anyone
trampling on my dignity!
Hey, hey!
Happy now?
We only have our balls left.
Do you want them too?
No.
Go bring my bag back too.
I'll wait here.
Hey!
You're still here?
And why the hell did you guys
take your shirts off?
I told you to leave, didn't I?
Who are you?
Are you the governor?
Why should I listen to you?
You bastard.
You're seriously getting on my nerves.
Someone like you needs to learn
who runs this area.
Don't hurt my bro, you son of a bitch!
Hey!
My stuff!
Hey. You okay?
I told you they picked a fight with us.
He's sleeping with my bro's girlfriend.
You guys can sort out
the cheating yourselves.
But this turned into a brawl
and damaged someone else's property.
How are you going to take responsibility?
I only have 5,000 on me. Will that work?
I want 50,000.
If you don't have it, go sleep in jail.
Arrest him, officer.
Hold on, officer.
I have to go home and take care of
my sister tomorrow. I'm begging you.
Help me talk to him.
I saved you.
Hold on, officer.
Could you please
add another charge for them?
They wore my designer clothes
and ruined them!
No one stole your clothes.
I just borrowed them without asking.
Shut up.
My clothes and watch are worth 450,000.
I have proof that they're all mine.
If they don't have the money
to pay me back,
then add another charge.
I told you I don't have money.
What do you want me to do?
Can I work it off?
No.
No money?
Then go to jail!
Hey, easy.
Hey!
Come on!
Please help me. I'm begging you.
Please. I'm begging you. Help me!
Mr. Tofu, please help me.
Hey!
You tofu-faced idiot!
Come on!
Hey. You okay?
You okay?
We're sorry, To.
You shouldn't have to
take the blame for us.
You're such a boss.
It's okay.
I'll call and ask Seng to help us out.
I'll probably have to
borrow money from him.
It's my fault. I should've stopped you two.
Hey, someone bailed you guys out.
This is for saving me.
I paid for the damage to the shop.
Thank you.
You didn't help us for free, did you?
That's right.
You guys are going to work off your debt
until it's fully paid off.
And if you even think about running off,
you'll be spending a long time in jail.
I'm not going to run away.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
7 DAYS LATER
Lew!
Tonlew!
Hey!
What did you do?
You almost burned the whole house down.
I was going to make a fermented pork
omelet using your recipe.
I was on my phone too,
so I forgot to turn off the gas.
Wow.
Be more careful next time.
Our house is made of wood.
It's perfect fuel for a fire.
Why didn't you wake me up
if you wanted an omelet?
I would've made it for you.
I didn't want to bother you.
It was already morning when you got back.
I wanted you to sleep.
Next time, you can wake me up.
Just let me know what you want to eat.
I'll make it for you.
Go have a seat.
You just made things harder.
Here comes the real thing.
The original fermented pork omelet
from your brother To.
The just-woke-up recipe.
Try it and see if it still tastes the same.
Exactly the same.
Do you need a ride to school?
No.
Every time you drop me off in the rescue
car, people think something happened.
I don't want to cause a scene.
Isn't that a good thing?
You'd stand out.
How about I turn on the siren
next time I drop you off?
No thanks.
When's your tuition due?
End of this month.
Good. There's still plenty of time.
What do you mean ‘plenty of time'?
Today's already the 25th.
Huh?
It's the 25th already?
Mm.
What?
It feels like I just paid for it.
If it's too expensive, I can transfer
to another school. I don't mind.
No, you don't have to.
Just work hard in school.
Leave the money to me, got it?
Yeah, I'm hurrying.
My car is still being fixed.
Just hang around while you wait for me.
Like I wait for you every time.
I have to go.
Hello.
Toto Service.
Happy to serve with my life.
Today, I'm on duty to
drop you off at work, sir.
I don't like that.
Can I do it again?
Toto Service.
Get anywhere fast the way you like it.
I'm on duty to drop you off at work, sir.
Your men were the ones causing trouble.
Are you really taking
all the responsibility?
I'm the self-sacrificing type.
As the leader, I have
to take responsibility.
Besides, working with someone
as picky as you
is something only I can handle.
We'll see if you can handle it.
Where's the car you're using
to take me to the airport?
Don't worry. I prepared a royal ride
worthy of your status.
This way, please.
THE WINNERS RESCUE FOUNDATION
Hey!
Did you bring a body transport car
to pick me up?
Exactly.
I was worried you'd be late for work,
so I came as fast as I could.
Hey!
There's actually a body inside!
Of course.
It's a body transport car.
What were you expecting, minced pork?
I think the person has
been dead for 10 days.
There are so many worms
crawling all over the body.
The smell is really strong.
Get in and see for yourself.
I'm getting a taxi.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What taxi? I came all the way here.
Get in.
No way!
I owe you money.
Let me hurry up and work it off
in this lifetime.
No, I'm not going.
Let's go.
No way!
No, I'm not going!
Hey! No!
Open the door!
Open it!
Hey, drive carefully!
I don't want to become the next body.
You know nothing. So many people
would kill to be my passenger princess.
Who would even want that?
Count me out.
You don't need to pick me up again.
Just find another way to pay me back.
Okay, fine.
If this is not thrilling enough,
I'll take you to do something
even more thrilling.
If you don't want my pick-up
and drop-off service,
allow me to help you relax instead.
A friend of mine owns this massage place.
I'll give you a free session today.
Take off your clothes and lie down.
Do I really have to take off my shirt?
Yeah.
Maybe just massage over my clothes.
I don't trust you.
Please.
You don't have to guard
your body that much.
It's not like I'm even
that attracted to you.
You're not my type.
Come on!
Right there.
How are you feeling?
Good?
Yes, right there.
So good.
Oh.
Mm.
So good.
It's getting even better.
I guarantee it'll hit the spot.
Hey! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
B to B, of course.
Body to body.
I'm going this far for you.
You better cut my debt down a lot, okay?
Cut what?
I want no more of this!
That's enough. Stop.
No!
I'm about to show you my signature move.
Reaching into the Dragon's Den.
Hey, no!
Stop!
Nooooo!
Hello, Lion.
Where are you?
(I'm at home sick, lying in bed.)
Oh? Really?
Do you want me to come over?
Have you taken any medicine?
(It's okay. You don't have to come.)
(I don't want you
catching the virus from me.)
(I just need some
rest and I'll feel better.)
(I'll see you later, okay?)
Okay. Get plenty of rest.
We turn left at this intersection, right?
Sorry, can we turn right instead?
I want to stop by my partner's place.
Sure.
Thank you.
Hey!
Lion!
Could it be his birthday?
Hey, Lion.
Lion!
Hello, Lion.
How are you feeling?
(I'm still not feeling very well.)
(I'm in my room sick, lying in bed.)
Which room?
(Well… my bedroom at home, of course.)
But…
(Kanit, is something wrong?)
Oh, it's nothing.
Don't forget to take your medicine.
Get well soon.
(Okay.)
(I'm going to get some sleep.
(I'm really not feeling well.)
Bye.
Tomorrow morning, I have to wake
up early for a wedding in Phang Nga.
I might…
not be able to go with you anymore.
My friend needs help,
so I have to cover his flight.
We're heading out.
Mm.
Once I'm done fixing
this, I'll head out too.
See you.
See you, bro.
(Calling Polca 01.)
(A cat is stuck on the roof of a house)
(in Charan Soi 91.)
(We need you on-site ASAP.)
Do you seriously not have any other team?
(If I did, would I be calling you?)
(Go help them out.)
(That family donated a lot to us.)
Alright.
Let's go.
We're on standby 24/7 anyway.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Excuse me, can you follow that car?
Oh.
Okay.
Hey! Hey!
Pull over!
Hey!
By the time we get there, that cat
might've already come down from the tree.
Hey! Hey! Pull over!
Hey!
I have something urgent!
Can you call the boss
and say we'll be late?
Yeah, okay.
Let me text him real quick.
Stop the car!
I have something urgent
to talk to you about!
Hey!
Cats stress me out more than people do.
Damn it.
I'm not even this stressed over people.
Hey, go cut them off up ahead.
You got it, boss!
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
Stop!
Hey!
Hey, why did you stop the car?
Get out and talk to your rival.
Hey!
Do you want to die? Is that why
you're blocking the rescue vehicle?
What's this?
Did you come to collect the debt?
Isn't this too much?
Please just let me work. I'm begging you.
I'm not here to collect your debt.
I've figured out how you can repay me.
Is this really the time?
Can't you see I'm in a hurry?
I can't wait.
I'm too anxious. It has to be now.
What is it? Make it quick.
I have to go save a cat.
I need you to investigate
my boyfriend's cheating.
What?
I just caught my boyfriend lying to me.
And I remember you just helped your friend
investigate their cheating partner too.
I knew it.
You dared to risk your life
because your man's going to dump you.
How about this?
If I help you with this,
can we consider my debt paid?
If you can prove it with evidence,
I might consider forgiving your debt.
Then don't worry.
Other people's business
is my area of expertise,
Mr. Boiling Tofu.
Just don't be all bark and no bite.
I need results too,
Mr. Black-Smoke Barking Dog.
You'll see.
I'm not all talk.
Be careful.
Hey, bro.
Stop flirting.
That cat is waiting.
Who's flirting?
Why would I even flirt
with someone who looks like this?
You're not even good-looking.
(Next Episode)
What about catching my boyfriend cheating?
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
I'll open your eyes
to your boyfriend's true colors.
He's a lying piece of shit.
People usually sneak off to clubs.
He sneaks off to a temple.
Kanit.
If you have to doubt
your partner like this,
you'll never be happy.