Of course, you're always there.
I know you wouldn't abandon me.
And I know you will always protect me.
That's why I didn't get scared,
as long as I'm with you.
Wait a minute. She?
Of course, I want to know.
When can I meet them? Can I?
Perfect! Can we meet them tomorrow?
- Just for you.
- Perfect!
So, you're still not sleepy?
Just a little talk, she shouts right away.
That's because of you!
You're so annoying!
You keep getting ahead of her
in making decisions in her life,
especially in her relationship with Mikoy.
If she wants to tell Mikoy
the truth, fine!
If she doesn't, then don't!
What do you mean Chiara is distracted?
She's not distracted.
You're just not used to it
because it's your first time
seeing your daughter in love.
That's exactly why I'm worried.
So what?
Let me remind you
that our child's life has not been easy.
A chaotic life!
Since she was young,
she always has to keep
her eyes open all the time!
So just let her be.
Let her go crazy over Mikoy.
I don't care.
At least now, for the first time,
there's someone else
who will sacrifice for her.
Right?
See!
That's what you're good at.
You really love sleeping!
Mikoy?
I need your help.
Why, what's wrong? Where are you?
No! I'm just at home.
No emergency, no danger.
Then why did you call?
I have a big problem.
What?
I need friends!
Hey!
You know, I really want to kiss you
because Daddy Sir
is so impressed with you.
Dad is so happy.
Can you believe it?
He even gave an extra allowance!
Want me to treat you?
Let's watch a movie.
I'll pay for the popcorn too.
Thanks for the offer.
But I need to catch up on my lit readings.
Do you want me to help you?
I've got it.
So you like romantic novels.
No wonder you were so good
at being romantic last night.
Just because I'm reading this doesn't mean
I suddenly became Jane Austen.
I'm not romantic at all.
Yeah, right!
I don't think so.
You're actually really sweet!
I just did what you suggested.
That I use my imagination.
That I imagine the person I really like.
So, you really imagined Jennie?
Jennie?
Not Jennie.
It's Luisa Mae.
Luisa Mae?
Why don't you have any friends?
I do have friends.
But none here in Manila.
They're back in my hometown.
Since Boss Mikoy is big time now,
you should be drinking
something expensive.
Sure!
What is this?!
One hundred and fifty per liter.
Tomorrow, it's plus 30.
You walk home.
This won't work on Chiara.
Of course, I'm new here in Manila.
I don't really know many people yet.
Okay, but why did you
use that as an excuse?
I couldn't think of anything else.
We just have to find some people
who can pretend to be Mikoy's friends.
So we'll hold auditions for new friends?
Come on.
That's probably not necessary.
Because if you think about it,
it looks like I already have friends here.
What if she recognizes you?
What if she's already spotted you?
She probably won't notice.
I'll handle everything.
I'll cover for you, okay?
You'll handle it, and we suffer?
You'll cover for it,
then we're the ones who fix the mess?
Hey!
Come on!
That's extremely risky!
It could compromise our mission.
Don't say yes!
But if Chiara finds out
that Mikoy is lying
and that he doesn't
really have any friends,
then he loses her trust.
And our mission
will be even more compromised.
Okay.
It's up to you, but I'll be in disguise.
You won't recognize me.
Which one there is Luisa Mae?
‪Five, six, seven…
There.
She's pretty, right?
That's Luisa Mae.
In fairness, she's stunning!
They're good, right?
And she's so kind too.
Huh? Of course, definitely!
Sweetheart, come on.
They'll definitely like you.
Where are your friends?
- Mikoy!
- There!
Sianong!
Good to see you, bro!
Huh?
Finally! Now Chiara has a face
that Mikoy always talks about.
And I'm not surprised
why he keeps you hidden.
Because with…
that beauty of yours,
a lot would try to steal you.
That's right.
You're good, Sianong.
You're better than "alright".
- Alright is alright.
- That punchline was strong!
Alex? Where is he?
- Oh.
- Right, where is…
Wait, you know he's usually around here.
Wow!
Mikoy!
Alex!
Chiara the Valtrovi?
Oh! I so love your earrings.
They're so beautiful!
You're so fancy, girl!
Well, my eye bags are as deep
as the Mariana Trench
from working graveyard shifts
at the call center,
and I still can't afford Tom!
What did you feed Chiara?
Did you use some love potion from Quiapo?
Huh? No way!
Don't tell me she fell
for your sexy dance moves?
Uh…
No way! Come on!
And you said
I could pass as Enrique Gil
on a rough day, right?
Right?
- Right?
- Yuck!
Oh my gosh!
Hey guys, before anything else,
this is the old news,
Alex, Sianong.
Chiara Valtrovi.
Wow, now he's speaking English
and being all sweet?
Wait.
You look familiar.
Oh! No! No! You know, Chiara,
you're not gonna believe this.
Our friend Alex here…
She's really pretty, right?
She actually looks like a famous actress.
Her name is…
- Kim!
- Dominguez.
- You idiot!
Santo Domingo!
- Oh right! Santo Domingo!
- Ah, yes! Yes!
It's always awkward at first when meeting.
That's true!
- Hey, guys, let's sit down.
- There!
- Let's go!
- Yes!
You haven't slept yet, have you?
Yeah!
There!
Does she know you?
Luisa Mae.
Or you're just her stalker?
I'm not a stalker!
I'm just not sure if she knows me.
But of course, I know her.
Everyone knows her.
That's why she's
the most popular girl in school.
I'm sure you have a lot of rivals.
Wait! Why do you even like her?
Well,
there are a lot of reasons
why she's the popular girl in our school.
Aside from her beautiful face,
you know, she takes a lot of initiative
with donation drives,
both inside and outside the school.
She also organizes
free food drives for strays,
free spaying and neutering
for cats and dogs,
community pantries.
She even holds job fairs
for senior citizens.
And you know, she also fights for causes!
Wage increase.
Lower prices of basic goods.
- Vote wisely for the country!
- Okay, fine! Fine! Fine!
She has everything.
She was born with ube toppings
on top of her head.
She's the most special
of all special halo-halo!
Wait, Sophie.
You still owe me a favor, right?
Can you find a way for us to meet?
Tell us a story. How did you meet?
But this time, from Chiara's POV.
Oh, right.
We already know your side!
No, I think it's better
if we start with Alex.
How did you and Mikoy meet?
Mikoy and I…
When I applied here in Manila for Prague,
I worked part-time
as a waiter at a restaurant.
The two of them were always there.
That's where we met.
Right! Right!
And honestly, I always had my eyes on him.
Even from afar,
I could sense that he's a fun guy,
very sweet, and so fun to be with!
- Oh, right! Right!
- See?
He's really fun to be with.
Really?
You're just hyping me up.
Right?
When we first met, you were kind of…
out of it!
Right?
Wow!
You guys seem like such a fun group.
How about we create fun memories with me?
Go ahead, girl. What do you want?
Oh…
What are you doing?
What else? I'm going to sleep.
I wasn't born
with ube toppings on my head,
so I need eight hours of sleep.
At least that way,
I'll have something decent
for the front page.
Didn't I already fix your room?
I already had it arranged
with the building service.
Why don't you just stay there?
I've gotten used to it here.
And if I go back there,
I might not be able to sleep well.
Not be able to sleep.
That's not going to work anymore, Sophie.
You need to get used to your own space.
Wait.
Why are you making
such a big deal out of this?
What if someone sees us here?
What would they think?
Like, you know, we're dating.
You know how fast
rumors spread these days.
Why do you even care
about what other people say?
Are you a celebrity?
Or even an influencer?
It's not like that.
This is for you too.
What if someone likes you?
Then they might think
you already have a boyfriend.
Or they might think badly of you
because you sleep here.
Oh, please.
I don't care about
what other people think.
And besides, don't gaslight me.
I know you're really just concerned
about yourself.
Because if your crush Luisa Mae
finds out about this,
it might ruin your plan.
Fine, I'll just go sleep in my room.
You're really annoying.
- Let's go!
- What a relief!
- Yes!
- Oh…
You can do it.
Oh!
You can do it, Chiara! Like this.
Then imagine your target is huge.
Just beginner's luck.
My turn.
- Let's go!
- Okay, listen, Bok--
Just in case you miss, okay?
You need 170 points to win.
Okay, okay.
Another triple twenty!
- Great follow-through!
- Alex, look!
Alex, you just need a bullseye
for 170. Okay?
If she doesn't hit a bullseye, she loses.
- Oh my God. Triple 20.
- No way?
You're amazing!
Let's go!
Insane!
You're so good!
You probably think that just because
Alex likes you so much,
she'll give in to you.
I actually I get it why you're friends.
You're very competitive too, like Mikoy.
Back in Prague, he never wanted to lose
when we were drinking.
But to be fair,
you really pushed me to my limit,
even though it was
my first time playing darts.
Actually, we still
need to win Chiara back.
In the game she's good at.
- What's that?
- You see?
Wait a minute.
What are you good at?
What do you think?
Is it effective?
Do you think Chiara believes
we're really friends?
Of course!
And those cutesy moves of yours
are something else.
Honestly, it actually suits you.
It's cute.
That acting could win Oscars.
You even made me believe
that you're really my friend.
Why?
Aren't we really friends?
It's awesome.
Well, fair enough.
Actually, it's kind of a privilege
to be friends with Kim Santo Domingo.
Oops. Kim Dominguez, I mean.
You're unbelievable.
- Ouch.
- So dramatic.
You should always be like this.
It really suits you.
‪Then, suddenly--
Yes, so much.
He told you that, right?
But we don't really talk about it.
And I don't think we want
to talk about what happened.
I've actually been worried about Mikoy.
I don't know, maybe
he's hiding something from me
or he's keeping things inside.
But I guess he's just really such nice guy
who doesn't want me to worry,
so he doesn't talk about it.
But now that I've met you guys,
I feel relieved,
knowing he has friends he can rely on.
You know what? Take care of Chiara.
She's really special.
Let's do this more often.
I'd rather just face
whatever happens to me here.
Even if I have to go all out
against the Moravianos.
What I will never do is run and hide.
I was born here in the Philippines.
And I will die here.