I just imagined the person I like.
Luisa Mae.
Leave me alone.
But if it's true that I am truly exposed,
I prefer to face what awaits me here.
Even if I had to fight the Moravianos.
I was born here in the Philippines,
and this is where I will die.
Alex, my life is here.
Not abroad.
Mikoy?
Huh?
Where are you going?
Nothing. That was Alex.
I think she just enjoyed
being with us too much,
so she wants to go out of the country.
Oh!
Well, that will be great!
What did you say?
Uh, that…
Let's think about it.
This is your fault!
You got too close with them.
And now look,
they want to see us every day.
But I was hoping it would just be us.
I don't want any competition.
Sounds good!
Anyway, Mom is about to leave.
Oh, right!
Thank you, sweetheart! Thank you!
Mom!
Maybe we are overreacting.
I'm not sure.
I can't answer that directly, Bok.
How's the search for Vicek?
It looks like Vicek got caught.
But if Mikoy is already compromised,
he will be dead soon, too.
Oh, Mom, are you sure you're okay?
- We won't walk you downstairs, okay?
- Oh, no, it's fine!
Because my chauffeur
is already downstairs.
- He's waiting for me.
- Wow!
He's just a driver!
Thanks a lot to Chiara!
Of course, Mom!
Don't forget. Eat properly,
and don't let the sweat dry on your back.
Chiara, I'm really sorry, but I just need
to visit our Tortahan Shop first.
Mom! Mom, it's okay. No problem at all.
Oh, your medicines, your vitamins.
Take them!
And sleep early. You know, Manila
is a city that never sleeps!
So you're not the city, dear, okay?
- Yes, Mom. Okay.
- All right, just pray.
Mom, okay.
- Just pray.
- No problem, Mom!
- Okay.
- Okay. Good, good.
- Mom, you don't have to worry.
I'll take care of Mikoy.
I know that.
I know you won't neglect my child.
Just go there once you're okay.
Just tell me right away.
And you, my dear!
Listen to Chiara.
- Okay, Mom.
- Listen to Chiara!
- You might be the stubborn one!
- Of course, Mom!
Of course, I'm scared of her!
She's the boss.
And you know, what else, my dear?
- What is it, Mom?
- If there's a problem, okay, don't--
Promise, I'll call you!
- Yes, promise!
- And don't stay out too late!
- Yes. You too, Mom. Let's go! Let's go!
- Right? Don't forget what I said.
- Okay, bye, Chiara!
- You didn't forget anything.
- Bye, Mom!
- Everything is complete.
Do you want me to cook for you?
Shower?
Come on. Let's shower?
Come on!
Oh?
Rock-paper-scissors?
No.
What do you want?
- Let's do tag. Tag!
- Huh?
Oh, is that how it is?
Why would you even say that Mikoy
is like some disposable plastic?
That's the reality Mikoy got into
and the one we entered as well.
Maybe you're forgetting that.
Mikoy is a person. He is not a toy.
You shouldn't be talking like that.
What do you mean,
I shouldn't talk like that?
What's wrong with what I said?
And we have enough
years of service to know
that if our asset gets compromised,
and also, we fail to give them
protective custody,
he or she will most likely be dead.
To be honest,
it seems like you're the one
getting compromised.
I've noticed lately the way you're
getting attached to Mikoy, our asset!
Maybe you're forgetting
our asset is still a person.
Mikoy is still human!
But the point is, he's our asset!
So that's how it is, huh?
Come here!
- Ouch!
- Ah!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I can still stretch. Look.
I still have full range of motion.
- Full range of motion, huh?
- Yeah.
No more…
distractions.
Let's test how far
your range of motion goes.
Oh, that seems a bit much.
- Oh, wow!
- I have full range of motion.
So this is the Bisdak Heartthrob
from Cebu?!
Ma'am?
Call me Mama, since you took
a bullet for my daughter.
Right. Wait a minute.
Why does this feel a bit awkward?
Ah, not really, ma'am.
Oh, I mean, Mama.
We were just stretching.
- Oh! Just stretching?
- For therapy.
Did it stretch enough?!
Mmm.
The most stretchable of all.
Papa, if you're thinking
of sending him back to Vertex,
not yet.
I know his wound has healed,
but I'm worried
about the leftover traumas.
Of course not, my dear.
Ah! Kurt!
Bring out the food you brought!
It's time to stretch
our small and large intestines!
Let's eat!
So, I'm doing this quick campus feature,
you know, "Getting to Know
the Faces of the University".
It's super chill.
That's cool.
Okay, sure.
I tear up at social experiment videos
about kindness.
If it comes, why not?
I don't have an ideal guy.
You shouldn't really have standards
when it comes to relationships.
The most important thing is the profound
connection between the two of you.
What's your idea of a perfect date?
Sharing a bucket of sour cream popcorn.
I'm not complicated.
Wait, where will you release this feature?
Um…
Actually, I just really wanted
to get close to you,
so I could introduce you to my friend.
By the way, Papa.
I heard you had an emergency last night?
Oh my!
Someone from the Czech Republic arrived.
Not a check, though.
He's a no-go!
What do you mean by ruin the mood?
You know I've never liked him, ever since.
Shouldn't that make it better since
you've known each other for a long time?
He even came to visit you
here in the Philippines.
Vicek?
Oh, Vicek.
Will he be working for us again?
Why is that?
Isn't he good security?
Well, he looks like it.
But did he steal money?
Oh! I know!
He has many wives, right?
I knew it!
Let's just say that we had
a little disagreement.
There he goes again.
Was that funny?
That was funny to you, huh?! Oh!
You scared Mikoy.
He almost peed his pants.
I'll just get something.
Wait a minute.
Why don't we have any dessert?
Ah! Ah, yes! We do!
Mom's crema!
Oh! It's from my in-law. It's delicious!
Could you get it, please?
- Yes, I'll get it.
- Yes!
Imagine, you go out of your way
to give him what he wants.
Exactly.
But what he wants… is you.
But you know, I wouldn't do this
if I didn't really owe him
a debt of gratitude.
Because this is so pathetic!
That's too much!
But it's true.
You know what?
Just between us, okay?
You two aren't even a good match.
And you wouldn't even like him.
Why not?
Because he's naive, a coward,
and he doesn't fight back.
You know, the type who's too kind.
So people take advantage of him,
and when they do,
he just lets it happen.
And another thing!
He doesn't know anything about life.
He's already messed up,
and he'll just make things worse.
What's wrong with you, Angelito?
It's getting worse!
So if I were you, stay away
from that friend of mine!
You won't gain anything from him.
You'll just waste your time on him.
He sounds like a terrible guy.
- Exactly!
- Oh!
But who is this terrible guy?
Just so I'm sure I can avoid him.
He's Angelito D. Pinagpala.
We're basically best friends now.
Really?
Yes! Didn't you say I should
build you up to her?
So I became friends with her.
She's so nice, right?
I told you she's really easy
to be friends with!
Is that so?
You know, be careful with nice people.
Because they might be the ones
hiding dark secrets.
Oh? Who said that?
No, I just watched a documentary
where the serial killer
actually eats everyone he likes.
What are you even watching?
You should watch it too!
It's very insightful about human behavior!
There's no way Luisa Mae
is a serial killer.
How do you know?
Nothing.
I just know.
Like how
you knew Owen would get you into trouble
when he invited you to the bar?
You talk too much!
If you don't want to build me up,
then don't!
That's not what I meant!
All I'm saying is,
don't focus on just one girl.
Who?
You!?
Oh? Why are you getting mad?
It's true.
We're not a thing.
We're just friends, right?
Whatever!
I already briefed
the Senate Law and Order Committee
and Intelligence Services
about our missing Czech, Vicek.
I wish they were as bald as me.
NORBERTO S. RUIZ
Norberto…
My friend.
What?! What, Senator?
Didn't I warn you that we shouldn't
tell him about anything!
You even said it yourself
that Mikoy is smart!
That's what Vicek told me.
See? You get triggered right away.
If that's what he said, it's not reliable.
That's why we need to be more careful.
I've already done everything.
Why are you dragging him into this?
Dad, Mikoy loves me.
And I love him very much.
So please,
don't drag him into this
because he has nothing to do
with this mess.
And if he did, I would know.
I would notice if Mikoy
was doing something wrong.
You think I can no longer do
what I used to do.
Then you're wrong.
Tonight,
I will finish the mission
that was given to me.
CERTIFICATE OF APPRECIATION
Are you just going to accept
their decision?
Will you just let them decide for you?
If there was something he could do,
he would've done it already
to protect me.
Whatever is ordered from above…
that's what we must follow.
Especially not at this time.
Because of you, we are building cases
against the Moravianos.
You will continue building cases
Your mission will not stop,
even without me.
What if the one who replaces you
is not as supportive of this mission?
What if they undermine
everything we're working on?
I loved this agency.
If I stay here,
this agency will probably
make more enemies,
and it will only make things
harder for you.
Sometimes you just have to play along
with what those above you want.
Even without me.
I am confident in both of you.
That you will finish this fight.
Are you okay?
Wow.
That's impressive, huh?
Since when did you learn
how to speak Czech?
Nothing, just on the app.
But seriously, are you okay?
Do you want the truth?
No, I want the lie.
Of course.
Of course, I want the truth.
You said it before, right?
We're already part of each other's lives.
He says I'm too distracted because of you.
He doesn't understand
that I have to focus on you.
Especially in case someone
takes you away from me.
What?
That seems impossible anyway.
Because I'm already locked in your heart.
Actually… I can't even find the key.
I threw it away.
That's so cheesy.
No, but seriously,
your dad has a point.
Maybe because, you know…
your life is getting off track.
The life you left in Prague, right?
Well, my life is here now.
His name is Mikoy.
Isn't that even cheesier?
But you're right.
I just need to take care of something,
and I will be free.
I just have some business to handle,
and everything will be fine.
And once I do that,
I'll be free to be with you.
- Are you busy?
- Not really.
Can we have dinner?
Are you okay? You're acting so weird.
You suddenly invite me
to watch a movie and have dinner.
Are you dying?
You just want a simple life, right?
Wait a minute, Angelito.
What are these questions?
Where is this coming from?
Do you know something I don't?
This Norberto guy,
if something bad happens to him…
I'm pretty sure there
would be a big investigation,
and that would put us
in a very bad situation.