Where is Mikoy?
Didn't he tell you?
He went to the office.
He didn't come to the office today?
Yes, ma'am. Mr. Pinagpala
has not yet reported to the office.
Do you want
a flying kick to your face, huh?
What am I saying?
Hey! Hey.
Mikoy!
I understand where
you're coming from, okay?
But what Alex and I
are telling you is true.
Even then, I still don't like that guy.
Wow, you're being a smartass!
You're being sarcastic, huh?
‪Calm down. Calm down!
Vicek!
And from the right corner,
standing five foot ten but
six foot on his Tinder bio!
Weighing 155 pounds,
the Pride of the Philippines!
The Nation's top drinker
and the ultimate brother!
Mikoy Pinagpala!
- Mikoy! Mikoy!
Mikoy?
‪You can do it!
‪Go, Mikoy! He's about to lose!
‪-You can do it, Mikoy!
‪-Go!
‪Go!
It's taking so long.
It's my second cup of coffee already.
What the heck?
Is this going to end already?
- Looks like a tie!
- All right, I'll handle it.
- Fighters!
- What now?
You know if you have
a nine-tailed beast inside you,
you have to unleash it now!
You're finished!
Mikoy! Mikoy!
‪We're for Mikoy! We're for Mikoy!
- Never give it up!
- We're for Mikoy!
‪-You're the man!
‪-Hey!
What's going on here?
What's going on here, huh?
What is this?
Bok, we're just… having some fun.
So he's okay with Boss?
We already talked.
- Hey, easy.
- Give me my 2,000.
- Mikoy, let's go.
- Hey!
Alex.
Thanks, okay?
Did I do something wrong?
Next time you come to this office,
don't walk in like it's
the grand premiere of your movie!
Someone might recognize you.
Is that why the General removed me?
Because of my grand entrance?
Sorry about that.
I got a little excited.
No.
There are people who wants to shut down
what we're doing here.
Huh?
How come?
Clearly, some people think
what we do isn't important.
That's why General Norberto
is very worried.
And if something bad happens to you again,
he thinks that it will lead
to the demise of the agency.
And they'll use that against us.
Is that all?
Come on!
You can see I've got nine lives!
So I've got eight left!
Right?
Sorry.
But…
that's not going to happen.
Why do you say that?
Because you're always there.
I know you won't leave me.
And you'll always protect me.
Of course you will.
That's why I am not afraid,
as long as I'm with you.
So, shall we go?
Sianong has been waiting
in the briefing room.
He might end up being "shorts" later.
Let's go.
You told your Dad I'm your boyfriend?
And now you want me to meet him
and pretend to be your boyfriend?
Hey, Angelito! Angelito, wait!
You're single anyway, right?
Listen to me, Angelito. Wait! Wait!
Just hear me out first.
- Okay, fine.
- Here's the thing.
Ever since I leaked to you
that information about the Valtrovis,
Dad's been furious.
To the point that he's questioning
my decision-making.
So you lied?
I didn't know what excuse to make.
So come on, please!
What I don't get is,
why do you have to use me
as an excuse as your boyfriend?
I was just hoping Dad would think
I'm just soft-hearted and blinded by love,
that's why I ended up
leaking the information.
Please, Angelito! Please, Angelito!
Angelito! Wait! Wait!
Angelito, if Dad finds out
that I lied to him again,
he might suspend my privileges.
Then I might be stuck at home,
and I won't be able
to come to Campus anymore.
Please, help me out!
I'll help you too.
I will never turn you down.
The Sinigang Cartel making a move
against the Moravianos
was their biggest mistake.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
After the incident at the Valtrovi party,
we believe Viktor moved immediately.
Yup.
And we also believe
that those elements of the Cartel
have been integrated into the Moravianos.
Just to make sure they won't go
against the Valtrovis.
So why is Raphael's painting here?
Wow!
Cultured!
Just because we're simple
doesn't mean we have no culture!
But since we don't have her face,
we use Raphael's artwork.
Wait, wait. Wait. She?
I just want to know how.
That's what you think.
And once we capture her,
we can extract information from her
that we can use against the Moravianos.
Have you seen anyone
around Viktor and Donabel
who could possibly be
the assassin La Fornarina?
No one.
I didn't really notice anyone.
But if I see anyone suspicious,
I'll report it.
Okay.
But one thing is for sure.
I'm absolutely certain about this.
This La Fornarina,
this world-class assassin,
is very close to Donabel and Viktor.
Wait, isn't that kind of weird?
Getting that close to a killer?
Let's go!
Come on!
Just relax.
Relax?
How can I relax?
At any moment, I'm going to meet
your dad and lie to him.
What's so hard about that?
Why, do you think I grew up
lying all the time?
At the very least,
I'm sure you've lied
once or twice in your life.
No way! I don't lie!
Especially since they say if you lie,
you'll get a lot of mouth sores.
That's not true.
Yes, it's true that lying is bad,
but sometimes it can come in handy.
Yes! Especially if you're a politician!
Because as they say,
"We lie every day because we're always
putting on a performance."
Because the world only wants to see
the best version of ourselves,
so we hide who we really are.
So, one way or another,
you've already lied.
You're just making things harder.
Here's what we'll do.
If you don't want to lie,
just use your imagination.
I'm sure you have a crush
or someone you like.
For example, Jennie from BLACKPINK.
Imagine a scenario where you two
are already together.
Imagine what you would say
when she introduces you to her parents.
That's it!
Let's go!
Come on!
Is that Angelito?
Hi, sweetheart!
You arrived just in time.
Come on. Let's have dinner?
Smells good!
But of course,
you smell better, my sweetheart.
Let's eat?
Wow.
Roasted chicken sisig?
Boracay.
Palawan?
What's the problem with Mikoy?
If we want Mikoy to trust us,
we need to trust him first.
That won't happen.
What if it does, Bok?
Okay, here.
What if Mikoy screws us over?
If he betrays us,
I'll be the one to kill him myself.
You said it.
By the way, where's Mom?
She's asleep.
Do you want me to wake her up?
No, it's okay.
Let her rest for now.
Yes.
Mom mentioned earlier…
that you decided
to go to the office today.
Yes.
I told her about it.
So, how was it?
Was what?
The office!
Right?
It was fine.
Just okay.
Did the people there miss you?
Well, for sure,
since you've been gone for a while.
Of course.
Who else?
I'm definitely missable.
Do you have any questions for Angelito?
What did your father say
when you told him about the Valtrovis?
At first, he was surprised.
But he told me
not to tell anyone about it.
That we should keep it a secret,
even from Mom and my brother.
Your father is a very smart man.
Can I count on you
not to tell anyone else?
Yes.
You can count on me.
So, let's have dinner, okay?
I want you to tell me
the love story
between you and my daughter, okay?
Let's eat! Let's eat!
See, Angelito?
You can do it!
You know,
what I hate the most
are people who lie to me!
So you know, and I know,
that you did not go to the office today!
Right?
Because I called your office,
and not a single one of them
saw your shadow at Vertex Global!
So, I am giving you one more chance
for you to come clean
and tell me the truth!
Because you won't like
what I'm going to do.
Okay.
You're right.
I didn't go to the office.
Gotcha!
And if you didn't go to the office,
where did you go?!
Is it true that you are FUBU
with my daughter?
Did I say something wrong?
What does that even mean?
True love, right?
Don't ask me what it means anymore.
And if it's not that,
what do you have with Angelito?
Are you really serious about my daughter?
Okay, fine. I'll admit it.
I left the house…
to meet my friends.
And I met them because…
What?
Why didn't you just say so?
Are your intentions pure with her?
Yes, sir. It's true.
How can you say that?
Honestly,
I don't know if I can find
the right words for this.
But, I watched it in a teleserye.
It said there that
when you find the person meant for you,
your world starts to slow down,
the surroundings start to glow,
and the birds start singing.
And honestly, sir,
that's the cheesiest
and corniest thing I've ever heard.
Until…
I experienced it.
When I met your daughter, Sofie.
Not only did my world slow down,
but time itself stopped.
Not only did the surroundings light up,
but everything became more vivid.
And not only did the birds sing,
but my heart started screaming.
Please give me a chance.
Sweetheart, I understand.
Especially since the only faces
are mine and your mother's.
And with us being here, we might
be making things worse for you.
You might be remembering
that traumatic event again.
Oh?
That might be it.
If you need space, just tell me.
I can leave for a while,
if that's what you want.
No! It's not like that, sweetheart, but…
Sorry, I just didn't tell you because…
I didn't want you to worry.
Sweetheart, that made me worry even more.
You could've just told me.
If you wanted to hang out
with your friends,
then go ahead.
I promise, next time,
I'll ask for permission.
Well, how was it?
Which one?
Your friends! Right?
Did you enjoy it? What did you do?
Well…
It was fine.
We just kept it chill.
We didn't really enjoy much because
you weren't there.
Okay, never mind.
It's fine.
Maybe you don't even want
to introduce me to them.
No! Sweetheart, of course not!
Are you kidding? Everyone would love you!
- Really?
- Yes!
- I mean,
I'm really in love with you!
Really?
Super, yes!
How many friends do you have?
Are there many? Are they all from Cebu?
Well, actually, just two of them.
They're from Manila.
It's…
Alex and Sianong.
May I?
Of course!
Of course it's you.
Perfect timing.
Can it be tomorrow?
Of course!
Who else but you?
Chiara the Valtrovi?!
Actually, I'm worried about Mikoy.
I didn't know if he might
be hiding something from me,
and I want him to be part of my life,
for good.
I have a man who knows
about Norberto Ruiz.
It looks like he was captured
by Valtrovi's.