I thought a thief had broken in.
No one can get in here.
I’ll make sure.
La Fornarina.
Dad, I don’t want to say anything bad
about Chiara’s family.
They’ve done nothing but good to Mikoy.
I have a friend who said
the Valtrovis are part of a syndicate.
He’s General Norberto Ruiz.
Angelito, promise me…
that this information won’t get out.
- We keep it between us.
- Yes, Dad.
Don’t be afraid
because nothing bad will happen
to your brother again.
Is it true?
The government is dissolving the agency?
There are strong rumors
that we’re one of the agencies
to be shut down.
You all know there’s a crisis right now.
The authorities need to cut costs.
They know how critical our work is.
If we’re gone, who will protect the people
from dangerous foreigners?
Let the politicians handle those matters.
What’s important is we’re still here.
Not because we have something to prove,
but because that is our responsibility
to the nation.
La Morte Bianca specifically instructed
that I’d be the one to finish him.
Don’t worry,
we always have our eyes watching him.
To make sure that he has no way out.
He won’t even realize he’s already dead.
The average…
Hey!
Hey, it’s you.
Just "hey"?
Why? Did I do something to you?
Impressive, huh?
Playing dumb school of acting
after I gave you a very
sensitive situation about your brother?
What? No update at all?
What update do you want?
If you told your father
that the Valtrovis
are connected to syndicates.
Hey! Lower your voice.
Someone might hear you.
Sorry.
But yes, I already gave
my dad that information.
So, what happened?
Well, he said
we shouldn’t talk about it for now
and not to tell anyone yet.
Why?
So they’re not going
to do anything, your dad?
Your family?
I don’t know.
AGENT DARA
How are you, my friend?
Here.
I'm sure we can find
something useful against the Valtrovis.
We need Mikoy.
Bok, Mikoy is being guarded 24/7.
He’s not available!
No matter what information Bistek gives,
Because if there really was a smoking gun,
the Czech police would’ve
dismantled the Moravianos.
But clearly, they haven’t.
So, no matter
what paper trail they dig up,
nothing will link the legal operations
of the Moravianos to the Valtrovis.
Only Mikoy can provide that.
But how are we going to do that?
Mikoy isn’t here!
We can’t talk to him!
We can’t reach him! Okay?
Because all his calls are monitored 24/7.
We can’t visit him.
So, what do you want to happen now, Bok?
Huh?
Are we just going to wait
for his call forever?
Who is this?
Hello? Yes? It's Piolo Pascual.
If you're offering a loan again,
I’m not in the mood.
Mikoy?
Yeah!
Yeah, it’s really Mikoy!
Come on.
No "How are you" or anything?
"Are you okay?"
I already know you’ve been missing me.
Silly!
Things are chaotic here.
Show yourself already!
Here I am! That’s why I’m calling!
Because I need to see you soon.
Tomorrow, okay?
Didn’t they even realize
that your brother Mikoy
is in a very dangerous situation?
He has no idea how chaotic
and dangerous this world is.
He entered a relationship
with a criminal’s child.
Chiara might even be a criminal, too!
Hey! First of all,
if there’s anyone I trust the most,
it’s my brother Mikoy.
Fine.
If you’re right that he got
into a complicated
and dangerous situation,
I still believe
he’ll always do what’s right.
Second, the way you talk, it’s like
you’re absolutely sure
the Valtrovis are evil.
I’m not even sure if everything
you told me is true.
Tell me.
Why shouldn’t I shoot you?
Will you join my enemies
who is now making a move against me?
You still haven’t changed, Norberto.
I still know where you hide your gun.
I knew it.
It felt a bit light.
Norberto, I didn’t come here to fight.
I’m here because I want to ask
what my child
has to do with the Valtrovis.
You sound completely convinced
the Valtrovis are really bad.
As if that’s already the truth?
Because what? Your father said so?
Isn’t it possible
that your father is wrong?
Then you immediately judged
an entire family just like that?
That’s the problem with you!
The truth is already slapping you,
but you still refuse to face it!
Well, maybe it’s because
you’re also enjoying the privileges
brought by the syndicates.
A foul is a foul!
But if you’re going
to keep turning a blind eye,
then don’t blame me
when something bad
happens again to your brother.
That’s not funny!
It's just a joke.
I’m sorry.
Oh no.
My sweetheart is in a bad mood, huh?
Did I do something wrong?
I’m doing everything you want, aren’t I?
I’m eating healthy foods.
I even eat bitter gourd.
And your dance therapy, too.
I’m even getting back
to my original stretchability.
Look.
I’m okay now, sweetheart.
You’re really good.
But I still need your help.
I was about to take a shower.
But I can’t reach…
my back.
There’s no wound there.
On the other side.
And also, didn’t you say you’re okay now?
So you should be able to wash
any part of your body,
even your hard-to-reach areas,
without my help!
I’m meeting my mom
for some "me" time.
Huh?
Why is she like that? What happened?
- What did you do again?
- Nothing!
I’m just my usual charming and cute self.
I used my Enrique Gil moves,
but still, no effect.
Maybe you did something not so good, dear.
Me? No way!
Me, Mom?
I’m so good!
I follow all her instructions.
Since I left the service,
I changed my name.
Now I am Mario Pinagpala.
No matter what name you use,
you are still known as Isidro Catacutan,
the feared Butcher of Butuan.
That’s right.
And there’s still fear inside me.
That’s why I need to know
what the truth really is
about the Valtrovi family.
Are they part
of a big syndicate?
Let me ask you something.
Did you thank her already?
That’s exactly what I’m saying!
Huh! That’s what’s wrong with you.
You just keep tugging!
Do you even know
what she did for you? Huh?
Since you’re in the hospital,
she hasn’t slept at all.
Just to watch over you.
Every minute of her life,
she devoted to you!
Just so you could recover immediately.
And then, not even a thank you.
You didn’t even say anything?
Hey, Mikoy!
You should be ashamed, huh!
You need to repay her love
for what he showed you.
You need to reach the moon
and all the stars
and offer them to her, huh?
So you can at least show her
that you appreciate her care.
That’s how it should be.
Roger that, Mom!
Operation "reach the stars
and the moon" commences.
Good job, dear!
- Good job!
- Thank you, Mom.
Wait, wait. Where’s Dad?
Oh, I don’t know!
He said he was visiting a friend.
A friend?
Since when did Dad
have a friend here in Manila?
I didn’t know that this
was connected to a big syndicate.
It was just a desperate
kidnap for ransom group
that expected a big payday,
the ones who targeted the Valtrovis.
Did you forget that I can read you easily?
I can tell when
you’re not telling the truth.
I admire your instincts,
but you are wrong in this case.
I have never been wrong about you.
You don’t know me that well.
And what if I tell you
that my reliable source is…
your daughter Sofie.
- My own child told you that?
- Yes.
I was actually surprised
that she shared this information
with my other child, Angelito.
How did she meet Angelito?
Actually, I don’t know.
But from what I understand,
they’re schoolmates,
and they’re in some kind of a…
relationship.
What kind of relationship?
Kids these days, they call it,
FUBU.
FUBU?
Your daughter's relationship status
is not my concern.
What matters to me right now
is Mikoy and whether he’s safe.
Actually, Norberto,
at first, I didn’t know anything,
I had no suspicions.
When Chiara and the Valtrovi family
came to us,
when we received a large order
and it was delivered to your office,
But I still didn’t notice those red flags.
And my child almost lost his life
because of this.
There is no greater horror
than seeing your child
fighting for their life.
That’s why I thought,
I knew I had to ask questions.
I have a strong feeling that there’s…
there’s a bigger story
behind Mikoy being shot.
And it was your daughter
who confirmed my suspicions.
Mom?
Chiara?
Are you here?
- Ah!
- Hey! Ouch! Ouch!
Why are you hurting me, dear?
What are you imagining?
Ah!
Is it about what La Morte Bianca
wants you to do?
Mom!
Alright.
Let’s just name her Bianca Umali?
Mom!
Bianca King?
I’m just trying to lighten
the mood because
this family has been under so much stress.
It’s really overwhelming.
Your Dad, he’s extremely stressed
because he was given an ultimatum
that we should have no more
enemies here in the Philippines.
And you, I know that
you’re stressed too
because of your mission, right?
The truth is,
I don’t know the answer to that question.
You know that even if I know something,
I cannot divulge that information
to a civilian like you.
Norberto!
If you were in my position,
and it was Sofie who was in danger…
If I were in your position,
I would do the same.
Idiot!
Wait, Isidro.
Isidro, listen to me!
Am I doing the right thing?
Why are you suddenly having doubts?
What are you thinking about?
And then after what he did for me,
sacrificing himself for me,
I knew right there and then
that he’s the one
I want to be with for life.
Oh? Well, there you go!
So what’s the problem?
Of course not, dear.
You can see we’re having a serious
heart-to-heart talk,
why would I laugh?
What kind of mother would I be
to laugh at your feelings
and turn them into a joke?
Okay.
Well,
I’m just thinking.
What if Mikoy has flaws?
he’s actually a womanizer?
Mom!
You said you wouldn’t laugh!
- What kind of mother are you?
- Sorry!
That Mikoy? Doing multiple
extra-curricular activities?
- I don’t think so.
- Well,
he’s still a man. It’s not impossible.
Well, you do have a point.
But I don’t see Mikoy as someone
who can multi-task like that.
Isidro, wait! Listen to me!
Isidro! For once, can you listen to me?
I know what’s going through your mind.
And I’m warning you, as a former friend,
do not take the law into your own hands.
Don’t do something
you’ll regret in the end.
We’re talking about
my family here, Norberto!
My family!
And if your family was put
in a dangerous situation,
no law would be able to stop me.
If I have to kill again,
for them,
I will do it.
Well, my child,
I’ve had so many relationships.
I’ve practically beaten
the United Nations in numbers.
I already know how to read
and judge men like…
a flirt.
Isidro.
This is not the right way.
So many of our friends
should’ve still been alive!
If they weren’t mistreated
by the system you’re talking about!
Fixing the system that disgraced them!
What a waste, Norberto.
It looks like you’ve been
consumed by the system too.
You were the one who turned your back!
You were the one who abandoned us!
Where were you when I needed you?
You were the one who quit
fighting for what’s right!
Just like before.
You can’t stop me.
I will do everything I have to do.
I won’t stop you, my friend,
but let me warn you.
If you do that, there’s no turning back.
I will become your enemy.
I will stop you.
Where’s Mikoy?
Oh, he didn’t tell you?
He went to the office.
That’s what you should
watch out for with Mikoy, okay?
If there’s missing time for you.
Mr. Pinagpala is currently
on indefinite leave.
You?!
You may leave.