Knowing the Moravianos,
they won't move without directions.
Clearly, they have a target.
Which is my close friend?
And when they target you,
they target to kill you.
Yes. Only by doing so
can we get Chiara back to focus.
Back to us, where she belongs.
So it's time to kill this Mikoy!
And Mikoy and I are allowed
to live a normal life that I dream of.
I just feel like I still don't know
that much about you,
about your life.
I still don't know Chiara
outside her family.
Look at the height.
It's exactly the same height as Chiara.
That's the average height
of Filipinas, okay?
Not all Filipinas are like you
with your model height.
Here.
When she wiped something off her face,
she used her left arm.
Remember the dart game?
Yes.
But being left-handed
isn't exactly rare for a Filipina,
if that even is a Filipina
you're talking about.
But that's blonde hair. Look closely!
Everything you're telling me
are just pieces of evidence
that might be circumstantial. Okay?
Maybe she dyed her hair blonde
because she got bored with her life.
Or maybe she wore a hoodie
because her hairfall got worse.
Bok.
You know how valuable
Chiara is to our asset,
and you're risking alienating her
from our most important asset.
For what exactly?
Is this really how we work as agents now?
Well, if you're looking for my friends,
they're in Prague.
Didn't I tell you I grew up there?
And even if you do meet them,
I don't think you'll like them
because they're not
as warm as your friends.
Oh, right.
You said that before.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Am I being too intrusive?
It's just that you
already know me so well,
from head to toe.
You even know every little detail.
You've even met my friends
from Cebu and Manila.
I just thought, you know,
I'd get to know you better
if I spent time with the people
you spend time with
outside your responsibilities
of being a Valtrovi.
That's all it was.
I understand why you thought that.
But me, I'm not worried.
Because I know we still have a lot of time
to get to know each other.
Hunches are also important
in our line of work.
I know, but we need concrete evid--
I heard you mentioning
something about a hunch.
I have a question for you.
Which came first?
The egg or the chicken?
That's what you were arguing about?
Because what we were really talking about
was our lunch later, right?
Not hunch.
Anyway, sir.
The egg or the chicken?
Even if we leave this world,
no one will ever answer that question.
So instead of sulking there,
come with me to the conference room.
In uniform, check!
Giving orders, check!
Grumpy, check!
So, come to the conference room.
I'll tell you what happened. Come on.
You? The egg or the chicken?
I don't get you. Hurry up already.
You're as pale as an egg.
Angelito.
Yes, you're taking forever.
I've been here for a while.
You didn't even say
you'd wait for me here.
What if I didn't come straight here?
- Then your eyes would've turned white.
- Stop getting annoyed already.
Give me that.
It looks like you're having a hard time,
that's why you're so grumpy.
Why, what is that?
You don't have a fever.
Why are you like that?
I'm perfectly fine.
My immune system is really strong.
Why?
Am I not allowed to be nice to you?
If someone's nice to you,
they're automatically sick?
I'm just looking out for you
because you're like that with me too.
You kind of take care of me
in your own weird way.
Right?
What if we go to the mall
after your class?
Yes, if that's okay with you.
Why did you suddenly decide to invite me?
What's that?
Is something wrong with your mouth?
Maybe a mouth sore?
Nothing really.
So you can have fun
and forget about
your stressors for a while.
I'm not used to seeing you like that.
Punching people.
You're still not over that.
But…
Since you're being so sweet right now,
fine, I'll go with you.
I'm game for the movie.
Okay then.
I'll walk you to your class first,
then after your class,
I'll see you outside, okay?
- Okay.
- Alright, let's go.
Are we waiting for someone?
Okay.
Senator Quintin.
Traffic as usual.
Is it really traffic?
Ever since I was single, that has
already been our country's problem.
Now I'm already the Chief Director,
and it's still our problem.
Plus other things,
like drugs, syndicates,
gambling, corruption, goodness.
If we go through
every single problem in this country,
we won't finish this meeting.
Before anything else,
this is why I'm dressed like this.
The fool, Chief Velasco,
is actually on leave,
and he invited me to play golf
at his favorite golf course
to talk about your issue.
Yes, the one who loves
playing golf to de-stress.
If you were the one who won the lottery,
you'd have all the time in the world.
But anyway,
the good news is,
you, my friend, are going to keep
your position for a very long time,
and now you can go back to stressing
over the country's problems again
because we revoked your resignation.
There it is!
Keep your voice down.
This is embarrassing.
It's okay, I know you're excited
to have your father figure back.
My announcement isn't over yet.
There's a catch.
They're sending someone
to monitor your agency closely,
and you need to coordinate
with the National Police
on every move, every breath,
every touch you make.
And the person
they sent to monitor you is him.
Come in, dear!
- You?!
- What?!
Oh my God.
Hold on.
Who are you?
Oh, gosh, Bok.
We don't need a walking CCTV around us.
What does the National Police
want from us anyway?
First, they wanted to remove
an efficient employee.
Second, what they want
is for us to be monitored
on every move we make.
Are we incompetent?
I also don't agree with what they want.
But we're already in this situation,
and the verdict is final.
You know we'll just get angry,
but nothing will happen.
Nothing will happen.
We'll just keep ranting, but nothing.
It'll still be the same.
But what's really surprising
is it's really Ben!
Wasn't he the one who lost a witness
because of being too overconfident?
- Bok.
- Joe.
- Move that away. I'll sit here.
- Bok, two o'clock.
- He is approaching.
- I like this spot.
Hey?
Just a moment ago, you were chatting.
Then I arrived, and you all went quiet.
Were you talking about me?
The file?
- Send it to me already.
- Do not flatter yourself.
You're not that relevant.
I'm back to being relevant
to your life again,
and this time, you can't ghost me anymore.
That's a parcel, right?
- You're a scammer.
- What?
What do you mean, what?
I already know that modus.
You come here
to the house, knock, and say,
Then the payment is COD?
A lot of my neighbors
already got scammed by that, okay?
But not me, darling,
because I don't use COD.
All my online shopping,
I pay through e-wallet.
Okay? Goodbye.
Look, I'm not wearing a helmet.
I don't have a motorcycle.
He sent you here?
So you're the package?
Is anything wrong, dear?
Is this about…
Mikoy?
He said he wants to get to know Chiara
outside of her family and business.
He said he wants to get to know
my friends and stuff.
Well then…
He wants to know you completely,
the other side of you.
Oh, right.
That version of you
is kind of complicated,
and apparently, you're living
a double life when it comes to Mikoy.
Mom!
But dear,
aren't you tired yet?
Isn't that right, my dear?
Why don't you just tell Mikoy the truth?
I know, I get it.
There's a chance he'll leave you,
but if he really loves you,
he'll still accept you completely,
flaws and all.
I know the things you're doing
aren't exactly something to be proud of,
those security measures for this family,
but you did it out of love.
Because you love me and your father,
because you're protecting this family,
and I know Mikoy will understand that
because he's a great guy,
and he's such a good son.
I know he'd also do everything
for his parents.
Maybe your father is right.
You need to tell Mikoy the truth.
So the weight in your chest
can somehow lessen.
I don't think I need a secretary.
I can manage my job anyway.
I just need, you know,
a bit of rest, and I'm as good as new.
But instead of giving instructions,
I might as well just do it myself.
I can handle it.
It's just the two of us here now.
So be honest with me.
Why did the National Police send someone
to monitor the agency?
Do they suspect any of my people?
It's a safety measure, my friend.
No hard feelings.
They were informed
that someone wants to kill you,
and if that happens,
it will be a big blow
to the National Police.
Chief Velaso also said
that you're not alone in this fight.
Is it because of his past
with your adopted daughter?
Agent Alex has a mind of her own.
That guy might get killed before I do.
That's the General Ruiz I know.
The so-called terror of Bataan.
No impact!
Like "Butuan's Executioner"!
Oh, come on, you still can't move on.
Well, he did get a better title
after all, then got it--
I'm just glad you're safe, my friend.
Skintone? It's kinda dull.
How about this?
It's too revealing.
I think this is it! Pink.
To look sweet! See? Perfect!
PHILIPPINE UNIVERSITY
Where could he be?
He's taking too long.
Where are you Angelito?
Why aren't you answering my calls?
What time is it?!
This Angelito is really annoying!
He told us to watch a movie
so I could de-stress,
and now he's the reason I'm stressed!
- I told you.
- Sofie?
Wow.
Is there really no subtlety
in your reaction?
It's like your face has subtitles.
I can clearly see
you're disappointed to see me.
Ouch.
Don't you remember me?
I'm the one who was with Angelito before,
when you brought Owen along to apologize.
Sorry, I don't remember you.
Okay, Laurence
with a letter U and not a W,
if you're really Angelito's friend,
do you know where he is?
But now he's a no-show.
No.
I didn't see him at the dorm either.
Actually, I was also
about to watch a movie.
Want me to join you instead?
This is so annoying!
Wait.
Why did you assign Carlota
as Mikoy's secretary?
You didn't even ask me.
She's like the female version of Vicek,
but without a traitor's blood.
We are the danger to Mikoy and his family.
You already know the answer.
And if you want Mikoy out,
you also know what needs to be done.
The truth is finally out.
You're only doing this
because you're still suspicious of Mikoy.
That's why you took Carlota
to investigate him, right?
Alright then.
Do a cartwheel into a split.
Sure, sir! That's my favorite!
Wait.
Here I come.
Sir, if you didn't know,
I used to be a gymnast.
I was part of the national team.
Do you want another one, sir?
Or anything else you want me to do?
No, it's okay.
Go ahead, cross the misua.
- Let's see how good you are.
- Misua!
Apologies, sir,
but I promise I'll find out what misua is.
Once I learn what misua is,
I promise I'll cross it.
I'll study it. Sorry, sir.
No, I'm good.
It's okay.
I'll just take care of something.
Hello, Alex, we have a problem.
Something like that.
Where are you now?
There were changes in my position
as COO of Vertex.
Wait, what changes? Did you get fired?
No.
That's a big problem.
Did Chiara want this?
No.
I actually don't know.
We haven't talked about it yet,
but her father ordered it.
But for sure, she won't like this.
How are you so sure?
I just feel it.
That's just how Chiara is.
You know, whenever girls get close to me,
she gets mad.
She's a bit of a jealous type.
Mikoy, I just want to know.
How well do you really know Chiara?
It looks like someone
is investigating her.