Sianong!
Sianong.
What about Alex? Where is he?
Chiara the Valtrovi?!
There it is!
It's just beginner's luck.
You're so cool!
Oh, yes, so much.
I'm actually worried about Mikoy.
I didn't know
if he's hiding something from me.
Do you want fish and chips? Huh?
Hey!
What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
- That's why.
You don't want fish and chips.
You want chicks!
Mikoy…
Let's talk. Man to man.
That got serious all of a sudden.
Are you drunk? It's just juice.
Okay.
Let's just talk
man to man, seriously, okay?
- Okay.
- Listen.
All right.
I just want you to know
that Alex is risking everything
just to be here.
For you.
Okay?
And now that they've met, we've all met,
she now has a face to Chiara.
And now that she has Chiara's face,
soon she'll have a face
to the whole syndicate.
And if ever
Alex's identity gets exposed
to the syndicate,
consider her dead.
Because Viktor won't be happy.
Alex really trusts you. A lot.
But don't get me wrong.
I understand you love Chiara.
But we need to do the right thing here
because we have a mission to accomplish.
Hey, do you understand me?
Okay. I'm saying all of this to you,
because if there ever comes a point
where I have to choose who to save
between the two of you,
my answer won't change.
I understand.
You don't have anything to worry about.
Mikoy loves you very much.
You're always the one
he keeps talking about.
From the moment he met you in Prague,
until you came with him
here to the Philippines,
he can't stop talking about the fact that,
even though you come
from different social classes,
you never looked down on him.
And your family welcomed him
with open arms.
A man who will sacrifice everything
for the person he loves.
And one day, if there ever comes a point
where you have doubts in him,
always remember,
he stopped a bullet for you.
Because if I have to choose
between Park Seo-joon and Mikoy,
I will always choose the guy
who can protect me with all his heart.
Right?
Mikoy!
- You took so long.
- Oh my gosh.
You know what? Take care of Chiara.
Let's do this more often.
I'm already sick of seeing
those two idiots' faces.
- Okay.
- Let's order.
- Go ahead.
- Fish and chips?
I don't drink anymore.
Yes.
Guys, excuse me.
- Sure, sure.
- Okay.
What's the problem, sir?
Something happened to Vicek!
My cat is vomiting yellow.
It's okay, I understand.
I used to be a "meow-my", too.
I also had a cat, so it's okay.
Wow, the night is just starting.
We were just dancing with Mikoy.
Uh… Okay.
Maybe we'll crash otherwise.
- She's a bit drunk.
- Yes, right.
I'll just come with you.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm a bit drunk too, guys.
- Okay.
- Till next time.
- See you again.
- Take care.
- Thank you so much! Bye!
- Nice to meet you!
- Bye, Chiara!
- Bye!
Oh…
Sir, what happened?
NORBERTO S. RUIZ
GENERAL
What? How did that happen?
Sorry, it's late already.
I just want to ask, are you even sure?
Maybe he just went out to take a walk.
Maybe he went clubbing or something.
I was ordered to assist Vicek.
So I went to his hotel earlier
to check if he needed anything.
Whoever did this, he's a professional.
La Fornarina.
Where is the target?
Maybe his wife or child is there.
They don't need to be involved.
I've got this.
What information do you have on him?
What does he know now?
Leave it to me.
Whatever angle you look at it,
it looks like the Valtrovis
already have him.
Vicek knows that Mikoy is our asset.
And I'm sure Viktor will force him
to extract whatever information
he can from him.
- Mom.
- Mikoy, dear!
You know, too bad,
your father just called.
Oh, how is he?
He always asks about you.
He even said, "How is he doing?
Is he able to move now?"
I told him you can already do
all your normal activities.
Right?
Then he even laughed. He was shocked!
Because I already told him
you went out with Chiara.
Where is Chiara?
She went back to the mansion, Mom.
Her father texted. There's an emergency.
I hope she's okay.
Yes, she'll be fine, Mom.
Chiara texted me too.
She said everything's okay.
Dear, is there really no problem?
Yes. There's nothing, Mom.
Because I talked to your father
before he left.
Don't take it the wrong way.
About Chiara's family.
Of course, dear, we know
that a very big mess happened.
So, your father is a bit concerned.
The old man keeps asking
if you're really safe with the Valtrovis.
Mom…
Nothing bad is going to happen to me.
I think God really loves me.
Look at me.
- Until now, I'm still alive.
- I'm telling you, dear.
Don't treat it like a joke.
Because your father and I
won't be able to take it
if something bad happens to you again.
Yes, Mom.
Vicek is missing.
The Czech asset is missing?
Do you know how hard it is
to deal with the Czechs?
I'm on full-time offense
just to convince them
to cooperate with us.
And now their man is missing.
What if I don't get invited
to the European forum
on unified publishing,
intelligence exchange, counter terrorism,
organized crime suppression,
and administrative synergy?
Do you know how fancy their buffet is?
Huh!
What if I don't get invited next year?
And if they kill that guy Vicek,
that will be a diplomatic headache.
And the Moraviano will
not just be your problem,
but your position will be at risk.
NORBERTO S. RUIZ
GENERAL
- Vicek is missing.
- What?
Maybe he just went to Boracay.
You know, sunbathing
while drinking coconut juice.
Vicek knows about you.
So, if he's in Viktor's hands,
he can extract information about you,
compromising your position.
And if that happens,
you will be declared as a burned asset.
Burned asset? What does that mean?
So you need to be placed
in protective custody.
Where? At your apartment?
Do you have a hot shower?
Then where? Hey, wait a second!
Don't tell me it's at Sianong's! No way!
Come on! Give me a little dignity.
Not here in the Philippines, but abroad.
ALEXANDRIA CORTEZ
AGENT
Somewhere far from the Moravianos.
And you'll also need a new identity.
A new identity and a new life.
Abroad?
No way, Agent Alex!
I won't hide and change my identity!
Who do you think I am, Casper?
I can't just ghost my family!
Especially the people I love.
If they got Vicek,
they can get you as well.
Well, if it's true I've been exposed,
I'd rather just face
whatever happens to me here.
Even if I have to go all out
against the Moravianos.
What I will never do is run and hide.
I was born here in the Philippines.
And I will die here.
Mikoy?
We're practically best friends now.
Be careful with nice people.
- They're the ones hiding dark secrets.
- You talk too much.
If you don't want to hype me up,
then don't!
Whatever!
My friend, they are asking
for you to resign.
They said you had an emergency last night?
Vicek?