The government is dissolving the agency?
La Morte Bianca specifically instructed
that I'd be the one to finish him.
The Valtrovis are connected to syndicates.
Even though you changed your name,
you're still known as Isidro Catacutan.
What if Mikoy has a flaw?
What if he's a womanizer?
Yes, it's me! I know how much you miss me.
Dad?
That's right!
He's the perfect example
of a troublesome womanizer.
If only you knew the headaches
I went through with your father back then.
Get out!
Huh?!
I don't care! I don't care!
With this kind of beauty, you have
the audacity to cheat on me?
You're a demon!
Oh my God!
There are infinite possibilities
in a multiverse.
All I'm saying is,
if Mikoy ever does that to you,
then beast mode on!
Although I know
you wouldn't be able to do that
because you love Mikoy so much.
And don't get me wrong, my dear, okay?
I love your father so much,
but sometimes I just really want
to slice him into tiny pieces!
He's getting on my nerves, girl!
Based on my experience,
there's only one way for you to find out.
- Just one.
- What?
What I mean is,
if you really want to know
if a man is cheating on you…
When men start lying
about the time that's
supposed to be for you, well…
then he's busy with someone else.
That's what you should
watch out for with Mikoy, okay?
If there's missing time for you.
Oh.
Where are you?
We need to meet.
I need to prepare.
And I need to protect my family.
I will see you in a couple of days.
This is a hold up!
Wait, do you have any cash?
Man, I don't have cash.
My wife has my wallet.
If I were you, I'd just leave.
Oh, really?
Get the wallet!
I need this tomorrow, okay?
Okay, Mother Eagle.
Bok.
Bok!
What… What did that Mikoy say?
Nothing.
He wants to re-establish connection
and says that he's ready
to get back into action.
That's it?
After being gone for so long
and going radio silent,
that's all he can say?
He'll just say he's ready and that's it?
May I remind you, Agent Sianong,
that in those weeks you said
he was radio silent,
he was also recovering
from a gunshot wound.
So it is understandable
that during those times,
he was not exactly
investigating things for us.
Imagine, he was gone for weeks.
We don't know what happened
to him during that time.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
Pursued him to turn against us.
What if?
Hey!
Marshmallow in water!
It's bland, huh?
That's not a marshmallow.
What is this?
It's for the hands.
That's why.
Sorry.
That's why it's bland.
So that's how it is.
I need to laugh, right?
Oh, yes! You already told me that!
It was funny!
He thought it was a marshmallow.
Like a sitcom joke.
That I've already seen.
Don't you have anything else?
Well, he's putting up this comical facade.
He looks like a clown.
Always joking around.
Because there's a saying, right?
That the funniest people
are the smartest ones.
And the most cunning ones
are confident enough to look foolish!
Mikoy doesn't need to know
who I really am.
Dear…
If Mikoy truly loves you--
Do you think I'm worth loving?
Do you think I deserve
someone like Mikoy?!
If he ever got to know who I really am?
If he found out everything I've done?
Would he still risk his life for me?!
No!
Mikoy would never love someone like me!
So, please spare me the lecture
about whether it's right or wrong
that I'm living a lie.
All I know is he loves me,
and I love him so much.
What matters is…
that we're together.
Dear!
Why did you call me
and say you wanted to see me?
Who is this they're saying is your FUBU?
Huh?
Oh, no, Daddy Sir, you know
that's just fake news!
That's not true!
And what even is that?!
I don't even know what "FUBU" means!
And now they're saying you have one?!
Daddy Sir, let me assure you
none of that is true.
You see, Daddy Sir,
my bashers are just trying to ruin me.
Don't pay attention to them.
They're just rage-baiters.
I didn't get that from social media
or online.
Angelito Pinagpala's father
told me about it.
And he spoke to me personally.
Oh?
Look at your face.
What he said is true, isn't it?
He understands me.
I understand him, too.
What I don't understand is,
why would you tell him
very sensitive information
about my investigation?
First of all, you shouldn't
have been there in the first place.
You didn't ask for my permission.
Good thing Angelito's father came to me.
What if he had posted that on Fishbook?
What if he gave an interview
to the press, huh?!
You're right.
You also put your own life in danger.
What?
I didn't think it through.
Because I love Angelito so much.
Looks like she's been struck by lightning.
Yes, struck by lin-czech.
Huh?!
Lightning! What lin-czech? Light-ning!
Yes! Lin-czech!
I'm tired. I don't want to argue.
Fine, she was struck by lin-czech.
That your daughter is very much in love.
Yes, okay. I'm sorry.
She needs to accomplish it!
The life she chose.
The life that will make
our daughter happy, Viktor.
Wow, Mom!
- Amazing!
- Chiara, my dear!
Come here!
Teach me how to do Zumba!
I need to lose weight, dear!
You know me. I need inspiration
because all I've got is perspiration.
But Mom, you're already so sexy!
And if I'm blessed enough
to reach your age,
I'd want to be
as beautiful and sexy as you.
You really are something!
What a flatterer!
You really are blessed, huh?
You sure love to chatter.
- I don't know about you.
- Oh, by the way, where's Dad?
Oh, he told me last night
he had something to take care of.
It's because there's a piece of land
his parents gave him.
So he needs to fix the title
before it gets land-grabbed.
- That would've been such a waste.
- Right?
So I just let him go.
Oh my.
What about Mikoy?
Didn't he tell you?
He went to the office.
Huh?
But we already discussed it.
He wasn't supposed to start working yet.
That's what I told him too,
because that's what
we agreed on last time, right?
That's what I remember.
But he said he had
something to take care of.
So he left really early!
When a man starts lying
about the time that should be for you,
then he's busy with someone else.
The only thing he won't be able
to hide from you
is the time that's no longer yours.
That's what you should
watch out for with Mikoy, okay?
If there's missing time for you.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
That's enough!
A.k.a. Sianong, for a cuter vibe!
A.k.a. Alex, for a cooler vibe!
This is Super Special Asset
Michael D. Pinagpala,
a.k.a. Mikoy, for a cuter vibe,
reporting back for duty!
Why?
Did you think I'm dead?
No matter how many bullets hit me,
even if I get sprayed by a machine gun,
or dropped with hundreds of bombs…
still alive!
You?!
Angelito!
I'm sorry!
This is my peace offering!
I saw it at the mall.
It's so cute, just like you.
One for each for us!
What's going on?
Nothing.
I'm just saying sorry
because I realized that you were right.
That I was getting too involved
in your family matters.
And I was interfering
too much in your life.
So sorry!
Sorry.
Sorry too for what I said.
Maybe we just weren't
in the right headspace that time.
So, are we good now?
Yes! Angelito and I are good now!
It's nothing! Just let it go.
- Hey, Mikoy!
- Hey!
- Wait, hold on!
- Wait!
- What are you doing here?
- Hey!
You bastard!
- Mikoy.
- Mikoy!
Mikoy, what are you doing?
What are you all doing?!
What is he doing here?
Mikoy, can you put
that weapon down, please?
Mikoy, put your gun down!
- Put your gun down!
- Please, can you?
Listen to me! Believe me!
I know this guy!
He's the head of security of the Valtrovis
and most likely one of Moravianos men.
- Mikoy!
- I will never forget
the face of this idiot!
Mikoy, we know!
We know his background with the Valtrovis.
- That's enough.
- Oh?
So that's it!
Then why did you let him in here?
- Working for us?
- Yes.
Since when?!
Since you went on vacation leave!
- Hey! That wasn't vacation leave!
- You were gone for days.
That was sick leave!
And put that down already.
You might hit him.
Okay, fine.
Don't be too nervous.
I'm not a newbie with guns anymore.
My teacher was really good.
And next time, lock your holster!
It's too easy to grab your gun.
See?
I understand if you weren't able
to gather any intelligence,
considering your recent shooting incident.
Oh!
It's nothing, sir.
Oh gosh.
Your mission is over.
You may leave now.
Christy!
PHILIPPINE UNIVERSITY
You know, I'm glad we're okay now.
Because I actually
have a favor to ask you.
- Favor?
- Yes.
So that's why you made up with me.
You need something.
Hey!
I don't ask favors often.
All right.
What do you need?
I want you to meet my Dad.
For what?
Because I think I might have told him
that you are my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?! Me?!
Yes.
- Sir!
- Just put it there.
What is that all about?
Why are you firing Mikoy?
I honestly think
we don't need Mikoy anymore.
You know that's not true.
Mikoy is still critical to this mission.
Can you at least have
the decency to tell me the truth?
Don't give me softball excuses.
Why do you want him out?
You know, we are under a lot of pressure.
We have many detractors
looking for a reason
to shut this agency down completely.
Now, if they find out
that we recruited
an untrained civilian as an asset,
and Mikoy dies in the line of duty,
that's it!
Everything will be gone!
Then why are you afraid of politicians?
And this is what you'll do in return?
You're going to remove
our most useful asset?
If this is our final mission,
then so be it.
I don't care if tomorrow or the next day
the government dissolves us!
I will only do what I know is right.
And he has already sacrificed a lot
for this mission.
And if you take him out,
you won't just be betraying Mikoy.
You will also be abandoning
your principles as the agency director.
So?
- He didn't come to the office today?
- Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Pinagpala has not yet
reported to the office.
Just relax.
Is that Angelito?
We believe La Fornarina
is now in the Philippines.
What's the problem with Mikoy?
If he betrays us, I'd be the one
who's going to kill him.
So, how was it?
It's okay.
I don't like it
when someone is lying to me!