[rock music playing]
Seriously? Math really said that?
CHAPTER 50:
A CLASSIC, NOT A CLICHÉ
I'm telling you he did.
[chuckles]
-So, how about this one?
-Uh, no.
This one?
[sighs deeply]
The problem is we don't know
what kind of style he prefers.
Feminine or sexy?
I think he likes both feminine and sexy.
He seems quite greedy, you know?
[gasps] Oh, hold on a sec.
VIDEO CHATTING
EUI-JU, GO-YA
Huh?
[whimsical music playing]
Ta-da.
Seriously?
You don't think
it's a good choice?
For a first date, it doesn't work?
[clicks tongue]
[Woo-su] Eui-ju.
Yes?
What's your plan Saturday?
[sighs]
What on Earth could he want to talk about…
[gasps] …just the two of us this weekend?
[chuckles]
Ah, I don't know.
[breathes deeply]
So what should I wear? [groans]
[groans] Why is it only Thursday?
[groans] Why is it only Friday?
It's almost Saturday already.
But why is time passing so slowly?
[groans, sniffles]
[exclaims]
[bell rings]
[server] Welcome.
EPISODE 16
-Did you have a reservation?
-Uh, yes. Probably. Yes.
May I have the name for it?
It's Ga Woo-su.
Uh… I don't have it.
Yeo Eui-ju?
Yeo Eui-ju…
Not that either.
Anyway, there'll be two of us.
-[chuckles] Sure. Please come this way.
-Yes. Thank you.
[server]
Ma'am, let me get some water for you.
Thank you.
All right.
Please let me know if you need anything.
Okay.
What do I do? I'm so nervous.
[Go-ya] Don't show it though.
He won't find you attractive.
Order cream pasta. You know why, right?
[Eui-ju] That's too much of a cliché.
[Go-ya] Mm-mmm.
It's a classic, not a cliché.
Trust me on this.
[gentle romantic music playing]
[server] Welcome.
[tense music playing]
[Eui-ju sighs]
I guess Mr. Ga invited us to help us
patch things up.
I guess so.
-[door opens]
-[bell rings]
[server] Welcome.
You guys are early.
-Did you have a reservation?
-Yes…
…under "after-school" for 12 people.
Uh… We have one under "Actors' School",
not "after-school" though.
It's "after-school". After.
[server chuckles]
-Oh, it's still for 12 people, right?
-Yes.
All right. Please have a seat there.
Why are you guys there?
[sighs]
-[students chattering]
-Oh, my gosh. This place is so nice.
[student 1] Looks so good.
-Thank you.
-Ah, I can't wait.
I appreciate your hard work.
Why don't we have a toast?
-[student 2] Sounds great.
-[student 3] Sure.
Good job.
-Thank you!
[student 4] Thank you!
Hey, why are you guys
all dressed up today?
I know, you guys look so pretty today.
Be… Because it's Saturday. [chuckles]
This is awesome.
[sighs]
[phone vibrates]
[student 5] Mr. Ga, this is to die for.
[Go-ya] How's the date going?
Send me some pictures.
-Mr. Ga, can I have some of that too?
-Sure, go ahead.
-[student 5] Huh? Me too.
-Yes. [chuckles]
[student 4] I want some too.
Okay, should we take a pic
for the memories?
-[chuckles]
-Sounds good. Let's do it.
We need a picture together.
For sure. For sure.
[chuckles]
[with mouth full]
Wait, you're blocking me.
One, two, three.
WITH MR. GA
AFTER-SCHOOL MATH FINISHED
[students cheering]
[alarm beeping]
[grunts]
[beeping stops]
[sighs]
[yawns]
[somber music playing]
[breathes shakily]
Dong-ju.
[door opens]
[Dong-ju] What is it?
I can't see.
[Dong-ju] What?
Take me to the hospital.
Okay, hold on.
Hey, Gi-jeon. Gi-jeon. Wake up.
-[Gi-jeon] What? What is it?
-[Dong-ju] Woo-su has a problem.
[machine beeping]
I can't see.
[doctor] So your right eye had
a total corneal transplant before?
Yes.
What we can do for you now is
a deep anterior lamellar keratoplasty.
It replaces part of the cornea
except for the inner endothelial layer.
[Dong-ju sighs]
He had the surgery ten years ago.
He was fine.
-No side effects afterward.
-Exactly.
We all thought he was okay.
So why…
[sighs]
[crying]
Hey.
Are you
crying?
I feel so bad for that bastard.
[sobs] I knew when he played the smart-ass
and read all those damn papers.
I knew this would happen, but…
He didn't listen
and became a teacher, damn it.
I've been worried sick every single day.
In case he'd end up like this
and give up on his studies.
[sobs]
-He's gonna be all right.
-[sniffles]
Hey, what happened to all that trash talk?
Hey, come on.
You know how much he cares for Woo-su.
TREATMENT ROOM 1
[gasping]
-Please register at the reception.
-Oh, okay.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
So, what's the problem?
[Da-ju gasps] Hey, you're just an idiot!
You think you're so smart
but can't even take care
of your goddamn eyes.
Why can't you do that one simple thing
when all you do
is scold people for nothing,
you arrogant prick?
-Calm down, okay? Calm down.
-[breathes shakily]
I'm getting surgery.
Will that make your eyes better?
[somber music playing]
[doctor] Well, honestly speaking,
there's a 50% chance
that your vision will recover to
its pre-surgery state.
Your cornea is exceptionally thin,
and the situation is quite complicated.
Just don't exert yourself
and get plenty of rest
until the surgery, okay?
I'm going to get admitted,
and they'll see
if my condition is suitable for surgery.
[sniffles]
Don't make a fuss and go home.
Let's get you admitted first.
-[chattering]
-[door opens]
-Hi.
-[students] Hello.
-Hello.
-He's here.
[Dong-ju] Hello, everyone.
[sighs] Your homeroom teacher won't be
coming to school for the time being,
due to his eye problem.
So I'm here on his behalf.
I'll be taking attendance.
Mr. Yoon, Mr. Yoon.
How bad is his condition?
What exactly is wrong with him?
Uh…
[sighs] I remember you said overdoing
himself would put his other eye at risk.
What did you mean by that?
If he's away for the time being,
is he hospitalized?
How long will he stay at the hospital?
Eui-ju, don't you have a class to go to?
[breathes shakily]
Which hospital is he staying at, huh?
Just tell me that.
You can tell me that much, can't you?
[sighs]
[doctor] Your cornea is a bit thin,
but there shouldn't be any major problems
in proceeding with the surgery.
It will definitely help sharpen your focus
and improve you vision in general.
[somber music playing]
-[sighs]
-[chuckles] Come on.
Are you scared?
[scoffs] No, I'm not.
-[Gi-jeon chuckles]
-You were really in pain before,
but you look all right now.
[inhales deeply]
Can't you have them do something
to make your double eyelids thicker?
[chuckles]
You don't do
personality transplants here, do you?
[sighs]
Come on, man. Don't be a wuss.
Good luck.
See you later, four eyes.
-[chuckles]
-Wait…
You don't have glasses.
So, "geek" will do.
[chuckles]
You're feeling okay, right?
Good luck, huh.
It's time to go now.
Okay.
See you.
Don't cry, okay?
-[Da-ju exhales sharply]
-Goodness.
Yeah.
[exhales sharply]
[dramatic music playing]
-Huh? What? Eui-ju?
-Hey!
Hey, Eui-ju.
Hey, Eui-ju. Where are you going?
-[Go-ya] Where?
-[Dan-ji] Did you see her face?
[Dong-ju] He asked me to keep it a secret
until his surgery is over.
He probably didn't tell anyone
in case they worried.
He's at Hana University Medical Center.
[doctor sighs]
Fortunately, the surgery
went smoother than we previously expected.
Are you feeling uncomfortable in any way?
-No, I'm all right.
-[chuckles]
May I ask when I'll be able
to start reading again?
Uh, give it about a week.
It'll still be uncomfortable,
but you should be able to read.
Full visual comfort though,
that could take three or four weeks.
I see. Thank you.
[chuckles]
You just need to focus on recovering.
[door opens]
[sighs]
[rapid footsteps approach]
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
Eui-ju, two demerit points
for ditching school.
[breathing heavily]
[breathes shakily]
[whimpers]
Mr. Ga.
Are you okay, though?
[breathes shakily]
Just tell me if you're okay.
About your ridiculous
absolute-value question…
My answer is…
the promise from ten years ago.
[child crying]
[poignant music playing]
Hey, are you in a lot of pain?
YEO EUI-JU
[young Eui-ju] It's my mom.
She said she won't let me
watch Pichi Pichi Pichi
if I get the questions wrong again.
[crying continues]
[crying stops]
Open your hands like this.
Twelve means
all ten of your fingers plus two more.
One, two, three, four, five…
-It's seven.
-That's right.
So now whenever you do subtraction,
try doing it from the two-digit number,
not the one-digit number.
Does that mean that the ten-digit friend
is lending a hand to its one-digit friend?
That's really nice.
[young Woo-su] Right.
Let's try another question.
[young Eui-ju]
Look, maybe I'm a genius now.
Math is super easy.
[chuckles]
Now I'll get 100 on my math work,
and I'll show you the next time we meet.
I promise.
[giggles]
[chuckles]
Hmm.
We met again ten years after that day.
Yeo Eui-ju?
-Yeo Eui-ju!
-Over here.
Four points.
[Woo-su] A four in math?
[chuckles] You just hate math, huh?
You can't imagine the struggle
watching you try to keep that promise.
Wow… [gasps]
Those destined to meet
always do after all.
We're meant to be.
What?
Uh, nothing.
[chuckles] It's nothing.
I remember now.
You're that boy.
The handsome guy who was good at math.
Whoa. [chuckles]
You remembered?
You have no excuse now.
Hold on.
[gasps] This means,
I was eight when I met you
for the first time
and that's earlier than
when Deul-i met you, is that right?
What?
[chuckles] Yes. I win.
[scoffs] Are you serious?
[chuckles]
[scoffs]
Anyway,
is she not coming to visit?
She's got no reason to.
But isn't she… Isn't she your girlfriend?
Not at all. We're just friends.
Oh, come on.
You have a different look on your face
when you're with her.
You smile a lot. A sweet smile, you know?
Something like this.
Don't you smile when you're with a friend?
Is that it?
[clears throat]
Then maybe… [inhales sharply]
I can get my hopes up a little.
What?
Nothing.
I wish you a quick recovery.
[chuckles]
Go home. I'm tired.
-[grunts]
-Yep.
-[sighs]
-[Eui-ju] Goodbye.
Eui-ju, help me with this
before you leave.
Sure! [giggles]
I'm home.
-Hey, Mom.
-[with mouth full] Welcome home.
-Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom.
-Hmm. What is it?
Remember, remember when you took me
to that hospital in Seoul,
what's that hospital called?
What?
What are you talking about right now?
This is so random.
You know,
you took me to that hospital in Seoul,
back when I was in first grade.
What? Why would you see a doctor
when your mom's a pharmacist?
You've never been sick enough
to go to a hospital.
That's not true. I have.
[indistinct voices on television]
I haven't?
You haven't.
Dad, I haven't?
Huh?
What the…
When was it then?
W-w-was it someone else?
[mysterious music playing]
[interviewer] Mr. Ga,
you were well known for
being a math prodigy
when you were just a young boy.
CHAPTER 51:
THE NONSENSE ABSOLUT VALUE
Could you tell me
what inspired you to become a teacher?
Just before my second Olympiad,
I withdrew from the competition.
The official reason
was deteriorating eyesight,
but the real reason was something else.
During training camp,
I met this one other guy.
GA WOO-SU
MATH TEACHER, MURIM GIRLS' HIGH
He was always late because he overslept.
He'd get caught reading comics
during problem-solving sessions.
And yet, he breezed through
every problem I couldn't solve.
-[Eui-ju chuckles]
-Bang.
[Woo-su]
It was the first time I felt humbled.
[chuckles]
I could tell he had outstanding intuition
and that he genuinely loved math.
I knew I'd keep meeting people like that
through life,
and I just didn't have
the confidence to keep going.
I thought, "what should I do now?"
I got my eye surgery,
after dropping out of the Olympiad,
and, at the hospital, I met a little girl.
In that child's bright eyes,
and the way she jumped up and down
with excitement,
I was reminded of the moment
I first fell in love with math.
And for someone who
had only ever been a student,
it was the very first time
that I felt true joy
in teaching someone else.
[sighs]
[interviewer] I see.
So, I'm guessing that student
followed in your footsteps,
competed in the Olympiad,
and obviously are really good at math.
Well…
life rarely goes the way you want it to.
-[chuckles]
-Has she lost it?
Now one last thing,
can you tell us
what does math mean to you, Mr. Ga?
[inhales sharply]
TEACHERS' OFFICE
[poignant music playing]
[Woo-su] Math is…
-Hello, Mr. Ga.
-Hello.
[Woo-su] Math is…
a process
of discovering my own limits
at every single moment.
[student 6] Oh, yeah. I can't wait.
[student 7]
I wonder when he's gonna come in.
-Oh, hello.
-Hello.
[mouthing] I got 55 points.
[sighs]
Great job on making it through
another boring school year.
Yes, that's right.
We went through so much!
-Good job, everyone!
-Yeah, we did it!
-Good job, girls!
-We went through so much…
-[laughing]
-…but we did it!
And now you're gonna be seniors.
[students groan]
If you just spend your vacation
having fun,
you'll regret it in March.
I'm not telling you
to focus only on studying.
Evaluate yourself.
Know what you like and dislike.
Learn what you're capable of
and what you want to achieve.
Keep moving forward.
I want you to have faith in
whatever path you choose, and walk on it.
No matter what anyone else says.
Each one of you
is…
a star that shines differently.
[groaning]
Oh, Mr. Ga.
[students clamoring]
It's sweet.
I can't take it. He's so sweet.
[student 8] That was so sweet.
[student 9] Aw, Mr. Ga. I love him.
Dismissed.
-Aw, thank you.
-Thank you.
[students chattering, giggling]
[student 10] Bye, Mr. Ga!
[cheering]
["Sweet & Sour" playing]
CHAPTER 52:
I'M GLAD WE MET
-[Eui-ju] What do you think?
-[Dan-ji] I really like it.
"You and I are the closest at heart.
A star that's distant for a moment,
but close for a long time."
-What do you say?
-Oh. [chuckles]
Eui-ju and Go-ya, huh?
-This is pretty nice.
-Not bad at all, you know.
[Dan-ji] I give you that!
-[laughs] Nice job.
-[Jenny] I love it.
I really do.
-[Yeong-jae] You're the best.
-We did do a good job.
[Dan-ji] "Close for a long time."
This is totally us. Don't you think?
-[Yeong-jae] It's so like us!
-[Dan-ji] Oh, Eui-ju.
Oh. I'll visit you for sure, okay?
It better be soon.
Okay. I'll make it real soon.
-[sighs] Jenny.
-[chuckles]
Don't forget about us.
And don't ever dare to leave
our group chat, okay?
I'll annoy you with emoji bombs
all the time.
Please do.
[both chuckling]
All right. Bye, Jenny.
[groaning]
Well, make sure you get
a boyfriend by the time you come back.
[all laughing]
I will.
Anyway, what's taking Eui-ju so long, huh?
There she comes.
-Run, guys!
-[Dan-ji] Eui-ju, hurry!
-[Yeong-jae] What took you so long?
-You're so late!
Come on, Ji-a… [panting]
Ji-a wanted to say goodbye to Jenny,
and I waited until she was done working.
Hey, when did I say that?
Yes, you did. [laughs]
Ji-a. Ji-a. Mmm.
I can't get used to her hyper personality.
I get it though.
You guys are like a cat and a dog.
-Meow! Woof! Woof!
-[chuckling]
So true.
I'm sorry that
I didn't look after you better.
Take care of yourself out there.
And eat this on your way.
[groaning] Oh, my deskmate.
-[all laughing]
-[Eui-ju] Geez.
-Oh, don't cry.
-Thank you.
Jenny, this is for you too.
Take care and don't ever forget us, okay?
Mmm.
Ta-da!
A STAR FAR AWAY
[all] Whoa! [laughing]
-[laughing]
-[gasps]
[Dan-ji] No, it should be mine.
Eui-ju.
[groans] Aw…
Aw, I'm going to miss you.
-Mmm.
-Me too.
Thank you.
[kisses]
[all laughing]
-Bye!
-Bye, Jenny! We love you!
[Jenny chuckling]
Guys, I'm right here!
[chuckles] I'm here.
[chuckles] I love you, girls!
Be safe!
-Bye, bye, bye, bye!
-Bye, Jenny!
[chuckles] See you soon!
Bye! Love you!
[sighs]
I'm really happy I got to meet you all.
[gasps]
Thank you for making
every day full of fun and laughter.
Every memory I have here in Korea
is with you girls,
and…
and I loved every single moment.
I might be leaving,
but our friendship is forever.
We'll meet again.
Thank you for welcoming me warmly
and making good memories with me.
See you again.
Let me take your picture.
-Good idea.
-Do it, do it, do it.
-Stand here.
-[Dan-ji] Beautiful Korea.
[shutter clicks]
-Tteokbokki. I like tteokbokki.
-Do you like tteokbokki?
-Yeah.
-You do? It's so good.
If you like spicy food,
you should try jjampong.
What do you say to fried chicken or pizza?
[laughing]
[Eui-ju]
I was able to finish writing the novel,
thanks to the support of my readers,
who desperately wanted me to resume.
Later, the novel was launched
and reached over a million downloads.
It's so exciting. [gasps]
I became a top-tier writer at last.
Oh, you want to know how it ended?
WE WERE FRIENDS, FINAL EPISODE
[inhales sharply, sighs]
Okay. Fine.
Now that I know
your heart belongs to Kang Tae-ha,
[scoffs]
I'll stop right now.
-Si-on.
-[sighs]
I told myself I'd never regret this.
Turns out I do.
I always was mean to you, wasn't I?
Thanks for everything, Choi Yoon!
Come on, don't act like
we'll never see each other again.
Today will be the last time.
Is that necessary?
Si-on, you were my world in high school.
I don't want to lose you.
[scoffs]
I know I'm the winner,
but, strangely,
I don't feel pleased at all.
You think this is a game?
What do you win, huh?
A medal or something?
You bastard.
[tense music playing]
[both breathing heavily]
Uh, don't do this.
-Huh?
-[sighs]
I'm leaving.
[gasps] Hey, Si… No, wait.
[Jae-min] Well…
You guys were all here.
I looked everywhere for you.
Sit down. Sit down. Sit. Come.
What's going on? What's with this mood?
Did someone die or something?
[laughing]
I'm not in the mood for jokes now.
You got dumped?
-[sighs] Uh…
-[sighs]
So you're giving up?
No…
I'm not giving up on Yoon!
-Hey, Han Jae-min.
-What? What?
What do you want?
Damn.
Yoon, are you okay with
cutting ties with Si-on?
No, right?
Tae-ha, you too, punk.
Are you sure you can be happy
while Yoon is sad?
Let's all live together!
Huh?
-Together?
-The four of us.
What's the big deal?
You never truly know someone
until you've lived with them.
-[sighs]
-Only then…
you get to know their true colors.
Uh…
-[Jae-min laughs]
-Still, it's unnecessary to live together.
Getting cold feet?
Then chicken out while you can.
Ha! There's no way.
[scoffs] I'm more than ready for it.
[scoffs]
-Still, I don't think this is--
-[shushes]
[shushes]
Don't worry,
my baby deer.
-[chuckles]
-Huh?
It'll be super fun.
As if.
It's going to be a living hell.
[chuckles]
Is this round two?
Oh, please.
All right, let's go!
Here we come. Home, sweet home!
Whoo! Bang, bang!
All right, let's go!
MOST POPULAR WEB NOVEL OF 2026
WE WERE FRIENDS
[Shin] Here you go. [groans]
FINAL CHAPTER:
FIRST SNOW
-Honey…
-[grunts]
…do you remember this?
Oh, man. Yeah.
This is when I went to the ER
for food poisoning. [groans]
The ER?
[Shin] Huh?
Remember that time you fed me
all those raw oysters to boost my stamina,
and I… [groans]
[Ma] Oh, you mean when we went to Seoul?
What's going on?
You're leaving tomorrow, right?
Are you done packing up?
Mmm. Are you saying goodbye?
[Eui-ju] I came to give you this.
I-I hear medical fees are expensive
and it's not easy
getting medicine in the States.
What if you get sick there?
[inhales sharply]
You absolutely cannot get sick.
And make sure you don't get too close
with Deul-i while you're over there.
But don't go getting close
with the American girls either.
Just study
and come straight back, all right?
Oh, and watch out
for pretty American girls…
Oh, and cute guys too.
I guess you never know, right?
And if anyone talks to you,
do not smile at them ever.
Got it?
[chuckles]
Thank you. [chuckles]
[groans]
Oh, you really shouldn't smile like that.
[sighs] This is not good at all.
You're going to study
and do your research in the States
only during vacation, right?
You have to come back, okay?
You don't have to worry.
And good luck with your writing.
What's your next project?
[chuckles]
The title is…
[whispering]
["Why the Night" playing]
-[sighs]
-[chuckles]
Have a safe trip.
Thanks. Stay safe okay.
[exclaiming]
Mr. Ga! Mr. Ga!
Mr. Ga, come back out!
Look, it's snowing!
It's the first snow! [laughs]
The first snow.
[laughs] It's snowing!
Mr. Ga, it's the first snow!
[Woo-su] Is that exciting?
[Eui-ju] Of course!
My first snow!
The first snow!
[laughs] My first snow!
[students clamoring]
["Sweet & Sour" playing]
[students]
♪ Everything is sweet and sour ♪
[in Korean] ♪ This might be the real me ♪
[in English]
♪ Everything is sweet and sour ♪
[in Korean] ♪ Fill it sweetly ♪
[in English] ♪ Sweet and sour ♪
[cheering]
-[song stops]
-[chairs clatter]
[cheering]
[song resumes]
[chanting]
-Jenny!
[cheering continues]
[all, in Korean]
♪ What's really on your mind ♪
♪ If you feel uneasy ♪
[in English] ♪ You know it's all right ♪
[in Korean]
♪ When you look up to the sky ♪
[in English] ♪ It's sweet and sour ♪
♪ Everything is sweet and sour ♪
[in Korean] ♪ This might be the real me ♪
[in English]
♪ Everything is sweet and sour ♪
[in Korean] ♪ Fill it sweetly ♪
[in English] ♪ Sweet and sour ♪
[cheering]
-Bye!
THE END