[rock music playing]
CHAPTER 46:
EVEN IF I HAVE TO DROP OUT
[slurps] Mmm.
[sighs] What time does it start?
Was it 9:00 am?
Insane. A disciplinary committee?
[sucks teeth] Just eat your food.
Your novel became a big hit.
So, what's the problem?
Keep writing and make money.
That way you can give me
a lot of pocket money.
You can just drop out and take the GED.
Your dad and I
won't take your side
because we're your parents.
We will accept whatever the school
decides to do about you. You understand?
Honey…
[sighs]
What's the plan today?
Shouldn't we come up with a plan together
or something?
[sighs]
Whatever you guys decide.
That's right.
I believe Eui-ju must
learn a lesson from this.
Especially if she intends to keep writing.
And eventually
make a living out of it too.
[downcast music playing]
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
EPISODE 15
Oh. [stammers]
DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
#GRADE HEAD - MS. JANG
#HEAD OF STUDENT AFFAIRS
MR. SONG
#VICE PRINCIPAL - MR. SEO
I've asked you all here today,
regarding Yeo Eui-ju and the novel
that she has written
about her own teachers,
which you must've read by now.
As you know the characters in the novel
are based on actual people, her teachers.
And this raises concerns
about the violation of
teachers' rights and defamation.
Thus, I'd like your opinions
on how we should proceed with this.
Ms. Kim,
I was so shaken by it
that I couldn't even finish reading it.
Oh… [chuckling]
…it was just too embarrassing.
[clears throat] A mistake like this
can be made out of curiosity.
And yet, she's at the stage
where her sexual identity
as well as her own values must take root.
I believe adults must stop her
from taking the wrong path.
-[tense music playing]
-Since she is still a minor,
she must be disciplined severely
before she turns into a criminal.
A crim…
-A criminal?
-[clears throat]
Ma'am, what are your thoughts then,
regarding the novel written by Eui-ju?
Uh… [clears throat]
Well… [sighs] …let me share a word
about this whole thing with you.
First of all, I would like to apologize
if our daughter
has caused discomfort and concern
to any of you here today.
I only have myself to blame.
It's… It's really all just my fault.
I should've…
I should've paid more attention to her.
However! [breathes shakily]
How can a parent stop their child
from doing what they love?
Especially when their child
shares with them…
[sincere music playing]
…that it's the… [sighs] …the only thing
that keeps them going in life.
She's still too young
to have a good sense of judgment.
Please give her a chance to reflect.
-Please understand.
-[stammers] Please understand.
Uh… [sighs]
And now, let's hear from
the actual victims, the teachers.
[smacks lips, sucks teeth] First of all,
I'd like to say a word
on all of our behalf.
Finding out the teachers
were dragged into this,
I found that very shocking.
Mmm, and then it hit me, "Is this what
they think every time they see me?"
That feeling was really hard to shake.
We've given this situation
some serious thought,
therefore, we've come to a conclusion.
[inhales sharply]
What do you suggest we do, Ms. Kim?
[owl hooting plays]
[stammers] Whatever you decide,
we're all on board ma'am.
Oh. [chuckles]
Uh, what about the others? [chuckles]
I want Eui-ju to take this chance
to understand how serious it is
to write a novel about actual people,
especially without their consent.
It doesn't matter
if they're turned into fiction.
And also she must not take it lightly.
[sighs]
Kill 'em with kindness, I guess.
[inhales deeply]
I'll…
choose kindness.
[Seo] That's ridiculous!
If we let her slide like this,
it will destroy our school's authority.
She must be expelled.
Ma'am, let's expel her.
[dramatic music playing]
I told her to.
I knew and I told her to keep writing it.
It's my responsibility.
Of course, when I first found out
I told her to delete it right away.
I couldn't understand her.
But Eui-ju knew what her dream was
and she was working to get closer to it.
Her certainty…
was very admirable.
[groans]
So, I just told her to keep going.
To be there, to cheer for her,
and to watch her grow.
Eui-ju's a student
who does get it done
once she puts her mind to something.
Watching her as her homeroom teacher,
I had no choice
but to respect her persistence.
Now that we know her dream
is to be a writer,
I'd give her a chance,
so that her persistence…
can grow into real talent,
and her energy and passion
can carry her all the way to her dream.
Please understand.
[inhales deeply]
Let's hear from you too.
What do you say, Eui-ju?
Are you going to keep writing?
No, right?
I…
Yes?
[inhales shakily]
I do want to keep writing.
[stammers] What?
[Eui-ju breathing shakily]
I'll accept any kind of punishment…
[hopeful music playing]
…and from now on, I'll write on my own,
only with my own ideas.
And honestly,
I'm truly sorry for everything that I did.
I've already deleted We Were Friends.
But for me writing is…
something I want to continue doing.
Even if I have to drop out of school…
I will keep writing novels.
[groans]
[sighs]
I'll discuss this
with the teachers in charge first.
And…
in four days I'll let you know
what the punishment is. Let's go.
-[sighs]
-My apologies.
Goodbye.
[Seo] Geez.
[door closes]
-I'm really sorry.
-[Da-ju] It's okay.
Mr. Ga, I actually didn't know you were
her homeroom teacher all this time.
It's all good.
I should've been paying closer attention.
-Please don't worry about it and go home.
-I see.
Goodbye.
I'll go speak with the principal.
-Okay.
[Ma, softly] Oh… Goodbye.
Mom, Dad, you can… [stammers] …leave.
Leave?
Oh, okay.
We'll… get going.
See you at home.
-[chuckles] Goodbye.
-Take care.
Good luck in class.
Eui-ju, back to class.
We'll have to wait
for Mr. Ga to come back.
I apologize for what I did.
[both chuckle]
I didn't expect to be
in your practice novel.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Yoon.
[sincere music playing]
A writer writes stories based on
what they observe and imagine,
but you must be careful
when it involves actual people.
You understand that, Eui-ju?
Yes.
You know what?
I saw this coming
when she wrote that reflection letter.
Seriously, it had way more details
than it needed to have.
So now I'm going to watch
how you do the Japanese essay homework.
And if it doesn't touch my heart
in any way,
I'll give you a flat-out F.
-Yes.
-[chuckles]
Poor Eui-ju. I mean…
Mr. Jung, sorry. Because of me--
Oh, no. Don't worry.
I don't know much about writing anyway.
[chuckles]
But I hear you're quite good at it.
Huh?
That's what matters.
Don't worry about it, Eui-Ju.
Just go back to class.
Yes.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No matter how I look at this,
this is straight up defamation.
[scoffs] I just cannot let this go.
I-I-I'm getting a lawyer
and I'm taking this all the way.
Don't worry it's just a joke, he's joking.
Go on. Go.
I mean, why am I described
as someone so cheap, huh?
Tell me,
do you take me for someone who hides
instead of fighting for justice?
-You don't fight for justice.
-Not at all.
No. It's not true, right?
[comical music playing]
Hey, what if people actually see me
as that kind of person?
-[Gi-jeon] That's what you're like.
-No way.
-You did a good job.
-You did good. Really.
His character, it was the best.
[chuckles] Don't listen to him.
-Go on, Eui-ju. Go, go.
-[Dong-ju] You did well.
Hey! You have to change it!
Oh, come on!
-How did it go?
-Eui-ju.
Oh, Eui-ju.
-How did it go?
-What did they say?
-What did they say? Come on, tell us.
-Uh…
-What's the verdict?
-I'm not sure yet.
They'll let me know after the meeting.
-Oh, no.
-What?
Then, will the results
come out today or when?
What did they say?
[Go-ya] And Mr. Ga, what did he say?
Didn't he say anything? Come on, tell us.
Actually,
Mr. Ga already knew
because he's the one who caught me first.
-Huh? He already knew?
-[chattering]
-Mr. Ga?
-He said it was actually his fault
because he's the one let me keep writing,
even after finding out about it.
[Go-ya] He said that?
[students gasping, whispering]
[Dan-ji] So he actually
knew about the whole thing?
Then…Then, what's going to happen now?
[Eui-ju] I think
they're discussing it right now.
[solemn music playing]
Her novel's just as popular
as those by established writers.
In terms of books, you can say it became
a bestseller as soon as it was published.
So what if it's that popular?
It's downright embarrassing. [huffs]
There was a novel by a writer
named Love Hani
when web novels first started.
It was harshly criticized at first,
but then it became popular enough
to be made into a film.
Love Hani donated part of her royalties
to her alma mater.
Could you imagine
how proud that school was?
She donated her royalties?
It's still no… Unacceptable.
What are you staring at, Mr. Song?
[inhales sharply] Can you please tell me
what you are reading?
Oh, gosh, Ms. Kim.
This is actually a big deal.
See?
I guess Eui-ju's novel is really popular.
I mean, people are writing tons
of comments online.
They all want to know why
she decided to leave
and why she decided to delete the novel.
Right, as if. [scoffs]
How many could there be?
How many read it?
Like a thousand? [chuckles]
[chuckles] What?
What are you talking about? Huh?
The most recent comments alone
add up to 108,420!
What? That many people read it?
[amusing music playing]
Still, it's unacceptable.
A student using her teachers
for a novel like that.
Oh, wow. [chuckles]
Guess what?
They even started a petition
under the Committee
-so they can get Imuk to come back.
-Mr. Song!
My biggest concern is that
our school's reputation might be damaged
if this information gets out.
I see it differently.
If anything, this shows that
our school produced a student
with actual literary talent!
Mr. Song, please.
[clears throat]
This is something to be grateful for.
She could become sensational
like what's-her-name.
The one who wrote Harry Potter.
I mean, it's possible, right? Hmm?
-Right. Sure.
-That's right, Ms. Kim.
Let's see now. [breathes deeply]
[groans] What should we do?
[groans]
4 DAYS LATER
[inhales sharply]
Yeo Eui-ju's actions not only constituted
a serious violation of school rules,
but they also had a negative impact
on all her fellow students.
[inhales sharply]
However, given her genuine remorse
and our belief that
she is fully capable of doing better
we have decided to give her
one last chance.
We will hold her accountable,
but won't prevent her from her dreams.
[inhales sharply]
Therefore, Murim Girls' High School's
final decision in this matter will be…
[dramatic music playing]
…suspension for five days.
[amusing music playing]
Anyway…
Am I in the novel?
-What did they say?
-How did it go? Huh?
I'm suspended…
for five days.
-Suspended?
-You're suspended?
-Suspended!
-You're only suspended?
[squealing, cheering]
[triumphant, cheerful music playing]
Hold up, should we celebrate
she's only getting suspended?
What about college applications?
Even with a perfect portfolio,
her record still matters.
-Oh…
-No, no, no.
I remember nothing stays on your record
unless it's a school violence issue.
-Oh, really? Thank goodness.
-In any case,
I'll have to accept it,
it's my fault after all.
Oh, come on, what could be the problem
when it's just a suspension?
[squealing, cheering]
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[clamoring]
CHAPTER 47:
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY FIRST STUDENT
[class] Hello.
I'm sure you've already heard
that Eui-ju got suspended.
It's only right for her
to take responsibility,
but… I'm responsible as well.
A teacher must always remain neutral,
but I didn't.
[sincere music playing]
If this has hurt anyone's feelings,
I apologize.
I'll try to pay more attention
to what you say,
but I'll also ask you
to try to understand each other
instead of arguing about
who did what wrong.
[class] Yes, sir.
Okay. Good luck with your classes today.
Hey, sorry.
Sorry.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Thanks.
What is it?
I didn't get to thank you
for what you did for me.
Thank you, Mr. Ga.
Don't mention it, all right?
So… [inhales sharply]
…Mr. Ga, why would you
do something like that?
Like what?
You actually convinced the principal
and all the teachers.
And I was just wondering why you did it.
["Why This Night" playing]
To me, you're…
You are…
my first student.
Because…
I'm just your student?
Choi Ji-a, Eun Ha-su, and you,
to me, are who actually deserve
some kindness.
Stay away from trouble
while you're suspended.
Go home.
[whining]
CHAPTER 48:
TURN OVER A NEW LEAF
[funky, upbeat music playing]
What? You can't have this.
[Mom] Suni, go wake your sister up.
[chuckles] Okay. All right.
-Bang. [giggles]
-[Suni whines]
[sighs]
YEO EUI-JU
[Da-ju] Mmm. Goodness.
I'm gonna give it a try.
I've finally decided to stop running away
before I see things through.
-What's this about?
-Who are you talking about?
[pensive music playing]
-Going somewhere?
-[Da-ju] What is it?
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
-[chuckling]
-What is this?
-I know it's supposed to be tofu…
-What is it?
-…but this will do.
-Oh.
-That's true.
-Hey!
-It's not like she came back from prison.
-Ooh.
-Sort of similar.
-I know.
We can say she's been discharged.
Now go live your life right, buddy!
Mmm. Thanks so much, buddy.
[students chuckling]
-[chuckles]
-This is for you.
Have this as you write.
Don't let your sugar levels get too low.
Thank you so much.
-It's chocolate!
-Hey, don't mention it.
Ooh! I have a GOAT writer friend!
Listen.
-Go, Eui-ju!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
[Jenny] Try some! Try some!
[Eui-ju] Okay, okay.
-Eat something white to start your life.
-I'll give it a try.
[cheering] Yes! Yeah!
[cheering, chuckling]
Have some! Have some!
-Give me one!
-Hey! Only one!
You know…
I hated that you were getting
all Mr. Ga's attention.
I felt like maybe
he would pay more attention to me
if I ruined you.
But I was wrong about it.
I'm not gonna make excuses.
I just want to apologize to you.
I'm really sorry.
[sincere music playing]
[sighs]
Thanks to you
I was able to own up to my mistakes.
If none of this had happened,
I would've kept writing
with all that guilt hanging over me.
[chuckles]
Let's get to the auditorium.
The auditorium?
What about the morning assembly?
We have Professor Na Deul-i's
lecture today.
By the way,
she's not Mr. Ga's girlfriend, is she?
One, two. Testing mic, testing.
Check, one, two.
-Say ho, ho, ho!
-[crowd] Ho, ho, ho!
[phone buzzes]
Dan-ji wants me to bring her
a remote control from the media room.
-Go on without me. [chuckles]
-Okay.
Hello.
Oh, hello there.
Oh! Aren't you the student
from the coffee shop the other day?
[sighs] It's so good
to see a familiar face.
[chuckling]
I was feeling nervous, you see.
Why?
Well, I've hardly ever talked to
students before in my life.
I hear students these days are scary.
I'm worried I might make a mistake.
The girls aren't mean.
They won't bite you
unless you take their food.
-[chuckling]
-[chuckles]
You came for this?
-Yes.
-Let's go.
[inhales deeply] Will I do a good job?
You've lectured
bigger audiences than this.
Ugh, I'm so nervous though.
[groans]
Wish me luck!
Says someone who'll do well.
But I've never done it
at a place like this.
[chattering, chuckling]
-You're cheating!
-[Jenny] I got you!
Eui-ju.
What did she say?
-We made up.
-You did?
Yeah, we did.
[applauding, cheering]
IN MY OWN WAY,
AT A PACE THAT SUITS ME
Hello, it's nice to meet you all.
My name is Na Deul-i.
[funky, upbeat music playing]
I've prepared a few slides about myself.
Now, guess what this is.
It's my very first test result
when I was in first grade.
Strange, right?
-Because I'm supposed to be a genius.
-[crowd chuckles]
What's your standard in choosing a job?
-[students] Fame. Money.
-Fame. Money. Right, money.
They say science students score higher
on the MBTI Thinking scale.
The real question most of you
are probably asking right now though is,
"Are you seriously a T right now?"
Yes, you should give it a try too.
At that time, everyone was pretty sure
that the Korean team
was going to place first,
but someone decided to drop out
right at the end,
and the team ended up placing second.
Guess who that was.
It was your math teacher right there,
Mr. Ga Woo-su.
[crowd chuckling]
I believe that all of you will be able to
find your own answer one day.
It's so annoying
that she's so cool.
-[sighs]
-[Deul-i] I'll be rooting for you.
All right. This was Na Deul-i.
Thank you for listening. Thank you.
One, two, three.
Go back inside now.
[students] Thank you.
Could you take a picture of us?
-Mr. Ga, me too.
-Me too!
Take one of us too!
All right. One, two, three.
[camera shutters]
-Thank you.
-Mr. Ga, me too.
-One by one, yeah?
-[students] Yes!
Oh, thank you. [chuckles]
-One, two, three.
-[camera shutters]
[students chuckle]
-One, two, three.
-[camera shutters]
-You're so cool.
-Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you, thank you.
Come. Come.
[chuckles]
All right. One, two, three.
[camera shutters]
[both] Thank you.
I got to relax and pull it off
all thanks to you.
-I really appreciate it.
-[chuckles]
I was able to relax thanks to her.
The after-school class
will have a pop quiz today.
Write it on the blackboard.
-Yes, sir.
-Go on.
-Goodbye.
-Bye-bye now.
-Let's go.
-[students chuckling]
-Did you take it?
-Yeah.
[chuckles]
Whoa, they do make a great couple.
Sorry.
[sighs]
Yeah, I know.
He belongs with her and not me.
Let's go.
Happy you stayed for the research
instead of going to the States?
CHAPTER 49:
THE ABSOLUT VALUE OF ROMANCE
So, does that mean we're rivals now?
Who will be first?
I mean, who will find the proper answer.
Yeah, I guess time will tell
if math on its own has any value at all.
[scoffs]
You'll regret it when it's too late.
Go on.
[smacks lips] All right fine.
I'm leaving, okay? [scoffs]
-Bye.
-Bye!
VISITOR PARKING LOT
[class] Hello, Mr. Ga.
All right, there's a pop quiz today.
You have 20 minutes
to solve the questions.
Pass these back.
PAST MATH EXAM QUESTIONS
[pensive music playing]
3. PROPERTIES
OF LOGARITHMIC FUNCTIONS
2. MEAN VALUE THEOREM
1. DIFFERENTIATION
OF POLYNOMIAL FUNCTION
[exhales shakily]
[sniffs]
If you're done,
submit it and you can leave.
Stop and bring it over.
Bring it over.
Leave it here and go home.
[hopeful music playing]
[Eui-ju] Absolute value refers
to something that exists solely as itself
without being compared to
any other object.
A state where no conditions
or constraints are attached
and nothing can stand against it.
Find the absolut value
of the following romance.
What is the absolut value of
glasses divided by pigeon
multiplied by the square root
of emergency room
plus the square
of after-school class plus novel
multiplied by the limit of bus stop?
ABSOLUTE
-Seriously?
-Can't you even spell it right?
I know how to spell it.
This is just
a literary device I used
to emphasize the word "absolute."
[sighs]
Both your spelling
and your equation are a mess.
Is there an answer?
Of course! This is the only problem
I've been working on lately.
What's the answer then?
I've got…
only one answer.
[sighs]
To me…
To me,
the answer is…
This absolut value…
The value is you.
[tender music playing]
My absolut value of romance…
is you, Mr. Ga.