[This drama is fictional
and bears no resemblance to reality]
[Some scenes feature AI technology]
[All child and animal scenes
followed strict safety guidelines]
[Episode 3]
Excuse me.
Hello, sir.
So this is where you've been.
You got here faster than I thought.
Wait here. I'll grab you something to wear.
No, I'm okay...
You looked better before you changed.
Less douchey.
Go inside and change.
So why'd you come find me?
Aren't you curious how I found you?
Someone's been tailing me
for the past few days.
[Freshness that wins hearts]
What now?
Am I busted?
Hey, Ju Young Jae.
It's been a while.
- He got caught?
- Sorry, Soo Bin.
He asked me to keep it a secret.
You scared me.
I've got a thing about flowers.
That's why I brought it.
Go ahead, hit me.
Thanks to you,
our show hit its highest ratings ever.
So as a thank-you,
I came to ask if you'd come
on the show one more time.
That's a strange way to show thanks.
I'm asking you.
You came all this way just for that?
Well, why'd you turn your phone off?
But hey...
I got to come back home for once.
It's nice.
All thanks to you.
I was hoping for more.
Huh? Your phone works just fine.
Was Jin Su's place called Feast or something?
Where was it again?
Why don't you just look it up
on that working phone?
You're right.
See you, then.
Director!
Wait!
Director, let me drive you!
Hold on!
If you show up one more time,
my whole life could change.
Take a right at that intersection.
First, my pay goes up.
Then I'd have a steady income,
so I could cut back on out-of-town gigs.
I get so much out of this,
I can't even list it all.
Are you okay with me doing the show?
Of course I am!
My life gets a major upgrade out of this.
Personal feelings? Who cares.
Did Producer Kyung tell you that?
That your life gets better if I do it?
So you'll do it?
Soo Bin, what do I do?
I don't think I can make it today.
Have you eaten?
Do you want to grab a bite?
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Thanks for the food.
Why couldn't your mom make it?
- Yeah, I don't know.
- Why not just go to her place?
Why are you meeting her outside?
Yeah...
You mean the day after tomorrow.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Yeah.
- Jin Su's doing well, right?
- Of course.
Same as always.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Please, don't say that.
- Come again.
- I will.
Even if you call me last-minute,
I'll be right there.
You keep calling on me, so of course I will.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Take care.
They're booking you
for a festival two days out?
It has to be a fill-in gig.
Works for me, though. Fill-ins pay better.
That's how hard I'm hustling.
But if you'd just come on the show?
See? It's peak festival season.
Wait, no. It's Producer Kyung.
- Yes, Producer Kyung.
- Hey, Yi Jae.
Why haven't you reported back?
Is he doing it?
I'm talking to him right now.
He seems pretty busy with his next project.
We're working out the schedule.
What if we get axed before that?
Hurry it up already.
I'm working on it.
Why are you so impatient?
- If I go on the show, will things change?
- Hey!
- What?
- If I go on the show,
will Ju Yi Jae's life change?
Hey, are you crazy? What's wrong with you?
What?
You said if I went on the show,
your life would get easier.
So that's what I'm doing.
I'll do the show.
Yes, order coming up!
It's two portions,
but I made it more like three.
That one's on the house.
The sashimi's drying out. Where is he?
Sir, we need to hire someone.
Sorry about that.
[SimSim Fisheries]
Here's your sashimi bowl.
- Some side dishes too.
- Sure, I'll bring more.
Hey!
It was great.
I'll pay.
Oh, okay.
- Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes.
Who is this?
[To SimSim Fisheries, stay healthy, Sim Yu Geon]
You know who this is?
- No idea.
- A singer or something?
That's the owner's son.
Handsome, right?
I thought you were his son.
He does look like...
the owner, though.
We went to school together too.
You here visiting?
- Yeah.
Your son is famous?
Yeah, my son's an actor.
- An actor?
- Really?
What's he been in?
He debuted as Friend Three
in "Devil High School,"
stole the show in episode four,
scene 27 of "The Young Master in My Garden,"
and delivered a legendary line
just before the episode eight finale
of "I Won't Love Anymore."
"Director, the car's ready for you."
And many, many more.
- You seen it?
- You seen any?
- We've been here too long. Let's go.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Yeah, it was great.
- Come again.
- Thanks.
- Come again!
- Yeah.
They haven't seen any of it.
Take all that down.
Yes.
[To SimSim Fisheries, stay healthy,
Sim Yu Geon]
You look gorgeous in this, Ha Na.
I wonder where he's striking poses this time.
[First Love's Smile]
[Casting Audition]
Sim Yu Geon.
Yes.
Yes, come on in.
You're not quite
the right fit for the character.
Marriage?
I thought I made myself clear.
Then kill him.
[Casting Director]
Yes.
Sir...
Can you be certain we're alive?
Next.
That was a bit disappointing.
Ha Na,
your revised schedule's in.
Hold on, Director Kang.
Yes?
Why am I the only one off that day?
Is there something else on my schedule
I don't know about?
That day, you have
a joint event with the CEO...
What is it this time?
You need to go accept the major donor award.
Excuse us.
Let's step out.
A picture-perfect mother-daughter moment,
wouldn't that be lovely?
The exemplary mom is the one getting the award.
Why do I have to go?
So I can be your accessory again?
Does that bother you?
Hey, why would that bother you? It's an honor.
I'm bothered because you don't get
why I'm bothered.
You think it ends with me skipping out?
When shooting gets pushed back,
who has to deal with it?
The crew and the other actors, that's who.
That's part of their job.
People with power get to dictate time, too.
Doesn't it embarrass you? Living like that?
I'm so happy you get to live off
your mom's success.
Makes me feel
like all that hard work was worth it.
It's that "living off Mom" talk
that makes me miserable.
Oh, you brat.
You don't even know
what real misery looks like.
If you go around apologizing
on set again like last time,
you think people will respect you for that?
It just makes you look weak.
No, Mom, you're the one making me look weak.
When you mess up, of course you apologize.
And my screw-ups are
usually because of you anyway.
Keep your voice down.
There are rats everywhere out there
trying to dig up dirt.
Oh, CEO An,
I'm so sorry.
I'm a little late, aren't I?
I know you've been waiting a while for me.
So thoughtful.
By the way, who's the girl
doing my Ha Na's hair?
I've never seen her before.
She was originally assigned to Si Hyun,
but she's quick and has a great eye, so...
Swap her out.
Look at that hair.
No taste at all.
Now.
Yes.
Are you serious? Soo Bin is back in town?
Yeah, he just had bibimbap
at our place a little while ago.
And he was with Yi Jae too.
Oh my.
Didn't Director Woo send him off
to the States for school?
He never showed his face around here,
so I figured he was off being a doctor.
So that film director who was on Yi Jae's show
is really Director Woo's son?
That's what I'm saying.
He changed his whole name.
I almost didn't recognize him.
Why did he suddenly become a Lee?
Lee An Woo, was it?
Or Lee An Ku?
It's really something.
Yi Jae was the one who was always
running around saying she'd make movies.
How did it end up the other way around?
I know, right?
Soo Bin is staying at my place.
- Oh my, you scared me.
- Oh my goodness!
Hey.
What are you doing sitting here?
Waiting for the bus.
Oh, I see.
Oh look. Here they come.
- Oh my.
- That's them.
- Yi Jae.
It really is them.
See, I told you.
Those two have always been joined at the hip.
How sweet.
But you don't run the guesthouse anymore.
Figured he had his reasons.
The bus is here.
Right.
- Don't get up. Keep doing what you're doing.
- Okay.
- I'm off.
- Bye.
Grandma Jong Sun!
She's not here.
You give it to her.
Sure.
Hold on a sec.
Here.
[Gyeongseong Love Song]
I'm giving this back to you.
You gave me this script
and said you'd wait.
I think it belongs with you now.
So now you're returning my dream?
You sure about that?
What if I rip it up or burn it?
If that's the ending you want, then do it.
I overlooked the fact
that I'm someone from your past
and only thought about moving forward.
I was wrong.
The ending of our story should've
come before the script's ending.
I'm sorry. I really mean it.
I'm sorry I didn't see it myself,
and I'm sorry it took so long.
Those years of waiting you talked about,
they were years I didn't want to remember.
All because of that?
You tanked your college
entrance exam over this?
You let a girl ruin your future?
It wasn't because of Yi Jae.
I never wanted to go to medical school.
Soo Bin.
- You little!
- Please stop!
Mom!
No!
Hit me.
Until you've gotten it all out.
As punishment,
my father tried to ship me off to the States,
and until I told him myself that I'd obey him,
I wasn't even allowed to leave the house.
It only took ten days.
For me to give up on myself.
I'll go.
To the States.
I'll live the way you want me to.
Good.
That's how it should be.
But,
how could you not give up on me
when I'd given up on myself?
That huge heart of yours
made me even more ashamed of myself.
I'm not asking you
to understand now, or to forgive me.
I just
wanted you to feel a little better.
Right.
That's a relief.
So it wasn't my fault.
There were circumstances you couldn't help.
I see.
But I don't feel better.
You're hitting me with this now
and calling it comfort?
You know the worst way
to be remembered by someone you loved?
Not as the bad guy,
but as a pathetic loser.
You pathetic bastard.
Hey!
Huh?
You're back.
I washed that to put barley tea in,
and you went and stuck flowers in it!
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- Did you eat?
- Not yet.
What were you doing that you haven't eaten yet?
I was waiting to eat with you.
You sweet talker.
- Let's go inside.
- Okay.
The yard looks clean, doesn't it?
It does look nice.
- Good job.
- Yeah.
You could've called ahead.
I would've made something for you.
Noodles are fine.
I'm still having no luck with the deposit.
Tell the landlord to wait a bit longer.
If worst comes to worst,
I'll just put the shop up for sale.
You said you'd buy the house back.
Now the shop's on the market too?
I'll figure it out.
- Do you think you can?
- I'll just have to find a way.
When will you have it?
I feel terrible making excuses every time.
What about me? Aren't you sorry?
I gave up on feeling sorry for you
because there's just no end to it.
I'm sorry you got stuck with me as a mother.
You better pay me back.
It's not a gift.
You know what this money means to me, right?
I earned this money on boats,
up mountains, and in the mud.
Of course, I know.
But...
I saw him on your show.
I'm done.
Mom.
Did you know I hit my highest ratings yet?
I'm practically the MVP of our show right now.
Producer Kyung loves me,
and the executive producer
absolutely adores me.
Really?
Well, they should be giving you a raise,
not just showering you with compliments.
Of course they will!
Who do you think I am?
I'm Park Hyun Ok's daughter, Ju Yi Jae!
Girl, you are all talk.
- Leave it, I'll do it.
- No, get out of the way.
- I said I got it.
- Move.
Mom, since when are you so strong?
- I've got it.
- What've you been eating?
What else would I eat? Just rice.
Don't you dare tell Mom about this.
I need extra pay to keep quiet.
You got caught and you're still this shameless?
Pleasure doing business with you.
[2011 Bunam Youth Film Festival Grand Prize
Winner, Ju Yi Jae]
[Gyeongseong Love Song]
This cold raw fish soup is on the house.
Look at you. You've gotten even more handsome.
It just makes me so happy
to see you after all this time.
Right?
I'm so happy too.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. It's not much.
Enjoy your meal. Okay.
Eat up, son.
You too, Mom.
You love wrapping it in white kimchi.
Here, open up.
- Ah.
Is it good?
Everything tastes better when you feed me.
It's been forever since I had raw fish.
That's just because you eat fancy now, right?
Eating with you is the best thing
in the world to me.
I'm sorry I didn't keep in touch more often.
We can just see each other like this now.
I'm just thrilled you're back in Korea.
So today,
it's my treat.
Here, open up.
- Here, careful.
- Ah.
Soo Bin...
is it still too hard for you to visit?
Maybe next time.
Your dad's...
not doing this because he hates you.
Mom, please.
Okay. I'm sorry, son.
Stop apologizing...
and get in.
Promise me you'll call
when you come down again.
I'll be waiting.
I will.
Get home safe.
[No Jaywalking]
- I'm sorry.
I'm not going.
You promised! We'd make movies together!
What does that matter?
What the hell are you doing?
Are you okay?
I just got a little dizzy.
Hey.
I eat carrots now.
I realized I couldn't be a picky eater
if I wanted to survive in this job.
Enough time has passed
for us to change this much.
But why are there...
some things that never get better?
Why do the good memories fade,
but the bad ones...
stay so vivid?
Maybe that's why we have to hold on
to the good ones even tighter.
That's why I'm here.
Yes, Producer.
I just need to head to Jeonju Station, right?
[Gyeongseong Love Song]
The title is "Gyeongseong Love Song."
Nan Young is a gisaeng
who dreams of becoming a poet.
But after her best friend is shot and killed,
she lives only for revenge.
[Written and Directed
by Ju Yi Jae & Woo Soo Bin]
Then, a man appears before her
like it's destiny.
None other than the rich young master,
Moo Gyeom!
You have to have the rich heir.
Poetry, booze, and women.
A guy who just enjoys life
without a single care in the world.
How could anyone not fall for a guy like that?
But here's the twist.
He's actually a freedom fighter
hiding behind a playboy mask!
Hold on, it gets better.
The most shocking truth is...
He's the exact enemy
Nan Young has been hunting her whole life.
Revenge or love, that is the question.
- Bang!
- Ugh.
So... does someone end up dying?
Someone has to.
A romance needs to be tragic.
I prefer happy endings, though.
[Gyeongseong Love Song]
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Remember when I came to you
about making movies?
How could I forget?
You showed up with no money, no bags,
just that one script in your hand.
Exactly.
Even when things got tough
and I wanted to quit,
I held onto that script to keep going.
That's why Yi Jae gave it to me.
She was holding onto me so I wouldn't give up,
asking me to keep dreaming together.
I realized it way too late.
And that's exactly
why you worked like crazy to get here.
Is that why I lost her?
I made it this far because of that script,
but maybe having it in my hands is
the exact reason Yi Jae ended up
giving up on everything.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Just eat your food.
I gave the "Gyeongseong Love Song" script
back to her.
- But she hasn't called me yet.
- What?
Please.
Hold on. What if...
No.
She knows how much that script means to us.
There's no way she'd throw it out.
But the bottom line is,
you don't actually have it on you right now.
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's it. I'm heading back.
I haven't found soft tofu stew
better than LA's anyway,
and I'm sick of you.
I'm officially giving up my dream
of going independent right here.
I'm leaving. I'm out.
You scanned it, right?
Me?
No.
Man.
You're taking this joke way too far.
You're kidding, right?
Just a little closer.
- See you later.
See you later.
Congratulations on your wedding.
Thank you.
These are gorgeous.
Orders just came down from headquarters.
We're going with Plan B.
Cut!
Okay.
Alright, we're breaking for lunch.
- Enjoy your lunch.
- Enjoy.
How did that take look?
Thank you.
- Five rolls of gimbap.
- Yeah.
Wait, what? Five rolls?
That Go Sang Yeon...
I grabbed yours for you, though.
And you should eat in the van.
The CEO specifically said
you have to eat inside.
- She told me to tell you...
- I'm eating outside.
But that dress is so uncomfortable.
Just get in and eat with me...
I could do a backflip in this thing.
Don't worry about me and go eat
before Sang Yeon gobbles everything up.
But your dress...
What?
Never mind.
I seriously don't want to film right now.
Sorry?
Is it so wrong to not want to shoot?
No,
that's completely fair.
You didn't get one of these?
Yeah, they said they ran out.
That jerk, Go Sang Yeon.
- Want some?
- I'm good.
I can't finish a whole roll anyway.
Just eat it.
My arm's getting tired.
Well...
Thank you.
You're bored too, right?
Gang Member Number 3.
I actually need to get going.
What?
You're done right after lunch?
Lucky you.
I actually can't leave right now
because of you, Ha Na-nim.
Adding "nim" makes me sound like God.
I'm Buddhist.
Just call me Ha Na.
Right.
That thing you're sitting on is...
my bike.
- Hop on, then.
- What?
Could you just take me for a quick spin?
Come on, I gave you my gimbap.
Just ten minutes.
Or five?
I'll call it even for the food.
Sweet!
Like this?
It's just like "A Moment of Romance" today!
What? A moment of what?
That Hong Kong movie...
Never mind.
Whoa, whoa!
Did you see that? I almost just died!
If I'd looked back, we'd both be dead.
- Hold on tight.
- Okay!
I finally feel alive again.
Thanks, Yu Geon.
Chae Yeon!
Ha Na.
Where have you been?
I've been looking everywhere for you!
She actually remembered my name.
Look at the state of you!
What is that on your head?
A helmet.
Wait.
The helmet...
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Producer Jaden just landed.
- What?
- Producer Jaden just landed.
Should I book that sushi place
in Cheongdam for the meeting?
- Why there?
- You said it was the best sushi of your life.
Why would I take a Korean-American
to my all-time favorite sushi place?
Word is he likes Korean food.
Book a traditional Korean restaurant.
- One that has really nice side dishes.
- Yes.
- And about the meeting with Writer Noh...
- Hey!
Ugh, just text it to me.
Who on earth named this thing
the "Stairway to Heaven?"
I'm staring straight at the gates of hell.
Anyway, where did Ha Na run off to
in the middle of all this?
Well...
she was looking for someone.
- And?
- So I found him for her.
Just tell me who it is!
Well...
Are we playing "Twenty Questions" right now?
Who are you?
I came to return this.
Something smells really good.
I just got off my shift at a BBQ joint.
By the way,
the sunset from up here is gorgeous.
How long have you been waiting here?
You literally see me up there every single day.
How are you not a fan?
How did you even find my place?
From this.
[Sim Yu Geon]
But my address isn't even on this.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Sorry? Thinking about what?
Riding on your bike.
I've never felt anything like that before.
Could you take me for another spin sometime?
Sure.
But...
why are you doing this?
What's wrong with that?
It's just...
you're kind of scaring me.
I'm scaring you?
Well, it's just...
This kind of stuff always works on TV.
Works? What do you mean?
I guess that only works on TV.
Look, as you probably know,
I'm actually amazing at everything else.
I can do forward rolls,
shoot a gun, ride horses,
and even jump off high buildings.
- Right.
- But...
I have absolutely no idea how to make friends.
Which is why I don't have any.
Are you saying
you want to be friends with me?
I guess...
Yeah.
Then let's be...
friends.
You mean it?
Yeah.
Then consider this
a gift to celebrate our new friendship.
Huh?
I...
I have to go now, friend.
Bye.
Bye, friend.
Seems like she knows
exactly how to make friends.
It's been a while, Jaden.
Hello, CEO An.
Or should I be calling you CEO Seo now?
Whatever you're comfortable with.
I never thought I'd see the day
you'd be smiling in front of me.
Did that day come sooner than you expected?
You've grown a thick skin.
It's nice to see
you've lost some of that innocence.
Let's order first.
Talking business on an empty stomach
makes me nauseous.
Here, let me.
So, you're saying you're open to co-producing?
Since I'm starting out in unfamiliar territory,
I wanted someone I could trust to guide me.
And you think I'm the right person for that?
You're the one who reached out to me first.
How naive.
You have no idea what I might demand.
Let's save the project talk
for when the first draft is ready.
I'm actually much more interested
in the off-screen drama.
How much are you willing to share with me?
I'd be happy to share everything I know.
I heard there's quite a backstory
to that script.
Rumors say it involves a first love?
That only applies
if we're official partners, though.
Since we're not there yet,
I need to be a bit careful.
I'll reach out as soon
as the first draft is ready.
Sounds good.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Why'd he come all this way
if he wasn't coming in?
Maybe he's just uncomfortable?
Uncomfortable? About what?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to walk on eggshells around me.
You said CEO An is our best bet anyway.
Yeah, for now, she is.
And I'm not walking on eggshells.
I'm actually really pissed off right now.
You need to get that script back from Yi Jae.
- Why?
- What do you mean, why?
You went on TV and blabbed all about a script
without even having a first draft.
Every single person I meet brings it up.
CEO An even brought up the first love rumor.
Don't tell me...
In Uk.
Yes, I said it was me.
I told her I was your first love.
[Yi Jae]
Yeah, hello?
Where are you? Get to Sangam right now.
Producer Kyung wants a meeting.
I'll text you the address.
Why are you going to a meeting?
I have no idea why
you're even going to a meeting. Whatever.
Just go
and make sure that script is still alive.
- Yes, boss.
- Right.
Please get out.
My phone!
It's still early, let's get another round.
That's enough. Your taxi's here.
- Here!
- Who called it?
- I did.
- You shouldn't have!
Let's get one more round.
Back to your wife you go.
I don't want to go home
- because of my wife.
- But you love her!
Hey! I do not!
- Make sure he gets home safe.
- Sure.
- Alright.
- Seriously...
I'm not going home!
Wait, what?
I thought we were having a meeting.
- Huh?
- Is everyone gone?
It's over.
Why are you so late?
You call this late?
I even printed out the prep sheets.
And I called him, too.
"Him?" Why did you bring a dog? Where is he?
Woo Soo Bin. Director Ian Woo.
Oh, him.
Hey, he already agreed to do the show,
so we're good.
I'll take it from here, so you stay out of it.
Since when do you handle things yourself?
Did you even have a meeting today?
Wait, did you just call me
to be your designated driver?
Designated driver?
Ding, ding, ding.
Your driving is more comfortable
than my own mattress.
I'm counting on you.
- She can't drive.
- Excuse me?
She's been drinking.
Huh?
You had drinks with me, remember?
I'm so dizzy.
How am I even here?
Why am I here?
How did I get here? So dizzy...
You were completely fine a second ago.
What are you talking about?
This is why day drinking is the worst.
I guess I do smell alcohol.
Is he always like this?
What?
No, well...
he does make me work when he's drunk,
dumps his crap on me,
- and uses me as his driver, but...
- What?
Hey! Ju Yi Jae!
Still, he's not a bad guy.
We've been friends since college,
- almost a decade?
- Right?
No. He really is a bad guy.
Excuse me,
what do you think
you're doing right in front of me?
Then what exactly are you doing to Yi Jae?
What?
What are you talking about?
I already know everything.
Should I say it,
or do you want to tell her yourself?
They're canceling "Here Comes Yi Jae"
in the upcoming revamp.
Can't you just do a better job, man?
People are saying the producer is
riding the reporter's coattails.
Just keep the ratings up.
Even better if we hit a record high.
Do that, and I'll make sure
your job is safe no matter what.
I'll do my best.
I was just...
Forget it.
I'll hear it straight from him.
Get in.
What?
I said, get in.
Okay.
I thought you were drinking.
I didn't drink.
Give me a straight answer.
This is my mom's car!
I'm still making payments...
What? Am I getting fired?
I think I'm going to throw up.
Hey, this...
And you totally used me.
Hey.
Hey!
Look, I'm sorry.
But I had to save my own skin...
No, that's not what I meant...
Hey, watch the road!
Watch out!
Since when did you write me off?
I know I could get fired at any moment,
but this is crossing the line.
Hey, Yi Jae...
just listen to me.
Hey, where are you going?
What?
You and I are done as of today.
- Get out.
- Huh?
I said, get out!
Hey, hold on a second.
- Get the hell out!
- No!
Get out!
Oh, no...
I didn't...
- Come here.
- I'll sew it up for you.
Come here. Get out!
Get out!
Hey.
My keys...
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey!
No!
You crazy...
Hey! My keys...
Where are they?
Hey! Ju Yi Jae!
I feel like...
I've been rushing through life,
just putting out fires as they come.
Who would've thought
a job I took just for the money
would turn into weeks, months, and years?
That alone is impressive.
That's why so many places want to book you.
But...
I'm not irreplaceable.
Who else is going to show up
on "Here Comes Yi Jae" if you don't?
You're right.
I gave it the wrong title.
I said "Here Comes Yi Jae!"
and now I'm just gone.
I didn't love the job,
but it meant a lot to me.
It put food on the table and paid off my debts.
You jerk.
Why do you keep following me around?
You won't even let me cry in peace.
Ju Yi Jae.
Now I see why you said
being pathetic is the worst.
Because it stays with you forever.
You do look...
a bit pathetic...
right now.
Not that I could ever forget you anyway.
Woo Soo Bin.
My biggest regret isn't you.
It's me.
Ian.
Let's go get some breakfast.
In Uk.
It's freezing.
I look forward to working with you.
Please stay at the hotel
just until the studio is set up.
You need to write.
You were laughing at me earlier, weren't you?
Who do you think you are,
messing with my friend?
Come on, friend. Let's go.
When you're stuck in the same house
and spending all day together,
you naturally catch feelings,
and it turns into a hot, R-rated romance.
What are you even hesitating for?
Looks like...
we're about to do it right now.