(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Scenes with child actors
followed production guidelines.)
So this is a report from the National
Agricultural Science and Technology?
It's a soil sample analysis report.
Let's open it.
Man, this looks complicated.
So what does it say?
This...
is not an external invasive organism.
So that means no one deliberately
spread it?
That's right.
It's a native microbial population...
commonly found in local soil.
So...
that means it was already in Yeonri-ri
to begin with?
Yes. Under normal conditions,
it stays inactive.
But under certain
environmental conditions,
it rapidly multiplies.
So, something about the soil
in Yeonri-ri changed?
It wasn't a natural change,
but an artificially altered
environmental condition.
For it to spread across
the entire village,
it would have to be a pretty major change.
I'm telling Mom.
Go ahead.
That tickles. Stop.
Is anyone home?
Ms. Cho Mi Ryeo.
Yes?
Is Ms. Cho Mi Ryeo home?
Registered mail delivery.
Okay.
Yes, that's me.
You are Ms. Cho Mi Ryeo, correct?
This is a special court delivery.
Please sign here.
From the court to me?
Yes, right here.
Here you go.
Goodbye.
A lawsuit to recover a loan?
Where are you?
Pay me back, you wench.
You thought I wouldn't find you?
You thought hiding in some rural town
in Korea would keep me from finding you?
What's this? It's registered mail.
- Is it for me?
- No, give it back.
Is it for you?
No.
This...
is study material for Ji Gu's class.
They send things like that in the mail
these days?
Yes,
since it can't be leaked carelessly.
You don't need to worry about it.
(EP10)
(Before the Soil Dries, The Miracle Fades)
Wow, this is crazy.
Dad, look at this.
Wow. Are these the peas
you planted at school?
They've grown a lot.
You two will be harvesting these soon.
Even the sprouts look like you two.
Older and younger brothers.
Dad.
I think I've got a talent for farming.
Peas sprout quickly in the early stages,
so anyone can grow them this much.
Seong Ji Gu. Are you jealous?
Because mine's way bigger than yours?
It's not about height.
The stem needs to be strong
to last longer.
Should we give it nutrients or something?
Yes.
Dad, I want books.
Get me every book
from growth conditions...
to pests on peas.
Ji Gu. Reading books alone
won't make the peas grow.
(Complaint)
(Amount 30,000 dollars)
In two weeks,
I have to pay back this amount?
What do I do?
Unbelievable.
I know where you are.
Don't even think about running,
and pay up.
If you don't, be ready to go to jail.
(Delete)
Honey, I just need to start
the rice cooker?
Well...
I'll do it.
Just wait.
Honey, nothing's wrong, is it?
- I'll be right there.
- Do I just press start?
Hold on.
The aroma is sweet and nice, right?
Yes.
The apples...
are really red and beautiful.
These are Gamhong apples...
from the orchard we visited before.
They have such a beautiful color,
so they look great on tarts or cakes.
They taste great too.
No wonder.
Gamhong apples taste good
even with the skin on.
You're just cutting apples.
Do you really need to be this close?
Dad, don't you have anything better to do?
I've got plenty to do. Keeping an eye
on you is my job.
What do you mean?
We're in the middle of developing
a new menu.
- Right?
- Right.
I heard you like sweets.
We're trying to make a sweet dessert
using apples.
You're so scrawny and pale.
If only you were big and solid
like some people.
Dad, Ji Cheon is such a solid,
dependable person.
What do you know?
I'm home.
My deer is home.
My lovely deer, have some apples.
Thanks.
Is it good?
It's sweet.
You're on my side, right?
But what are you doing here
while they are working?
Come to our room right now.
Go home now.
Stop smiling and go.
You think being handsome is enough?
Keep working on those sweet recipes.
- Go. Hurry.
- Let's go to our room now.
- You think being handsome is enough?
- Why do you care?
Rest well.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
You see how well I folded these?
I've been an expert on folding clothes...
since I was in the army.
You went through a lot while I was gone.
While you were gone, I finally realized...
that the word "wife" comes from...
the meaning of "the sun of a household."
Without you, the warmth in the house
was gone.
It didn't feel like our home anymore.
It's all talk.
Not at all.
I want us to do everything together now.
Housework and the kids.
You know cabbage seedlings?
If you plant one only,
even a small gust can break it.
That's why you must plant them
in pairs, side by side.
It's the same with a married couple.
Things that are too heavy
to carry alone...
are manageable
when you carry them together.
Whether it's about Ji Cheon...
or something else I don't know about,
don't carry it alone anymore.
Okay?
Honey.
I'm your husband.
If anything gets too hard,
let me know everything, okay?
Okay.
There's nothing wrong.
I'm just a bit tired.
You're tired?
Yes.
I'm fine.
(Mat Story)
An unidentified fungal outbreak?
They say farming depends on god.
It seems god is really helping us
this time.
There's no better excuse
than a natural disaster.
Keep a close eye on Manager Seong Tae Hun.
What's Seong Tae Hun going to find...
just by looking through a microscope?
The land is dying.
What could he possibly do
to save the land?
That punk. All he has is his height.
I'm sorry.
You can't leave things up to god only.
If something goes wrong later,
god won't protect you too.
I'm not sure what you mean.
I've been loyal to you this whole time...
Keep a close eye on Seong Tae Hun.
And don't think your position...
is any safer than his.
Yes, sir.
Seong Tae Hun.
(Yeonri-ri)
There's such a thing as a jinx.
Don't city people know that?
Chief, have you teamed up...
with that Mat Story lackey now?
What are you talking about?
Can't you see that...
I'm working day and night for Yeonri-ri?
Just let me know if you need any help.
I'll join you.
Has anything...
changed in Yeonri-ri
compared to last year?
Even small things are fine.
Please tell me everything.
Yes.
There was something really shocking.
Yes, that did happen.
What is it?
Did the soil temperature change?
Or maybe the groundwater level...
You know that house with a persimmon tree
in the back hill?
Pardon?
Have you noticed anything unusual...
around Yeonri-ri lately?
Could that be it?
What is it? Tell me.
The cow at the house with a persimmon tree
in the back hill...
had twins.
They even handed out rice cakes.
Twins?
Is this about their cow having twins?
Yes.
He doesn't understand how special that is.
Then...
Yes, Cheon Ji's place.
Cheon Ji's place?
- Yes, their hen.
- Yes?
That hen...
lays three eggs a day.
- For real?
- Yes.
So...
You're headed somewhere?
I just want to be alone.
That man coming here
was the biggest change here.
But if you blend pumpkin only,
isn't it too thick and heavy?
Yes, it is a bit thick,
but I intentionally reduced the sweetness.
Our drinks are all based
on healthy recipes.
My mom used to be really sick.
I see.
But she's okay now.
She went through cancer treatment before.
During chemotherapy, your mouth gets sore,
so you can't really eat anything else.
It stings.
I see.
(Cinnamon powder)
What if we add a bit of this?
The aftertaste is clean.
And it really cuts through the heaviness.
Cinnamon also helps with bloating...
and digestion.
It might be good to add turmeric too.
It gives a nice yellow color...
and has anti-inflammatory benefits.
We don't have turmeric here,
but I have some at home.
Do you want to try making it
together later?
My goodness.
What is this smell?
I smell something beautiful.
The flower of youth is blooming in full.
Look, Hye Sun.
I don't know anything.
What's blooming?
What are you talking about?
I didn't see anything.
Right. I didn't see anything,
so I don't know anything.
I don't know anything.
My goodness. Mi Ryeo ran away from home,
and you shared a few meals together.
So...
you've gotten attached now?
It tastes okay, right?
Yes, I think it's good.
Here.
Take just one sip each.
I put a lot of effort into making this.
Why does it look like this?
Are you trying to kill me?
Ji Cheon, is this apple juice?
Apple?
Is it an Aori apple?
Come on.
You loaded this with sugar.
Hey. There's spinach and carrots
that you hate the most.
Give me some more.
More?
Carrots?
Something in the environment
that changed suddenly...
The beginning is what matters most.
Let's go back and re-examine everything
step by step.
Let's look carefully.
What changed?
Just wait until I find it.
Nothing seems to have changed
in the past few days.
The soil in the village seems fine.
What could it be?
What's the source of the problem?
Mom.
Mother.
Maybe I should quit studying...
and just become a farmer.
There's not that much difference...
between studying and farming.
Don't think of them as your kids.
Think of them as boarders.
It's easier that way.
Sure.
If that's what you want to do,
that's good.
What?
Mom, did you hear me?
I said I want to be a farmer
instead of studying.
Yes, I heard you. That's fine too.
But take your time thinking
about your future.
Should I ask Dad for a field of my own?
These days, smart farming is the trend.
You can just press buttons
on your phone like a game.
Then water comes out,
and temperature adjusts...
It's insanely easy.
You can learn how to be a farmer
on YouTube.
You little...
Seong Ji Sang.
What?
Why are you suddenly talking about
becoming a farmer?
What on earth is going on
in that head of yours?
- You make me so angry! Hey!
- What?
- Why you little...
Hey.
- Don't come near me.
- Stop right there.
Seong Ji Sang.
I told you to do your homework.
Why are you tagging along?
Mom.
It's because he has a girlfriend.
What?
He's tagging along,
hoping to run into her.
Right?
That's not it.
You're speaking of a girlfriend
in Korea as well?
What will you become when you grow up?
I told you. A farmer.
You think farming is easy?
Farmers need to study
and know their stuff too.
Why do you always yell at me?
He's so immature.
Right?
What's your dream?
My dream?
For you...
to grow up healthy...
and become good people.
No.
That's our dream.
I meant your dream.
Don't you have one?
I used to.
But...
it's been so long, so...
I don't know.
Then you can start thinking about it now.
Now?
Yes.
Ji Sang wants to be a farmer,
and I want to be a scientist.
If you start now,
you can achieve your dream later too.
Yes.
Thank you, son.
All right.
Let's go.
Wait up.
I don't get it.
No matter how much I look,
I just can't figure it out.
There wasn't any additional fertilization,
and it hasn't even rained.
It's not pesticides,
and it's not temperature either.
The fact that it's continuously
multiplying means...
there has to be another cause.
(No decrease in mycelial activity)
What on earth is driving you?
- Let's go.
- I'm hungry.
My arm hurts.
Hurry up.
Why do I always have to do this stuff?
- Come on. You're older. Right?
- Yes.
I'm always the one carrying heavy stuff.
Hurry up. Let's go
make something good to eat.
What's for dinner?
They live here, right? Try knocking.
Knock?
No one seems to be home, right?
Mom, the tangerines. They're rolling away.
What's wrong, Mom?
- Mom.
- Boys.
Hold on. Sit down.
Didn't you hear something?
Am I wrong?
It sounded like a person's voice. No?
Mom, the tangerines...
I don't think anyone's home.
Hold on.
- Is someone out there?
- Mom.
There's no one inside.
Where did she go?
What's going on there?
What are you doing here?
Well...
Who is that woman over there?
What is she staring at?
Go stay at our place for now.
- Let's go talk to her.
- Okay.
Take your kids and go to my house.
Let's go to the chief's house.
Let's go. Hurry.
Be careful.
Who are you,
and why are you loitering
in front of that house?
The woman who lives here racked up
a huge amount of debt in Canada...
and ran away in the middle of the night.
She's a con artist...
who scammed a bunch of moms and ran off.
You know that?
The two of you.
Did you both lose half your tongues?
Why are you speaking rudely
to someone you just met?
You must live around here.
You know the woman who lives here, right?
Where is she?
If you're here to collect a debt,
handle it quietly by calling her.
Why are you hanging around
someone else's neighborhood,
someone else's house like this?
No one lives here anymore,
so just get lost.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Why are you behaving so uncivilized?
Did you just push me?
That was a mistake. It was dangerous.
You should leave now.
If you stay any longer,
this won't end well.
I don't think I can leave.
My arm isn't moving.
I think I should call the police.
What did you just say?
I don't know what's going on,
but in situations like this,
you fight with numbers.
- Got it?
- Yes.
I'd rather fight one-on-one.
Shoo. Go away.
Shoo.
You heard that?
This is how things work in Yeonri-ri.
An eye for an eye.
You get back what you give!
Do you want to fight?
Do you?
Unbelievable.
Hold on. This is ridiculous.
I don't believe this.
What's wrong with her?
I'm so scared.
Hey, Jessica.
- Where are you going?
- Jessica.
Come back here.
- Sisters.
- I'll just...
- You got here too late.
- Did we? It's okay.
I was scared.
You got scared?
- Don't worry.
- You've been through a lot.
You haven't eaten dinner yet, right?
I'll make you something real quick.
Just wait a bit.
Hey.
Are you breathing okay?
Slowly.
What happened?
My kids...
I wanted to give them better education...
so I got greedy.
After going to Canada,
I felt bad about asking my husband
for more money.
Then...
I was told there was a good opportunity
to invest the money.
So I took on debt.
But it was a scam.
Those scums.
Of all people, how could they scam you?
Calm down.
I never thought things would
get out of hand like this.
In the parents' group,
that scammer borrowed
even more money in my name...
and ran off.
Then they should be going after
that scammer.
Why are they coming after
an innocent person?
But it is true...
that I borrowed money from them
and couldn't pay it back.
Goodness.
What are we going to do?
Here.
A lawsuit has already been filed.
I could even be arrested for fraud.
What are we going to do?
Here.
Have you talked to your husband
about this?
But this...
I mean...
I basically ran away
and came back to Korea.
But my husband...
was assigned to Yeonri-ri.
He's trying so hard
just to hold everything together.
How can I tell him?
What am I going to do? I just want to die.
That's nonsense.
I'm sure there is a way out of this.
What am I going to do now?
I'm sure there's a way.
You've been through a lot.
Fifteen days since the fungus
was discovered.
(Native microbial community,
not natural, artificial change)
I still haven't found the cause.
Wait.
It's not here.
There's...
no fungus.
It's the same soil,
but there's no fungus in here.
If this wall reduced the impact,
then was something carried by the wind?
(Yeonri-ri)
As we get closer
to the neighboring village,
the fungus clearly decreases.
Why did it spread only in Yeonri-ri?
Hold it tight.
- Like this?
- Yes.
If I pull too hard,
your eyes will end up
looking narrow and sharp.
You look more handsome with round eyes.
Okay.
Thank you.
When we came here for a picnic before,
it was full of pine trees.
But now it's completely bare.
Do you remember what you told me here
back then?
You said...
your love would stay green all year,
like those pine trees.
But they're gone now.
Who knew...
they'd cut them all down in just a year?
- Exactly.
- Where did they all go?
So this didn't change naturally.
It was cleared all at once
with heavy equipment?
An artificial environmental change
instead of a natural one.
I found it.
What was that?
Eureka.
Isn't that Mr. Seong from Mat Story?
Mr. Seong?
What could it be?
Pine trees.
There used to be a pine forest
behind the village, right?
Yes. It was dense
before they cleared it all out.
Does that have something
to do with the fungus?
What about the neighboring village?
They didn't cut down their pine trees?
That area wasn't part of
the development project.
What about the pine trees?
It was the pine pollen.
The pollen naturally drifting
from the pine forest...
was acting as a natural disinfectant.
It kept the fungus from growing.
But once the pine trees were cut down,
the fungus spread freely.
My goodness.
We destroyed the village's shield
over a bit of money.
We found the cause.
Hurry.
Good work.
Get some rest now.
Hello, sir.
It's me, Ju Hyeong.
You said you have a distant relative
who runs a nursery, right?
Can you ask him if he can gather...
pine resin and pollen for us?
Yes.
All right. Bye.
Hello? It's the Yeonri-ri village chief.
Do you have any pine resin powder?
Everything you can get.
Pine resin, pine trees...
Yes.
Who else is there?
Wow.
Yeon Su's family. I'll ask them.
It looks like...
she was just trying to educate her kids,
unfairly got scammed,
and took a huge hit.
So, here's what I'm thinking.
We still have money left
in the women's association fund, right?
Let's use that first to put out
the immediate fire.
That's what I propose.
Hey.
Do you know how hard we worked for that?
At the last bazaar,
I was flipping pancakes all day...
and ended up covering my body
with pain patches. Don't you remember?
We saved that for when something big
happens in the village.
If we give it all away at once,
isn't that a problem?
- She's right.
- What will we do?
Right.
Is it such a waste to put food
in a family's mouth?
What's she saying now?
Why are you bringing food
and family into this now?
If she's not family, then what is she?
Ok Rae.
You remember when Mak Rae completely
ruined their field?
What did Mr. Seong do?
He didn't say a word
about his ruined field.
He looked after Mak Rae first.
Yes, I know that too.
What about now?
He's running himself ragged...
trying to save the land.
Is it right for us to just look out
for ourselves like this?
Besides, we're not giving it for free.
We're paying back a debt we owe.
You don't think I know that?
I just had to say it.
Since they came to Yeonri-ri,
they're one of us.
They're family now.
You ladies are the best.
But do you think that Mat Story lady...
will just accept the money
if we give it to her?
Shouldn't we have a proper reason?
She won't accept it otherwise.
Since it's for the happiness
of Yeonri-ri people,
we can call it the Happiness Fund.
- Yes.
- That sounds great.
Come on. The Happiness Fund?
Do you have any other ideas?
That sounds suspicious.
Then do you have a better idea?
Let's hear it.
There are tons of names for grants.
Just put some words together.
How so?
- Yeonri-ri.
Settlement.
Support fund.
Settlement support fund.
Why are you mumbling? I can't hear you.
The Yeonri-ri Settlement Support Fund.
That's perfect.
Just say we forgot to give it
when they first moved here.
That's a great idea.
It's so sophisticated.
Did you just come back from Seoul?
Okay. Talk it through a bit more.
All right.
I love you so much, Nam Hye Sun.
You know my insurance money?
Withdraw $20,000 and transfer it to me.
$20,000? Why?
Is there someone else?
Im Ju Hyeong.
You talk too much.
Do you want to skip dinner starting today?
Just send it.
All right.
Why does she need $20,000?
What is it? Is something wrong?
I guess she wants to buy something.
My goodness.
You were talking as if...
you'd grab even the stars and moon
for your wife.
Is it something really expensive?
It's not that. It's not me who's paying.
It's my wife's insurance money.
Never mind.
If it's what my Hye Sun wants,
I won't ask any questions.
Will this be enough?
There's no other way
except this natural treatment.
Right. We can't let the land die.
The land is Yeonri-ri's lifeline.
This will suppress the fungus.
What's going on out of the blue?
(Yeonri-ri Village Hall)
- Goodness.
- You're here.
Was there a women's association
meeting today?
You should've told me sooner.
You're here now. That's what matters.
Have a seat.
Hello.
Well...
Here.
Yeonri-ri Settlement Happiness
Support Fund?
What's this?
We should've given this to you
when you first arrived,
but I just forgot.
It's the money we saved up,
selling cabbage,
and running bazaars.
Come on.
It's something everyone gets
when they first move here.
Right, Seon Ja?
That's right. I got it too.
That's just how Yeonri-ri is.
Right, sisters?
Right.
Everyone gets it.
I've lived here my whole life,
but for this land to have a future,
new people have to come
and put down roots.
That's a great line. Applaud.
Right. That's the New Roots Support Fund.
No, it's the Mak Rae Support Fund.
It's a fund for the happiness
of Yeonri-ri, right?
The Happiness Support Fund.
The official name is...
Yeonri-ri Settlement Happiness
Support Fund.
- Take it.
- No, I can't.
Come on.
Just accept it. I got it too.
Just accept it.
I got it too.
It's okay. Take it.
But...
This is too much.
I can't accept this much.
Come on.
Don't say anything and just take it, okay?
No, I can't.
Ms. Cho Mi Ryeo.
Thank you.
All right. It's late,
but we sincerely congratulate you
on settling in Yeonri-ri.
Applaud.
Welcome to our village.
You're one of us now.
Don't even think about going
anywhere else.
Of course.
We're one family now.
- One family.
- Yes.
Family.
- That's great.
- Family.
We're family.
($31,453 transfer completed
to Kim Hyeon Ju)
The payment's been confirmed.
The debt...
is fully paid now.
All we wanted was our money back.
I hate wasting time getting tangled up
in things like this.
So I hope I never hear from you again.
(A lawsuit to recover a loan)
It's resolved now,
but how will I ever repay this kindness?
Be gentle.
If it gets blown away in the wind,
it'll all be for nothing.
I know.
Goodness.
You're spraying it onto your face
instead of the ground.
Look who's talking.
What?
Is that so?
The fields of Yeonri-ri...
will recover for sure.
A miracle isn't something
that just falls from the sky.
It comes from the hands of the one
who brings the land back to life.
A miracle...
If that miracle happens,
you're much tougher than me.
You're the one who'll save Yeonri-ri
to the end.
I'll give you that, Seong Tae Hun.
You mean that?
If I don't,
would I be out here doing this with you?
Cross.
Here.
I added some honey
to the ginger tea. Drink.
That feels much better.
Pine pollen got into my mouth.
I spat it out, but it just kept coming.
Honey.
Is there...
anything I can do for Yeonri-ri?
You?
Why do you ask out of the blue?
Just because...
I received so much kindness...
from the people here.
Honestly,
I thought they'd treat us...
like outsiders...
and push us away.
But I was wrong.
They treat us so well.
I feel the same way.
While you were away,
the village chief and the members
of the women's association...
took turns bringing side dishes every day,
so the kids wouldn't go hungry.
They did?
The things you'd have to pay for
in Seoul...
are just given out of kindness.
I think...
we ended up in a really strange village.
It's coming back to life.
Our field is back to life too.
It's good now.
- We did it.
- It's okay now.
We're good.
It's back to life.
We did it.
We're good.
I did it.
Seong Tae Hun and I...
watered it, and sprayed the powder.
Seong Tae Hun and I did it.
I did it.
How could this be? This is great news.
If it weren't for you, we would've been
in big trouble.
We almost plowed everything up...
and ruined the entire year's harvest.
You're the true savior of Yeonri-ri.
If we hadn't listened to him,
who knows what would've happened.
You're right.
We're sorry, and thank you.
I'll treat you with respect from now on.
You're the best.
The best.
Seong Tae Hun.
You're the best, Mr. Seong.
All right.
Settle down, everyone.
Mr. Seong did a great thing for us today,
so we must treat him.
Come over to my place tonight.
Bring the kids too.
Are you cooking an entire cow tonight?
Just a cow? I'll cook a hen too.
Are you ready?
We're ready.
Mr. Seong.
Come hungry tonight.
Thank you, everyone.
Honestly,
I know it wasn't easy...
to trust me and wait.
I'm just an outsider, after all.
Even if it was the chief's request.
You're the one who saved Yeonri-ri's land.
Today, you're the star.
I'm saying this loud and clear.
I, Im Ju Hyeong, chose him.
This man is a resident of Yeonri-ri
from now on.
You got that?
Yes.
Seong Tae Hun.
Yeonri-ri is a fascinating village.
No matter where you are or what
you're doing, everyone knows everything.
Right.
We probably even know how many spoons
the neighbor has.
So it felt awkward at first.
There was no place to hide.
It can feel unfamiliar and uncomfortable
for people from Seoul.
But these days, I find myself
looking into others first.
Grandma Deok Rae...
gets wrinkles around her eyes...
when she smiles, and she looks so kind.
When Grandma Ok Rae gets angry,
the line between her brows...
is so sharp like it was drawn
with a ruler. It makes her seem lively.
What about Grandma Mak Rae?
Grandma Mak Rae...
When she eats...
and gets food on her face while smiling,
it feels like sunlight spreading.
You really studied them in detail.
Dong Sik from the hardware store
and Seon Ja too.
It's like everyone carves...
their own life into their face.
There's nothing fake about anyone.
But...
among all of them, your face
has the most to look at.
Like how the tip of your nose turns red
when you're cold,
or how your lips tremble slightly
when you talk.
I can't seem to look away from them.
It feels like I'm reading a sentence
that I want to keep just to myself.
What?
What kind of sentence could there be
on a face like mine?
Your hands are warm.
Mine are freezing.
Let me borrow your hand for a moment.
I find your face interesting too.
Do you know?
When...
a book is really good,
the closer you get to the last page,
the more you wish it wouldn't end.
You're like that too.
You're a book I want to read
slowly and savor.
Thanks.
What are you always so grateful about?
Just for your existence.
(MAT STORY)
(Executive Office)
Come in.
Did you call for me, sir?
You're here, Mr. Seong.
Have a seat.
I think it's time you knew.
We're planning...
to build Mat Story's third factory
on the Yeonri-ri site.
A factory?
It'll be a smart factory, so it won't
even need much manpower.
That land in Yeonri-ri...
is the perfect location.
There are new instructions
from the executive director.
Here in Yeonri-ri,
our company's new vision will take shape.
May I ask about...
the new vision you're planning?
Before I answer that,
I need you to swear
absolute loyalty to me.
I should've realized it then.
Whose heart...
the tip of that pen would
eventually be aimed.
Mr. Seong.
No, sir. We can't build a factory
on that land.
What do you mean, we can't?
The people there...
have lived for generations
trusting that land and farming it.
To them, it's not just land.
It's their livelihood, their life.
I've been there and seen it. I know.
If you build a factory there, they will...
Mr. Seong.
I know you care,
but business isn't run on feelings.
More importantly,
the villagers have already
given their consent.
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
Wait.
This is the list
for the free fertilizer distribution.
I personally...
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
This can't be.
The title should be...
Mr. Bae asked me to pass this along.
He said...
your role in the first task
is extremely important.
First task?
Yeonri-ri residents.
Mat Story is giving away...
premium fertilizer for free.
Yes, it's free. Take as much as you like.
It's okay.
Trust your village chief and take it.
Please sign here.
Please sign.
My good intentions...
(Free fertilizer distribution list
for Yeonri-ri branch)
Right here.
had become the most perfect weapon...
to destroy their lives.
(Mat Story Third Factory
Establishment Consent Form)
You did great work.
It isn't easy to go to each villager...
and collect their signatures.
Thanks to you, construction will go
very smoothly.
Just stay on my side...
and enjoy the result of this list.
I know how country people are.
They talk about being family
and being one,
but the real family you want to protect...
isn't them, right?
A miracle isn't something
that just falls from the sky.
It comes from the hands of the one
who brings the land back to life.
If that miracle happens,
you're the one who'll save Yeonri-ri
to the end.
I'll give you that.
It's coming back to life.
The time limit of the miracle...
was shorter than I expected.
This man is a resident of Yeonri-ri
from now on.
- You got that?
- Yes.
Before the soil I restored
even has time to settle,
I might have to be the one...
to end that miracle myself.
(Cabbage Your Life)
Didn't you see the news?
They're building a Mat Story factory
in Yeonri-ri.
What in the world are you talking about?
Is the company forcing you to do this?
This isn't your wrongdoing, is it?
We'll begin the land acquisition process
starting today.
Please cooperate in persuading
the villagers.
Are you really a monster?
We thought of you as family.
How could you do this to us?
You should leave.
It feels uneasy...
to see everyone including Bo Mi trying
not to make you feel uncomfortable, right?
You weren't exactly welcomed
from the beginning.
Just sell your land, Chief.
Then I won't approach anyone else.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)