[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 4]
What are you looking at?
Jiang Man.
Some people
say one thing but mean another.
They talk so tough,
but their legs tell the truth.
What a brilliant painting.
Wow.
There are way too many people here.
They're all talking and laughing,
but why do they feel so lifeless?
I'll move here.
Nice move.
Who was that?
Who threw that?
Are you blind?
Was that you?
Didn't you see me standing here?
Are you blind or what?
I'm talking to you!
You should apologize if you hit someone.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
As teacher says,
when you know you're wrong,
you must put yourself in their shoes
and understand their pain.
What you said is very true.
Thank you.
Class is starting.
Let's go.
What is all this?
Are they crazy?
[Elite Academy]
Greetings, sir.
Please take your seats.
Everyone,
in a few days,
we'll be having another exam.
So annoying.
We just got here,
and already there's an exam.
In class,
you do not speak out of turn
or show disrespect to your teacher.
You...
How could you just kill someone like that?
She was already condemned to death.
She got what she deserved.
Elite Academy took you in
to help you
wash away your sins.
As for what just happened,
just consider it her bad luck,
taking the punishment for you.
Since you're new here,
I'll give you one more chance.
If it happens again,
I won't be so forgiving.
You are all convicted sinners.
The reasons for your crimes
can all be traced back to one source.
Qin Yuren is truly cunning and ruthless.
So what this academy seeks to do
is teach you
the rites women ought to honor.
This assessment will be an essay exam.
You'll work in groups of three.
You'll each complete the exam on your own,
but the group with the highest total score
will be richly rewarded.
The group with the lowest score
will be severely punished.
Your preferred teammates
can be filled in during the exam.
All right.
Class begins now.
Open Admonitions for Women.
A woman has four virtues.
[Admonitions for Women]
First, womanly virtue.
Second, womanly speech.
Third, womanly bearing.
Fourth, womanly work.
As for womanly virtue,
it requires exceptional talent and wisdom.
As for womanly speech,
it requires a sharp tongue and eloquence.
[Strength is prized.
Women are praised for weakness]
As for womanly bearing, one must
always maintain a beautiful appearance.
[A woman must cultivate the four virtues
to establish herself]
I've read Admonitions for Women.
And it says the exact opposite.
[A woman must cultivate the four virtues
to establish herself]
The original book tells women
to be cautious and modest.
But her version tells women
to be bold and outspoken.
This academy...
Qin Yuren...
What exactly is she trying to do?
There isn't much more food
than on the first floor.
And there are so many more people.
Are we even going to get enough to eat?
One meal a day.
No wonder we're starving.
I'm getting out of here.
I have to fight my way up.
Hello, pretty ladies.
You're new here,
right?
You just came up from the first floor,
You two need something,
right?
We just got here too.
Only a few days before you.
So?
We're all new here,
so we should help each other.
Don't you think these people look
really weird?
They look
pretty dumb.
If we team up,
the exam will be a piece of cake.
Sorry,
you're a little late.
Our group of three is already full.
We can still help each other out.
You might find
some people are worth working with,
while others
should be left behind.
More help isn't always better.
Too many hands
can just get in the way.
I'm not good with strangers.
So,
I really don't like
people acting like we're close.
Let's go.
Okay.
Don't stand so close to me.
I can't stand people like you
hugging others for no reason.
Where did you get this?
In the last exam,
I got second place.
I got third place.
The teacher rewarded us.
Join us.
Good food
won't be in short supply.
What's wrong, Man?
Yanzhi.
Maybe you should
find someone else to team up with.
I'll only drag you down.
This is a death match in Lingya Tower.
It won't be like a normal exam.
If it's really about
poetry, books, rites, and music,
then that Dao would be even less reliable.
Yeah.
You're right.
Yanzhi.
Then
you should team up with those two sisters.
Those two
may seem more normal than the others,
but I'd never team up with them.
Why?
Intuition.
Those two are definitely up to no good.
What?
Do you want to stay here?
Not really.
I'm just afraid I'll be a burden to you.
Stop putting yourself down.
We promised
we'd get out of here together.
Yes.
Man.
Yeah?
How did you end up here, anyway?
What kind of crime
could a sweet girl like you
possibly commit?
Yanzhi.
Do you really want to know?
Forget it if you don't want to tell me.
It's fine.
I'll go get ready.
For tomorrow's exam,
I'll do my best.
Yes.
Don't be ridiculous!
You took the blame for her.
Everyone in this tower
is a vicious criminal.
Do you know how dangerous that is?
I know.
You told me.
Entering Lingya Tower
means almost certain death.
Master was right.
Everyone here
has committed serious crimes.
It's best to find an opportunity
to figure out their backgrounds.
Know yourself and your enemy,
and you'll know
when to advance or retreat.
The academy has rules.
After the hour of Hai,
students must not
set foot outside the dormitory.
Violators will be severely punished.
Let's go.
Come with me to see the teacher.
What is this?
This is a poison gland.
It spreads along the arm to the shoulder.
Once the poison gland reaches the neck,
and enters the back of the head,
there will be no cure.
Isn't my mother all right now?
Why
hasn't she woken up yet?
The poison in your mother's body
has only been temporarily suppressed.
But for her to fully recover,
and wake up,
we still need to find the antidote.
Yanzhi,
stop chasing after them.
Master, they...
Come with me first.
Master.
Master, what are you doing here?
While I was away,
you started acting recklessly again.
I suspect this floor...
Listen to me carefully.
Just stay on this floor.
As for the antidote,
leave it to me.
I think this floor has something to do
with my mother's antidote.
Just now,I found the same poison gland
on that student
as the one my mother had.
Did you find something out too?
Qin Yuren is meticulous.
If you act rashly,
you'll only play right into her hands.
Don't you know that?
Master, if the Tower Master
finds out you're here,
won't you be in danger too?
It's fine.
I happen to have important business here.
Recently,
there have been fewer and fewer people
going from the second floor to the third.
And the death matches on the second floor
have also been getting duller.
If this keeps up,
it's bound to upset the guests.
You want
to put Elite Academy in order.
Ever since the second floor
was handed over to Qin Yuren,
I haven't interfered at all.
If it weren't for the fact
that she can
make these tobacco paste for me,
I would never have tolerated her behavior.
Qin Yuren has always been arrogant
about her talent.
I'm afraid
she won't give in so easily.
She's been at the Elite Academy
for so long
that she really
considers herself a teacher.
Then what do you mean?
If Qin Yuren keeps
refusing to know her place,
then make her
just like those students.
This academy on the second floor...
Could it be
a place to test drugs on them?
Exactly.
Then the poison in my mother...
It must have been from an early trial.
Now it seems
Qin Yuren should have the clues.
Good.
That's great.
My mother can be saved.
Let's go.
Let's go find Qin Yuren right now.
You'll only alert her.
Besides, Lingya Tower is heavily guarded.
Once the Tower Master is alerted,
all our efforts will be for nothing.
Take the exam as usual tomorrow.
I'll find a way to help you.
As for everything else,
I'll handle it.
Master.
[First Meeting]
Master, please teach me
your strongest martial art.
I want to avenge my parents.