[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 16]
[High Art]
You're back, Yanzhi.
Shh.
How did it go?
Who was it?
Was it Wan Hongliu?
It has nothing to do with Wan Hongliu.
Not Wan Hongliu?
Then who was it?
Anyway, rest assured.
Tonight,
no one will bother us anymore.
Let's go back and get some rest,
so we can do our best
in the final round tomorrow.
My Lady,
are you satisfied this time?
I often hear my father praising you.
You certainly live up to your reputation.
Thank you for the compliment, My Lady.
I don't deserve it.
Forgive my presumption.
If you hate a female prisoner,
I can take care of her for you.
Why did you come here in person?
Is it just for amusement?
At first, I just wanted to see
what kind of person she is.
But I didn't expect
that at death's door,
she would still dare to talk back to me.
That is outrageous.
Since this female prisoner
shows no remorse,
why don't we...
No.
Let her climb.
The higher she climbs,
the harder she will fall.
You mean...
Let her finish the last round
of the death match.
I want to see
what she's really capable of.
[High Art]
Hey,
wait for me!
Hurry up!
I was worried,
so I came back.
In this Lingya Tower,
those are just illusions
meant to numb people.
The more it is like this,
the more dangerous it becomes.
They are living human beings.
They shouldn't be here
to be treated as playthings.
Do you think
they would dare to shoot the arrows?
I don't think they'd dare.
They are sisters, after all.
People who come here
are capable of anything.
If you don't believe it,
look for yourselves.
They're really ruthless.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'll bet on the Red Team
for today's three rounds.
I still have faith in Voice-Keeper.
Me too.
I wonder what you think
about this round, Miss?
I'll still bet
on the same one as last time.
Not me.
They lost points,
so we don't need to shoot.
Yeah.
So accurate.
For the Red Team,
two points deducted
for spilling the shimmering elixir,
and five points added
for hitting the jade bead.
A total of three points.
Blue Team, get ready.
It seems we need to change our plan.
If we want to beat the Red Team,
we have to shoot our arrows.
That's our only choice.
Tuya,
I'm not good at archery.
I'm afraid I'll knock it over
or hurt someone.
I'll leave the scoring to you later.
Okay.
No, I'm not sure I can do it.
Nan Yanzhi believes in us.
We must believe in ourselves too.
Okay.
Believe in ourselves.
Hit!
See?
I was right, wasn't I?
Are they really going to win?
Impossible.
I've never seen Voice-Keeper lose
in the Hall of Elegance.
You are nothing but a convicted prisoner
who cannot even leave Lingya Tower.
Why should I believe you can
help me find the real culprit?
What if I can leave this Lingya Tower?
I'm afraid you won't survive
tomorrow's death match,
let alone leave this Lingya Tower.
Alright.
How about we make a bet?
If we meet outside in the future,
I will help you find the real culprit
who killed your husband,
and you promise to do me a favor.
How about that?
What a pipe dream.
We can discuss this
after you leave Lingya Tower
and come find me.
It's a deal.
Bow.
I, Nan Yanzhi...
I, Jiang Man...
-...pray that Heaven blesses our dynasty
-with a long reign.
-May we have an abundant harvest.
-May the weather be favorable,
-and disasters be kept at bay.
Offer the shimmering elixir.
Ah!
What happened?
We were just one step away.
She must have done it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
Man.
Did you do it on purpose?
I know you two don't get along,
but you shouldn't
talk about her like that.
At this point,
she had no reason to lose her grip.
Nan Yanzhi.
You lose.
Come.
Jiang Man, get up.
Come on, take it easy.
Oh, come on.
If it weren't for her,
I might not have been able to beat you.
President Wan,
you...
Jiang Man, I've got your back.
There's no need to hide.
Guards!
Man!
Yanzhi.
Why did you do this?
What is going on?
I was right.
She betrayed us!
Man.
Is what she said true?
I'm sorry.
We've been through
life and death together,
and experienced so many
hardships to get here.
Why did you do such a thing?
I finally considered you a friend.
How could you do this
at a matter of life and death?
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry, Dao.
I let you down.
I let all of you down.
Jiang Man.
You don't need to blame yourself.
You are much more sensible
than these stubborn fools.
Don't worry. I will deliver
on what I promised you.
Wan Hongliu, you are despicable!
Chilan Tuya.
Are you jealous of me now?
I gave all of you a chance.
I'm afraid it's too late for regrets now.
If you want someone to blame,
blame yourself
for insisting on taking her side.
Man,
I don't believe what she said.
I want to hear it from you.
Tell me!
Yanzhi...
Man,
I treated you like a sister.
Didn't we agree to leave here together?
Why on earth did you do this?
I want to live.
I don't want to die.
I've had enough of living in constant fear
and going hungry
every single day.
Only by following President Wan
can I live the life I want.
This is the life I want.
This is Lingya Tower.
Get this straight.
Do you want to stay here forever?
Haha!
Lingya Tower?
Even if we get out, so what?
The world outside is
just a bigger Lingya Tower.
I have a lowly background.
I'm not like you.
No matter how hard I try,
I'm destined to be trampled on.
Now,
I just want to live
like a human before I die.
You're wrong.
Now you're truly living
like less than human.
Enough. Take them away.
Nan Yanzhi,
you have no power or influence.
You can't make any waves.
Despite your best efforts,
you fell short in the end.
Human nature is sinister.
You've finally seen it for yourself.
Wujiu.
Since you're back,
why didn't you report to me first?