[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 21]
[Virtue and Merit in Equal Splendor]
My mother was born a noblewoman.
But she ended up a prisoner
in Lingya Tower.
Then that bastard Meng Shuo defiled her.
That was how she had me.
The other women in prison looked after us.
They taught me to read and fight.
But I could only watch them
participate in the death match,
dying one by one,
and I was powerless to help.
Master.
It's all in the past now.
Let's not talk about it tonight.
Here.
Okay.
Cheers.
Long trapped in a cage,
now free in nature again.
If Lingya Tower didn't exist,
I'd really want to stay here
with you forever.
Then tonight, let's pretend
none of it exists.
No tower.
No cage.
Just wine.
Just rabbit.
Just master and disciple.
Then eat up.
Maybe this meal
is the last peace we'll get.
Here.
Yummy.
It's so yummy.
Master.
If you hadn't learned martial arts,
you could've been a cook
and fed me for life.
Slow down.
Don't choke.
Look at you.
Master.
Do you remember
when you first came to our home
and had your first meal?
It's been so long.
You still remember?
How could I forget?
You were badly wounded.
We cared for you for so long.
We nearly thought you'd never wake up.
But after you woke up,
the first thing you did
was ask for meat.
Back then I risked my life
escaping the tower.
It was the first time I'd seen the world.
Thankfully I met you all.
Rabbit.
You...
My mother made this rabbit
specially for you.
Can I become your disciple?
I like rabbit too.
Can you teach me how to catch one?
Look, my braiding isn't that bad, right?
Master, when will you start teaching me?
When did I agree to
take you as my disciple?
Since I combed your hair for you,
please think about it, Master.
I've never taken a disciple.
I don't know how to teach.
I've never had a master either.
We can look out for each other.
I'll think about it.
I'll take that as a yes.
Let's pinky swear.
No backing out.
Do you know
how much pain
it takes to gain such skills?
Master.
Master, teach me your best martial arts.
I want to avenge my parents.
Things have been hard
for you lately.
Not at all.
If it weren't for you, Master,
I don't know how I would've kept going.
I made this for you, Master.
I call it filigree bangle.
Someday, when you wear it,
we'll storm Lingya Tower together.
We'll be unstoppable
and nothing can stand in our way.
Lingya Tower is full of danger.
I can't let you risk your life with me.
How could I just watch you
go in alone, risk your life
and do nothing?
Then you'll have to.
I have my own plan.
Master.
You said it yourself.
Lingya Tower is extremely dangerous.
One more person means better odds.
Besides, if a sinful place
like Lingya Tower
isn't destroyed soon,
more women will fall into it,
becoming playthings
for the rich and powerful,
and living a life worse than death.
Master. Master.
Just admit it this once.
Admit that you need me.
Please.
Fine.
But
you have to listen to me.
Yanzhi.
Actually, you don't have to do this.
Burn it.
Burn this place to ashes.
Then there'll be no turning back.
I know you're set on revenge.
But your mother is already...
If anything happens to you...
I...
Master.
In this world,
other than you,
I have nothing left to hold on to.
[Virtue and Merit in Equal Splendor]
Yanzhi.
Going to Lingya Tower
will definitely be dangerous.
You will enter with me
disguised as a mute servant.
We'll split up,
so I may not be able to protect you.
Be careful at every step.
Don't worry, Master.
I can take care of myself.
Hyah!
Wujiu.
It's late.
What are you still doing here?
Tower Master.
The Lantern Festival is coming up.
I was ordered to
select the female prisoners,
so I dare not slack off.
Tower Master.
Hei Ya asks to see you.
Be thorough.
No mistakes.
Yes, Tower Master.
I'll go keep an eye on Hei Ya.
You stay here
and continue the operation.
Yes.
Be careful, Master.
Stop right there!
You got out.
Why come back?
Getting the antidote wasn't enough?
You came back to kill Hei Ya.
How bold of you.
You knew?
Did you really think
that your plans with Zhuang Wujiu
could fool everyone?
If the Tower Master
and I hadn't shown mercy,
you never would've reached
the fourth floor.
Don't act like you're so righteous,
as if that could wash away your sins.
Enough talk.
Come on.
Qi.
Nan Yanzhi.
You're alive.
Thank goodness.
I missed you so much.
Qi, you can talk?
My lord.
The girls serving you tonight
have all entered the tower.
Looks like the real show
is about to begin.
Zhuang Wujiu.
How do you like the show
I arranged for you?