[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 17]
I told you before—
whoever loses the competition
will be punished.
I'll give you one night
to think it over.
By dawn,
I expect to see a corpse.
And if there isn't one
by tomorrow morning?
Then I'll have
to collect all your bodies.
So
you're not as fragile as you look.
I don't have a choice.
I need to survive.
They sent you to kill me?
I'm nothing
more than a female prisoner.
I never did anything.
But
ever since you arrived,
this place has become strange.
I've never seen the present
target anyone like this before.
Who exactly are you?
Instead of asking me,
maybe you should
ask yourself that question.
What do you mean?
You should know these tricks well enough.
After all,
you used to be one of them,
didn't you?
Voice-Keeper Taiyin.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
How fitting.
Do you remember
this guiding ring?
It isn't mine.
Who are you?
Who are you really?
Where did you get that ring?
Do you still remember Nan Shiren's family
at the foot of Guitian Mountain
outside the capital?
Nan Shiren...
He once had a simple,
happy family of three.
But one day,
an assassin broke in
and killed him in a single strike.
His wife was also poisoned
with a deadly toxin,
and to this day,
she's still bedridden.
I already told you,
I'm not...
What kind of skill is it
to bully a child?
A child?
I thought so too at first.
But I've been observing you
these past few days,
and I've realized—
you're not a child at all.
Your appearance can deceive people,
but your real skin
tells the truth.
As expected—
fine on the outside, rotten within.
Your body has already decayed,
just like your heart.
So,
still going to deny it?
Could it be…
you are…
I am.
I am!
Tell me—
why did you kill my father? Why?
He had already retired into the mountains,
living in seclusion.
He stayed out of all worldly affairs.
Why did you have to hunt him down
and kill him?
Why?
I have the antidote.
If I die,
your mother…
your mother will die too.
The Tower Master
has been overworked again lately—
you've even gotten more gray hairs.
Well,
can I not be overworked?
If I don't worry more,
Zhuang Wujiu will tear
the whole place down.
Please calm down, Tower Master.
Wujiu is just young.
Once she's been through more,
she'll come to understand your intentions.
There's still something
I can't quite put my mind
at ease about.
Tower Master, please give your orders.
I'm worried Wujiu won't be able
to bring herself to do it.
If she can't go through with it…
you'll need to help her.
The poison your mother was given
was personally crafted by me.
Any standard antidote
requires my blood—
without it,
no one can cure her.
So you really can't be trusted.
The antidote is real.
But you must die tonight—
otherwise I won't live
to see tomorrow either.
Master!
The antidote!
I found the antidote!
My mother can be saved!
Wujiu,
why did you put your blade away?
Keep going.
I was sent by the Tower Master
to keep an eye on you—
don't disappoint him.
Shut up!
Do you still
not know Zhuang Wujiu's real identity?
Wan Hongliu,
I told you to shut up!
Nan Yanzhi,
the Tower Master of Lingya Tower…
is my father.
Master…
you're lying to me, right?
You must be lying to me…
How foolish.
A little kindness
and you believed everything.
Back then, the order to wipe
out your entire family—
that was given
by me to Qi Songyue.
Impossible…
impossible…
how could that be?
We were the ones who saved you back then!
I treated you like my own family—
how could you?
Then why didn't you kill me back then?
Because watching you suffer
and break apart
is far more interesting.
I taught you, didn't I?
Never trust anyone.
Master,
tell me it's all a lie.
You raised me,
taught me martial arts,
and took care of my family.
You never let me suffer
even the slightest grievance.
You were the one who kept me
from being consumed by hatred—
you were the one
who made me look forward to the future.
And now you tell me it was all fake?
Well, who made your parents
build Lingya Tower?
Your parents knew too many secrets—
they were always destined to be silenced.
I should even thank you.
Without you
bringing me into your home,
I would never have found it.
Even your entry into Lingya Tower
to retrieve the antidote—
that was all part of my plan.
I originally
meant to keep you alive
and slowly torment you to death...
but you
turned out to be useful.
So
you were using me all along?
Thanks to you,
I was able to expose Kou Wan and Zan Hua,
and wipe out
all those hidden traitors.
Impossible…
you were clearly trapped
by this tower too.
You barely escaped
and finally learned
to live like a human again.
You clearly despised everything
about this place.
Enough
of your little drama.
Zhuang Wujiu,
the Tower Master
is running out of patience.
Father, please spare Yanzhi!
You've actually done
♪ Longing lingers between your brows
after our long separation ♪
so many treasonous things for her
behind my back.
If you weren't my daughter,
I would have torn you to pieces.
She only entered the tower
to find the antidote—
♪ Words fail, so hear the insects
through the endless night ♪
she meant no harm.
Wujiu,
you're far too naive.
Do you really not know
Lingya Tower was built by her father?
♪ Obsession melts to ink,
sorrow staining line by line ♪
Do you not know
how her parents died?
She came into the tower
to avenge her parents.
♪ A short letter holds
ten thousand words left unsaid ♪
So she must die.
I'll give you one last chance—
kill Nan Yanzhi with your own hands.
Otherwise, I will show no mercy to anyone
♪ Beneath the lamp,
we watched the days fade into dusk ♪
who has ever helped you.
♪ The strings are broken,
and love has vanished like clouds ♪
♪ As splendor fades,
frost seals the heart shut ♪
♪ Flowers bloom and wither, their fading
fragrance leaves silent heartbreak ♪
♪ Half a life of longing—
who understands this devotion ♪
♪ Beneath a lonely lamp, faint light
falls upon the mortal world ♪
♪ The ink still dries, yet these feelings
remain bound to this world ♪
Nan Yanzhi,
don't you want revenge
for your parents?
Then do it.
This is your last chance.
♪ Amid pine winds and bamboo shadows,
I watch the moon sink and stars drift ♪
Let me see
whether the skills I taught you
are enough for you to kill me.
♪ Through years of blooms and falls,
every word stays buried within ♪
♪ All beneath heaven are passing souls—
only my truest heart remains ♪
♪ Half a lifetime wandering far and wide,
longing for home ♪
♪ Having embraced the boundless stars,
this heart still walks toward the dawn ♪
Your filigree bangle—
take it back.
♪ Beneath the lamp,
we watched the days fade into dusk ♪
♪ The strings are broken,
and love has vanished like clouds ♪
Zhuang Wujiu,
♪ As splendor fades,
frost seals the heart shut ♪
from this moment on,
all ties between us are severed.
♪ Flowers bloom and wither, their fading
fragrance leaves silent heartbreak ♪
♪ Half a life of longing—
who understands this devotion ♪
♪ Beneath a lonely lamp, faint light
falls upon the mortal world ♪
♪ The ink still dries, yet these feelings
remain bound to this world ♪
♪ Amid pine winds and bamboo shadows,
I watch the moon sink and stars drift ♪
♪ Through years of blooms and falls,
every word stays buried within ♪
♪ All beneath heaven are passing souls—
only my truest heart remains ♪
♪ Half a lifetime wandering far and wide,
longing for home ♪
♪ Having embraced the boundless stars,
this heart still journeys toward♪
♪ The dawn ♪