[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 7]
Master.
This is the new drug recently sent
from the Elite Academy.
Its effect is even better than before.
Within half a year,
the elites will surely be addicted to it.
And once they stop taking it,
they will become irritable and restless,
suffering a fate worse than death,
until they waste away and die.
Good.
But this alone is not enough.
May I ask, Master,
what dissatisfaction do you have?
I have painstakingly
managed this Lingya Tower,
not only to weaken their minds,
but also to strengthen my own power.
Please enlighten me, Master.
Why hasn't that batch of money
arrived yet?
Is it because you have slacked off,
or because you can't
keep your subordinates in line?
I have failed in my duty.
Please punish me, Master.
You don't have to be like this.
If your subordinates are disobedient,
just replace them.
It's no big deal.
Get up.
Master,
I will urge them as soon as possible.
When old-timers stay
in this tower too long,
they inevitably flaunt their seniority
and become self-righteous.
To achieve great things,
you must be absolutely ruthless
when the time calls for it.
You are right, Master.
This matter is of great importance
and allows no mistakes.
Yes.
I heard you mention before
that the man was slashed
on the neck by you,
nearly losing his life.
There is actually such a big hole here.
[Zan Hua]
Oh.
Still having guests late at night?
Three more newcomers.
It's really getting livelier around here.
Who is...
Who is this person?
We are here for the death match.
I've never seen anyone
in such a rush to die.
I do like you reckless fools
who don't know your place.
But it's getting late today.
If you want to take the death match,
wait until tomorrow.
Tell me first,
what is the death match on this level?
No rush.
We'll see if you can survive tonight.
What are you doing?
Don't try any of your dirty tricks,
like poisoning my food.
I won't fall for your tricks.
The Gaobao kiln
has been making slow progress lately.
My Lord has urged us many times.
About this matter,
I always feel uneasy.
Zan Hua
is your adopted son.
With him around,
I suppose
nothing will go wrong.
I am
not worried about him.
It's just that...
If you are concerned,
I
am willing to offer my services.
Holy crap!
Why are there so many people suddenly?
Why is this place so weird?
Who are you?
This cell is full.
You can make do in my place for the night.
Come.
You three will sleep here tonight.
I've made the beds for you.
No, don't trouble yourself.
Why is that person carrying a sword?
Did anyone say swords aren't allowed?
Living with someone like that,
I wouldn't be able to rest easy
at night.
Yanzhi,
do we really have to stay here today?
If you don't want to stay,
then get out.
Miss Tu Ya.
These three just arrived
on this level today.
They don't know the rules yet,
so please don't hold it against them.
Come.
Oh, by the way,
just call me Kou Wan.
Kou Wan.
It's fine.
We'll do it ourselves.
Based on your description,
the poison your mother took
was likely the work of Taiyin,
the voice-keeper before me.
This voice-keeper Taiyin,
where is he now?
The voice-keeper Taiyin,
had always been here refining drugs
for the Tower Master before me.
Only the Tower Master
has seen his true face.
Later, because of a great contribution,
he was promoted to the upper level.
So,
he is now the voice-keeper
on the third level.
If Zan Hua is the voice-keeper Taiyin,
I'd better figure out
the situation here first.
Could it be
that there's a foundry inside?
Who is it?
Come out!
If you don't come out,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Zhuang Wujiu.
You are not staying down below
where you belong,
but sneaking around here.
What bad idea are you cooking up again?
The Tower Master is dissatisfied
with the coin delivery progress,
so I was ordered
to come to the Gaobao kiln
to inspect the situation.
You may rest assured
and report back to the Tower Master
that we will finish the task on schedule.
That's good.
Zhuang Wujiu.
Finish your inspection
and leave immediately.
You are not welcome here.
You and I bear no grudges.
Why act like this?
I know what you're here for.
Rest assured.
As long as I am here,
don't even think about
getting close to her.
Why are there so many people?
Is someone going to die again?
What are we competing in on this level?
Everyone!
This round of the death match
is called the Golden Cave.
Golden Cave?
What do you think we have to do?
Who knows?
It's very simple.
You will be randomly paired up
into groups of two.
Roll the dice to determine the winner.
The game lasts for three rounds.
Those who win three consecutive rounds
can not only leave the third level,
but also take away as much gold
as you want from here.
Why is there so much gold?
Something's wrong. It must be a trap.
Better be careful.
I am not playing.
I've hated gambling my whole life.
This is the death match.
If you don't play...
What if I don't play?
Come.
Show her.
Everyone.
Now, you will be randomly
divided into pairs.
There are dice
and a dice cup on each table.
The mute servant will judge the outcome.
The winners will advance
to the next round.
As for the losers...
Well, you just saw what happens.
They get thrown down, of course,
and get their 'Third Eye' opened.
Let's not stand at the same table.
That way,
we won't have to play against each other.
Dao.
Don't say any more.
I don't want to gamble,
but I have to stay alive first.
Everyone, hurry up!
Don't dilly-dally.
Gamble early or late,
you'll still have to gamble.
Die early or late, you'll still die.
If you don't get to the table,
I'll throw you all in to feed the snakes.
Is this game really purely based on luck,
just comparing the numbers?
I don't think so.
The simpler the game,
the less you can let your guard down.
Why is Qi here too?
Could Master have brought him here again?
Is everyone ready?
Golden Cave.
Round 1.
Begin!
[First Meeting]
It's been hard
on you lately.
Not at all.
If it weren't for Master,
I wouldn't know how to keep going.
I made this for you, Master.
I call it the filigree bangle.
Someday, when you wear it
and we storm Lingya Tower together,
we will surely be invincible
and completely unstoppable.