[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 9]
-Let's go!
-Dao.
What are you trying to do?
Taking you out of Lingya Tower
to find an antidote for you outside.
Let's go!
Dao, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Let's go.
If we fight our way out now,
before my snake venom is cured,
I'll be dead.
Then what should we do?
Where can we get an antidote?
Where is it?
But Yanzhi,
if the snake venom
reaches your heart meridian,
it will be hard to remove it.
If I were outside right now,
I would definitely have a way to cure you.
But there's nothing here.
I...
Your snake venom...
What should I do?
Well,
it's fine.
Just let nature take its course.
Stop crying, both of you.
Let nature take its course?
You are about to die!
How can you tell me
to just let nature take its course?
Dao,
since I'm going to die anyway,
before I die,
can you grant me one wish?
What is your wish?
I will help you fulfill it,
no matter what it takes.
I've noticed you've always treasured
your tiger‑head hat.
I really want to know
why it is so important to you.
If you tell me,
I'll know what I'm dying for,
and it will be worth it.
That's it?
Mm.
I'll tell you.
I sewed this hat
with my own hands...
for my child.
Her name is Doudou.
She is a girl.
She is very smart,
very sensible,
and very cute.
In the past,
I was a washerwoman.
I made a living
by washing clothes for others.
Women like us who do manual labor
have always been looked down upon.
At that time,
the men who came to my shop
all treated me...
as a garment they could try on at will,
taking liberties with me as they pleased.
Let go!
They teased and insulted me.
It was always like that,
and I got used to it.
You're back.
Later,
a constable in town
came to my home
with a few ingots of silver to propose.
My parents saw that he was generous
and agreed to the marriage.
At first,
he treated me very well.
I naively thought...
I had found a good husband.
Who would have known
it was all bullshit?
When he saw I gave birth to a girl,
he was greatly disappointed.
He didn't even hold her once,
and he went out to seek pleasure.
That bastard
beat and cursed me every day.
He even developed a gambling addiction.
He sold every valuable thing in the house,
completely ignoring
whether Doudou and I lived or died.
I could only wash clothes for others
during the day
and mend clothes at night.
After he took my hard‑earned money,
he even complained
the copper coins smelled of soap.
Later,
his gambling addiction grew worse.
He even...
even sold Doudou for money.
Give me back my Doudou!
[Indenture]
So that's why you hate gambling so much.
So,
Dao, the reason
you want to get out so badly
is just to find Doudou.
Even if I spend my whole life
and risk my life,
I will go and find her.
Dao.
I believe
you will definitely find her.
Mm.
Thank you, Nan Yanzhi.
I'm sorry.
You did it all to help me,
and you saved me so many times.
You almost lost your life.
Actually, I'm already fine.
That snake's venom can't kill me.
How is that possible?
What do you mean?
I'm fine.
Look.
It's getting better.
Are you sure you're fine?
Are you sure you won't die?
If you don't believe me, ask Man.
It's true.
Yanzhi's wound is already healing.
She's out of danger now.
You lied to me!
You scared me to death!
Nan Yanzhi.
Thank you.
Alright.
Alright, alright.
Right now,
the most important thing for us is
to figure out a way
to survive tomorrow's death match.
Mm.
Yanzhi,
have you thought of a new way?
Mm.
But I still need you, Man.
Me?
We don't have much thatch left.
I would like to get some from you.
Sure.
Thanks.
Ms. Kou. Let me help you.
No need.
It's okay.
Let me help you. You get some rest.
Thank you so much,
Miss Man.
It's nothing.
With my condition,
even washing clothes
is so difficult for me.
I feel really bad about it.
There's nothing to feel bad about.
We are all in the death match together.
We're in the same boat.
Of course we should help each other.
It's a pity that we're all going to die.
If everyone could think the way you do,
before we die,
maybe we could
live a bit more comfortably.
You don't need to be so sad.
In addition to being sad,
what else can I do?
Once tomorrow arrives,
we'll have to accept our own fate.
Ms. Kou.
To be honest,
there is a sure way
to win the death match.
Really?
Actually, it's like this.
Tu Ya.
Tell me how to win.
How would I know?
I just heard everything.
You told Jiang Man and the others
there is a sure way to win.
Then you should ask her.
Every time I killed someone,
they had a lot of complaints about me.
Do you think they would tell me the truth?
I can tell you.
So...
can you remove the dagger first?
The token the mute servants hold
has two sides.
One side has engraved diamond patterns,
rough and uneven.
[Token]
The other side is as smooth as a mirror.
If you look closely,
you can tell the difference.
The smooth side means betting lower.
[Token]
The rough side means betting higher.
Is what you said...
true?
You don't believe me?
Of course I believe you more.
Compared to you,
that person...
is more dangerous.
You mean... Jiang Man?
You don't know her past.
But I
have seen her cruelty.
[Token]
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting.
The final round of this death match
is about to begin.
Wait.
If we still split into pairs and compete
against each other in the third round,
it would be too boring.
Oh?
Then what do you suggest?
How about...
each of our two sides
sends one representative?
If we win,
all the female prisoners here
will go to the fourth level.
And if you lose?
If we lose,
naturally everyone else and I will stay,
at your disposal.
Mm.
This bet is interesting.
But...
But what?
I wasn't asking you.
A matter of such importance
is not something you can decide.
Haha.
What a joke.
If I can't make the decision,
who else can?
Naturally...
Ms. Kou.
Me?
I'm just a weak woman.
Without this crutch,
I'm afraid I wouldn't even make it
past the third level.
Why ask me?
You can't get out
because you simply don't need to.
Am I right,
Lord Voice-Keeper?
Miss Nan,
please don't make fun of me.
Ms. Kou, no need to be modest.
You're a voice-keeper,
yet you're willing to stay among us.
You really have exceptional courage.
Miss Nan,
what do you mean?
First, there are no calluses
where your hand holds the crutch.
That means your injury is not an old one.
Having a crippled leg
and knowing no martial arts,
how did you manage
to survive the death match
from the bottom level
to the third level step by step?
They just took pity on me
because of my crippled leg.
Second,
he doesn't have
a guiding ring on his finger.
Moreover,
Jiang Man went to your room last night
and deliberately told you
how to win the death match.
I said the token had engraved patterns,
but I didn't say
they were engraved diamond patterns.
Yet you mentioned it when you told Tu Ya.
Did I say
they were engraved diamond patterns?
I'm afraid...
you misremembered it, Miss Tu Ya.
I didn't misremember it.
And the answer you told me
was the exact opposite.
You never wanted me to leave here alive,
did you?
In our tribe,
those who don't keep their word
shall be publicly executed.
You told her everything I told you?
When did you two...
become so close?
We haven't known each other for long,
but we
both want to live.