[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 23]
Everyone.
Tonight
is the annual
Lantern Festival death match.
It is also my wedding
as the Master of Lingya Tower.
And I hope
this thrilling hunt of life and death
will help celebrate such a grand occasion.
Celebrate with all under heaven!
Eternal Prosperity of Lingya Tower!
This round of the death match
is called the Hunting Grounds.
The female prisoners are the prey.
One point for a hit with bow or crossbow.
Two points for close-range injuries.
Five points for taking a head.
Whoever scores the highest by the end
will be crowned champion.
And rest assured, everyone.
All the prey have already
taken a muscle-weakening drug.
They are completely defenseless.
So enjoy the hunt to your heart's content!
Where're my friends?
They're already here.
Ah!
Dao. Tuya.
Nan Yanzhi.
Master!
Yanzhi!
Why are they down there?
Yanzhi, I promised you
I would not harm them.
I said they would
appear alive at our wedding.
But whether they survive
this round of the death match
depends on their fate.
You lied to me!
From now on,
if our world holds only each other,
that wouldn't be so bad.
Despicable!
Everyone, the grand annual
Lantern Festival death match,
the Hunting Grounds,
begins now!
Master!
Please be careful!
What's going on?
Weren't they given
the muscle-weakening drug?
[Elite Academy]
Officer Qin.
And all of you...
Bet you didn't expect this, Nan Yanzhi.
The two of us have been
helping you in secret all along.
On the night of the Lantern Festival,
most of the tower's guards
will be gathered at the Hunting Grounds.
That will be the perfect chance
to unlock the prison cells on every floor
and lead everyone out of Lingya Tower.
Every year, the muscle-weakening drug
given to the female prisoners
is prepared by me.
And this year is no exception.
Once chaos erupts in the Hunting Grounds,
we'll coordinate with you.
We'll open the cells on every floor
and release all the female prisoners.
By then, our people
will disguise themselves as nobles
and slip into the crowd.
With our forces working inside and out,
we'll definitely succeed in one strike.
Mm.
Nan Yanzhi.
You're still alive!
Keep your voice down.
This is my master.
Master?
I owe you an apology.
For the sake of the plan,
I had to hide my identity.
So it was you.
Dao.
Tuya.
Jiang Man?
What are you doing here?
Earlier, when Man broke the bowl,
I was the one who told her to do it.
Sorry for not telling you beforehand.
You actually lied to us.
I knew it.
There's no way you were smart enough
to betray us all of a sudden.
This time,
we're not only here to save you.
We're here to save everyone.
Mm.
Once the death match begins,
the three of you lead everyone out.
What about you two?
I'm going to destroy Lingya Tower
and wipe out these monsters for good.
Count me in.
But if you stay,
you'll be facing a perilous battle.
The warriors of my tribe
do not retreat.
And we would never abandon our comrades.
I'm not leaving either.
If I ran away now,
I probably wouldn't sleep peacefully
for the rest of my life.
Anyway, we either live together
or die together.
Mm.
I'll fight alongside Yanzhi too.
In that case,
then we live and die together.
Fight through death to live.
Live and die together!
Fight through death to live!
Everyone!
The time for revenge has come!
Kill!
Archers, fire!
Go, now!
Hurry!
This way!
Kill!
Prime Minister!
The female prisoners
in the tower have revolted!
Quick! Notify the nearby
prefectures at once!
Tell them to send
reinforcements immediately!
Yes, Sir!
Master, over here!
Kill!
Go after Prime Minister Lin.
Leave him to me.
Nan Yanzhi,
why are you still so stubborn?
I'll give you one last chance.
Come back to my side right now.
You're just as rotten as Lingya Tower now.
Even if I die,
I will never be with you.
Nan Yanzhi!
Kill!
Zhuang Wujiu.
Spare my life,
and I can erase your criminal status.
I can even grant you
a position of honor and prestige.
Then you'll be admired
by all under heaven.
Ha!
What good is fine silk and glory?
What good is endless wealth?
None of it can erase
the pain I've endured all my life.
None of it can cover up
the filth of this world.
Then what is it you want?
As long as it's within my power,
I'll give it to you.
For all the suffering
and injustice we endured,
even if I'm torn to pieces...
I'll make you pay in blood!
Hyah!
♪ Frost still lights the old road,
while hatred traps my disciple ♪
♪ Back then, you reached for me
with tears in your eyes ♪
♪ I wiped your tears away
and carried your future on my shoulders ♪
♪ I'd trade half my life
just to see you safe ♪
♪ Your kindness is carved into my heart,
so I dared to challenge fate ♪
♪ In this cruel world,
you were my only warmth ♪
♪ You taught me to wield my sword through
the fog and led me out of darkness ♪
♪ You showed me
that loyalty outweighs life itself ♪
♪ Ours is a bond of souls,
and the greatest gift of all ♪
Master,
when will you start teaching me?
♪ I once swore to protect you
until you found freedom ♪
When did I ever agree
to take you as my disciple?
Master, please teach me
the strongest martial arts!
♪ Though my sins can never be repaid,
I still tend your wounds ♪
I want to avenge my parents!
♪ I only pray Heaven
never leaves you alone again ♪
I made this for you, Master.
I named it the filigree bangle.
♪ Now that revenge is won,
my heart feels emptier than ever ♪
One day, when you wear it,
♪ What I fear most is you
sacrificing yourself for me in the end ♪
if we charge into Lingya Tower together,
nothing will stand in our way.
♪ Even if fate leaves us no road ahead ♪
We'll be unstoppable.
♪ I still wish to face
this doomed path by your side ♪
♪ The wind cuts like blades,
the night feels like a grave ♪
Why didn't you kill me back then?
Why?
♪ Together we walked
through blood and chaos ♪
♪ Our hearts bound as one,
our fates intertwined ♪
♪ Our vow was carved deep into our palms ♪
♪ If not for you, how could I
stand tall within the flames? ♪
Other than you,
♪ Without your protection,
I'd never have made it this far ♪
I have nothing left to hold onto.
[Virtue and Merit in Equal Splendor]
♪ The one who escaped the prison,
the one who forged the sword ♪
♪ Together we walked
through blades and fire as one ♪
You don't have to hesitate
because of me anymore.
♪ Falling into the snow ♪
Stop carrying everything alone.
I want to fight by your side.
♪ Your eyes reflect our final farewell ♪
For my parents,
and for you,
let's make them repay every debt they owe.
If Lingya Tower didn't
exist in this world,
♪ Master, stay awake.
I still want to hear my name from you ♪
I really would like
to stay here with you forever.
Then tonight,
let's pretend
that none of this exists.
♪ Don’t cry, disciple.
I'd protect you through every lifetime ♪
No tower.
No cages.
Only wine.
♪ Only now do I understand ♪
Only you and me.
♪ The hottest, deepest, fiercest feeling ♪
♪ Is this very moment ♪
♪ This life is enough.
This life is enough ♪
♪ It began with passion and ended in joy ♪
♪ May we still protect each other
as master and disciple in the next life ♪
♪ And walk together to the end
of the road we never finished ♪
Master...
♪ Snow buries our names ♪
They
came to save us.
♪ May the wind remember their brave ♪
Nan Yanzhi!
Yanzhi!
♪ Silhouettes ♪
Miss Zhuang!
Yanzhi!
Nan Yanzhi!
-Nan Yanzhi!
-Zhuang Wujiu!
Zhuang Wujiu!
You fulfilled the promise
you made to everyone.
I won't let anything happen to you.
We succeeded.
Yes, Yanzhi.
Look!
Everyone escaped from Lingya Tower!