[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 11]
Ms. Kou,
I advise you to sign
and put your fingerprint
on Xie Quan's confession of guilt
-sooner rather than later.
-Mr. Xie is modest and courteous,
of upright character.
He would never do
such heinous things.
Hmph.
Such an unbreakable bond of love.
Guards,
beat her!
[Xie Mansion]
Half a year later,
the matter with Prince Xu came to an end.
Ms. Kou was released,
but having endured brutal torture,
[Xie Mansion]
she was covered in scars
and left with a broken body.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get out.
Where did you come from, you beggar?
Do you know where this is?
How dare you barge in here?
I'm looking for Mr. Xie Quan.
Our Mr. Xie has married into
the Princess Mansion.
He doesn't live here.
You stinking beggar,
why don't you take a look at yourself
in the mirror?
Do you think the Prince Consort is
someone you can just ask to meet?
When did he marry into
the Princess Mansion?
Get out of here right now!
[Xie Mansion]
What are you arguing about?
What's the noise?
The hairpin.
This is my hairpin.
This was a reward from our master.
What's it to you?
Ru Yue.
You are Ru Yue.
I am Ms. Kou.
I'm not Ru Yue.
You got the wrong person.
I am Ms. Kou.
Go, go, go, go!
-Hurry up!
-Ru Yue.
Go, go, go, go!
[Xie Mansion]
To extricate himself from the matter
involving Prince Xu,
Xie Quan ultimately chose to marry into
the Princess Mansion.
[Xie Mansion]
And Ms. Kou's savings
were swindled away by her own maid.
Poor thing,
during those six months in prison,
[Xie Mansion]
she had been foolishly clinging to
those so-called promises.
Don't you think
that this Ms. Kou
is the most foolish woman in the world?
Then I want to know;
what happened to that heartless man
and that ungrateful maid
in the end?
Oh.
One year, on the fifteenth day
of the first lunar month,
people found the severed arms,
legs, and heads
of the Prince Consort Xie
and Ru Yue
scattered all over the city.
After hearing my story,
do you still believe in promises?
Sweet words come from no loyal lips.
The fickle world abounds
with smooth‑talkers.
It's getting late.
I advise you
to take this gold.
I will have someone
escort you safely to the fourth level.
You've finished your story.
I have a story too.
This ring,
do you remember it?
This is the guiding ring of Lingya Tower.
Where did you get it?
Ten years ago,
Lingya Tower sent an assassin
who killed my father.
My mother was also poisoned
with a strange toxin,
and has been unconscious ever since.
And this ring
was left behind by the killer then.
I fought my way up the Tower
and learned
that the killer was voice-keeper Taiyin.
And she
is right here on the third level.
Are you saying
that I am
the one who killed your father?
That's right.
I should kill you
with my own hands right now
to avenge them,
but my Master repeatedly warned me
not to act recklessly.
So on some matters,
I decided to ask you face to face.
Your Master,
Zhuang Wujiu?
What else did she tell you?
Are you suspecting
that the voice-keeper on the third level
is the one who murdered your parents?
That man with a hairpin
is so ruthless.
How could he not be
the voice-keeper Taiyin.
Yes
and no.
What do you mean?
Let me take you somewhere.
Zan Hua
is not the voice-keeper.
I've been here before.
Isn't this where female prisoners
are enslaved to mint coins?
Exactly.
Look closely.
No!
Ah!
Hey!
Isn't that the female prisoner
who played the Golden Cave?
She's still alive.
By order of Tower Master,
the voice-keeper mints new coins here.
Smelting gold requires excavating caves.
Later she discovered
that by using the complex
and varied cave structures,
she could hide female prisoners in them,
making them hard to find,
so she started
helping these female prisoners
fake their deaths
to deceive everyone.
Even if she has found her conscience now,
it doesn't prove
that she isn't the one
who murdered my parents.
On the entire third level,
apart from the voice-keeper,
there is no one else
with that ability.
She even told you all this.
I know
you've saved many people.
But when facing an enemy,
I will never show mercy.
The answer you want,
I can tell you right now.
I am not the voice-keeper Taiyin,
and this ring is not mine.
All guiding rings
for voice-keepers of Lingya Tower
are sized for the left ring finger.
The size of this ring...
See?
It shows the owner's finger
is much thinner than mine.
I apologize for my offense just now.
Please forgive me,
Ms. Kou.
Zan,
put the sword down.
Wan,
it would be one thing
if she were just an ordinary person,
but she's with Zhuang Wujiu.
I can't let her leave.
Zan,
let her go.
Are you not even going to listen to me?
You previously hid the truth
from Tower Master,
mixing impurities into the coinage,
secretly transferring the remaining gold
to Zhuang Wujiu for transport.
That alone is a capital offense!
If it weren't for her
repeatedly bewitching you,
how could you have done
such a rebellious thing?
Listen to me.
Let's capture this person
and report to Tower Master.
Maybe we can make amends for our crimes.
Zan
Zan, don't.
Kou Wan.
Lingya Tower has always been brutal
and ruthless.
Having been here for so many years,
how could we not know that?
Even if you grab her and run,
I still can't escape death.
Releasing the female prisoners
is an act of redemption
I truly wanted to do.
It has nothing to do with Zhuang Wujiu.
Even if I die,
I could never be a treacherous person.
Why did Master summon me
overnight?
There are two chests of gold here.
This chest is the one I sealed previously.
And this one is what you delivered
two days ago.
Forgive my ignorance, Master.
I do not understand what you mean.
Then watch closely.
I failed in my duty of supervision.
I deserve ten thousand deaths.
What happened?
The adulteration of the gold coins
has been discovered.
Tower Master is coming to punish us.
I've arranged everything else.
Leave with me quickly.
I can't leave.
If I leave,
Tower Master will blame
everything on Zan.
What's more,
the female prisoners we painstakingly hid
will certainly die.
I will do my best to mediate
and keep everyone safe.
But if you don't leave,
you will die.
Sorry, Zhuang Wujiu.
This needle will put you
to sleep for a while.
Zhuang Wujiu.
There is absolutely no way
I can escape unscathed this time.
Only my death
can ensure all your safety.
You and I still have unfinished business.
You can't...
Zhuang Wujiu.
Promise me.
Those gold coins we hid away,
you must guard them well.
And if someday those female prisoners
manage to leave Lingya Tower alive,
I leave them in your care.