[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 22]
Master.
I failed to maintain discipline
and deserve death.
Kill her,
and I will absolve you of all guilt
and let the matter rest.
Thank you for your mercy, Master.
Zhuang Wujiu, you have rebelled
against your superiors
and shown utter disrespect
for your elders.
Out of our years
of father–daughter bond,
I will give you one chance—
end your own life.
Spare me the trouble of doing it myself.
So
your so-called fatherly affection
was just an act in the end.
You couldn't even keep up the pretense.
Preposterous!
I gave you life.
If I want you dead, you will die.
My mother gave me my life.
Back then, you defiled my mother
in Lingya Tower.
Do you know that my very existence
is the shame she carried all her life?
Even if I wronged your mother,
I have not treated you badly.
Forcing me back to Lingya Tower back then
was only to turn me
into your killing weapon.
You used all those so-called rules
of propriety and family ethics
to control me.
But when life and death were on the line,
I was nothing more than
a disposable pawn to you.
That is your destiny.
And today, I will reclaim your life.
You are not worthy of being a father.
Wujiu,
be obedient.
Listen to me.
"Be obedient."
"Resign yourself to fate."
I've heard those words countless times.
And every time I hear them,
my urge to kill you grows stronger.
You lowly woman!
There is no forgiveness for your crimes.
Meng Shuo, your crimes
are beyond redemption.
Heaven cannot tolerate you.
For my mother,
and for all the lives
you trampled in Lingya Tower,
I will carry out justice
in the name of heaven.
Wujiu...
do you...
do you truly hate me that much?
If not for Yanzhi,
why would I have needed
to wait until today?
What a performance.
This is the most brilliant
death match
I've ever seen.
What a pity—
Meng Shuo labored for Lingya Tower
for so many years,
only to end up dying at the hands
of his own daughter.
Tragic... truly tragic.
No need for this hypocritical sympathy.
You are
the true culprit
behind Lingya Tower's crimes.
Just them?
You think they can stop me?
Hahaha...
Young people are always so impatient.
The show isn't even over yet—
why rush to leave the stage?
Qi.
Yanzhi.
Let her go.
Zhuang Wujiu,
I'll make you finish this performance.
Surrender yourself...
or
watch her die.
You...
You are truly despicable.
Hahahahaha...
As a senior statesman of the realm,
you privately established Lingya Tower
and even took pleasure
in enslaving people.
Aren't you afraid
that one day the truth will come out
and you'll be utterly disgraced
and infamous for all eternity?
Do you really think
exposing my identity
will bring down Lingya Tower?
Hmph.
How childish.
Over the years,
it's not that no one has known
who I truly am—
they simply don't dare speak out.
Because they all understand
that the moment
anyone tries to reveal the truth,
I won't even need to give an order—
someone will make sure they stay silent.
You are utterly inhuman,
completely devoid of conscience.
You will face retribution.
Retribution?
You mean these death row prisoners?
If you think they were forced into it,
you're mistaken.
You don't believe me?
Fine.
Then I'll let you see it clearly.
Qi,
open every cell door.
Open all the cells.
These low-born criminals
are guilty of grave offenses.
Even if they escape, so what?
They'll still have nowhere to belong,
nowhere to live in the light of day.
At least here,
they can cling
to what little life they have left
and live out the rest of it in misery.
Hahahaha...
Qi,
you've done well this time.
It wasn't a waste keeping you
in hiding in the Tower all these years.
You are truly a visionary, Master.
I have only been acting under orders.
Qi,
from this moment on,
you are the new Tower Master
of Lingya Tower.
I am honored by your support, Master.
I will serve you
even at the cost of my life.
Qi...
You're awake?
If a new bride sleeps this much,
she'll surely be picked on
by her in-laws one day.
Hahaha...
Thankfully,
they're already dead.
What did you make me eat?
Relax.
It's just some tendon-weakening powder.
How could I ever hurt you?
I finally found you after all this time—
I won't lose you again.
You're holding me too tightly...
It hurts.
Can you help me up?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I have no idea how Master is doing...
For now, I can only pretend to comply.
Yanzhi,
can you pat my head again?
Just like before.
Qi,
did you choose that name yourself?
No.
They gave it to me.
I hate being called that,
so I killed everyone
who called me that.
Everyone—except Master, of course.
But
I call you that too.
You're different.
I like you.
I like it when you call me that.
Qi,
you said "Master" just now.
Are you with Meng Shuo?
Hahaha...
Thanks to your master,
Meng Shuo is dead.
Now
I am the Tower Master of Lingya Tower.
You...
How could you be the Tower Master?
Then... where is my master?
I've served Master for many years.
Of course this is Master's arrangement.
Your master tried to assassinate Master
and was captured.
The "Master" you refer to is Hei Ya.
Then where is my master?
If you want her to live,
you'll do as I say.
Qi...
you've set this place up like this...
are you—
I want to marry you.
Tomorrow night
will be our wedding night.
You want to marry me?
Don't worry.
I won't hurt you.
I'm now the Tower Master
of Lingya Tower.
I can give you whatever you want.
I just want you by my side
and to treat you well.
Qi...
I...
getting married like this
is all too sudden.
I... I-I...
I know you like me,
Qi.
But feelings take time to grow.
Why don't we spend
a few more days together?
Let me calm my heart first.
Okay?
Nan Yanzhi,
we're both intelligent people.
There's no need for such lies.
Qi,
if you truly care for me,
you should respect me
and not force me.
Nan Yanzhi,
do you know how much effort I spent
persuading Master to allow this wedding?
Tomorrow night
is the Lantern Festival—
and the time of our wedding.
If you agree to marry me,
your master
and all your friends
will be alive to attend our wedding.
If you refuse,
then there won't be any wedding...
and there's no reason
for them to live either.
Alright.
I'll marry you.
Hahaha...
But I have one condition:
not a single one of them
can be missing.
So you're one of Hei Ya's people.
If not for that,
perhaps we would never
have had such a relationship.
"The relationship?"
You and I walk different paths.
There is no relationship between us.
You are Yanzhi's master.
I've come to invite you
to witness our wedding.
Release Yanzhi. Now.
Don't worry.
I am now the Tower Master
of Lingya Tower.
Yanzhi will be safe—
as long as she marries me.
Hmph.
You? You're not even worthy.
Look at yourself in the water
and see who you are.
How are you
any different from Meng Shuo?
I am nothing like Meng Shuo.
He was driven by greed.
I have only Yanzhi in my eyes.
You are beyond saving.
Truthfully... I sometimes envy you.
You got to stay by Yanzhi's side
and share so much with her.
Thank you for taking care
of her all these years.
From here on,
I will take care of her.
Dao. Chilantuya.
You two,
please come in.
It's you.