[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 19]
"On the screen, the candle's shadow
deepens as night grows old.
The Silver River slants
and the morning stars grow cold."
Perhaps it just depicts a scene like this.
You are...
Liu Yuan?
Exactly.
Yang, let's go.
Please stay, Miss Lin.
I have no ill intentions.
However, after spending several days here,
I've been overcome by boredom.
All I want is a mere chat with someone.
What beautiful scenery today.
It is truly rare.
Miss Lin,
if you are in the mood,
why not stay here with me
to taste some tea
and admire the moon?
[Auspice from the East]
Prefect Wang,
what brings you to my place
in the middle of the night?
I had to rush here at night
for a serious matter
that can't be delayed.
What exactly is this highly confidential
and urgent matter?
Prime Minister, do you know about
Lingya Tower?
What tower?
Lingya Tower.
Lingya Tower...
What's this place for?
Rumor has it that it was set up
by powerful figures in secret.
To have fun, they make death row inmates
fight for their lives in there.
Many officials in the court
are deeply involved.
In the long run,
I'm afraid this will harm the state.
Oh?
I can't believe
such acts of defiance would occur
under my governance.
This is the list of related officials
that I've managed to gather.
It is for your review, Prime Minister.
How audacious of these people!
This matter involves
numerous officials at all levels,
even including...
Including who?
You are actually a nice person.
It's a real pity
that my heart belongs to someone else
and has no room for another man.
It doesn't matter.
I'm already content with
a simple chat with you
like a confidant of yours
under the moon.
Word has it
that you deliberately cut your own face
to avoid being married to another man.
I suppose you also find me ridiculous,
don't you?
No, I really don't.
Instead, I find you deeply admirable
for taking that action.
Prior to entering this mansion,
I kept wondering
what kind of woman
would have the courage to do so.
I'm afraid my face under this veil
might frighten you.
I consider it a blessing of a lifetime
to see your face, Miss Lin.
Why would I be frightened?
What do you think?
The sight of your face
reminds me
of a line of poetry—
"Scars steel her jade-like soul of grace.
Her smile outshines the spring in bloom."
Nian'an spoke highly of you to me.
No wonder you could pass the imperial exam
with him in the same year.
You are indeed knowledgeable.
Prime Minister, the new son-in-law
of your choice, Liu Yuan,
is also involved.
[Editor of the Imperial Academy, Liu Yuan]
Liu Yuan is a frequent visitor
to Lingya Tower.
He has also committed several acts
of corruption and bribery.
Worrying that you might be
deceived by him,
I specially came to inform you.
I didn't expect Liu Yuan
to be this kind of person.
Prefect Wang,
you did a great job.
Only with pillars of the state like you
can the imperial court prosper forever.
I'm honored by your high regard,
Prime Minister.
I was just fulfilling my duty.
This matter is too importance
to be taken lightly.
I wonder who else is engaged in this
besides you.
Rest assured, Prime Minister.
I haven't told anyone else yet.
I even came
to your residence alone.
This visit is only known to you and me.
Very good.
Excellent.
It's getting late.
I shall take my leave.
My Lady.
My Lady!
My Lady,
are you alright?
I'll bring Miss Lin to her room.
As for you, go get some rest.
If you weren't
the Prime Minister's daughter,
who would have such patience with you?
After we share
a bed tonight,
let's see if you can still be so arrogant
and self-conceited.
It's you?
What are you doing here?
Just now, that punk
slipped drugs into your tea and pastries,
seeking a chance to defile you.
If I hadn't caught him in the act,
I'm afraid you wouldn't even
know how your life was ruined tonight.
What an outrage!
I thought he was a decent gentleman,
but he is actually an animal
in human form!
Hey, hold on!
I'm going to kill him.
Why are you stopping me?
A brutal animal like him surely deserves
to be chopped into pieces.
But if you kill him now, at most,
you can vent your anger.
In turn, this might alert the enemy.
What do you mean?
Killing Liu Yuan won't
bring Shen Nian'an back to life.
Only by keeping him alive
will we have a chance
to find the hidden mastermind.
And that...
is the real beginning of your revenge.
Don't you long to avenge Shen Nian'an,
your beloved man?
If you want to find out the truth,
then take my advice.
Do you know who the killer is?
Uncle,
you asked me to come this late at night...
Ah!
Isn't that Prefect Wang?
Look at what you've done!
Why is your name on the list?
It...
How did he find out all about this?
How did he find it out?
Are you seriously asking me?
Shouldn't you be asking yourself?
If he hadn't come meet me first,
you would be brought
to the Minister
of the Court of Judicial Review tomorrow!
Uncle,
p-please forgive me!
It...
It was a momentary
lapse on my part.
You are so careless in your work.
How can I entrust you
with important tasks in the future?
You reproach is justified, Uncle.
I promise...
to act with great caution in the future.
I promise!
What happened to your head?
I...
N-Nothing happened.
I just got hurt
b-by accident.
Jingjing has always had a bad temper
since she was little.
Some things
had better not be rushed.
I understand.
I will follow your instructions, Uncle.
Get rid of the body.
Yes.
Consider it done, Uncle!
Master,
Prime Minister Lin killed Prefect Wang
to cover for Liu Yuan.
Prime Minister Lin is ruthless
and decisive.
There's nothing good in him.
Master, are you suggesting
that Prime Minister Lin
has a lot to do with Lingya Tower?
How are things on your end?
I've reached a consensus
with Lin Jingjing.
Let's just wait and see what happens.
Good.
Yang.
Mr. Liu.
Level with me.
After I brought Miss Lin back to her room,
who else saw us?
No one.
Last night, she came out soon
after entering her room.
No one went in there afterwards.
No one at all?
Could I have been hurt by Miss Lin?
Ah...
Or did you attack me?
No, I didn't.
I was in my room the entire night.
I didn't dare to take a step out.
Keep a close eye on Miss Lin.
Should anything happen,
let me know at once.
Otherwise—
you know
how Shen Nian'an ended up.
Yes, Mr. Liu.
Yang.
I can't believe you're spying on me
for Liu Yuan.
No, I'm not, My Lady.
I heard each and every word
you and Liu Yuan said just now.
No need to deny it.
Who are you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You agreed to spy on Miss Lin
for Liu Yuan,
so as not to be killed.
I heard that right, didn't I?
He also mentioned about
how Shen Nian'an ended up...
You've worked for me for a long time.
How exactly did you connect with Liu Yuan?
My Lady,
I don't want to die.
I was coerced into Liu's evil plan!
Coerced?
Don't you fear that I might kill you too?
Confess.
What exactly does Liu Yuan have to do
with the death of Nian'an?
My Lady...
If you tell the truth now,
we'll let you live.
But if you dare to lie again,
I'll end your life
on Miss Lin's behalf.
My Lady.
My Lady, I'm sorry I did wrong.
As long as you spare my life,
I'll tell you everything I know, My Lady.
My Lady!
You're so talented with your hands,
My Lady.
[Wish you good health, Nian'an]
But judging from the characters,
this sachet
isn't for Prime Minister Lin, is it?
It's not, you clever girl.
Deliver this to Nian'an's residence today.
Got it.
Wait!
I remember.
I must hand it to him personally.
Understood!
On my way to Mr. Shen's abode that day,
I happened to see him.
So I wanted to greet him.
Mister...
But then I saw him discreetly entering
a tea house through its rear door.
Shortly after that,
I noticed another man
went into the tea house too.
That was exactly Mr. Liu.
It seemed unusual to me,
so I decided to go up to Mr. Shen
after they both came out.
A moment later,
I saw Mr. Shen being carried out.
I was too terrified
to make a sound.
At the very end,
two more people came out of the tea house.
Rest assured, Prime Minister Lin.
I'll be on the task right away.
I-I didn't see anything.
Yang.