[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 18]
Yanzhi.
Nan Yanzhi.
Open your eyes.
Mother.
I finally got the antidote.
Wait for me.
Yanzhi,
don't blame me for being too ruthless.
If it weren't for this,
how could we have fooled Meng Shuo
and the entire Lingya Tower?
[Virtue and Merit in Equal Splendor]
Mother.
Mother!
Mother?
Mother.
Mr. Wu,
where is my mother?
[Tomb of the Late Father, Nan Shiren]
[Tomb of the Late Mother, Madam Yang]
Please.
[Auspice from the East]
Uncle, I'm sorry
for keeping you waiting.
Not at all.
You came at just the right time.
Please, have a seat.
Go ask
why Jingjing hasn't come yet.
Yes.
My Lady,
Mr. Liu has been waiting for a long time.
You should at least go see him.
Otherwise, snubbing him like this
might bring shame to the Prime Minister.
Given my current looks, I don't believe
anyone would truly be willing to marry me.
We still haven't found
the killer of Nian'an,
and you want me to remarry.
No way!
Jingjing,
I want Liu Yuan to marry into our family.
He is also an imperial scholar.
He is no worse than Shen Nian'an.
Nian'an is the only one I love.
I'll never love anyone else in this life.
Jingjing,
Liu Yuan and Shen Nian'an
were close friends.
He has
a good reputation
-for both his talent and character.
-I've made up my mind!
Don't push me any further!
Matters of marriage
are decided by parents
and matchmakers' words!
You are not allowed to act on your own!
Is that so?
If you insist, Father,
I'll have no choice but to do this!
Jingjing,
I just want you to find a good husband.
Why are you trying to kill yourself?
Father,
my face has been disfigured.
Surely no one will be willing to marry me.
As for my marriage,
you don't need to worry about it anymore.
My Lady,
why did you have to do that?
Even if you don't want to remarry,
you didn't have to
ruin yourself like that.
My Lady!
Your husband is already gone,
but life still has to go on.
Isn't that right?
If it weren't to avenge Nian'an,
I'm afraid
I would have died with him long ago!
But the Prime Minister...
Help me tell them
that it's inconvenient for me
to receive guests.
Why didn't you just kill me back then?
Why?
I don't have a mother anymore.
I'll never see my mother again.
Auntie,
it's all my fault.
If it weren't for me,
they wouldn't have found this place.
I implicated you.
Wujiu.
It's not your fault.
If you truly want
to repay my family's kindness,
please...
take good care of Yanzhi.
Mother!
Does it still hurt?
Compared to the torture you've suffered,
my injuries are nothing.
Master.
From now on,
you don't need to worry about me anymore.
Don't shoulder it all by yourself anymore.
I want to fight alongside you.
For my parents
and for you.
Let's go make them pay what they owe
together.
Okay.
We'll do it together.
Master.
So you knew Shen Nian'an.
All those years,
he had been investigating the mastermind
behind the Lingya Tower,
Hei Ya.
[Hei Ya will show up soon. Come quickly]
Unfortunately, I was still too late.
Before I could meet him,
he was murdered.
No wonder the killer was so brutal.
So it was Hei Ya.
So if we follow this lead,
we can find Hei Ya, right?
Yes.
Later, through some investigations,
I found some clues
in Prime Minister Lin's Mansion.
The Prime Minister's Mansion?
Yanzhi,
I need your help now.