[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 5]
Master.
It's you.
What are you doing here?
You mean she didn't kill you?
Now that I see you're all right,
I can relax.
You mean
she brought you here?
Then I guess
she sent you to keep an eye on me
so I wouldn't do anything reckless.
Qi?
That's your name?
Then I'll just call you Qi from now on.
Tomorrow's exam questions?
How did you get this?
Did she ask you to give this to me?
On Choosing a Husband...
In the eyes of the world,
once a woman comes of age,
the most important matter in her life
is choosing a husband.
I have already taught you much
about the principles women
are expected to follow
and the proper way to conduct yourselves.
Based on what you have learned,
write an essay on the subject
of choosing a husband.
You will have 2 hours
to complete the exam.
Unless you turn in your paper,
you may not leave the examination hall.
You may begin.
[On Choosing a Husband]
Everyone will remain here
for the next 2 hours.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
At this rate, just copying
all of this down
will take until
it's time to hand in the paper.
How am I supposed to investigate anything?
[Teammate]
What is she doing?
Is she turning in a blank exam paper?
She's totally unreliable.
Wait.
What is it, Madam?
Didn't I just say
that no one is allowed
to leave the examination hall
during the exam?
Madam,
I've already finished my paper.
Are you certain
you're handing it in just like this?
I've already finished my paper.
Am I not allowed to turn it in?
Do you know what happens to those
who don't take the exam seriously?
I did take it seriously.
Everything I wanted to say—
and could say—on this topic
is already on the paper.
Unless I misheard
or overlooked something,
I don't believe you specified
a minimum word count, Madam.
You'd better think this through.
Once you leave this examination hall,
it'll be too late
to regret.
Thank you for the reminder, Madam.
She's really impossible to count on.
[Teammate]
I'm already out.
There's no way I'm going back.
If you make any more noise,
you'll only get me into trouble.
I know what I'm doing.
Let's go.
The moment I approached this place
last night,
I was stopped.
There must be something
suspicious going on here.
Looks like there's something
hidden underneath.
I'll go down and take a look.
Keep an eye out for me.
It's fine.
Looks like she's obsessed
with being a teacher.
Master.
I don't like being lied to.
Can you at least give me
some peace of mind?
Master,
things have already come to this point.
Either keep me by your side
and let me act under your watch,
or keep everything from me
and let me learn things
the hard way myself.
The worst that can happen is I die.
How dare you threaten me?
Master...
W-What
is this?
The toxin has already reached
the back of the brain.
She won't wake up again.
The antidote.
The antidote for my mother!
I've already checked.
The antidote isn't here.
Look at this.
[No. 5]
[No. 4]
[No. 3]
[No. 2]
These...
[No. 1]
Could these be...
That's right.
Different rankings
are given different medicines.
[No. 1]
No wonder some of them are unconscious,
while others are already like puppets.
They're using people as test subjects.
All the students on this floor
have become their drugged puppets.
And that's precisely
how Lingya Tower controls
those so-called nobles—with these drugs.
This medicine causes hallucinations,
making people feel as if they've entered
a state of ultimate bliss—
so intense it's almost uncontrollable.
Once they've tasted it,
they become hooked on the feeling.
[No. 1]
And this is supposed to be a reward
for the top-ranked student?
These drugs may be addictive,
but at least those
who take them still retain some sanity.
The other drugs
are even worse.
If they were all nothing but puppets,
she probably wouldn't get
her fill as a teacher.
So she lets the high-performing
students keep their minds,
while the weaker ones
are reduced to toys
for her to manipulate at will.
I get it now.
Qin Yuren controls those puppets
through the sound of bells.
Maybe we can use that against her.
Let's set Qin Yuren aside for now.
Shouldn't you
be taking your exam right now?
I've already finished my exam.
That fast?
Even a seasoned ghostwriter
would need quite a while to copy
all those essays I gave you.
How could you possibly be out so soon?
I only wrote one sentence.
One sentence?
Qin Yuren has always
valued order in the academy.
What you did
was utterly disrespectful—
you practically stomped her dignity
into the mud.
Master, don't worry.
I really did
answer the question seriously.
She asked us to write
about choosing a husband,
and what I most
wanted to say was this...
[On Choosing a Husband]
"I'd rather grow old clinging
to a fragrant branch
than dance with yellow leaves
in the autumn wind."
Everyone says
choosing a husband
is the most important thing
in a woman's life,
that becoming a wife
is the only path
available to her.
I don't agree.
I insist on walking my own path,
even if it means going against tradition.
Choose a husband?
I refuse.
She is...
rather interesting.
If you hadn't met in Lingya Tower,
perhaps
the two of you might have
become kindred spirits and talked
through the night by candlelight.
That Qin Yuren is arrogant
and cold-blooded.
I wouldn't want
to exchange a single word with her.
Actually, Qin Yuren
was never a truly wicked person.
She was held back by her feelings,
and later struck
by a terrible twist of fate.
That's how she became who she is now.
Master,
are you saying
you know her background?
[Elite Academy]
How did the exam go?
Not bad, I guess.
Yanzhi,
where did you go?
I've been looking everywhere for you.
What are we going to do?
Dao really seems determined
to team up with those two sisters.
Then what about us?
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
The results are out!
[Elite Academy Competition Rankings]
[No. 2 Bai Xiaohui]
I'm second again.
[No. 3 Bai Xiaoying]
I'm third again.
[No. 1 Nan Yanzhi]
Yanzhi,
you got first place!
You actually took the top spot!
You're amazing, Yanzhi!
What's the point of her doing well
when she's stuck with a teammate
dragging her down?
I came in last.
This isn't your fault.
If Madam liked my paper,
then she clearly wasn't looking
for conventional approaches.
But our group could've taken first place.
It's because my score was so low
that I dragged everyone down.
Look,
it's Dao's name.
[No. 4 Dao]
Dao did pretty well, didn't she?
Of course.
Our Dao did exceptionally well.
The three of us are definitely
going to come out on top this time.
Dao,
are you really not teaming up
with us anymore?
You two...
You are hopelessly dumb,
and she turned in her paper early.
Well...
Can you really blame me?
I trust all of you
are already aware of your results.
Next, I will announce
the final group rankings.
[Elite Academy Competition Rankings]
There were 20 students
taking the exam this round,
so it was impossible to divide everyone
evenly into groups of three.
As a result,
2 students were left without a group.
Their group total score
was at a disadvantage,
but fortunately, the 2 of them
scored high enough
[Elite Academy Competition Rankings]
that they didn't end up near the bottom.
Bai Xiaohui, Bai Xiaoying—
you were the two left without a group.
Don't look at me like that.
I can't stand self-righteous people
like you.
The 3 of us came up here together,
so naturally we're a team.
How did you get tomorrow's exam questions?
You don't need to worry about that.
Just focus on the exam.
What do you want me to do for you?
Nothing more.
Didn't we come up here together?
It's only natural that we help each other.
Then why not give the exam questions
to Jiang Man?
Jiang Man isn't strong enough
academically.
If she suddenly scores too well,
Qin Yuren will definitely
become suspicious.
I know
you're always on guard
around the people here,
but as long as you still see me
as a companion,
I'll stand by you through everything
and treat you with complete honesty.
How can you go back
on your word like this?
You have no integrity at all!
Shameless!
You're a disgrace!
I never promised you anything
in the first place.
I already told you
to stay away from me.
You're the ones
who kept getting your hopes up.
You...
Enough.
The groups have already been decided,
so further discussion is pointless.
Next, I will announce the top-ranked group
for this exam.
Let us congratulate the three of them.
Wait,
Madam!
I suddenly remembered something—
I seem to have left something out.
What did you leave out?
I forgot to write my name
on my exam paper.
So my result for this exam
shouldn't count.
Nan Yanzhi, have you lost your mind?
Exactly, Yanzhi!
Are you treating the Elite Academy exams
as a joke?
Madam,
it's precisely because
I take the exam seriously
that I chose to admit it.
But this academy
was never truly an academy,
and you were never truly a teacher.
So perhaps an omission like this
is hardly worth making a fuss over.
Very well.
As a reward for your honesty,
I'll grant your wish.
Guards!
This student's attitude is unacceptable.
Her results are invalidated.
What are you doing?
Her results are voided.
Let go of me!
[First Meeting]
Please...
don't kill me!
Nan Yanzhi,
you're so soft-hearted,
and you still want revenge?
Master,
please give me one more chance.
I'll go kill him right now.
Yanzhi,
there's no need.
You're too kind by nature.
Lingya Tower is not a place
for someone like you.
But Master,
my mother was poisoned by Lingya Tower.
I have to get the antidote!