[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 13]
You must be mistaken.
Take a closer look.
Man is so delicate—
there's no way
she could have done something like this.
What's the matter?
Your identity has been exposed—
are you lashing out in shame?
You murderer!
That's not true!
It was not me.
It was them who forced me!
They forced me!
They forced me...
Man,
I know you have your reasons,
right?
Man,
I trust you.
Do you trust me?
I want to know—
what really happened?
They all deserve to die…
all of them…
They all deserve to die!
I was never loved as a child.
My parents were gone,
my grandfather too—
just me alone.
The other kids always bullied me,
calling me a jinx.
The adults turned a blind eye.
Even stealing a bun would get me scolded.
Let go of me! Let go!
Struggling won't help,
-Jinx!
-Let go!
Your body's going to be used
sooner or later—
so it might as well be by me first.
The village women forced me
to work all day,
and at night the men took turns
abusing me.
They didn't even see me as human.
I'd been pent up for days.
So I poisoned the well,
and killed everyone in the village
with my own hands.
They all deserve to die...
They all deserve to die!
It's them who deserve it!
-They deserve it.
-Don't be afraid.
Yanzhi...
Yanzhi,
I just wanted to survive.
They forced me...
It's all over now.
It's all over.
No one can hurt you anymore.
Tower Master,
the bodies of Kou Wan and Zan Hua
have been recovered.
Although they committed
capital crimes,
they've been with me for so many years.
Find a secluded spot
and give them a proper burial
on my behalf.
Yes.
Wujiu,
how are your injuries?
Thanks to your concern, Tower Master,
my injuries are nothing serious.
Young Master,
I wasn't able
to come farther to meet you.
Please forgive me.
No need for formalities.
Having heard so much about Lingya Tower,
I came especially to see it for myself.
Welcome to the fourth level
of Lingya Tower.
Making it this far is no small feat—
so I hope you'll cherish it.
Cherish it?
We're not even having an easy time.
-What's there to cherish?
-The first four levels of Lingya Tower
are about seeking survival. The next
four levels are about seeking death.
The first four are nothing more
than a poetic game.
Only if you make it alive
to the fifth level
will you understand what it truly means
to be trapped in a hell with no escape—
even death will be out of reach.
So cherish
this final survival challenge.
Alright, I've said all that needs saying.
Take care of yourselves.
Those who wish to join this death match
can follow the mute servants.
Those who don't… fine,
you can stay here and slowly wait to die.
You…
Enough talk!
We've all come this far.
Without us,
you might not have even made it here.
Let's go.
Take this letter to the capital.
But I'm the voice-keeper of Level 1…
Inside the tower...
You don't need to worry
about what's happening inside the Tower.
I've got it all under control.
What's the matter?
Get moving.
But I…
Escort her out of the Tower.
I've already sent Wujiu away.
From here on,
do whatever you need to do.
Don't worry, Tower Master.
I'll make sure
she suffers more than death.
You rarely seem so unsettled.
What's the matter?
The Tower Master suddenly sent me
to deliver a letter.
I'm a bit worried.
Are you worried our plan
might be exposed,
or about your apprentice's safety?
Both.
Don't worry.
I've arranged for someone
to keep an eye on her.
You should be careful as well.
If nothing changes,
everything will proceed as planned.
Zhuang Wujiu,
I hope you will
put the greater good first.
[Eternal Prosperity of Lingya Tower]
I'm worried she might be in danger.
Keep an eye on her
until I get back.
[Hall of Elegance]
[Floor 4: Hall of Elegance]
This Lingya Tower really knows
how to make things interesting, huh?
First the village,
then the academy,
then the caves…
and now the Flower Pavilion.
These paintings are amazing.
Could these be the winners?
Music, chess, calligraphy, painting…
And archery.
[Hall of Elegance]
Everyone,
thank you for waiting.
[Wan Hongliu, Level 4 Voice-Keeper]
I am Wan Hongliu,
the voice-keeper of this level.
Welcome to this level's death match—
the Hall of Elegance.
The Hall of Elegance?
What is that?
Don't worry.
Let me explain everything.
[Hall of Elegance]
Before entering the death match,
you need to choose a team—
blue or red.
No matter what,
we're sticking together, right?
We choose the Red Team.
We also choose the Red Team.
That was fast.
Then only the Blue Team is left.
May I ask, President,
is there a limit on team size?
What if the numbers aren't even?
Lingya Tower never cares
about such minor details.
Team selection
is entirely up to you.
We choose the Blue Team.
I actually wanted the Blue Team all along.
It doesn't bother me.
I'll just follow you guys anyway.
Exactly.
Just… don't end up opposing that person.
Smart move.
You know it—
we're still the ones in charge here.
All right, now that the teams are set,
let me explain the rules.
This match is called
the Hall of Elegance,
so don't expect
any crude hand-to-hand fighting.
It consists of three rounds:
first, music and dance;
second, poetry and chess;
third, archery and etiquette.
Win two out of three,
and your team prevails.
The winners will
all advance to the fifth level.
Just dancing or playing chess?
That doesn't sound too difficult.
Yeah,
it doesn't seem as terrifying
as the previous levels.
Right.
This is a death match—
you mustn't take it lightly.
Got it, got it.
There's one thing I forgot to mention:
this match has a unique twist—
I, the voice-keeper, will be
joining the competition personally.
The voice-keeper is joining personally?
Then, President Wan,
which team will you be on?
Naturally, I'll be
the captain of the Red Team.
Wait, what? That's not fair!
I look forward
to your guidance, everyone.
There's little time—
hurry to the West Courtyard
and reunite with your former teammates.
She instructed us to the West Courtyard,
but no one's here to show us the way.
This level looks much bigger
than the ones before.
They're trying to be mysterious, huh?
What's this about?
Playing a game with the voice-keeper?
Are we really competing?
Let's not be so pessimistic.
We know each other—
we'll be more in sync than they ever are.
Yeah,
Yanzhi is right.
We've been through
plenty of storms already on this journey.
Hey, weren't our teammates
supposed to be here
in the West Courtyard?
I don't see a single one of them.
Ah! It hurts!
I can't take it…
Captain, you…
I haven't even started the match,
and I'm already…
Captain!
I can't take it…
Look up.
Ah…
It hurts, Captain!
It hurts so much.
I can't…
It's killing me. It really hurts…
You won't manage without some force.
You're too tense.
How else are we supposed
to get through this?
Ahem...
You're new here?
Yes.
Perfect, perfect!
You all look nice,
and your bodies are in great shape.
Clearly, you can sing and dance.
You're… the captain?
Yes,
I'm Qi Songyue.
How old are you?
Have you come of age?
Get down and keep going.
Mm…
I'm the most musically skilled
among us.
If you are better than me,
the captain can defer to you.
We're new here
and obviously not as familiar
with this place.
You should take the lead.
We're all unfortunate souls.
Age doesn't matter.
We just have to look out for each other.
So… what were you just doing?
Oh, you didn't know?
The first round is music and dance.
Everyone performs a group dance together.
If anyone makes a mistake along the way
and we end up losing,
they will face punishment.
Last time we lost,
the few who were taken
away still haven't returned.
Hey, keep pressing down like that.
But President Wan didn't even tell us.
I told you so.
That Master Wan
is the sneakiest of them all.
So…
what do we do?
If I don't dance well,
won't we…
Hey, don't worry.
Look, we're new here—
aren't there a few newcomers
on the other side as well?
Captain,
do you know what they're up to?
Normally, President Wan
and the others practice at the Qunhua Hall
in the East Courtyard.
Could you take us to observe, Captain?
As the saying goes, know your enemy.
That way, we won't fall
into chaos ourselves.