[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 8]
Golden Cave Guessing Game.
Round one.
Begin.
Golden Cave Guessing Game.
What exactly is it?
Can she really
tell the dice by sound?
Please, God,
watch over me.
Buddha, Bodhisattva Guanyin,
I beg you.
No more touching once it's shaken.
Open it.
I survived.
I survived!
[Token]
I survived.
What good are last-minute prayers?
When your luck is bad,
even the gods can't save you.
I'm doomed.
You must have made a mistake.
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Let go! Let go of me!
Stay away.
Don't come any closer.
Stay back,
or I won't go easy on you!
Stay back!
Let me go!
You've made a mistake.
Did you grab the wrong person?
Let me go!
Dao.
Don't be afraid.
I clearly won.
Why are you killing me?
Because you're stupid.
You're not following the rules.
My roll was clearly higher.
Are you sure you understand the rules?
Please, don't kill me.
I can stay here
and serve you like a slave.
Me too.
Please don't kill me.
Then as you wish.
Send them to the underworld
to serve as slaves.
No!
Don't kill me!
What are you waiting for?
Begin.
Aren't we comparing the rolls?
I actually survived.
Right.
My roll was lower than hers.
I thought I was done for.
Do you remember what that man said?
The dice decide the winner.
Not that part.
Could it be...
The mute servant will announce the winner.
That's the part.
So you mean
our victory or defeat
is decided by the mute servant?
Yes.
Then how does the mute servant
know who wins?
So our lives are in their hands?
Then how do we beat this game?
I haven't figured it out yet.
I need to watch a little longer.
Maybe I'll find a way through.
Master, the new minted coins are here.
Please inspect them.
Well done.
With these,
it won't be long before
the world
belongs to Lingya Tower.
[Long Live Lingya]
Round two of the Golden Cup Guessing Game
begins.
[Token]
The token has different patterns
on each side.
Come on.
No more touching once it's shaken.
Murder!
Why did she kill again?
Weren't the rules clear?
Only one person can win.
So as long as
she gets rid of her opponent,
no matter the outcome,
she survives.
Looks like there are no rules here at all.
To win,
she'll do anything.
Good thing I wasn't paired with her.
Who exactly is this woman?
I heard
she's a centurion of the Chilian Clan.
The number of people who died at her hands
might be more than
the people who died here.
Are we continuing or not?
Begin.
Hey.
Why haven't you opened it yet?
What are you waiting for?
Five.
[Token]
The smooth side means high.
So the other side means low.
[Token]
Dao bet on low.
That's my dice!
Give it back!
I won! I won!
My dice!
You two bet on low.
I won!
Looks like
one of you
has figured out the rules.
You've got the wrong person!
There's nothing in her dice!
I should have won!
No, my hat!
-You've got the wrong person!
-My hat! My hat!
Let me go!
Hat!
My hat!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Here.
Thank you.
Sis.
You were bitten by a snake.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Guards.
Take her away
and lock her up for two hours.
Why?
What are you doing?
Don't come here!
She disrupted the order,
so she must be punished.
If you interfere again,
I'll throw you into the snake pit too.
Dao.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
Nan Yanzhi.
What a pity.
She probably
won't make it through the night.
What do you mean?
Dao, what does that mean?
What do we do now?
Master.
I knew you would come to save me.
How many times have I told you?
The prisoners in Lingya Tower
are all serious criminals.
You can't trust them so easily.
Today, for someone you barely know,
you risked your life.
Are you trying to drive me mad?
But
you also said
entering Lingya Tower
means almost certain death.
If that's the case,
then I need real friends.
So you were foolish enough
to risk your life
to make friends?
Do you know how dangerous
the snakes down there are?
Good thing I was here.
Otherwise, you wouldn't even
be able to get out of here today.
Are these snakes really that venomous?
But I still haven't found
my mother's antidote.
What should I do?
But don't worry.
The snake venom isn't fatal.
It only knocks people out,
as if they were dead.
Once the toxin wears off,
you will be fine.
It's not venomous?
Master, why didn't you say so?
You scared me to death.
If I don't teach you a lesson now,
you'll never learn.
I can't watch over you forever.
I have important things to do.
Right.
If the people
thrown into the Ten Thousand Snake Pit
didn't die,
where did they go?