[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 14]
[Qunhua Hall]
Judging from how they look,
I don't think they're much better than us.
One, two, three, four.
Plus President Wan,
there are eight of them in total.
But we only have seven people.
Will our formation look bad?
What are you afraid of?
I think they're just putting on a front.
Are you sure...
they're just putting on a front?
I'm afraid we can't defeat them
on pure ability.
In my opinion,
we're definitely going to lose.
How come...
those two girls
look familiar to me?
They look familiar to me too.
It's you lot!
Run!
P-President Wan.
If you want to watch, do it openly.
Why do you have to be so sneaky?
President Wan,
they've always been like this—unruly
and up to no good.
How have you been, ladies?
Little did I expect
to meet you two here again.
It's all thanks to you.
You didn't sign your name.
So we became the champion.
And we reached here effortlessly.
The two of you are
so smug after taking advantage of others.
It's enough that you aren't grateful,
but to kick us when we're down
is just too much.
President Wan,
they were shamelessly peeking at us.
Such sneaky skulkers deserve punishment.
We'll teach them a lesson
on President Wan's behalf.
Don't you dare touch us!
Who are you?
How bold of you
for bringing a sharp weapon.
How dare you commit assault
in President Wan's presence!
Tu Ya!
You can't do this.
Stop pestering us,
or I won't go easy on you.
Tu Ya!
-President Wan!
President Wan,
our behavior today
was indeed inappropriate.
If that caused any offense,
I'd like to apologize to you,
President Wan, and everyone present here.
President Wan,
don't be fooled by her sweet talk.
Those who break the rules like you lot
-deserve severe punishment!
Enough.
All this yelling and arguing
is not fit for decent company!
Since they have apologized,
let's stop pursuing the matter.
Hurry up and go prepare for the match.
-President Wan!
I mean, break it up.
-Yes.
Thank you, President Wan.
[High Art]
Oh, no.
I really can't do this anymore.
It's like my waist is breaking.
My legs!
I can't keep this up.
Please spare me.
Pace yourself.
Hang in there.
Why doesn't she need to practice?
For a martial arts practitioner,
these are just basic skills.
Look how cocky she is.
Come on.
Press my legs harder.
[High Art]
That flute is from your hometown, right?
Don't be nervous.
I'm here to send you a handsome gift.
President Wan,
we are on different sides.
We have nothing to talk about.
No wonder you could be a centurion
in the Chilian Tribe.
It seems
I'd better present a big enough gift.
Cut the crap.
Just speak your mind.
Fine.
I'm looking to make a deal with you.
As long as you help me
fight against Nan Yanzhi,
I promise I will
let you go back to the Chilian Tribe.
[High Art]
All guiding rings for the voice-keepers
in Lingya Tower
are sized
according to their left ring fingers.
As for the size of this ring...
See?
It shows that the owner of this ring
has much slenderer fingers than I do.
I don't find anything
noticeably suspicious
about these girls' speech and behavior.
But as Master said,
I must not easily trust anyone.
People who have worked as voice-keepers
stay alert all the time.
She can't possibly miss
such an obvious assassination attempt.
Could she be... on the Red Team?
Who are you?
Master.
What brings you here?
The Tower Master suddenly ordered me
to deliver a letter for him.
I have a bad feeling
that someone might harm you.
Put this on to protect yourself.
Isn't it the filigree bangle
I gave you as a gift?
What exactly is going on?
I'm still investigating it.
Meanwhile, I'll try to keep you safe.
Master, I...
Now, go and get some sleep.
Don't cause extra trouble.
But...
Just go.
Nan Yanzhi.
What a surprise...
that you're acquainted
with the mute servant.
Why are you like a cat,
walking around without a sound?
Nan Yanzhi,
your death is not far off.
Are you going to kill me?
I am not the one planning
to kill you.
Today, Wan Hongliu approached me
in private,
asking me to join her in fighting you.
At this time of year,
people in the Chilian Tribe
would slaughter cattle and sheep
to celebrate the turn of the year.
At night,
everyone would gather around the bonfire,
singing, dancing,
and drinking heartily.
Now is the perfect time, isn't it?
As long as agree to help me,
you'll just be in time
to go home for the event.
It's a shame
that all my tribespeople are gone now.
At this time last year,
there was a traitor in our tribe.
All my fellow tribe members were killed.
And I was...
falsely accused
of colluding with the enemy,
which reduced me to this state.
Therefore,
in my whole life,
there's nothing I hate
more than traitors.
What we the Chilian tribespeople
despise most
is such backstabbing and shady schemes.
Tu Ya, I was simply...
Alright.
It's not safe to stay here for long.
We'd better hurry back.
Tu Ya.
Tu Ya, thank you.
I once said
we would leave this place together.
I believe we can make it happen.
Save that speech after we survive
tomorrow's death match.
You have fought many battles,
so you certainly understand
that there are always opportunities
for us till the last moment comes.
Opportunities?
Under my watch,
you will not have one single opportunity.
Everyone,
welcome to the Great Hall of Elegance.
The first round is a dance competition.
The Red and Blue Teams
will each finish a dance
to a provided tune.
The winning team will be decided
based on the quality of the performances.
The first round
officially begins now.
Lingya Tower is truly
a place of hidden talents.
Look at the dance of these beauties.
They are all graceful and charming.
Even the top courtesans
of the Moon House in the capital
might not dance better than them.
I agree.
The Red Team is going to win!
My Lady.
Look how cocky they are.
It's your turn.
I forgot to tell you something.
The girl who causes the team
to lose at the end
will be killed.
Killed?
You didn't say that at the beginning.
This last-minute statement
shouldn't be valid, right?
President Wan, you're informing us
of a new rule just when our turn arrives.
This is meant to disturb
our peace of mind, isn't it?
If I had kept it from you
till the end of the competition,
it would be even worse, wouldn't it?
On this floor managed by me,
only one person will die in each round.
You're better off here than anywhere else.
Oh no.
What's the second move?
Oh, stop talking, Dao.
You're causing me to forget stuff too.
Isn't our captain right ahead?
Just follow her lead.
Man!
That was an honest mistake.
I beg for another chance,
President Wan! I...