[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 12]
Welcome, Tower Master.
I, Zan Hua, pay my respects to you.
Tower Master, why are you doing this?
You have the nerve to ask me?
I told you to keep an eye on Kou Wan.
I didn't expect you to be bewitched by her
and even join hands with her
to deceive me.
If I hadn't discovered
that the gold coins were adulterated,
how long did you intend
to keep deceiving me?
♪ Embroidered silk robe
wet with tear stains ♪
♪ Last night in dreams,
I called your name once more ♪
♪ Cold moonlight fills the little tower,
the person has aged first ♪
♪ When red beans ripened,
you paid no heed ♪
♪ My hair flies as the wind blows ♪
♪ Empty mountains, evening snow—
dim as a painting ♪
♪ This scene is hard to forget ♪
♪ One life, one dream,
sharing endless sorrow ♪
Tower Master.
You're still calling me Tower Master.
Many years ago,
thank you
for killing Xie Quan and Ru Yue for me.
Otherwise,
I would have died in the streets long ago.
I don't know how
I can repay such a great favor.
These adulterated gold coins—
is this how you repay me?
I've never intended to disobey you.
It's just that
I can't bear to see these noble people
treat human lives as their amusement
or profit from living beings.
I had no choice
but to do that.
Tell me,
where is the rest of the gold?
For the sake of our past,
I will give you a quick death.
I know I can't escape death.
I am at your disposal, Tower Master.
You still won't talk.
Bring him in!
Tower Master!
This has nothing to do with him!
It was all done by me alone!
Please, Tower Master,
don't kill the innocent.
I'll ask you one more time.
Where is my gold?
I don't know.
In that case,
I will give you one last chance.
Kill her,
and I will be lenient with you.
Sweet words are rarely sincere.
In a fickle world,
scheming politicians abound.
I don't blame you.
Do it.
You have lived such a hard life.
How could I have the heart
to let you leave alone?
Zan.
I remember you said before
that if one is unfaithful
and drags out an ignoble existence,
that's no different
from those filthy scums.
Right?
Zan!
Outrageous!
Do you both want to die?
Tower Master!
Your kindness in raising me—
I can only repay it in the next life.
What are you going to do?
Wan.
I've never heard you play the pipa before.
When I heard it just now,
it was truly enchanting and moving,
a heavenly sound without equal.
Being able to hear you
play a song in this life,
I have no regrets.
Why are you so silly, Zan?
I will buy the best pipa.
Then I will return to the capital
and reopen the Moon House.
I will tell the world
that Ms. Kou has returned.
Hahaha.
What about you?
What do you want to do after you get out?
I don't know.
But...
if you reopen the Moon House,
I will surely be the first to come.
Then it's settled.
It's a deal.
Did you know
about Kou Wan's matter or not?
Did you join hands with her to deceive me?
Do you think I can't find out
if you don't tell me?
Tower Master!
What?
You're finally willing to talk?
Do you know
what all these things you've done
are really for?
What do you mean?
Those noble people at the Lingya Tower—
no matter what amusement they want,
we do our best to satisfy them.
Yet they still only treat us as watchdogs.
Pat us on the head when we are useful.
Spit on us when we are useless!
How dare you say such treasonous words?
Do you know what punishment you deserve?
No matter how foolish or tyrannical,
the noble are always noble.
Because they were born noble!
Even if they become idiotic trash,
they can still trample upon us!
And no matter how well we do,
in their eyes,
they will never see us as human beings.
Enough!
I'm not sure,
but from your description,
that person should be her.
You know who Voice-Keeper Taiyin is?
I've never seen
what she looks like in person.
But before, Tower Master wanted
to transfer her to my level.
Yet later, he changed his mind
for some reason.
That means...
she is on a higher level.
I've finally reached the fourth level.
I wonder how Master is doing now.
Here's some wound medicine.
Remember,
you are the daughter
of the Lingya Tower's master.
I am ashamed to have a father
like you.
Thank you.
I didn't expect Ms. Kou to actually...
Truly, good people die young.
Master and I
have killed so many people too.
Then do the two of us
count as good people or not?
Tu Ya, stop.
Jiang Man.
Man.
Are you crazy, Tu Ya?
Man,
what exactly happened?
How did you suddenly offend Tu Ya?
I just wanted to deliver some food to her
out of kindness.
I didn't know she would try to kill me.
Shut up!
I don't want anything touched by her.
If you want to live,
stay away from her too.
What's wrong with you?
Picking a fight here for no reason.
Tu Ya, what do you mean?
I hope you can explain clearly
in front of all of us.
Two years ago,
someone single-handedly
poisoned the entire Jiang Village.
I don't want to die an unnatural death.