[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 20]
Mr. Liu threatened me,
saying that witnessing this
would surely bring me death.
If I wanted to stay alive,
I had to do exactly as he said.
My Lady,
I truly feared death,
so I had no choice
but to hide the truth from you.
Is what you said true?
It was my father who killed Nian'an.
My Lady,
this is a matter of great importance.
I can only tell you exactly
what I saw and heard.
As for the truth,
I dare not make any reckless assumptions.
What do you mean ''reckless assumptions''?
Isn't it obvious?
I never thought
that the culprit who killed my husband
would actually be my father.
I have failed you, Nian'an.
My Lady! My Lady!
My Lady, are you alright?
What's the point of ending your own life?
It might bring momentary relief
and put an end to everything,
but Shen Nian'an would have died in vain.
Even if I'm resentful, what can I do?
He is my father.
Your father killed him,
and made you marry a monster.
Are you willing to be manipulated by him
for the rest of your life,
living in the shadows?
Then what should I do?
You are yourself first.
Only then are you someone's wife,
or someone's daughter.
Remember:
For your own sake,
the edge of your blade
should be firmly aimed outward.
Make those who ruined your happiness
pay the price.
For myself?
Yes.
For yourself.
Weakness and submission only make
the wicked more unscrupulous.
Jingjing.
Stand up when you're done crying.
Take the knife they gave you
and strike hard at their weak spots.
Exactly.
I want revenge.
[Prime Minister's Mansion]
Father.
The Lantern Festival is coming soon.
I would like to go to the temple
to pray for blessings.
Pray for blessings?
Why?
Father, I have figured it out.
Some things are already set in stone.
Let the past be the past.
It is time to put an end to this.
I agree to the marriage
you arranged for me.
So I want to visit the temple,
consider it fulfilling a vow
on your behalf.
Jingjing, I'm glad you've come around.
Father, after all,
this is my marriage to Mr. Liu,
I would like to invite him to join me.
All right.
Jingjing has finally changed her mind.
I'll leave this matter for you to handle.
Yes.
I will go right away.
Hey.
Why did we stop?
[Tea]
Mr. Liu, my lady is thirsty,
and wants to go in for some tea.
Tea?
Aren't we almost there?
[Tea]
My lady feels a bit tight in the chest.
There happens to be a teahouse here.
She'd like to take a short rest inside.
Fine.
Hmph.
[Tea]
I think I've been to this teahouse before.
Jingjing?
Hey.
Where did she go?
You...
Who are you?
Seems you recovered from that hit
pretty quickly.
Oh.
It was you that night.
Just you wait.
Get out of my way!
Do you know who I am?
Who are you?
A lackey sucking up to the powerful.
A freeloading son-in-law.
Or perhaps,
you're both.
What are you talking about?
I-I don't understand.
But you had better know this:
My wife is the Prime Minister's daughter!
This is the capital.
How dare you commit violence here?
Commit violence?
It seems you've forgotten
how Shen Nian'an was killed by you here.
You are talking nonsense!
If you don't want anyone to know,
don't do it in the first place.
Did you really think you could cover up
what you've done?
How could you possibly know?
Could it be that bitch Yang?
Nian'an,
if your spirit is watching from heaven,
watch closely.
Today,
justice will be served for you!
Please let me go.
Please.
Let you go?
You will die the exact same way
Shen Nian'an did.
No.
You'll pay back double.
You've got it wrong.
I didn't kill Shen Nian'an!
It was
Prime Minister Lin
who insisted on killing him.
It has nothing to do with me!
Shen Nian'an was Prime Minister Lin's
honored son-in-law.
For no reason,
why would he kill Shen Nian'an?
You must have instigated
and bewitched the Prime Minister Lin.
That's not true.
Shen Nian'an
was investigating Lingya Tower
and found out
that Prime Minister Lin was involved.
What is the relation between
Prime Minister Lin and Lingya Tower?
I don't know!
All I know is
that Prime Minister Lin has always
had dealings with Lingya Tower.
Many officials in the court
were also introduced
by Prime Minister Lin.
I knew this matter involved many people,
so I kept advising Shen Nian'an
not to dig any deeper.
But he wouldn't listen,
insisted on handling it impartially.
You know how to wash your hands of guilt,
don't you?
Shen Nian'an investigating Lingya Tower,
if no one had reported it,
how would Prime Minister Lin have known?
You must have sold him out
to curry favor with Prime Minister Lin.
No, it wasn't like that.
Listen to me.
Prime Minister Lin has eyes and ears
all over the court.
How could Shen Nian'an's investigation
possibly escape his notice?
Think about it, right?
Prime Minister Lin found out
that Shen Nian'an held
a detailed ledger of
the gold flowing into Lingya Tower.
That's why he came to me,
wanting my help to get the ledger.
Oh.
So it was you
who tricked Shen Nian'an into coming here
and forced him to hand over the ledger.
Where is the ledger now?
Of course Prime Minister Lin took it.
It seems keeping you alive is useless.
Wait, wait! No, no, no!
Don't kill me.
I know where the thing you want is.
Inside Prime Minister Lin's room,
there is a secret chamber.
Shen Nian'an's ledger
is kept right there!
The sound from this wall is strange.
The secret chamber must be right here.
Master, look.
There are scratches on it.
The secret chamber.
Why are there so many gold coins
from Lingya Tower here?
Ah!
[Blueprint Collection of Lingya Tower]
This...
[Patterns]
[Gate] [Fence]
This is the design draft my father drew
for Lingya Tower years ago.
It really is him.
What's wrong, Master?
Every noble who enters Lingya Tower
has their own unique mask.
And this one belongs to Hei Ya.
Are you saying
that Prime Minister Lin is Hei Ya?
Yes.
Heroine.
I wasn't lying, was I?
I was truly forced into this.
Please let me go.
Jingjing, why is it you?
Every single thing you did
and every single word you said,
I heard it all.
Jingjing.
It's not what it sounded like.
What I said today was just
an expedient measure.
If my life wasn't at stake,
I would never have done this.
I thought you were just a hypocrite,
a power-hungry sycophant.
But I didn't expect
you to bite the hand that feeds you.
You are worse than a beast!
Jingjing,
listen to me.
Liu Yuan.
You can treat me as a stepping stone
to your success.
But your fatal mistake
was harming my Nian'an.
Today,
I will avenge my Nian'an
with my own hands.
Master.
The death match for the Lantern Festival
is fully prepared.
Bets can be opened at any time.
No rush.
Our honored guests have yet to arrive.
Wait a bit longer.
Yes.