[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 1]
Master.
[One month earlier...]
You're the only one who can't keep up.
I went to great lengths
to hide among these death row prisoners,
just to enter Lingya Tower
and find the antidote for my mother.
Master said Lingya Tower
is extremely well hidden.
Lingya Tower has 8 levels,
each guarded by a voice-keeper
who leads a group of mute servants.
The voice-keepers organize death matches,
forcing female prisoners
to fight one another to the death
for the entertainment of wealthy elites.
They treat human lives as worthless
and have no shred of conscience left.
For my mother,
I must enter this living hell
no matter what.
Food is here.
How are we supposed to eat this?
It's gone bad.
What do you mean?
Say something!
He's a mute servant. He can't speak.
He means
that by the time it's our turn,
this is all that'll be left for us.
What do you mean this is all that's left
by the time it's our turn?
Why is that?
Food
is distributed
from top to bottom here.
Those at the top
always get to pick first.
Then how do we
get to the upper levels?
Each level of Lingya Tower
has a death match.
The prisoners here fight,
wagering their lives on it.
If you win,
you move up a level.
If you reach the top,
you may win your freedom.
But if you lose,
you die.
Gambling with your life, huh?
If I want to join this death match,
what should I do?
Then you'd better find a way
to meet the voice-keeper first.
How do I meet the voice-keeper then?
Unless you go looking for death,
it won't happen.
-Are you alright?
-Are you okay?
[Zhuang Wujiu, Level 1 Voice-keeper]
In Lingya Tower,
suicide is the gravest taboo.
Hasn't anyone told you that?
Speak.
What are you plotting?
I want to take part in the death match.
It's been a long time
since I saw someone so eager to die.
If you're looking for death,
I'll grant your wish.
Go.
[Death Match]
Report to the Tower Master.
A death match will be held
on the lowest level.
Don't take it.
Whoever takes it
has to enter the death match.
-A death match?
If we're going to starve anyway,
we might as well fight for our lives.
-Yeah.
-Right.
We might as well take our chances.
Yes. Better to risk our lives
than starve to death.
Don't eat it.
Dear honored guests,
an additional match will
be held on the lowest level tonight.
I wonder
if you'd be interested.
What kind of match is it this time?
Yes, how does it work?
How many female prisoners have arrived?
[Level 1: Eight-Trigrams Death Match]
Welcome, everyone,
to the Eight-Trigrams Death Match.
You have 10 drumbeats.
Only those who find the Gate of Life
[Qian] [Kun] [Zhen] [Xun]
[Kan] [Li] [Gen] [Dui]
may leave
and advance to the next level.
Let the death match
begin.
You nearly scared me to death.
I thought you were
one of the mute servants.
Did you find…
Yanzhi.
It's me.
I saw so many people die
on my way here.
This
drumbeat is deafening.
It's terrifying.
That's the 2nd drumbeat.
If we don't find the exit
before the 10th drumbeat,
we'll all die here.
Huh?
Yanzhi.
I don't want to die.
This way.
An exit?
This isn't the real exit.
It's not real?
Man,
how many drumbeats have there been?
If I remember correctly,
it should be the 6th drumbeat.
We're running out of time.
We need to find the real exit fast.
Alright.
-Let's go.
How was it?
Dear honored guests,
are you satisfied with your picks?
I bet on 5 people,
and 4 of them died.
Damn, that's bad luck.
Play a few more rounds,
and you'll get the hang of it.
Hurry.
That's the 7th drumbeat already.
Three more,
and we're done for, aren't we?
With so many doors, when are we
supposed to find the right one?
The note.
[Qian] [Kun] [Zhen] [Xun]
[Kan] [Li] [Gen] [Dui]
This map shows eight doors in total.
We've already checked 6 of them.
[Qian] [Kun] [Zhen] [Xun]
[Kan] [Li] [Gen] [Dui]
My guess is
that the Gate of Life lies
in either the Qian or Dui direction.
We're running out of time—
we have to split up
if we want a chance to survive.
Alright,
you take this door.
I'll go over there.
Hey, take this,
and take care of yourself.