[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 3]
Is it done?
Along with the two attendants,
they've been disposed of as well.
It's his own arrogance to blame.
He didn't even know who he offended.
But he was our guest after all.
What if someone looks into it?
Don't worry.
The one who wanted him dead
will handle it.
Where did you go
during tonight's death match?
I saw the death match was about to fail,
so I planned to step in myself.
Unexpectedly,
I was still too late,
and accidentally let those three
slip through by luck.
It doesn't matter.
Even if
they escape this level,
they will die sooner or later.
But Wujiu,
I have to remind you:
if I find out
that it was you
who broke the rules of Lingya Tower,
I will absolutely show no mercy.
We've had our fun
and the vermin have been eliminated.
Send those three
up to the next level.
Yes.
[Second Level: Elite Academy]
Where is this?
Are we out of Lingya Tower?
Is this yours?
Who told you to touch it?
I didn't.
I didn't know it was yours.
I just picked it up.
If you ever touch my things again,
I'll chop your hands off, got it?
How can you be so unreasonable?
-She meant well.
-I don't need it.
Can you two stop
being so hypocritical here?
What is this place?
Lingya Tower.
You know exactly
what kind of people you are,
and how you got in here.
Don't play dumb.
In Lingya Tower,
it's either kill
or be killed.
Don't give me that sisterhood nonsense
or your scheming tricks.
Right.
There are no good people in this tower.
They are all beasts.
But an extra ally
is better than an extra enemy, right?
Who knows, maybe when you die one day,
someone might be there to bury you.
How kind of you.
Speak no evil.
[The Voice-keeper of the Second Level:
Qin Yuren]
I am the voice-keeper here.
Qin Yuren.
You can call me Madam Qin.
Your mother was poisoned
by Lingya Tower's toxin.
I can only temporarily contain its spread.
Master,
what is this?
The Guiding Ring.
Welcome to the death match
on the second level of Lingya Tower.
Death match?
It's starting so soon?
Our Elite School
uses exams as death matches.
Those with excellent grades
can be promoted to the upper level.
The rest who fail,
as long as they're willing
to remain my students,
can stay here indefinitely.
That sounds
a million times better
than the lower level, doesn't it?
This...
This place is so nice!
Why don't we just stay here?
Then we don't have to
take part in any death matches.
Stay if you want.
Looking at all these books
just gives me a massive headache.
If we stay here,
without participating in the death match
or attending these classes,
what will happen to us?
If someone always fails to learn,
they're definitely a bad student.
When such a hard-won opportunity
isn't cherished,
then the only option is
to kill them.
[First Meeting]
My mother made this rabbit meat
especially for you.
Can I be your apprentice?
I like rabbit meat too.
Can you teach me how to catch them?
Look, my braiding isn't that bad, right?
Master.
When will you start teaching me?
When did I agree
to take you as my apprentice?
For the sake of me combing your hair,
won't you consider it, Master?
I've never taken an apprentice.
I don't know how to teach.
I've never had a master either.
We can just look out for each other.
I'll think about it.
I'll take that as a yes.
Let's pinky swear on it.
No backing out.
Do you know how much pain and suffering
it takes to master these skills?
Look, Master!