[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 15]
The outcome is decided.
Blue Team made a mistake
in their dance
and failed to complete the performance.
This round
goes to Red Team.
Great!
We won!
Next
is the second round
of the Hall of Elegance competition:
Shi Qi.
Each team captain will appoint one person
to finish this game of chess.
When playing,
before placing a piece,
you must state the corresponding number
and Chinese character
[Home] [People] [Mountain]
[Dynasty]
for the intersection point
[Star]
based on the vertical
and horizontal lines on the board.
[Star] [Wind] [Sky]
A poem must be recited
before a piece is placed.
Exceeding the time limit means a loss.
Who can play such a complicated game?
Didn't I say the captains would choose?
Isn't that a death sentence
for whoever volunteers?
Not necessarily.
If you win,
you won't have to die.
Captain, don't pick me.
I don't know how to play chess.
I don't want to die.
Not only do you have to play chess,
you also have to recite poetry.
This is too...
How about...
I'll do it.
Nan Yanzhi.
Yanzhi.
I can't let you do it.
Don't worry.
It just so happens
that I know a bit of both.
How could you compete yourself?
I said
the captains choose the players,
but I never said
they couldn't choose themselves.
You...
We're doomed.
Now that President Wan steps
into the arena herself,
isn't Yanzhi in grave danger?
With voice-keeper stepping in personally,
it's certain death.
Is that so?
I beg to differ.
I'll wager a thousand taels
Hmm.
on her winning.
I want to meet someone.
I heard
she is in your Lingya Tower.
When the time comes,
I'll use my wager as a signal
to tell you who I want to meet.
The second round of the Hall of Elegance,
Shi Qi,
officially begins.
White snow on the three rivers
returns to the green mound,
the endless Yellow River
winds around black mountains.
[Snow] [Flower]
[Snow] [Three]
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
There is a time limit for making a move.
A timeout will result in a loss.
[Si hour] [Wu hour]
Past glories of the Six Dynasties
fade with the river's flow,
[Dynasty]
leaving only cold mist and dying grass
in a stagnant green glow.
[Six]
Seven or eight stars glimmer
beyond the sky,
two or three drops of rain fall
before the mountain.
[Star]
How can she make every move so fast?
[Wu hour] [Wei hour]
A cup of wine to go with a brand new song,
The weather and pavilion
remain the same as last year.
If Yanzhi takes this long every time,
will she lose?
She is definitely going to lose.
President Wan designed this board.
She knows every poem
corresponding to each character by heart.
How could a few cups of weak wine
[Star] [Wind] [Sky]
withstand
the rushing evening wind?
[Wind]
The year is drawing to a close tonight,
yet the wanderer is still miles from home.
May snow still blankets
the Tianshan peaks,
No flowers bloom,
only the biting cold speaks.
If you resign now,
I can let you choose how to die.
You'd better save it for yourself.
One flake, two flakes, three or four,
five flakes, six flakes, seven or eight.
Thousands, myriads, countless flakes,
flying into the plum blossoms,
vanishing from sight.
What kind of doggerel is this?
How can it count?
This is an imperial poem written
by His Majesty himself.
How could it not count?
Fine.
I'll let it pass.
You're just clinging to your last breath.
A thousand fathoms of iron chains
sink to the riverbed,
a banner of surrender rises
from Stone City overhead.
Sure enough.
How could these female prisoners
outsmart voice-keeper?
-The game is not set yet.
-That is right.
It's still uncertain who will win.
The seven-string zither plays a cold,
desolate sound,
true understanding
of this art has rarely been found.
My victory is certain.
One more move and she loses.
[Hai hour]
We first met when we were young.
You were fifteen.
I was seventeen.
Consider yourself lucky.
Time's up.
President Wan ran out of time!
So Nan Yanzhi won?
This round,
you win.
Ah!
-We won!
We won!
Weren't you supposed to die if you lost?
Yeah.
How can you just kill people randomly?
The loser
just needs to pick someone to die for her.
As long as someone dies, it's fine.
How could voice-keeper lose?
Could the women
from Lingya Tower play dirty?
Since ancient times,
gamblers must accept their losses.
Are you going
to renege on a promise with me,
a weak woman?
Humph.
Today,
we've fought two consecutive rounds,
with each side winning one.
I'm sure everyone is exhausted.
Let's call it a day.
Go back and rest.
We'll fight again tomorrow.
The final result
will be decided
by tomorrow's ritual archery.
President Wan,
what are the details of the third round?
Please explain everything at once.
That way,
we can rest easy.
You can rest assured.
Tomorrow's third round
will take place
in full view of the public,
competing in ritual manners
and archery skills.
How can these two
be competed simultaneously?
The Red and Blue Teams will
each choose four people.
Two of them will be dressed
in full ceremonial attire
to perform the ritual of bowing to Heaven.
The other two stand on the opposite side
holding feathered arrows,
aiming at the jewels
adorning their teammates' hairpins.
Shooting our own people?
Exactly.
The ritual performers
will each hold a bowl of dew.
When the arrow is shot,
Any body movement
results in a one-point deduction.
If dew spills from the bowl,
two points are deducted.
If there are mistakes in the ritual,
five points are deducted.
If the jade bowl breaks,
you'll lose the competition immediately.
What if we accidentally
hit our teammate?
Then you can only
consider yourself unlucky.
But there are also bonus points
for shooting well.
How?
Each archer has three arrows.
Hitting a jewelry
on the ritual performer's head
adds five points.
How do we decide who performs the ritual
and who holds the bow?
By drawing lots.
President Wan,
I have a request.
Speak.
Since the rules are clear,
I request President Wan
to draw lots now.
Alright.
As you wish.
Let's choose people.
Just the four of you.
We've made our choice.
What about you?
Since you guys know each other,
you must have better teamwork.
Yes, exactly.
You guys go ahead.
Count me in.
Okay.
Now we have exactly four people.
Somebody!
[Shoot]
[Ritual]
Now that the lots are drawn,
everyone go back and prepare.
See you tomorrow.
I wonder what tricks Wan Hongliu
will play tomorrow.
I read the rules for the third round.
Yanzhi has already made it clear
with President Wan.
I suppose she won't play any more tricks.
Hard to say.
How could someone used to playing dirty
suddenly become honest?
What's going on?
Is it Wan Hongliu?
You stay here and protect them.
I'll go out and take a look.
Nan Yanzhi.
Who are you?
How do you know my name?
I once bought your life
at the Lingya Tower casino.
Of course I know who you are.
Bought my life?
So you are from the higher-ups.
I wouldn't have thought
that a seemingly gentle
young lady like you
could also be a devil
who treats human lives like grass.
But we have never met before.
Never met before?
If it weren't for you,
my husband wouldn't have died.
Your husband?
You beheaded him
and abandoned his body in the wild.
Have you forgotten all this?
Only those on death row
would be brought to Lingya Tower.
How did you sneak in here?
The newly appointed top scholar
was beheaded and dumped outside the city.
The killer hasn't been caught yet.
I went to the authorities
to turn myself in
and took the blame.
Your husband was the new top scholar,
Shen Nian'an?
You remember now?
I didn't kill him.
I only took the blame for the killer
so that I could get into Lingya Tower.
Do you think I would believe you?
Everyone avoids Lingya Tower
like the plague.
You would confess to a capital crime
just to get in?
Sometimes,
the more dangerous the place,
the deeper the truth is hidden.
I don't believe your nonsense.
Today,
I will avenge my husband
with my own hands!
Wait.
I've seen his body.
He was killed with a single strike.
The wound on his neck is clean,
caused by a sharp, heavy weapon.
How could a woman like me
manage that?
Moreover,
before he died,
the tendons in his wrists and ankles
were severed.
This wasn't merely murder.
It was an act of vengeance.
Think about it carefully.
Who could possibly
hate him that much?
So much
that they wanted to make him
unable to even beg for death?