=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 21=
What are you doing?
Your Majesty.
What's been wrong with you lately?
You've been avoiding me this whole time.
I still have matters
to handle in my palace.
I'll take my leave first.
What were you two
talking about just now?
Why doesn't Your Majesty
ask Miss Shen instead?
I still need to visit the Empress.
I'll take my leave.
Go ask Handan about it.
Find out what
Shen Zhinian is upset about.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
I went to Tinglan Palace,
but Lady Shen and Handan were both gone.
Why is she suddenly angry with me?
What did I do yesterday to upset her?
Why not go comfort her, Your Majesty?
How?
Just do what Lady Shen usually does.
Didn't you say
she's the best at comforting people?
Send someone to check Tinglan Palace.
The moment she returns,
report to me immediately.
Yes.
Once we find her grandfather,
give her this death-exemption medal.
Where's the medal?
If Young Lady
wanted to avoid His Majesty,
there was no need
to crawl through a dog hole.
His men are guarding outside.
I don't want to see him.
His Majesty already gave you
the death-exemption medal,
and now he wants it back.
Isn't that bullying you?
He even deceived your grandfather.
Men really are like venomous snakes
once they turn heartless.
Your Majesty.
Leave us.
Yes.
About the death-exemption medal,
listen to my explanation first.
There's no need to explain,
Your Majesty.
You've never trusted me.
And now you want
to use my grandfather's family
to keep me under control.
That's not true.
Of course not.
I was the one who judged a gentleman
with the heart of a petty person.
I'll take my leave.
Your grandfather's
disappearance was an accident.
After hearing you mention them,
I only wanted to bring them
to the capital so you could reunite.
As for the death-exemption medal,
I forgot to withdraw the decree.
Since I already granted it,
why would I take it back?
I remember every word Your Majesty said,
and I believed all of it.
But there are always so many things
you keep hidden from me.
(Nangong Xuanyu.)
(Have you truly never trusted me?)
(Shen Zhinian.)
(What will it take for you to trust me?)
Your Majesty,
you're just
coming back like this?
Tonight is the full moon.
Do you expect me
to lose control in front of her?
I'll go prepare the water.
Come back.
She even managed
to get into my secret chamber.
I don't know whether to call
her bold or reckless.
And all of you,
with so many eyes watching,
yet none of you noticed
someone sneaking in.
Your Majesty,
I have an idea
to calm Lady Shen down.
Speak.
Women are soft hearted
and easily sympathize with others.
If Lady Shen sees
how much Your Majesty suffers
when the poison flares up,
she'll surely soften up
and stop blaming you.
I don't make a habit
of acting pitiful in front of women.
Only useless men do that.
I clearly tied it shut.
How did you get in?
Why are you burning up?
Are you sick?
Let go of me.
Nangong Xuanyu,
let go of me!
You are the Son of Heaven.
Please show some restraint.
Shen Zhinian,
don't leave me.
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
Forgive me, Lady Shen.
Whenever there's a full moon,
His Majesty's poison flares up.
At times like this,
he must avoid intimacy with women.
You mean
he's poisoned?
After His Majesty was born,
the late Emperor
personally forced poison into him.
As he grew older, the poison attacks
became worse and worse.
Every full moon,
it's like being trapped
between unbearable
freezing cold and scorching heat.
His muscles and bones
feel as if they're
being torn apart piece by piece.
What about the antidote?
While the late Dowager Consort
was still alive,
she did obtain the antidote.
But unfortunately, before the antidote
could be delivered to His Majesty,
the late Dowager Consort passed away,
and the medicine disappeared with her.
Then
go look for it now.
It can no longer be found.
That medicine was made
by the late Dowager Consort
using her own heart's
blood as the catalyst.
The bond between mother and child.
There was only ever
one pill in this world.
Take him back.
Could My Ladyship please help
care for His Majesty tonight?
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪
Because of the poison
in His Majesty's body,
his wounds are always slow to heal.
But the path to the throne
is filled with danger.
His injuries
have never truly healed.
(His injuries are this severe,)
(and he still runs around
everywhere every day.)
(Why doesn't the pain kill you already?)
Serves you right for taking my medal.
Serves you right
for taking my grandfather's family away
without telling me.
Serves you right
for losing my grandfather.
Tyrant.
Cold blooded.
Cruel.
That feels good.
Your Majesty.
What's going on?
I didn't sleep at all last night,
and I had to attend
morning greetings first thing today.
I'm exhausted.
Lord Jiang, do you need something again?
My father's case
has already been handed over
to the Court of Judicial Review.
For a while,
I won't be entering the palace again.
But I still can't stop worrying
about the Empress.
I'd like to trouble Lady Shen
to look after Her Highness for me.
If the Empress ever needs me,
I'll do everything I can.
Thank you.
After this, I'll resign
and travel through the south.
Lord Jiang was never meant
to be confined by court life.
I'm sure everything
will go smoothly for you.
She's really difficult to deal with,
prickly from head to toe.
No wonder she's such
a perfect match for Nangong Xuanyu.
Then what do we do now?
Since that's the case,
doesn't Nangong Xuanyu
want to find the Prince of Jin?
Release Song Yuqing.
Why is Your Majesty
holding my imperial decree?
Are you going back on your word again?
About the death-exemption medal,
I wasn't the one
who ordered it intercepted.
And your grandfather
wasn't abducted on my orders either.
I've already explained everything.
Why won't you believe me?
You claim to value fairness,
but where is that fairness?
You're the one who drew me in first.
Fine.
You want to talk about fairness, right?
Then let me spell it out for you.
The first time
we met in the Cold Palace,
weren't you trying
to push me into the lake?
At Shanglin Garden,
when I was nearly strangled to death,
didn't you just stand there and watch?
When I was in the Cold Palace,
you ignored me completely.
If Handan hadn't been poisoned first,
the one in trouble would've been me.
Was that fair to me?
You're arrogant, and suspicious by nature.
You don't actually think
I really like you, do you?
You said you liked me
just to deceive me.
Shen Zhinian,
that's deceiving the Emperor.
I wouldn't dare.
What is there that you wouldn't dare do?
Last night,
you poked at my wound
six times in a row.
You were counting?
Wait,
you were conscious last night?
How much did you hear?
Everything.
Everything?
Shen Zhinian,
I feel pain too.
My chest is practically
full of holes from your poking.
That was because
Your Majesty was already injured.
I don't care.
You still have to take responsibility.
Why are you acting shamelessly?
And if I refuse?
What will you do?
Exterminate my whole clan again?
Can you stop throwing accusations at me?
I've never slaughtered innocent people.
Sorry.
It's all my fault.
(He actually apologized?)
Your Majesty,
good news.
we found them.
Yiqing.
Bao'er.
Zhinian.
Aunt.
Are you alright?
I am He Yiqing. Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
What exactly happened?
Why did you go to Mount Nanhua?
Where's Grandfather?
It's a long story.
Hyah!
Who would've thought
that not long after
Zhinian entered the capital,
she'd already risen to Lady of Beauty
and even brought us
to the capital to reunite.
Zhinian has finally made it
through the hard times.
Indeed.
Stop for a moment.
Stop the carriage.
This doesn't look
like the road to the capital.
Lady Shen is praying at South Mountain.
We're taking a detour to South Mountain.
Move.
Hyah!
Grandfather,
those men just now looked unfamiliar.
They weren't
the same people from before.
I thought so too.
Officer,
Bao'er has an upset stomach.
He'll go into the woods.
Wouldn't want
to offend you with the smell.
Go on then.
Don't wander too far.
Come on, Bao'er.
Why aren't they back yet?
Did they run away?
Let's go.
Go check.
Hyah!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Don't run!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Along the way,
Bao'er and I
almost didn't make it back alive.
We finally managed to escape,
but on the way,
we ran into another group.
They seemed to be searching
for some kind of herb,
shouting about burning it all down.
Luckily,
His Majesty's men
found us in the end.
Eunuch Ming, take Young Master He
and Bao'er away to rest first.
As you command.
We'll take our leave first.
Zhinian,
do you know
what's special about Mount Nanhua?
The land and water
at Mount Nanhua are excellent.
Many rare medicinal herbs grow there.
Back then, my mother often went
to Mount Nanhua to gather herbs.
At that time,
your mother should've already married
into the Shen family as a concubine.
Why would she frequently
go to Mount Nanhua?
I don't know the reason either.
I only remember
that every month,
my mother would leave at the same time
with someone from outside.
Unfortunately,
I was too young back then
to remember what
that person looked like.
But I do remember
a bright red scar on the person's wrist.
A scar?
Come with me.
Have you seen these women before?
No.
These are portraits
of my mother and Madam Lian.
Do you see the red scar on the wrist?
It was left behind by a secret
punishment used in the palace.
First, the hand is cut off,
then bone nails
are driven into a wooden hand.
One of Madam Lian's hands
is made of wood.
You mean
the person meeting with my mother
might have been someone from the palace?
Or perhaps...
it was Madam Lian herself?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪