=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 17=
Your Majesty.
You're here.
I specially had
Peng fish sent from Chizhou as tribute.
I knew you'd like it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Are Your Majesty's eyes uncomfortable?
Why are you leaning in so close?
You usually seem quite clever.
Your eyes are the problem.
What did I do now?
Please enlighten me, Your Majesty.
No.
Figure it out yourself.
Why pretend to be clueless?
Why is Your Majesty so angry?
Your cheeks are puffed up from it.
Impudent.
You dare pinch my face?
I know my mistake.
The dragon's head,
the dragon's face,
the dragon's mouth,
are to be revered,
not touched.
Of everything about you,
your mouth is the sharpest.
Thank you for the praise, Your Majesty.
I wasn't praising you.
I was scolding you.
I can't hear it.
As long as people call me sharp tongued,
quick witted,
or fierce,
I take it all as praise.
When you face a true enemy,
that sharp tongue of yours
won't be enough to protect you.
♪A fair lady sighs, what eve is this?♪
The enemy's eyes,
the enemy's throat,
the enemy's heart.
Drive it in deeply like this,
then pull it out hard.
Shen Zhinian,
if anyone dares offend you in the future,
use this hairpin
and kill him.
(Yuehui Pavilion)
What are they doing?
Looks like His Majesty is
teaching Lady Shen martial arts.
Martial arts?
Is she planning to fight
beside him on the battlefield too?
Your Highness, let's return to the palace.
Go tell His Majesty
that I won't be attending
his birthday banquet.
Your Highness,
Young Master said
you should worry less
and rest more.
Don't do anything you shouldn't.
So my brother still
has time to worry about me?
All his attention
is on Shen Zhinian now.
Hurry and deliver
the item to His Majesty.
Otherwise later,
His Majesty won't even have time for me.
Yes.
Ah.
So boring.
I really want to leave
the palace and have some fun.
Your Ladyship.
Why are you looking so upset?
His Majesty is taking Shen Zhinian
out of the palace
and wants you to cover
for them before the Dowager Consort.
That slave driver
only knows how to work me to death.
Here.
What is it?
Open it and see.
(Death-exemption medal)
A death-exemption medal?
Didn't you refuse to give me one before?
Why are you suddenly
giving it to me now?
When did I ever say I wouldn't?
The time simply wasn't right yet.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
we're about to leave the city.
Mm.
Where are we going?
I'm taking this year's poetry champion
to pay respects
to the owner of Xunlu Pavilion.
Your Majesty's mother?
Mm.
(Imperial Temple)
This is where
Your Majesty lived as a child?
Mm.
After Mother passed away,
I was thrown into a dog kennel.
Your Majesty.
What?
Feeling sorry for me?
Mm.
You're coaxing me again.
I mean it sincerely.
When I was little,
I once raised a mountain sparrow.
Its song was beautiful,
like music from the heavens.
Back then, I only had a bowl
of thin porridge each day,
yet every day,
I still fed it the first spoonful.
What happened after that?
Later, the mountains
were sealed off by heavy snow.
After the last grain of rice was gone,
I fed it with blood from my fingertips.
In the end,
it starved to death?
I ate it.
You ate it?
Are you afraid of me?
I'm not that mountain sparrow.
If one day Your Majesty runs out of food,
I will surely find food
to keep both Your Majesty
and myself alive.
You?
Support me?
Mm.
Though women may seem weak,
for the sake of those they cherish,
they can become
the strongest shield.
I'm like that,
and Your Majesty's mother was the same.
Your Majesty,
may I visit Dowager Consort Qin now?
♪All the spring colors
lean toward one person♪
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
(Your Highness,)
(I, Shen Zhinian,
pay my respects to you.)
(His Majesty has suffered
greatly along the way.)
(Spirit Tablet of Mother Consort Qin)
(They say a mother and child are always connected at heart.)
(Please visit him
in his dreams more often.)
What did you say
to my mother just now?
I'm not telling you.
It's a secret.
I heard that after ascending the throne,
Your Majesty improved the eternal lamps
in the Imperial Temple.
No matter how fierce the wind,
the eternal lamps never go out.
Seems it's true.
May I ask why Your Majesty is so obsessed
with eternal flames?
There used to
be a punishment in the palace.
Every time an eternal lamp went out,
the prisoner would suffer even more.
Let go of my mother!
- Let go of my mother!
- The eternal lamp has gone out.
- Add twenty lashes.
- Let go of my mother!
Let go of my mother!
Add twenty more lashes.
Stop blowing out the candles!
- Add thirty lashes.
- The eternal lamp can't go out!
No!
Since you like eternal lamps so much,
then I'll give it to you.
No!
If Your Majesty's mother
can see from heaven
that Your Majesty is living well now,
she would surely be happy.
Perhaps.
She definitely would.
Report.
Everything has been prepared.
Let's go.
Why is there a fish tank here?
There are fish.
Peng fish?
Why are there Peng fish here?
When I was little,
I always ran a high fever in winter.
My mother and Madam Lian
personally made this fish tank.
Every so often, Madam Lian
would bring back a Peng fish.
Whenever I had a fever,
she would use
the Peng fish gills to reduce it.
But Peng fish only exist in Chizhou.
And using Peng fish gills to reduce fever
is also a folk remedy from Chizhou.
How did Madam Lian know about it?
I don't know either.
Nor do I know where the fish came from.
I only remember that they were always
covered in injuries.
They sacrificed too much
for my sake.
I hope in their next lives,
they can live free of all worries.
This visit to the Imperial Temple today
truly surprised me, Your Majesty.
Why?
Only today did I realize
that Your Majesty
is also an ordinary person
of flesh and blood.
And only now do I understand
why Your Majesty
became the Nangong Xuanyu you are today.
♪A fair lady sighs, what eve is this?♪
♪You ride the wind,
stunning and graceful♪
Shen Zhinian.
Mm.
♪You do not know that nothing
is sweeter than a fleeting love♪
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
In the future, whatever I have,
I'll give to you.
Why aren't you thanking me yet?
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Why are you walking so fast?
It's getting late.
We should return to the palace quickly.
(Tinglan Palace)
Handan,
go find an escort agency
and send this token to Chizhou
for my maternal grandfather.
What?
Don't ask. Just go.
Yes.
Your Majesty, the people sent to escort
Lady Shen's maternal family
were ambushed at Mount Nanhua.
Their whereabouts are now unknown.
Send more people to search.
I want to see them alive,
or their bodies if dead.
Yes.
Why Mount Nanhua again?
What exactly is hidden there?
This is bad.
If something happens
to Lady Shen's maternal family,
it'll be hard to explain things to her.
Send more men immediately.
Yes.
Your Majesty, Lady Shen sent Miss Handan
to an escort agency
to deliver this item.
(Death-exemption medal)
Who told you to intercept this?
Your Majesty previously ordered
that every item leaving Tinglan Palace
must first be intercepted
for Your Majesty's inspection.
This is bad.
(Death-exemption medal)
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪