=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 22=
Yiqing, tell me everything
that happened on the way here,
from beginning to end.
Alright.
At first,
everything seemed normal.
But after we reached
the foot of Mount Nanhua,
I overheard the guards
talking inside the carriage.
They said...
The master from the palace
usually acts like a living bodhisattva,
but turns out she's just as ruthless.
Now that they've arrived
at Mount Nanhua,
there's no way
they'll make it out alive.
Hey.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Shut your mouth.
Then why didn't you tell
His Majesty just now?
I was afraid he might be
that so called bodhisattva.
It couldn't be him.
How does he
look anything like a bodhisattva?
Then who else
in the palace could be called one?
Could it be...
Dowager Consort Liu?
She was the first to go to Mount Nanhua,
and the Liu family
has always wanted more power.
It's not impossible.
Grandfather
is still missing.
What if something happens to him?
Don't worry.
We'll find him.
This...
These prayer beads...
Weren't they buried years ago?
Back then, Grandfather said
these beads were unlucky.
What kind of prayer beads
have one hundred and nine beads?
Take them off right now.
One hundred and nine?
You're right.
How could this happen?
Yiqing,
do you still remember
the person
who used to meet with my mother?
Why bring him up?
After Aunt was drowned,
he never appeared again.
He was from the same hometown
as your mother.
What a heartless man.
He was from the same hometown
as my mother?
Yes.
I heard
they even grew up together.
Then can you be sure
it was really a man?
Of course it was a man.
I just don't know his name.
Grandfather never allowed
anyone to mention him.
That man even secretly
came to see Aunt twice.
Grandfather was furious over it.
I really don't know
what spell Aunt was under.
Not only did she insist on seeing him,
she even followed him
to Mount Nanhua to gather herbs.
(Could it really be as I suspected?)
(Could Madam Lian
have disguised herself as a man?)
This is bad.
Bao'er is missing.
What?
That little troublemaker.
How could she run around like this?
What if she gets taken away
by that so called bodhisattva?
It's alright. Don't worry.
Stay here. I'll go look for her.
An assassin has entered the palace.
Every corner must be searched carefully.
No place can be overlooked.
Yes.
Whose child is this?
I'm from Lady Shen's side.
What?
Shen Zhinian
actually has a child this old?
His Majesty even brought
her child into the palace?
Are you a consort too?
You're so pretty.
What's the point of being pretty?
His Majesty still likes
your mother,
who's not even pretty at all.
My mother is pretty too.
My mother will hit you with a pot lid.
You're not allowed
to talk about my mother like that.
Don't cry.
Hey, don't cry.
No crying.
Your Majesty,
you even brought
her child into the palace.
Do you love her that much?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Bao'er.
Come here quickly.
Don't cry anymore.
It's alright now.
Your Majesty,
please don't scare Bao'er.
Your Highness.
When did I scare him?
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I shouldn't have offended you.
Shen Zhinian,
my chest hurts.
Your Majesty, stop acting like a child.
You're not hurting at all.
Shen Zhinian,
even if you gave me
just a little of your affection,
I'd still be happy.
It's not that I don't like you.
I just don't dare to.
Why?
Actually,
both Shen Nanqiao and I
were given a second chance at life.
In the previous life, she entered
the palace and became your consort.
But not long after,
you sentenced her to death.
The Shen family
and my grandfather's family
were both accused
of colluding with the enemy.
That day,
the streets of Chizhou
ran red with blood.
Before Bao'er died,
she was still crying out to me.
Auntie, save me.
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
♪The world is gentle only because of you♪
Impossible.
I saw with my own eyes
how my mother and Madam Lian suffered.
That's why I never
harm women or children.
Before I knew you,
I thought
you were cruel,
violent, and unpredictable.
But after getting to know you,
I realized there must
be hidden reasons behind everything.
Even so, I still don't dare to love you.
I'm afraid that one day,
my whole clan will be executed again.
That's why
I kept trying every way possible
to get the death-exemption medal
and the blank imperial decree from you.
All I wanted was to keep my family safe.
♪Love etched into my bones
is beyond concealment♪
♪Even in the deep palace filled
with sorrow and longing♪
I don't understand
this so called previous life,
but I understand myself.
I would never hurt you.
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
Auntie,
is His Majesty my uncle in law?
No.
His Majesty is the Son of Heaven.
He's the Emperor.
Then why is he holding your hand?
Only an uncle in law
can hold Auntie's hand.
I'm your uncle in law.
Come on.
I will take you
to find your great grandfather.
After dropping Bao'er off,
I want to go see Shen Nanqiao.
They've already
searched this place thoroughly.
If there was anything here,
it should've already been taken away.
But Shen Nanqiao has a habit.
She writes down anything
she can't remember.
Since she deliberately wanted
to help Lu Jianglin rise to power,
she definitely would've
used knowledge from her previous life
to help him earn merit
and advance his career.
I knew she'd hide it away
so Lu Jianglin wouldn't find out.
That way, she could feed him
information piece by piece,
and he'd have no choice
but to follow her lead.
(At the Thousand Autumn Banquet,
Jiang Wanning is named Consort)
At the Thousand Autumn Banquet,
Jiang Wanning is named Consort.
So in the previous life,
there really was a Consort Jiang.
Looks like she became
your second Empress.
Impossible.
She must've made it up.
Empress Jiang recovers from her illness
and resumes control of the harem.
She recovered?
Well, that's good.
If she truly recovers,
then I can at least give Jiang Chen
some peace of mind.
You and Jiang Chen fell out?
(After the Thousand Autumn Banquet,
Nangong Xuanyu executes Jiang Chen.)
Your Majesty.
The Prince of Jin has been found.
Where is he?
He escaped the city.
Find him at all costs.
I've completed everything
master ordered.
When will master let me live again?
Don't rush.
What's meant to be yours
won't be missing a single piece.
There's one more thing
I need you to do.
Yes.
Write another vertical stroke.
Hey.
Young Lady, Lady Liu wants
to see you for questioning.
Later, have someone
keep an eye on Bao'er.
Don't let him run off.
Practice properly on your own.
Today, you must get this
horizontal stroke right.
I will check when I come back.
Okay.
Lady Liu.
Shen Zhinian?
Why are you here?
Who dares tie me up?
Which fool did this?
I'll have his head cut off.
Keep your voice down.
Who did you offend this time?
You even dragged me into this.
In this palace,
who would dare kidnap even you?
Could it be Dowager Consort Liu?
Nonsense.
That old woman Liu
is still counting on me
to help her fight
for the position of second Empress.
She'd never kidnap me.
Then could it be the Empress?
That doesn't make sense either.
She may be fake and vicious,
but she's half dead already.
Why would she kidnap us?
The Empress...
Is she really sick?
Isn't she?
She's coughing up blood all day.
Now every time she opens her mouth,
I feel like she's about
to spray blood at me.
Hey.
Let me go right now.
And I'll spare your worthless life.
You dare kick me?
Lu Jianglin, stop!
What?
Lu Jianglin?
He's not dead?
Come with me.
Shen Zhinian,
things weren't supposed
to turn out this way.
The one you were supposed
to marry was me.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I never should've married Shen Nanqiao.
But I just couldn't accept it.
Why did you abandon me?
I wanted to make something of myself,
make you regret leaving me.
Let go of me.
I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
Once I finish helping them,
I'll negotiate with them.
I don't want anything anymore.
I just want to take you back to Chizhou.
From now on, we'll never step foot
in the capital again.
We'll live a good life together, alright?
Who are you helping?
Lady Liu.
Nonsense.
I've already been kidnapped by you,
and now you're trying to frame me too?
Those eunuchs were too stupid.
I never expected them to kidnap her too.
Someone secretly reported
that those eunuchs were using this place
to smuggle palace valuables out.
Stop right there.
So someone
really is up to shady business.
Renran,
open the barrels.
I want to see what they're hiding.
Yes.
Shen Zhinian?
You actually dared to smuggle consorts
out of the palace to sell for money?
You two are dead.
Earlier,
she humiliated me like that.
We might as well kill her too.
Then...
Then we can run away together.
Lu Jianglin, you're such an idiot.
You're even more foolish
than Shen Nanqiao.
Enough!
Shen Zhinian,
I've had enough
of your self righteous attitude.
Other than writing poetry
better than me,
what exactly makes you superior?
I'm better than you in every way.
If I were truly born a man,
I'd stand higher than you,
fly farther than you,
and I definitely wouldn't end up
like a stray dog the way you have.
You vile woman.
I've been far too lenient with you!
Your Highness,
Lu Jianglin kidnapped Lady Liu as well.
How dare he act on his own?
Renran escaped and came back.
She said that while she
and Lady Liu were inspecting the area,
they discovered eunuchs
had kidnapped Shen Zhinian
and planned to smuggle her
out of the palace to sell.
Like master,
like servant.
How could they even imagine
someone was trafficking palace consorts?
Since they've already been captured,
have Lu Jianglin deal with them too.
Don't spare Lu Jianglin either.
Haven't I warned you again and again
to clean things up properly?
Leave Shen Zhinian to me.
You've visited my Fengqi Palace
more in the past half month
than you did all year before.
Don't tell me
you've really fallen for her.
Don't try to act clever.
You're the one fooling yourself.
Do you really think
His Majesty sees you as a brother?
Every time you get close to Shen Zhinian,
he knows about it.
He's always been someone
who clearly separates
gratitude from grudges.
The only reason he's lived
peacefully with us all these years
is because he remembers
how we protected him
when we were children.
You make a good point.
But things have already come to this.
If you and I still want
to live peacefully
with His Majesty in the future,
then one person must be sacrificed.
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪