=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 20=
The envoy may enter
and pay his respects.
- Congratulations on Your Majesty's recovery.
- May Your Majesty enjoy endless fortune.
Let all share in the joy.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
I recently learned a new tune
and wish to perform it
for Your Majesty's enjoyment.
Duke Zhen,
your flute skills are exceptional.
It has been a long time
since I last heard them.
(Why does this melody
sound so familiar?)
- Your Majesty!
(Something's wrong with the music.)
Your Lordship, your status is too noble.
Please allow me to perform
in your place.
How dare you!
My hand slipped.
I beg your pardon.
You wretched concubine!
How dare you break my flute!
Guards!
Your Majesty!
His Majesty has passed away!
What?
This is bad!
Troops have gathered
outside the palace gates.
Your Majesty?
Guards! Protect His Majesty!
Duke Zhen,
you brought troops into the palace.
Are you attempting rebellion?
I'm protecting His Majesty.
Someone poisoned him.
It must be
this woman.
You're not dead?
Of course I'm not.
Every time you see me,
you shout, "Long live Your Majesty".
Surely, I must live a long life.
Did you think
a mere flute could kill me?
You lowborn brat
are good at putting on an act.
Fine.
I'm done playing along with you.
My army has already entered the capital.
You would be wise to hand over
the imperial seal.
And if I refuse?
Don't blame me for showing no mercy.
Guards.
Right now.
Have you all lost your minds?
I'm your true master.
Your troops were replaced
by my men long ago.
You colluded with the Prince of Jin.
I've known all along.
Your Majesty,
all of Duke Zhen's men have surrendered.
I've ordered a search
throughout the city for Prince Song.
I didn't realize Your Majesty had been
watching Prince Song all this time.
What a pity
about Your Majesty's birthday banquet.
We haven't properly celebrated
your birthday in years.
I had hoped
to celebrate it for you.
Jiang Heng ruined everything.
It's only a birthday.
It doesn't matter.
You were too reckless.
You almost ruined His Majesty's plan.
Lady Shen broke the flute to save me.
That's a great merit.
As long as Your Majesty is pleased.
Lady Shen,
what reward would you like?
Forgive my boldness, Your Majesty.
But I wish to ask for
a blank imperial decree.
You!
You dare!
I swear on my life
that I will never use the blank decree
to harm anyone,
nor will I use it
to seek the position of Empress.
I only wish
for a means
to protect myself.
Very well.
I'll grant you
this blank imperial decree.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
♪Moon sets on palace walls,
breeze hits the gates♪
Your Majesty indulges her far too much.
I only hope you won't regret it.
I shall take my leave.
I'll see you out.
No need.
You may leave.
- Yes.
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪In the palace, through dawn and dusk,
who keeps a lamp burning♪
A new batch of rare treasures
arrived recently.
I've had them delivered to your palace.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'm a little tired.
I'll take my leave now.
(She doesn't seem very happy.)
(Did I say something wrong?)
(Now that I have
a blank imperial decree,)
(how should I use it?)
You've been leading me around.
How much farther is it?
That man looks familiar.
Move. Quickly.
Are you alright?
Lord Jiang.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say you wouldn't attend
the imperial birthday banquet?
Something serious happened
at the banquet.
Of course I had to come.
I was on my way to Imperial Study
when I saw those two
sneaking into the courtyard.
Those two were the Jins.
I've sent someone to inform His Majesty.
I'll take you back first,
in case you run into the Jins again.
Thank you, Lord Jiang.
Master,
I've brought him here.
The Emperor is searching the whole city
for you.
The palace is the safest place.
Stay here for the time being.
Thank you, eunuch.
Shen Zhinian saw his face
on our way here.
He can't be left alive.
You killed him,
and now I have to smuggle the body out.
Kindly give me a warning
before you act next time, Prince of Jin.
Eunuch Pan, you should
be more careful yourself.
If something happens to me,
you won't escape either.
Handan.
What happened, Young Lady?
Lady Shen was attacked by assassins.
Are you alright, Young Lady?
Please sit.
Was it the same person
who poisoned before?
Does His Majesty know?
I've sent someone to inform him.
The palace won't be peaceful tonight.
Make sure the doors and windows
are locked.
In case the Jins come after you again.
Thank you, Lord Jiang.
Is your foot alright, Young Lady?
I'm fine.
I only twisted it a little.
Let me take a look.
Lord Jiang.
That's not appropriate.
I meant no offense.
My apologies.
It's alright.
It's getting late.
You should return to your duties,
Lord Jiang.
I'll take my leave.
It's fortunate
you ran into Lord Jiang.
Lord Jiang said
he was on his way to the Imperial Study.
Why would he
pass through Shanglin Garden?
(Jiang Chen is known everywhere
as a refined gentleman.)
(Why would he suddenly try
to touch my foot?)
Your Highness,
the man has been settled in.
There are many vacant palaces.
As long as he doesn't wander around,
he won't be discovered easily.
Mm.
What are you doing?
Why did you do that?
You found out?
You should never leave loose ends.
Have you forgotten what I taught you?
You're losing your temper.
That's unusual.
Did someone slight you,
so you came here to take it out on me?
I'm nothing like you.
So good at pretending.
Sir.
Stop beating him.
Hide him well.
If anyone discovers him...
You're dead.
Don't be afraid, Your Highness.
Lord Jiang is your brother.
He'll protect you.
Him?
He's more ruthless than Father.
No man in this world
can be relied on.
Your Highness,
I...
I'm not really a man.
You can trust me.
Pan,
let's go get the military seal.
Once I have the seal,
I won't have to fear anyone anymore.
Nangong Xuanyu doesn't love me.
I don't want to love him anymore either.
Chen doesn't care about me,
so I won't care about him either.
Alright.
I'll follow Your Highness
through fire and water.
Shen Zhinian.
Why is the door locked?
Open it.
Aren't you opening the door, Young Lady?
Tell him to leave.
Your Majesty, Young Lady was frightened
and has already retired for the night.
Open the door.
Young Lady is asleep.
Please come again tomorrow.
Alright, then.
I'll come again tomorrow.
Handan,
take good care of her.
One assassin is still at large.
Be careful these next few days.
Understood.
Tell him to leave.
I bid farewell to Your Majesty.
Why are the doors shut
in broad daylight?
Open up.
His Majesty is here.
There's no one here.
Did they all go out?
Your Majesty.
Why are the doors locked during the day?
Where is she?
Her Ladyship went out early this morning.
Where did she go?
She left at dawn with Handan.
She said she wanted to take a walk.
Where are the guards?
By your order,
the guards watching Tinglan Palace
were withdrawn
after the return from Xunlu Pavilion.
Go to Shanglin Garden.
The assassin is still out there.
It's not safe.
Lady Shen.
Lord Jiang, were you staying
in the palace all night yesterday?
Her Highness suffered heart pains
overnight.
I stayed by her side the whole time.
She likes plum blossoms,
so I cut a few branches.
You're a good brother.
Allow me to give one branch to you.
Consider it an apology
for my impropriety last night.
Don't take it to heart, Lord Jiang.
What are you doing?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪