=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 23=
For the two of us
to live peacefully by His Majesty's side
in the future,
one person must be sacrificed.
Don't lay a finger on him.
That depends on
whether Lu Jianglin can get it done.
He's an idiot.
Only you would use him.
What do you know?
I used him because...
Because of Shen Nanqiao?
She claimed she was reborn.
You...
You knew?
You have the Prince of Jin as leverage,
but you don't know
how to use him wisely.
I was the one
who let him leave the palace
to draw Nangong Xuanyu's
attention away.
You captured Shen Nanqiao
and Lu Jianglin,
then sent Lu Jianglin to me?
You were using me.
If I hadn't been cleaning up your messes
all these years,
do you think
you could've sat securely on that throne?
You refuse to take your medicine,
hurting yourself to look sick
and make others pity you.
How ludicrous.
Of course I can't compare
to Shen Zhinian,
who's good at seducing men.
Chen,
don't tell me you've fallen for her?
Fallen for her?
Your Highness,
do you know
why Nangong Xuanyu suffers so much?
Why?
Because he has been loved.
His mother loved him.
Madam Lian loved him.
Even Shen Zhinian loves him.
He knows what love feels like,
so he craves it.
I'm different.
I've never been loved.
And I don't need such a thing.
Your Highness, pull yourself together.
Before His Majesty returns,
we must finish what needs to be done.
You're right.
Those who need to die
must be dealt with.
Once His Majesty returns,
everything will go back
to how it was before.
No matter how much Chen wants to use me,
surely he wouldn't go so far
as to kill me.
How dare you kick me?
I've lived through two lifetimes,
and no one has ever dared
kick me before.
Your Ladyship,
what's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
You're truly a jinx.
Getting involved with a jerk like him
was bad enough,
and now you've dragged me into it too.
Thank you for saving me again,
Your Ladyship.
I wasn't saving you.
I was saving myself.
I know
you're not heartless.
I threw you into
the imperial prison before,
and you still think I'm not heartless?
Let me tell you something.
My heart
is the cruelest,
the most vicious,
and the most ruthless of all.
A truly ruthless person
would've executed me
the first time
they caught me.
They wouldn't have
merely forced me
to grow flowers.
That's re-education through labor.
It's how things are done in my hometown.
It was meant to teach you a lesson.
You two vicious women!
Untie me!
Didn't you say I was your master?
I'll grant you death today.
Your Ladyship,
I've told you everything I know.
What more do you want?
How do I know
whether you're still hiding something?
Shen Nanqiao died
six months after entering the palace
in the previous life.
That's all she knew.
Rebirth?
Your Ladyship,
could you step aside for a moment?
I'd like to speak with him alone.
I want to listen to it too.
To be honest,
I was reborn as well.
What?
In the previous life,
you and I were husband and wife.
Shen Nanqiao made a mistake,
and the entire Shen family
was implicated and executed.
After learning the news,
you handed me a letter of repudiation
and personally brought the decree
and send me to my demise.
Impossible.
That can't be true.
Now do you understand
why I broke off the engagement?
Talk about perfect timing, Eunuch Pan.
Arrest this wretched man.
Get them.
Your Majesty,
the Duke Zhen's troops
have been stopped.
But they claim the military tally
was handed to Her Highness.
Are you sure it was Her Highness
and not Jiang Chen?
They insist it was given to the Empress.
(It was given to the Empress...)
(Could events really unfold
exactly as Shen Zhinian predicted?)
(Nangong Xuanyu executes Jiang Chen)
That's not right.
After Shen Nanqiao died
in the previous life,
Jiang Chen continued living just fine.
You never gave the order
to execute him either.
Could the final note
have been fake?
You mean
the mastermind
deliberately left true information
in the first two notes,
so that we'd believe the third as well?
It's possible.
Return to the palace.
Why am I so unlucky?
I've been captured again.
And locked in the same room
as this jerk.
Tough luck.
Save your strength.
You're a walking disaster.
I must've been cursed to ever meet you.
You've already been reborn once.
Why would you still enter the palace?
You think life in the palace
is so wonderful?
Whether life is good or bad
depends on how you choose to live it.
We're about to die.
Happy now?
I never thought
that after living two lifetimes,
I'd still end up dying this miserably.
What do you mean?
Are you reborn too?
You could say that.
Forget about me.
Think of a way out first.
The Empress is a lunatic.
Who knows how she plans to kill me?
I don't think it's come to that yet.
Her Highness
wouldn't really kill us.
That makes sense.
His Majesty will come save you,
won't he?
Little White Snake,
you're here.
Ah!
Snake!
It jumped onto you.
It's His Majesty's snake.
Little White Snake,
did the scent of herbs
on the prayer beads
lure you here?
Could you bring your master here?
You still remembered to visit me?
Father.
Have some tea.
What does Nangong Xuanyu plan
to do to me?
I command 200,000 cavalry.
If anything happens to me,
they'll march straight to the capital.
Does he really dare touch me?
Father,
sometimes I truly hate you.
You forced me to marry him,
but you also made him my enemy.
You left me trapped
in the middle.
I married you to him
so we could control him
and use him for our case.
But look at you.
Useless fool.
Utterly useless.
You hesitated
and wavered.
If you'd rebelled outright back then,
perhaps this empire
would've belonged to the Jiang family.
But you feared rebelling
without justification
and being branded a traitor.
So you brought Nangong Xuanyu back.
And now that he's grown powerful,
you can't accept it.
Shut it.
Even your brother wouldn't dare speak
to me that way.
You forced him
to kill his mentor
whom he respected most.
He has hated you for a long time.
Let me tell you one more thing.
Your trusted aides have handed
the military tally over to me.
The 200,000 soldiers of yours
will now be under my command.
You!
The tea is poisoned.
You...
I'll do as you always wanted, Father.
I'll recover,
bear a child,
and serve as
his Empress.
Have you dealt with them?
Who exactly has been dealt with, Empress?
What are you talking about,
Your Majesty?
I don't understand.
It doesn't matter.
Wen Ling, go look for them.
Move.
Your Majesty,
what is this?
I'm searching for Shen Zhinian
and Lady Liu.
Why would they be here with me?
Our marriage
was part of Duke Zhen's scheme
from the very beginning.
Back when I was
gravely ill and unconscious,
he said I needed a wedding
for good fortune
and sent you into the Eastern Palace.
Before I ascended the throne, I asked
whether you wanted to leave.
I told you I could protect you for life.
Once I married you,
I became your wife.
Why would I leave?
I gave you the position of Empress.
But I wanted your heart.
My heart?
What you've always wanted
was supreme power.
Wasn't it?
So in the end,
you only want Shen Zhinian.
Yes.
What is so good about her?
Everything.
I love her.
Your Majesty,
you're heartless.
we found Little White Snake.
You found her?
Keep watch over her.
Yes.
You should be on your way now.
At least you'll have company
on the road to the underworld.
Don't worry.
You'll be next soon enough.
His Majesty's men are almost here.
Make it quick, then.
Zhinian,
this isn't our past life anymore.
I truly
love you.
I'll repay you with my life.
Please don't hate me anymore.
Die!
♪Moon sets on palace walls,
breeze hits the gates♪
♪Falling at first sight,
a life of turmoil wasted♪
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
♪All the spring colors
lean toward one person♪
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
♪The world is gentle
only because of you♪
♪In the palace, through dawn and dusk,
who keeps a lamp burning♪
♪Time silently scars those left behind♪
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
♪I don't ask for equality,
only that you hear me♪
♪Years of longing haunt
the palace gates, too deep to hide♪
♪I endured the years,
guarding a single truth♪
♪Spending my youth on deep love,
asking not of right or wrong♪
♪Though rumors cover the bed,
my heart is sincere♪
♪Only wishing to stay by your side,
never betraying this bond of fate♪
♪In the palace, through dawn and dusk,
who keeps a lamp burning♪
♪Time silently scars those left behind♪
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
♪I don't ask for equality,
only that you hear me♪
♪Years of longing haunt
the palace gates, too deep to hide♪
♪I endured the years,
guarding a single truth♪
♪Spending my youth on deep love,
asking not of right or wrong♪
♪Though rumors cover the bed,
my heart is sincere♪
♪Only wishing to stay by your side,
never betraying this bond of fate♪