=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 18=
Lu!
Get away!
Don't touch me!
If not for you,
how would I have ended up
beaten half to death by Duke Zhen's men?
Lu,
what are you saying?
Everything I did was for your sake.
Who could've known
things would go wrong?
Don't worry.
I'm already thinking of a solution.
I can still help you.
And you still dare toy with me?
You and Shen Zhinian,
you venomous sisters,
joined forces to ruin me.
What nonsense are you talking about?
How could I possibly
join forces with her?
I wish she would die in the palace.
Fine.
Then answer me this.
Why was Jinsong Pavilion a trap?
Why was Nangong Xuanyu
there waiting for prey?
Impossible.
In my previous life,
someone bought the puzzle box there
and was later favored by him.
In previous life?
Lu, your medicine has gone cold.
I... I'll go
prepare another bowl.
Nanqiao,
without explaining things clearly,
you think you can run away?
Lu,
what are you doing?
Let go of me.
Shen Nanqiao,
I've never understood
why you used to act so superior,
mocking and belittling me
every time you saw me.
Then one day, you suddenly insisted on
marrying me at all costs.
You even
resorted to schemes against me.
You deserve to die.
You deserve to die!
- You ruined my entire life!
- Lu!
I have a way!
I still have a way!
I really do!
Please don't kill me.
That foolish woman ruined me.
That foolish woman ruined me!
They all harmed me.
They all looked down on me!
But I'm not afraid.
My ancestors once held
the highest official rank.
Noble blood flows through me!
I will definitely
become the admired heir
of the Lu family once again,
and restore the Lu family's
century old glory in Chizhou!
Young Lady, something happened
to Shen Nanqiao.
What happened?
Shen Nanqiao and Young Master Lu
were struck to death
by lightning last night.
Their bodies were burned black.
How could that happen?
(Shen Residence)
If lightning truly
struck them down here,
then why are
all the plants in this courtyard
completely unharmed?
There's not even a trace of scorching.
The coroner's report says
their bodies were lying right here.
Then what explains
these drag marks?
Miss Nanqiao!
Something terrible has happened!
Master is in trouble!
What happened?
Why are you here, Miss Zhinian?
Miss Nanqiao, she...
Where is she?
What happened?
Tell me first.
Master and Madam
were on their way to the capital
to visit Miss Nanqiao.
But
on the way,
they received a letter telling them
to change course to Mount Nanhua.
But after entering the mountain,
they vanished.
Vanished?
Mount Nanhua again?
Shen Zhinian.
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Your Majesty.
Mm.
This is for you.
What is it?
Wen Ling said sweets
can cheer people up.
You don't actually think
I'm upset over Lu Jianglin's death,
do you?
Wen Ling said the first person
someone loves in their youth
is always different.
Don't worry.
I won't mind it.
He's dead now.
This is the last piece of candy
you'll ever eat for him.
(No way.)
(Is he trying to cheer me up?)
Once you've eaten my candy,
you're not allowed to be sad
over another man anymore.
Wen Ling taught you that too?
How does he know so much?
Does he have many wives and concubines?
He looks
quite honest and dependable though.
He's not honest.
He's quite the charmer.
These marks look like something
was dragged across the ground.
Mm.
I think so too.
Shen Nanqiao and Lu Jianglin
died under very suspicious circumstances.
And this elderly man
escaped to the capital to report
that my father and legal mother
also disappeared at Mount Nanhua.
(Again, Mount Nanhua.)
It's getting late.
Bring him back
to the palace for questioning first.
Come back with me.
Tomorrow morning,
we'll go visit Jiang Chen.
What happened to Lord Jiang?
He's ill.
He never used to take leave before.
But this time,
he requested seven whole days.
Is his illness really that serious?
Lord Jiang has always treated me well.
I should go visit him.
Lord Jiang?
You say it quite naturally.
He's a peerless noble gentleman.
And besides, he is Lord Jiang.
There's nothing wrong
with me calling him that.
He's a noble gentleman?
I'm the Son of Heaven.
"Peerless noble gentleman"?
Why don't you ever describe me like that?
I wasn't the one who wanted to go.
Then I simply won't go.
I'm ordering you to come with me.
I'm not going.
You must.
(Jiang Residence)
Lord Jiang doesn't live
at Duke Zhen's Manor?
After Duke Zhen's first wife died,
he took sixteen concubines.
So after Jiang Chen
came of age at eighteen,
he established his own residence
and rarely returned there.
The women in the palace all say
that Lord Jiang is as refined as jade
and as steadfast as a pine tree.
The most captivating man in Daliang.
Shen Zhinian,
do you really think
a death-exemption medal
can save your life?
You actually dare say such things to me?
Your Majesty sees all.
I'm not like
other women.
When I choose a man,
not only must he be handsome,
he must also be the most capable,
the most broad minded,
the most competent,
and the most manly.
Don't think a few compliments
mean I won't punish you.
It's because I'm magnanimous
that I let it slide.
Your Majesty has great power,
great authority,
and lives in a grand palace.
Everything about
Your Majesty is great except
your tolerance.
Shen Zhinian,
ever since receiving
that death-exemption medal,
you've become even bolder.
Your Majesty.
Lady Shen.
I heard you were ill,
so I came to visit you.
I'm not sick.
I just didn't want to attend court
and wanted to sleep in for a day.
Then let's sleep together.
Your Majesty.
This is completely improper.
If the old ministers found out,
they'd criticize Your Majesty again.
Then how about we don't lie down?
Would you like to play chess?
No.
Otherwise Your Majesty
will mock me again.
Then...
Go cook something for us.
Your Majesty is truly cruel.
It's bad enough you won't let me sleep,
now you're ordering me to cook too.
The last time I ate your cooking
was seven years ago.
Now,
you are the refined as jade,
steadfast as pine,
number one handsome man in Daliang.
Naturally,
I can no longer eat food made by you.
Your Majesty's mouth is truly unbearable.
Jiang Chen,
I'm taking away your title
as Daliang's most captivating man.
Lord Jiang was chased away by you.
(Zhinian,)
(with you by my side from now on,)
(my life will finally feel complete.)
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
But you deserve punishment too.
You heard someone insulting me
and still didn't defend me.
How would I dare interrupt?
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪