=Episode 24=
Young Lady.
You're awake, Young Lady.
Where...
Where are we going?
Back to Chizhou.
Young Master He and Bao'er have left.
Where's His Majesty?
A coup may break out in the capital.
His Majesty ordered us
to return to Chizhou first.
If the situation stabilizes,
he'll come fetch you.
And if it doesn't,
His Majesty said
you should find yourself a better man.
Duke Zhen commands 200,000 soldiers.
How could His Majesty
possibly withstand that?
(Why has the prayer bread
turned red?)
This isn't a prayer bead.
What is this?
Medicine.
The blood must've triggered
the medicinal properties.
Could it be...
I only remember
my mother often went to Mount Nanhua
with someone to collect herbs.
This is a portrait of my mother
and Madam Lian.
I understand now.
This is what my mother protected
with her life
after countless trips to Mount Nanhua.
What is it?
The antidote.
Yiqing once said
my mother's prayer beads
only had 108 beads.
Before she died,
she deliberately added one more.
So
my mother hid the antidote here
all along.
Handan.
Quick.
We're returning to the capital.
But the Duke Zhen Army
has besieged the city.
We can't get close to His Majesty.
Why don't we follow His Majesty's orders
and return to Chizhou first?
His Majesty can't be harmed.
Manshu Tears will kill him.
For the sake of the realm, if he dies,
the realm will fall into chaos.
Neither you nor I
will have anywhere left to survive.
And personally,
I can't let him die either.
Hurry.
Who are you?
Jiang Chen?
(Jiang Residence)
I prepared fish congee.
Eat it while it's hot.
Is His Majesty safe?
His Majesty fought his way
to the throne through bloodshed.
He endured countless hardships.
Even so,
does he mean he deserves to be used
and deceived by you?
I don't understand what you mean.
He treated you as a friend.
No matter what your father did to him,
he never once doubted you.
He even tried to shield you from it all
and let you remain
a clean and honorable young master.
You don't deserve to be his friend.
Shut up, Shen Zhinian.
You've been trying to get close to me
this whole time.
I suppose
it was because you hated him.
You wanted
whatever he valued.
Weiqi is a game
of strategy and patience.
This time,
I'll win.
Do you think His Majesty will guess
that the real military tally
of the Duke Zhen Army
is with you?
It doesn't matter.
Without the antidote,
he's as good as dead.
Sooner or later,
someone else will sit on that throne.
Little White Snake?
Why are you here?
How did you get here?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
I noticed Little White Snake
acting restless,
so I guessed something must've happened.
Eat this.
What is it?
You're quite trusting.
Aren't you afraid I might poison you?
You wouldn't.
Well.
How do you feel now?
The burning in my chest
is fading.
My guess is right.
What exactly happened?
The person my mother met
was His Majesty's loyal servant,
Madam Lian.
My mother
once gathered herbs at Mount Nanhua,
but the medicine was never used
on the people around her.
So I guessed
she gave it to Madam Lian instead.
And the Peng fish
in the imperial temple.
It came from your mother too?
My mother and Madam Lian
came from the same hometown.
She knew your situation was dangerous
and feared the antidote
would be discovered
and destroyed,
so she hid it
inside the prayer beads.
I see.
We should leave this place now.
Also,
Jiang Chen locked Handan away
somewhere else.
Don't worry.
She'll be alright.
Mm.
Your Majesty, why come so late at night
without notice?
I could've prepared to greet you sooner.
Stop now,
Jiang Chen.
I've never made a move.
What is there for me to stop?
What I don't understand is
that you clearly went after Prince Song,
why did you turn back halfway?
Because I never intended
to go after him.
Why?
You shouldn't have let Shen Nanqiao
leave behind that prophecy,
saying I would kill you.
Just because of that?
Surely you didn't think
Shen Zhinian would turn against me
over it?
She praised you as a noble gentleman.
You actually believed her?
You don't know her.
She's smooth-tongued.
Even when she hated me the most,
she still praised me
as if I were the moon in the heavens.
Enough!
The moon in the heavens?
You're nothing but filth
that crawled out of a kennel.
Your tongue can be just as vicious.
Since things have come to this,
there's no need to pretend anymore.
Shen Zhinian was right.
I hate you.
My father could've
become emperor himself,
but he brought you back
and made me serve you
as my master.
If you wanted the throne,
I could've handed it to you.
But since you insist on
taking it by force,
I refuse to give it to you.
You leave me no choice.
For old times' sake,
I'll leave your body intact.
Step back.
Can you handle this alone?
Who said I came alone?
Jiang Chen,
considering our past acquaintance,
I'll leave your body intact.
Jiang Chen,
stop this.
The Duke Zhen Army
mustn't enter the capital.
You have no military achievements.
You won't be able to control them.
I'm the Duke's son.
I hold the military tally.
Of course they'll obey me.
You've walked this path with me
all these years.
You should know better than anyone
what kind of people they are.
Your father has indulged their greed
for far too long.
Once they get the chance,
they'll tear each other apart.
The people of Daliang
don't deserve such suffering.
Stop being sanctimonious.
You know perfectly well
how many lives you've taken.
I only kill those who deserve it.
Enough talk.
I've spent ten years pretending
in front of you.
I'm sick of it.
Today, you and I settle this
once and for all.
Let go of Young Master,
or
I'll kill Shen Zhinian.
Luo Hao!
Jiang Chen,
since I entered the Duke Residence,
whether in study or martial arts,
I've always held back for your sake.
What did you say?
You couldn't surpass me,
so Duke Zhen forced you
to kill your own mentor.
Why are you trembling?
Stab him.
From that day on,
I yielded to you in everything.
You're lying!
Leave.
I don't want to kill you.
Nangong Xuanyu!
I don't need your pity.
Your Majesty,
Duke Zhen Army has sent assassins
into the palace.
Stay here.
This is the safest place.
Duke Zhen commands 200,000 soldiers.
Are you confident you can win?
With this position
comes responsibilities.
I don't want to see fathers and sons
turn against each other,
or mothers separated from their children
ever again.
Mm.
You'll win.
I'll wait for you.
(In the first year
of Emperor Xuan's reign,)
(news of Duke Zhen's death
spread through the army.)
(The Duke Zhen Army launched an assault
straight toward the palace.)
(Emperor Xuan remained calm
in the face of danger.)
(He deployed 200,000 Scarlet Phoenix Army
left behind by his maternal family)
(and personally led the battle.)
(The war reached a stalemate,)
(and blood stained the palace.)
Do you think he won?
It's been two days.
Why is there still no news?
You should've gone with him.
At least you could've bitten
a few enemies to death for him.
No.
I need to go see for myself.
Zhinian.
♪Falling at first sight,
a life of turmoil wasted♪
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
♪All the spring colors
lean toward one person♪
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
♪The world is gentle
only because of you♪
(Tinglan Palace)
Lady Shen, we've found your grandfather.
Grandfather!
Zhinian.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Come.
Sit.
Your grandfather is quite capable.
After escaping into the mountains,
he hid himself away.
Both the Empress's men
and His Majesty's guards
searched the mountains seven times,
and they couldn't find him.
Grandfather, you must've suffered a lot.
Young Lady, we've found her.
She was locked in the Jiang family's
dungeon the whole time.
Mm.
Wen Ling,
please take my grandfather to rest.
Yes.
Grandfather, go get some rest.
I'll invite you over again
when it's time to eat.
Alright.
Please.
Your parents have returned to Chizhou.
You should go back as well.
You're letting me go?
Yes.
(Release)
How ridiculous.
For two lifetimes,
I did everything I could
to scheme against you.
In the end, you're saving my life.
Shen Zhinian,
you're infuriating.
My mother once told me
that life is hard enough for women
in this world.
We should help each other.
Why make things difficult
for one another?
Go on.
If there's another life,
I won't fight anyone
for anything ever again.
Take care.
You too.
I've been in this world
for fifteen years.
This is my first time leaving
the capital.
Now, I'm finally going to do
what I want.
Are you really giving up
the status
of the Liu family's eldest daughter?
It's not some precious treasure.
It was nothing but a shackle.
Thank you for giving me
this fake identity.
From now on,
I'll use my real name again.
You haven't told me your name.
I'm not telling you.
What if you come after me someday?
Looks like you're smarter
than I thought.
I'm leaving, Your Highness.
The palace walls are tall.
You can stay trapped there yourself.
♪How many twists of fate
before we finally meet♪
♪The melody drifts
across rivers and mountains♪
My name is Tang Tingting.
Shen Zhinian,
see you.
(Even if this world)
(never leaves a path
for fragile branches,)
(my heart holds unyielding strength.)
(I'm determined to split stone apart
with these tender branches)
(and climb to the highest place.)
(Mother,)
(I did it.)
- Congratulations, Your Majesty amd Your Highness.
- May you shine together
- and enjoy everlasting blessings!
Once upon a time,
there was a wise and mighty emperor.
With a sword and a horse,
he conquered the whole realm.
Isn't he amazing?
He is!
Oh.
Your father is back.
Go on.
Father, you've returned from court.
Go fetch my "armor".
Mm.
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
What are you making for us tonight?
A fragrant and delicious Peng fish soup.
You're amazing.
Father, you're amazing!
What were you talking about just now?
Mother was telling a story.
Father, tell us one too.
Alright.
I'll tell you
the story of a tyrant emperor.
That's not right.
It's a wise and mighty
emperor.
(In the thirty-fourth year
of Hongye's reign,)
(Emperor Xing passed away.)
(Crown Prince Nangong Xuanyu
endured countless hardships.)
(He executed six princes,)
(purged the traitorous ministers,)
(and ultimately ascended the throne.)