[Episode 4]
Do you need help?
No, it's okay.
Sit tight.
Tell me.
Why don't I have
such a beautiful distant cousin?
You have to ask your aunt.
There's so much lavender.
Pull over. I want to have a look.
The lavender is so pretty.
There's so much.
It's so pretty.
Is it pretty?
It's all right.
Nothing to say to someone
who doesn't appreciate beauty.
What you see is beauty.
It cools you down and clears toxins.
Relieves wind and stops itching.
The essential oils and tea bags made of it
can calm you down
and relieve anxiety.
What a killjoy.
I often pass by after work.
I'm sick of it.
Thank you.
When you're not home,
you go to Shunyi for work?
You fix phones and laptops.
You do all sorts of odd jobs.
You must make a lot.
Xuan Island's business is good too.
Why is your family so poor?
You seem to be doing well in Beijing.
How did you end up here?
Right.
I heard from Hu
that you have good grades.
Why did you drop out?
Your dad asked someone to send you here.
I don't think he wanted you to leave.
Why are you still going abroad?
You...
can't talk nicely, can you?
You have to get an answer
when you ask a question.
You end up hurting someone's pride
when you pay.
That's arrogance.
You're the one who's prejudiced against me.
I didn't mean to hurt anyone.
Besides, I've already apologized
for what I said to your mom the other day.
If you don't want to answer,
you can just say no.
Okay. I'll say no.
Are you done looking?
No.
Come on.
Let's go home.
By the way,
I'll fix the laptop
and bring it back to you tonight.
Don't hang around Shunyi so often.
Why?
It's troublesome.
Is the laptop fixed?
- Auntie.
- Ye.
How is it? Can the laptop be fixed?
Mr. Ju said it can be fixed.
- Mr. Ju?
- Xing Wu.
- Uncle Zhao.
Mr. Ju?
Hu said it'll cost a lot to fix the laptop.
Take this first.
No, it's okay. You don't have to pay.
It can be fixed.
Just take it back. She doesn't need money.
- I hope I'm not holding you up.
- Grandma.
You didn't. Mr. Ju said
it can be fixed quickly.
That's good.
I feel bad for causing you so much trouble.
I bought some sea cucumbers for you.
Please accept it. I'll feel bad if you don't.
Take it.
Go on.
Okay. I'll take the sea cucumbers.
Take the money back.
All right.
I'll hurry back to tell my wife.
Go ahead.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- I'll get going.
- Bye.
Take care.
He's henpecked. His wife keeps the money.
Thank you, Ye.
Well, Hu made a meal for you.
It's hot in the pot.
I'm going next door.
Okay.
Help yourself.
Since when do you do favors
instead of taking cash?
Sea cucumbers in exchange for a computer?
It's a fair exchange.
Here, good for you.
If you want me to leave Xuan Island
as soon as possible,
then fix the computer quickly.
You're welcome.
[Shunyi Repairs]
My favorite.
I feel bad for her.
Her mom passed away a few years ago.
If it weren't for trouble at home,
her dad wouldn't have sent her here.
That's impressive.
Where's the money?
Tell me!
I'll kill you if you don't.
I mean it!
Don't hit my mom!
You were pregnant with another man's child
when you married me.
Have I ever despised you?
Now that my business has failed,
I've been living off you for a few years,
and you despise me for being incompetent?
I'll kill you!
Let go! Let go of me!
Wu!
Are you crazy?
How could you hit your child?
Don't cry.
Xing Guo Dong...
Wu. It's fine.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
Wu.
You must be tired.
Have some skewers.
I bought them from Mr. Zhang.
His TV box is broken.
He wants you to fix it when you have time.
Okay.
His son broke his leg at a construction site.
I don't think they'll pay much.
The engine on Mr. Liu's fishing boat
keeps stalling.
He wants you to fix it too.
Okay, I got it.
I'll make time tomorrow.
Okay.
Tell me.
How does it feel to fall from the sky
into the mud?
I'd have to fly up into the sky to find out.
It's indeed X-change.
The property certificate is done.
Now you can apply for a visa.
Thank you for helping me.
All set. Just need to sign up for classes.
Grandma.
Grandma, it's okay.
I'm here.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Grandma!
How is she?
She took her medicine.
She's asleep.
Okay.
Is your hand okay?
I'm fine.
I've fixed the laptop for you.
Thank you.
That's great. Everything is here.
Xing Wu doesn't talk nicely.
But he's quite skilled.
It's finally done.
Congratulations.
You've solved a big problem in your life.
Congratulations to you too.
You'll soon get rid of this jinx.
You're quite self-aware.
I'm happy today.
I can't be bothered to argue with you.
What?
Treat the wound on your hand.
It's hot. It's prone to infection.
Thank you for today.
It was nothing.
You're welcome.
You seem to know how to help patients.
Yes.
Because my mom had always been unwell.
Just in case,
I learned a lot
about first aid.
It's just that
she couldn't be saved in the end.
I'm sorry
to remind you of your mom.
It's okay.
It has been a long day. I'm tired.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
You're here.
This is the last dish.
Auntie, is today a special day?
Today is a special day.
It's all my fault.
I was too busy yesterday.
Grandma told me
that you saved her.
And you got hurt.
Our family owes you everything.
So I went out early this morning
and bought fresh stuff
to cook for you.
Is this necessary?
Of course.
Grandma, are you all right?
I'm fine.
It's just an old ailment.
Thank you for yesterday.
Look.
You suffered.
Wu.
As long as Ye is with us,
you make sure she's comfortable.
Take good care of her.
Otherwise, I'll hold you responsible.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Let's eat then.
- Here.
- Okay.
Let me get you a shrimp first.
- Thank you, Auntie.
- Fresh squid.
Lan Fang is the best at this.
Okay.
It's really good.
Have some soup too.
Are you installing an air conditioner for me?
It's a second-hand air conditioner.
Use it for now.
It's not a second-hand air conditioner.
It's a major upgrade in quality of life.
Does your hand still hurt?
It's much better.
How long has Grandma been sick?
It started in the past two years.
It's not just seizures.
Her hemiparesis is getting worse too.
Sometimes, she can't remember things.
The brain disease
is prone to all sorts of unexpected events.
That's why
you come home to watch her eat every day.
Because you're worried about her?
Li Lan Fang is impatient.
She often forgets to cook
while playing mahjong.
So I have to keep an eye on her.
You're very good to Grandma.
Grandma raised me.
I wouldn't be here without her.
You're amazing.
We're about the same age.
You're already the head of the family.
But where's your dad?
I've never seen him.
He's dead.
But I heard he was out there.
He's been gone for so long.
And he's in debt.
He's as good as dead.
All right.
This is so nice.
Now all we need is half a chilled watermelon.
That would be perfect.
Eat.
There really is one.
Why are you suddenly so nice to me?
Air conditioner and chilled watermelon?
You're not just repaying me, are you?
You're after my balance?
- I'll take it if you don't want it.
- Don't. I'll eat it.
It's so sweet.
This is what summer should be like.
To be honest,
before coming to Zhazhating,
I really didn't know
summer by the sea could be so hot.
How did you spend your summers before?
Normally.
Are you saying summer isn't normal here?
No, that's not what I mean.
I mean, in the past summers,
I couldn't feel the heat.
It was cool everywhere.
Look, there was an air purifier at home.
There was air conditioning at the malls.
Didn't you go out?
I had a driver.
If it got too hot, I'd go abroad.
I'd find a place to stay out of the heat.
However,
most of the time,
I'd stay at home and study with a tutor.
Sounds like a lot of work.
It's all right. What about you?
Me?
It's quite simple.
I go back and forth between Xuan Island
and Shunyi every day.
I do whatever I can.
If it's too hot,
I'll take Fuzz and Hu with me.
We'll go swimming in the sea.
That's pretty wild.
But it's quite tough.
You went from Beijing to Zhazhating.
It must have been tough too.
But...
today,
for the first time since I got here,
I don't feel
it's that tough.
Because of this used air conditioner?
It's not just the air conditioner.
You also changed the lock for me.
The showerhead.
And this chilled watermelon.
And the laptop you fixed for me.
Also...
I'm leaving.
Also, thank you...
for making this summer in Zhazhating
less desperate.
Who's so shameless?
Stealing clothes?
Stealing a girl's clothes?
They must be crazy poor.
What kind of people are they?
Tempted by a few pieces of cloth.
Are they even human?
What's wrong, Auntie? It's still so early.
Your clothes... Your clothes were stolen.
I didn't wash them.
I did.
Yesterday, you put your clothes there.
I just washed them.
It's all my fault. My stupid hands.
If I hadn't washed them,
this wouldn't have happened.
You didn't do it on purpose.
The point is, your underwear
is gone.
This must be a mistake.
Who would steal underwear?
At Zhazhating,
forget about underwear,
even the copper wires on the utility poles
might be stolen.
Hurry up and give the clothes back!
What are you doing?
You keep nagging all morning.
Are you two solving a case?
Did you catch the thief?
No.
I'm looking for them now.
Look at this courtyard.
It's only this big.
There are only a few families.
Everyone knows
who the sneaky ones are.
I hung the laundry yesterday.
Did you see it?
Look, I've been crazy busy all day.
What did you just say? You lost your laundry?
I didn't see them.
I didn't.
Why did you ask then?
- Who took it? Bring it back!
- What's wrong?
Why do people here steal everything?
Laptops and underwear.
Don't they feel uncomfortable
wearing someone else's underwear?
This place and I just don't get along.
This is so annoying.
Was it hung here and stolen?
I washed it last night and hung it here.
But it's gone today.
So annoying.
[Drink Together?]
Is it good?
It's good.
Have some, Wu.
Where are Qing Ye's clothes?
I didn't steal them.
Did I say you stole them?
I...
What are you doing?
The footprints under the clothes.
What's that about?
The footprints.
Don't you leave footprints there
when you hang the clothes?
What does it have to do with me?
Xing Wu.
Let me tell you. Don't be so shameless.
I have a temper too. All right?
- Wu.
- You stole the laptop too, didn't you?
It wasn't me. It really wasn't.
I wouldn't dare.
I only dare to steal wires.
What are you doing?
Wu. It's hot...
My face... Wu!
Wu, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Wu Lao Er.
I'm telling you.
Don't mess with Qing Ye.
Or next time,
I'll kill you.
All right, Wu.
I promise.
What are you looking at?
Never seen anyone pick up a shoe?
Come in.
Take your pick. Wear whatever you want.
This is all I have.
There's no need, Auntie.
I just lost a piece of underwear.
You don't have to lend me your clothes.
You're always wearing the same few outfits.
Did you not bring enough clothes?
Don't worry.
My clothes are all pretty.
I learned my taste from your mom.
This was the trendiest style
when I was young.
Isn't it pretty?
Try it on.
- Me? No need.
- Try it on.
- I can't.
- Try it on. It's pretty.
Trust me.
It looks good.
Come out. It's fine.
Come out.
Wu.
Where have you been?
Exercising.
You're back just in time.
Well...
Ye's a bit unsure. You can help her decide.
What do you mean?
Just come out. Come out.
My clothes look nice.
What do you think? Does she look nice?
- Why are you laughing?
- You can choose not to say anything.
I'll keep quiet.
Change. Let's change.
We'll keep going until you're happy.
Let's go. I've been saving these clothes.
Xing Wu.
Take a look. What do you think?
Got it. Change again.
Let's go.
How about
I do it myself.
Okay. Pick what you like.
Wear whatever you want.
Doesn't it look good?
What do you think, Auntie?
You look like my sister back then.
Your legs are so long.
It's beautiful.
Mom. Come out for a second.
What is it?
Later, go and buy some clothes for Qing Ye.
- I'm busy.
- Play less mahjong.
- Then you'll be free.
- Pocky's son is getting married tomorrow.
So tonight, they're having
the Pre-Wedding Banquet.
I promised Hu's mom and Fuzz's mom
I'd go over to help.
I have to go soon.
Are you in a hurry?
I am. Look. She's rushing me.
Just let her wear mine.
Who's going to buy it for her?
Figure it out yourself.
I'll take Grandma there first.
You take Ye there later.
We gave a wedding gift.
- We're going to eat our money's worth.
- Again?
Two hands in the sky.
Up.
Down.
You know Baduanjin?
I just started learning it three minutes ago.
I'm going to the county to buy something.
Do you want to join me?
It's okay.
I lost my laptop and clothes
as soon as I got here.
I think before I leave,
I'll practice the Turtle Breathing Technique
to calm down and recharge.
Okay. I'll get going then.
Wait.
You...
Well...
Can you bring me...
the clothes underneath?
Do you understand?
The ones that come in no size.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Wu, I have a job for you.
See you at Shunyi.
Did you put a camera on me?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I'll be right there.
My sister got you this job.
Isn't your sister
on a business trip in Hainan?
She knows you need money.
She's been keeping an eye out for you.
My sister treats you
better than me, her own brother.
Don't sugarcoat it. Get to the point.
What's going on with this job?
Mr. Ye is my sister's boss.
His son wants someone to build him
a model aircraft for a competition.
My sister recommended you.
An oil-powered model aircraft?
But I don't know much about it.
What model aircraft can't you build?
Master one, master all.
It can't be that hard.
I don't have much theoretical knowledge.
Maintaining the aircraft's flexibility
and maneuverability
is not easy.
With your sister's resources and connections,
it shouldn't be hard
to find an expert in this field.
They're nothing compared to you.
What do you think, Wu?
Do you want to do it?
It's not cheap to make this kind of model.
My sister said,
as long as you do a good job,
the price is not a problem.
It's 8,000 yuan.
I'll talk to my sister.
She said it's a deal.
Okay. Thank your sister for me.
Thank her in person.
She might be happier.
Are you really giving up?
I'll stay motionless until provoked.
Then I won't be defeated.
When you fought with me before,
I thought you were full of rebelliousness.
Full of rebelliousness?
I don't even have clothes to wear.
My online order won't be here for a few days.
This is...
This should be what you want.
Try it on later and see if it fits.
If it doesn't, I'll go change it.
All right.
Can you get up and move now?
- Why?
- Pocky's son is getting married.
I'm taking you to get some good luck
and get rid of the bad luck.
You get married at night here?
It's not a formal wedding.
The night before the wedding,
we treat the neighbors to drinks.
- Wu!
- Qing Ye!
Qing Ye! Wu!
Qing Ye!
Let's go to the feast!
Go, go, go!
Let's go!
Are you coming?
They're here.
- Congratulations.
- Good.
Get ready.
You're here.
Thank you.
Fen'er, tell them to serve
the cold dishes first.
- All right.
- Hu's mom.
Honey, serve the cold dishes first.
Come on.
Yu, is the water boiling?
Yeah, it's boiling soon.
Lower the heat.
The dishes are coming.
You can have some candies.
Here. Okay, come on.
Thank you, everyone. Thank you.
- The food is here.
- Ribs.
Have a seat.
Come on. Have a seat.
Have some peanuts and melon seeds.
Have a seat and have some food.
Have a seat.
Have a seat, everyone. Thank you.
Thank you.
That's a lot of work.
Are you impressed?
This is the scale of a banquet in Zhazhating.
It's an eye-opener.
Wu, Qing Ye.
- This way.
- Where?
Over there. This way.
Let's go.
Wu, Qing Ye, you're here. Have a seat.
The banquet is about to start.
Take good care of them.
Have a seat. I'll drink with you today.
Let's have a drink.
- Let's eat.
- I'll be right back.
Qing Ye, what would you like to drink?
Beer.
Can you drink?
Why don't you have a soft drink?
- I'm an adult.
- We all are. I have a driver's license.
Have a seat.
What are you looking at?
Gang. Here.
Take it back.
The laptop you sold me...
Where did you steal it from?
From the woman next to Xing Wu?
No, Gang. I... I didn't steal it.
How can you say that?
Right. You didn't steal it.
She gave it to you.
Wait, Gang.
Friends and family.
Folks and neighbors.
I'd like to thank everyone
for coming despite your busy schedules.
My wife and I thank you all.
Thank you, everyone.
Great!
So let me just say this:
Eat well.
Drink well.
Let the banquet begin.
- Yeah!
- All right.
- Let's eat.
- Let's go.
Come on. The feast is here.
Here.
Have a drink.
Is wedding food
always this hearty here?
Of course.
Marriage is a big deal in life.
The spread has to be top-notch.
This dish is what we save
for festivals in Zhazhating.
Called 'Destined Love'.
Braised sea cucumber with pork tendon.
What about that one?
'Match Made in Heaven'.
They all have auspicious names.
It looks delicious.
Qing Ye, this is
how we do it here.
Quick hands get the food.
Slow hands get none.
A new dish is here.
Come on.
I'll get right to it then.
You're so happy.