[Episode 6]
Xing Wu.
I have some good news.
I'm going back to Beijing.
Congratulations.
You can finally leave Zhazhating.
Same to you.
Finally, you don't have to
put up with me anymore.
- It's here.
- Yeah.
The pickup is here. Let's go.
We're taking this? Quite a grand send-off.
It's faster than a three-wheeler
and more spacious than an SUV.
Fuzz's dad lent it to us.
It's the best treatment in Zhazhating.
Auntie, Grandma, I'm leaving now.
If you have no one to eat with,
you can video call me.
Okay. Study hard when you get back.
Don't worry about us.
Ye, if there was anything
I didn't do well during your stay,
please forgive me.
Look at how great you are.
You're going to study abroad soon.
I won't pretend to want you to stay.
That would only hold you back.
Don't worry, Auntie.
I'll pay the balance.
Well... It's not that.
It was my duty to take care of you.
I didn't do it just for the money.
Besides, you didn't stay the full term.
You must not pay me the balance.
Don't you dare send it to me.
I definitely will. Uncle Sun will contact you.
Cousin!
- Here.
- What's this?
Fruit. Not cheap knock-offs this time.
They're really imported avocados and cherries.
Take them for the road.
And these are from my mom.
All your favorites. Eat them if you get hungry.
- Well...
- Just take it.
- Take it.
- It's quite heavy.
- Here, I'll take it.
- Let me.
It's a journey of several hours.
You'll get hungry, and you'll need it.
- Thanks, then.
- We should go.
- We're leaving now.
- Okay.
- We're off.
- Take care.
- Bye, Qing Ye!
- Have a safe trip.
Right.
Go.
- We're off.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye!
- Bye, Auntie, Grandma!
- Bye-bye!
- Bye!
Take it slow!
Sir, please stop for a moment.
I want to take another look.
It reminds me of when we first met.
Hello, beautiful.
Nuts.
You're quite good at swearing.
I'm about to leave.
Can't you say something nice?
I'm just telling the truth.
If I remember correctly,
it was on this very road back then.
You must have been calling me
a country bumpkin in your head.
I wasn't. I was calling you a jerk.
Then my first impression of you
was quite accurate.
Everyone else had something to say.
Don't you want to say anything to me?
Say what?
There's a good chance
I'll never come back to Zhazhating.
As a farewell,
you should at least say something.
Beijing isn't that far. What's there to say?
I thought you'd at least say,
"Hope to see you again."
You probably don't want to see me
or Zhazhating ever again.
That's true.
When you first arrived,
you must have been utterly disappointed
with everything here.
I felt like my life was over.
You practically had the word "disgust"
written all over your face.
Was it that obvious?
Like a startled cat,
your fur was bristling from head to toe.
If that's the case,
you were paying quite close attention.
- Pull over.
- Okay.
I didn't realize
lavender looks so beautiful up close.
These little flowers are so purple.
They're really pretty.
Are they? It's not your first time here.
Right. They're not just pretty.
They can cool you down and clear toxins,
relieve wind and stop itching.
They can be made into
tea bags and essential oils which can...
Can calm the mind and relieve anxiety.
Calm the mind and relieve anxiety.
- Good memory.
- Of course.
I'm leaving soon. Take a picture of me here.
Did you take it or not?
What are you laughing at?
I'm taking it. I am.
By the way...
Cousin.
I'm leaving anyway.
Let's take a photo together.
I don't look good in photos.
Save it as a memento, okay?
Hurry up.
Smile, will you?
Three, two, one.
I thought I was at a dead end,
yet Zhazhating has become my warm harbor.
Every breath of sea breeze here
carries the most genuine look of life,
giving me the strength to start over.
Go on.
Thank you.
Have a nice trip.
Let's...
have a hug.
You're never this polite.
It feels a little weird.
It's fine. You won't have to.
The contract has expired.
It's void now.
Goodbye.
Beijing, I'm back!
Wait for me, guys.
How come you even recorded a video?
I'm here.
Should I go straight to your place,
or should we grab a meal first?
Hello?
Hello, Qing Ye.
I'm from Huanji Study Abroad.
There's a situation with your application.
You'd better come over right away.
The school needs to see you now.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Qing Ye, you are outstanding.
But unfortunately,
the school cannot accept you.
Why?
[Anonymous Report]
We got an anonymous report about your family.
Someone reported me?
Yes.
According to the report,
you concealed your father's
alleged economic crimes and his frozen assets.
Under these circumstances,
the school has the right to revoke your offer.
And for the next five years,
you cannot apply to this school again.
I'm truly sorry.
Hello. This way, please.
- Two avocado specials. Thank you.
- Here.
Okay.
Hello.
When will you be here?
I got you your favorite drink.
Qing Ye.
Why are you here?
Meng Rui Hang asked me to come.
Right. You're finally back in Beijing.
We wanted to celebrate.
Leaving the group chat,
ignoring my messages,
and blocking me.
Is this your way of celebrating?
You wrote that report, didn't you?
Qing Ye, you're so smart.
I knew you'd figure it out.
All that talk about
letting me stay at your place.
You didn't want me to come back at all.
Why?
Because you like Meng Rui Hang?
So you knew all along.
But you pretended not to notice.
I like him,
but he only has eyes for you.
I wasn't pretending.
I just wasn't interested at all.
From today on,
we are no longer friends.
We were never real friends anyway.
He Le Ling!
Rui Hang.
You've gone too far.
Come in.
Your slippers.
Still the same ones.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Well, I won't stay for long.
I'll leave as soon as I find a hotel.
Quit being so polite.
I'd never let you stay at a hotel.
The housekeeper will get the guest room ready.
Just stay here.
Go on in.
I'll take that.
Ye.
Auntie.
Well...
Mom, I want Qing Ye to stay with us
for a while.
Of course.
No big deal.
Ye, come on, sit down.
Sit here.
How did you lose so much weight?
Here, have some water.
Thank you, Auntie.
Don't mention it.
Our families are so close.
I've always treated you like my own daughter.
Make yourself at home.
Are you hungry?
I'm not.
Don't be so polite with me.
I'll go wash some fruit for you.
Drink some water.
Hang Hang. Come and give me a hand.
I'll head over there.
You silly boy.
Why didn't you tell me
you were bringing her back?
What's the matter?
Your dad's company has done business
with theirs.
Our family could easily get dragged in.
At this point,
everyone is cutting ties with them.
Mom, what do you mean by that?
Do we have to cut ties with her, too?
What a naive child.
I'm doing this for your own good.
Do you want to end up homeless like her,
living in some poor countryside?
Qing Ye is in trouble, I have to help.
Others might ignore this, but I can't.
Silly boy, didn't you hear me?
Anyway, I've made myself clear.
Cut ties with her sooner.
Ye.
I washed your favorite cherries
and avocados for you.
Where is she?
Qing Ye?
She left?
Fine, let her go.
Sorry, the number you dialed is
temporarily unavailable.
What are you...
Hang Hang!
You...
Ye.
Your father's situation
is not very optimistic.
The victims have filed a joint appeal.
The evidence gathering and
investigation process are very complicated.
Right now, everything is uncertain.
But don't be too upset.
The investigation is still ongoing.
The legal team is doing their best
to clear your father's name.
Is there a good chance?
No one can guarantee anything.
Until the results are out,
no one dares to promise anything.
I understand.
Are you back in Beijing?
Where are you staying now?
If you have nowhere to go, come to me.
No need, Uncle Sun.
You've done enough for my family.
How about this?
I'll send you some more money.
Don't mistreat yourself.
Really, I'm good.
Thank you, Uncle Sun.
I'll hang up now.
[Unlock failed]
[Please try again]
Ye, it's raining.
We must put our hoods on.
Otherwise, if we get wet, we'll catch a cold.
Let's go.
You haven't eaten all day, right?
Just make do with this.
If you don't want to eat,
at least warm your hands with it.
Why did you come to Beijing?
Because I found...
a loophole in our previous contract.
It says here
the expiration date
[Temporary Residency Service Contract]
is the 10th.
That means before the 10th,
I must ensure your personal safety.
Right now, until the 10th,
there are still 15 minutes left.
And after 15 minutes?
If you're willing,
you can come back to Zhazhating with me.
My home is your home.
Do you want to renew the contract?
Effective immediately.
Yes.
But...
before we go back,
you have to come home with me first.
You can't even get into your house.
How are we supposed to go?
Don't worry.
I have a way.
By the way, how did you know where I live?
My mom told me.
The front door access code
seems to have changed.
Let's go through the back door.
Why not the back door just now?
I didn't think of it.
This way, this way.
These flowers are all dead.
Yeah.
Since my dad had his trouble,
nobody's taken care of this place.
They definitely couldn't survive.
Did your mom grow all of these?
She really loves gardening.
I was thinking of taking two pots
back to Zhazhating.
But that's out of the question now.
Look. Is this one still alive?
Let me see.
It's green.
Yeah. This one's alive. It's a Welwitschia.
An orchid?
This plant is incredibly tough.
It can survive in the desert
for a long, long time.
Easy to take care of.
Perfect for taking back to Zhazhating.
This one it is.
Let's go inside.
Come on, come on.
Why is your house...
Why is your house so cold?
You don't know, do you?
Central AC and ventilation system.
Nothing beats the comfort of home.
These trophies and certificates...
Are they all yours?
Back in school,
I entered all kinds of competitions?
Wait.
Xing Wu, Xing Wu!
Quick, come here!
Look.
Let's finish all of these today.
We won't get to eat them back in Zhazhating.
Here, take it.
How is it? Is it good?
It's good.
Well. Now try this flavor.
I absolutely love this one.
How is it?
Is it good?
This one's good too.
Try this one.
This is also delicious.
Try the one I just had.
It's my favorite flavor.
Your favorite?
What flavor is it?
Cookies &amp; Cream Vanilla.
- Is it good?
- Cookies &amp; Cream Vanilla.
This is good.
Welcome, Xing Wu,
to Qing Ye's summer.
Cheers.
Need a hand?
Go to the bathroom.
Grab all my skincare products
and toiletries.
Okay.
All here. Take a look.
Let me see.
Yes, that's everything.
Okay.
Xing Wu.
I've had this piggy bank since I was little.
It's gotta be full.
Quick. Help me crack it open.
Can I just smash it?
Sure.
Wow, that's a lot.
There's more here.
Give them to me.
Put this on.
Okay.
The clothes?
Put this on.
Too thick, too much space.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
This way.
- Who's there?
- Security!
- Follow me. Follow me.
- Stop!
This way, this way.
What are you doing?
Run! Run!
Stop there! Stop right there!
Wait for me! It's too dark. I can't see.
You'll see when it gets light.
Stop!
- Oh my god!
- Wait, wait!
It's spilling! It's spilling!
Oh, man.
Did... Did we...
Did we lose them?
Yes, we lost them.
No one in sight.
Why were we running?
The security guard chased me,
so I ran.
The sun is coming up.
Thank you.
Xing Wu.
A new day has begun.
Come home with me.
But I want to go somewhere first.
Let's go.
Mom.
I'm here to see you.
I brought you your favorite Coke,
[Tomb of Wife Lin Wanxin]
and the daisies you like.
Mom. I've been through a lot lately.
I thought
falling from the peak to rock bottom
was bad enough.
I didn't expect
I'd fall from rock bottom
even further into the abyss.
But
you don't have to worry anymore.
When I was at my most desperate,
someone reached out to help me.
Do you remember him?
My cousin from Auntie's, Xing Wu.
You probably haven't seen him for a long time.
This time,
he came to Beijing just to get me.
Hello.
In front of you,
I can't tell any lies.
I was indeed worried about Qing Ye.
That's why I came to Beijing.
But actually,
I...
I can't say
I came to Beijing solely for her.
Then why did you come?
This one is our top-of-the-line model,
and also the latest one.
It's waterproof, anti-corrosive, and foldable.
You really came to the right place today.
Right now, only our offline stores
can provide such custom service.
And right now, we have a promotion in-store.
I'll take this one then.
Sure, no problem.
Do you have a new one in stock?
Yes, we do. Please follow me.
The original price of this wheelchair is
7,999 yuan.
Since we have a promotion today,
after the discount,
it's 6,999 yuan.
How would you like to pay?
Cash.
Okay.
Here is 6,800 yuan.
I still owe 200.
Can I pay with a QR code?
Yes, that works.
Don't bother.
It's for Grandma's wheelchair.
I want to help out too.
[Zhazhating]
Zhazhating still smells the same.
You're gonna have to get used to this place.
Who says I'm not used to it?
It's the smell of the sea.
Everyone will be so happy
to see you back.
Who was it that told me
to leave as soon as possible
and never come back?
I only said that because I hoped
your family was okay,
so you could leave here as soon as possible.
Xing Wu. When did you get a cousin?
I've given this girl a ride before.
I never heard your mom mention her.
I picked her up on the streets of Beijing.
We're here.
Welwitschia.
It's a plant native to the desert.
Xing Wu.
Before I left, you said
that roses couldn't bloom in a barren desert.
That's true.
But,
weak grass doesn't grow in the desert either.
If you can survive the worst,
nature's got your back as the fittest.
Zhazhating, I'm back.
Ye?
Are you
back?
Auntie.
[Xuan Island Barbershop]
Auntie. This silk scarf is for you. Try it on.
For me?
I know this brand.
Designer goods really are different.
What a texture.
It's so smooth and silky.
And these skincare products
are for you too.
It's windy by the sea.
Don't forget to moisturize.
Are these all for me?
They must have been very expensive.
As long as you like them, Auntie.
I love them!
Grandma, this is the power switch.
Once you turn it on,
this lever is for forward and reverse,
and this is for steering left and right.
From now on, you can use this
to go have coffee with Grandma Zhao.
Wonderful.
And look.
This is a souvenir badge of Tian'anmen.
Qing Ye bought it especially for you.
It's so beautiful.
Wu, Ye,
you're both so thoughtful.
Look at me. I was so busy looking at the gifts.
I forgot to ask.
Why are you back?
There was a change of plans.
I'm not going abroad for the time being.
- You're not going abroad?
- No.
That's good news.
I don't know if it's
gold on the streets or cash in the air.
Everyone is scrambling to get overseas.
It's okay to stay. Life here is good.
Auntie, you're right. I think so too.
So I might
have to live here for a bit longer.
Sure, that's fine.
Ye, you can stay here
as long as you like.
So
how long are you going to stay?
A year.
A year?
Or maybe two years.
Come out.
I have something to tell you.
Come on, come on.
Come with me.
Go ahead.
- What's going on?
- Keep your voice down.
Ye.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
Wu will handle
your auntie.
You just stay here as long as you want.
I really feel for her.
Her family's in a huge mess.
She packed just a few things.
And she almost got caught by security.
Plus,
she can't go abroad.
Her friends in Beijing can't help her now.
Although we're not related by blood,
we should help her out.
Right?
Why does that
sounds so familiar?
You said it.
So you took it to heart?
But Mr. Sun is really something.
Why didn't he contact me in advance?
He should've told me what was happening.
I'll call and ask him.
- Come back here.
- I...
- What are you going to ask?
- He still owes me twenty thousand.
I need to know what's going on.
All her family's accounts are frozen.
You're not getting that money.
Uncle Sun is just an employee of her dad's.
There's no reason to ask him for money.
So you're saying
the money is gone,
and we'll have to cover her expenses?
Yes.
Look, I can forget about that money.
But have you thought about this?
She's not
staying here for one or two months.
It's one or two years.
What about her living expenses, tuition,
and all the everyday stuff
like eating and clothes?
Didn't she give you 30,000 yuan?
But I already...
Well, you know that.
I used that money to pay my debts.
It's nearly the end of the month.
I was banking on that 20,000 yuan
to knock off a bit more debt.
So what now?
Alright, alright.
I'll handle it.
Smile.
I can't smile.
You hear me? I can't smile.