Dumb flies.
Wu,
what's all the noise?
Do we have a bug problem?
Yeah,
a huge one.
Some pest just won't leave.
Good morning, ma'am!
Morning, Grandma!
A friend from school?
Here to study?
What a sweet, ambitious boy!
"Ambitious." Right.
He's got a major ulterior motive!
Be nice.
Come on,
have some.
I'm good.
I don't eat much in the morning.
Xing Wu and Grandma
can have some too.
Maybe I should
come by every morning.
I'll bring breakfast!
Got a microwave?
Nope.
We're a salon,
not a diner.
Ain't got time to host you.
Of course we do.
Morning, ma'am!
Morning!
Make yourself at home.
Auntie.
Oh, what a feast!
Eat up, sweetie.
C'mon, handsome.
Follow me.
Where to?
You'll see.
Come on!
Take a seat!
Wait, what's going on?
Giving you a trim.
But I just got one...
Don't be shy!
Come on,
no one leaves my shop
without a fresh cut!
Honestly,
my hair is totally fine...
You'll love it, sweetie!
Since you're
Qing Ye's friend,
I'll knock some off for you.
Done hunting flies?
Sparing his life.
Look at Miss Popularity.
Giving "private tutoring"
at the crack of dawn.
What's wrong with that?
He gets to practice,
and we get
business.
So, how do you like this "customer?"
Seems nice.
Easy target for a splurge.
Not sure
about that.
Now that
Mom's tasted
easy money,
she'd style
a fly
if it buzzed in.
Too bad you already
swatted them all.
Oh, please... they keep coming.
The GQ Heartthrob package!
We have a dress code...
Alpha males don't have
dress codes!
Maybe you could...
pick one for me?
Let's go with...
this one!
Alright...
Great!
Qing Ye!
Do I look like a stud?
Oh, boy...
wow.
It's... unique.
I got a VIP membership!
How much?
888!
How many digits?
Isn't that... a bit much?
Actually, it's a steal!
Sweetheart,
hottie here is a big spender!
You know,
Ye designed
the menu herself!
Come back soon!
Mom...
have some shame.
No,
seriously,
it's 50% off!
I did the math.
I can come see you 40 times
this semester.
With wash, cut, and style,
the whole deal!
Hey, we're
a reputable local brand.
I'd never rip anyone off!
Besides,
he gets
to study
and score a fresh look.
It's a win-win!
Mom, he's a kid.
He should be studying,
not styling.
40 haircuts in one semester?
He'll burn his scalp off!
I couldn't agree more.
Students
should focus on
school...
Exactly.
Instead of dropping out
and pretending
to be a big-shot boss!
Right, Grandma?
Right, sweetheart!
Qing Ye,
what about this one?
Actually...
you look great just like this.
Let's
celebrate our
newest VIP!
We must
give him the
royal treatment,
don't you think?
Hot stuff,
I'll throw in a free brow trim!
Come.
A brow trim?
What's that?
You'll see.
Come on!
Ms. Shu!
Yingjian?
What happened to you...
I look awesome, right?
You look... sharp.
Check out
the eyebrows.
Yeah... stunning.
Hi there!
Sweetie!
With this killer look,
we are gonna slay as
a power couple
in front of the guests!
Please... you're way out of my league!
Gotta run for the bus!
Shu Han,
later!
Wait up,
I'm coming with you!
What?
Ms. Shu,
sorry to make you drive out here.
I wanna try the
public transit vibe today.
Go for it!
I need to see Xing Wu anyway.
Go get her, tiger.
Sup.
You drive.
I have stuff to handle.
Have fun, kids!
See ya!
Peace!
Howdy!
Hey girlie!
Look at you, all smiles!
You bet!
Bring out
the premium cuts!
I'd like a feast!
Did you win the lottery?
Close enough.
It basically
feels like it.
Check this out!
Holy cow! 888?
Talk about
hitting the jackpot!
When money talks, you listen.
Let some of that good juju
rub off on me!
Before we dive in,
let's test
your level.
Read this passage for me.
You first.
My pleasure.
Welcome to our remarkable No.1 Middle School
of Anzi County
which is surrounded by beautiful seaside scenery.
Good job.
You're up.
Come on.
Oh boy... here goes.
Welcome... toyota... woof...
No... Yakuza...
No. 1!
Welcome to our...
Welcome to our
remarkable No.1 Middle School of Anzi County...
Hulk smash!
Your mom...
Mom...
Remarkable.
Is this even English?
It doesn't make any sense.
I know the letters,
but not the words...
Just sit down.
Beautiful SEAFOOD scenery...
Yum...
Well...
I know what
we're dealing with...
The main issue
is your
vocabulary.
In English,
vocab is everything.
Expand your vocab,
everything else gets easier.
That's why we start
with flashcards!
Yes, ma'am!
No, please!
We're not exactly
brainiacs.
Rote memorization is torture!
Exactly.
We're
blue-collar guys.
School was never our thing...
Come on.
I gave
my word
to get this English club going.
For you guys,
I'm going all in!
Let's go, squad!
We got this, guys!
We're in this together!
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, Big G,
can you rap?
Shakespeare with
a hip-hop beat...
Now that'd be pretty sweet!
Hi,
can I
get these
custom-made into pins?
Just English text?
Yes! Exactly.
Sure thing.
Welcome to
the club, guys!
Everyone
who joins us
gets a
super cute
button pin!
Check it out!
They've got
grammar hacks,
useful phrases,
and vocab.
Perfect for
studying on the fly.
Trust me,
English is
actually easy
once you find your vibe.
It doesn't
have to
be boring!
Now,
Big G is about to
drop a rap on
how to
crush vocab
with zero effort.
Let's get some snaps and claps!
1, 2, 3, hit it!
Welcome to English,
but not like school,
No boring textbooks,
we make it cool!
A few little words,
a suffix at the end,
turn it to...
Good afternoon,
esteemed guests,
faculty,
and
students!
Welcome, welcome!
Today
is a truly special day
as we gather
to welcome
our friends from afar
for an exciting cultural exchange.
Welcome.
Hello.
Thank you.
Welcome to No.1 Middle School
in Anzi County.
And this is our school chairman,
Mr. Zhong.
And this is our dean,
Ms. Yang.
And today's journey will be
led by these two students.
This is Ye Yingjian.
Hi, my name is Ye Yingjian.
And this is our student Qing Ye.
Hi, I'm Qing Ye.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
We shall start this journey!
This way.
Thank you.
This way. Please follow us.
Hi guys!
Welcome to
No.1 Middle School of Anzi County.
We're located in Anzi County.
We're surrounded by beautiful seaside scenery.
Yes.
Also, the campus is well equipped
with high-tech facilities,
including modern classrooms
advanced libraries
and a big gymnasium.
If you look at the wall, both sides,
they're Chinese famous figures.
Yes, I know this one,
Huai Luogeng.
Yeah, you know that.
This is our classroom.
OK.
This is my class.
All rise!
A round of applause!
Come on in.
The aquarium is acting up.
Customer service
will take two weeks.
Poor fish won't
survive that long.
The light's blown,
easy fix.
The water is still cold.
The temp control
is down.
Is it complicated?
Not really.
If the thermometer
is busted,
the temp control
won't get
the water temp,
so the heater
won't kick on.
You really know your stuff.
Your school is really well-planted, yeah.
Yeah, it's bringing us fresh air.
Yeah, we can enjoy some fresh air.
It's a really good place for students.
Oh, and what's this place for?
Oh, this is our English corner.
Hi, guys!
Hello everyone.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, nice to meet you too.
We always study here
and we can
exchange our ideas.
Oh, what's this?
This item called badge
is referred to
as "Baji" in Chinese.
It's extremely popular
among Chinese high school.
We use it for learning English with joy.
Oh, we also create some rap songs
for learning grammar and vocabulary.
Really?
Yes, wanna see?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Showtime, Big G.
Hello everyone.
My name is Fan Tong.
You can call me Big G.
It means fat tiger,
but I'm not fat as you can see.
I'll show you
how we learn English with joy in rap.
1, 2, 3, go!
Yo, welcome to
a class
that is super fun,
learning with a beat,
yeah, we've just begun!
Take the root "act,"
play it like a game,
watch how it changes, never stays the same.
I'm on stage performing,
an "actor" too,
but if I "overact,"
it's a bit too much for you!
Boring study methods
"counteract" the fun,
so let's "interact" together, everyone!
Thank you!
Oh, I'm really amazed by
the English proficiency of
the students here
and by the
educational concepts.
We can talk about collaboration later.
OK!
Go go go!
Bribble!
Do you like it?
I really love playing basketball, y'know?
You wanna try?
OK.
Have a try!
Thank you!
Let's go!
OK, now it's lunch time.
So let's go to the restaurant to eat.
Sure.
Let's go.
This way.
I really, really like Chinese food.
Ye Yingjian is really something!
Look at all these awards.
He's almost as good as you, Wu.
Hands off!
Xing Wu,
see if we can use
any of these light tubes.
Be right there.
Look here!
Hey, you two stand in the middle, please.
Yeah, come on!
I'm really happy.
Thank you.
Please!
Thank you so much!
Alright, eyes on the camera.
1, 2, 3, cheese!
Good to go.
That was fast!
First time fixing a fish tank,
and you beat your AC record!
Pack up.
Xing Wu,
you're the real deal.
Hit me up if it acts up again.
Got it.
Mr. Jiang,
I hear you,
It's not
a lack of interest,
I just don't
have the right project now.
Got it working?
Yeah, sure.
Let's touch base later.
Alright.
Talk soon!
So, you're Xing Wu?
Hello, Mr. Ye.
Hey.
She said you're a genius,
better than the certified techs.
Honestly, I didn't buy it.
All machines are
similar anyway.
I heard you did
a great job in Xinhai, too.
You look around
my son's age.
Why aren't you in school?
I wanted to make money.
Money?
Why is that?
Everyone needs money, right?
Sorry, gotta take this.
Hey,
Mr. Ma!
Dude,
I think
he really likes you.
Big congrats.
Another big shot likes you.
I only care about the paycheck.
He thinks very highly of you.
He's launching
a project on tech street,
and wanted me to ask
if you'd like
to run it.
See?
I told you so.
He loved that
batch of PCs you flipped
in Xinhai.
He's had you on his radar since then.
We barely talked
for three minutes.
That's all it takes.
He's been
in the game forever,
his eye is sharp.
Honestly,
if he hands you
this opportunity...
what's your move?
What's the package?
Dude,
running the whole tech street?
That's a total goldmine!
It's a highly coveted spot.
Even Yang Gang
has his eye on it.
I gotta see how big the bag is
before I make a move.
Nine-k base, fat commissions,
and full insurance.
Stick around
for three years,
and he will let you
buy a store for dirt cheap.
Plus,
he's in
real estate now,
so you might
even score a free condo!
[I want us to]
[make memories in school,]
[get out of this town,]
[and welcome a dazzling future together.]
Seriously sleeping on an offer like this?
When should I set up
your meeting?
Make it quick.
You got it!
Seriously,
why does she
get all the attention?
Because she's actually good.
You're taking her side?
Did you hit your head?
Yeah, girl,
she stepped all over you,
and you're still defending her?
She's a rich
city girl
with connections.
She outclassed me, period.
I'm over it.
That should've been your moment!
If she didn't butt in,
you'd be the one flexing
next to Ye Yingjian in that photo.
Average girls like us
don't stand a chance.
Even if we try our hardest,
we're not even in her league.
I can't stand her
high-and-mighty act.
She's barely here
and she's hogging the spotlight.
Chill the f*ck out!
She's got the receipts, though.
Well, you can take it,
but I won't!
Qing Ye,
I was looking for you.
Mr. Zhu.
Here.
What's this?
Your prize money,
as promised.
For making
us proud.
Thank you, sir!
Listen,
we don't have
the fancy resources
of a big city school,
but if you grind,
we've
got your back!
Got it.
Cool.
Catch you later.
See ya.
Guess who just got her prize money?
[Congrats.]
See?
I can help carry
the financial load now.
Totally found money!
So...
ready to join me yet?
[It's not "found money."]
[You earned it.]
[An interpreter would've]
[charged them double.]
You guys want something?
Look,
here's your welcome gift!
Prickly things
for little pricks!
One? Please!
Dang! The whole stash!
Enjoy the whole pack!
Yo, school over?
[Man,]
[Big G and I got benched]
[to finish our homework.]
Is Qing Ye with you?
[Nah, she split early.]
[Ain't she home yet?]
[ETA?]
[Gotta skip]
[Mr. Ye's dinner.]
[I'll apologize in person.]
Qing Ye!
Where've you been?
Why are you ignoring my calls?
My phone was on silent.
Who did this?
Does it matter?
Drop the scissor.
Lean back.
Does it hurt?
Are you serious?
It's fine.
I just want these awful things
out of my life forever.
Any bruises?
No.
Are you capping?
I'm not...
Alright.
Seriously...
come back to school.
With you around,
no one would dare touch me.
What makes you think that?
Because you're literally
a legend there.
My friend Shi Min
was hyping you up
so hard.
If you had my back,
those toxic girls
wouldn't dare pull this cr*p.
Not even if... It's to protect me?
Go dry your hair.
Gotta be somewhere.
Xing Wu!
Yo,
getting kept everyday is wild!
Like, I have a life!
Honestly,
college is
a scam anyway!
I should just pull a Wu:
hustle, grind,
and get my bread!
You got zero resume.
Hey! I've got skills!
Well...
Is it good?
Wu?
Yo, what's up?
Qing Ye home?
Yeah.
You hungry? Want one?
Real talk.
How's she doing at school?
Oh, wow!
She's thriving!
Literally
a main character!
Has she
pissed anyone off?
Doubt it...
She's just been
flexing too hard lately!
During the VIP visit,
she was hosting
the whole thing
in flawless English!
We were basically
NPCs in the back
going, "Welcome! Welcome!"
She's got crazy clout
now.
Did something happen to her?
Nothing.
Just asking.
Relax, dude.
She ain't no
pushover.
She can
handle herself.
But real talk,
clout brings haters.
A few girls
are definitely salty...
Who are they?
Ye-Ye is a straight-A student
and a total ten.
If I were a gal, I'd be pressed!
I want names.
You take after your mom.
Most people say
I got my dad's face.
Nonsense.
Your mom and I were
inseparable for ten years.
You're a carbon copy
of her young self.
Why'd you ghost her?
I got knocked up
before marriage!
I was adopted by
your grandparents,
living under their roof.
When I messed up,
I couldn't face them,
so I just dipped.
Do you miss her?
Oh,
hell yeah.
But I never
reached out.
One wrong step
and it's
a slippery slope.
My husband
left us,
my mother-in-law is paralyzed,
my boy dropped out,
and we're broke.
But we're
still breathing, right?
Every day above ground is a win!
Auntie,
I love your optimism.
Right?
My positive vibe
is my superpower!
What's that
Gen-Z term again?
"A happy little puppy!"
At the end
of the day,
it's all about
staying positive!
Auntie,
don't you want
Wu to have a real chance?
Schopenhauer said,
"fate shuffles the cards
and we play."
We can actually
choose how to play.
You have to
play smart.
If we just drift along,
nothing changes.
Why not take a leap of faith
and break free?
Sweetie...
This Schopenhauer guy...
sounds like a total card shark.
Does he play blackjack?
I bet he
cleans up at the casino!
Xing Wu...
Maid service already?
In your head!
I'm just...
browsing...
Your handwriting's actually neat.
And you're surprisingly
good at math.
That's it.
It was nothing.
Total flex.
You gotta learn to
handle yourself around here.
Let me teach you a move.
It better be a cheat code.
I don't do basic tier.
You bet.
Now.
Come at me.
How?
Any way.
Go for the kill.
Ow, ow!
Seriously?
This is your cheat code?
The lesson is,
fighting back blindly
when you're cornered
is a rookie mistake.
It's...
a gag gift from years ago.
How sweet.
Anyway,
my point is...
there is no
cheat code
for self-defense.
Technique
gets crushed
by raw power.
Case in point.
So I'm just helpless?
Run.
Rule number one: book it.
Run like your life depends on it.
Lecture over.
You're dismissed.
And if my cardio sucks?
What if they corner me
and I get wrecked again?
Unbelievable...
[What if they corner me]
[and]
[I get wrecked again?]
[Drop the scissor.]
[Seriously...]
[come back to school.]
Tofu, tofu,
fresh and bold!
Get it now before it's cold!
Morning!
Sup, stalker!
Hey.
Admit it,
you're playing bodyguard.