Put me down!
Second Young Miss.
I'm saving you,
and saving the Su family too.
You failed to recognize a true master.
Do you know what a chance you nearly missed?
You're still trying to fool me?
He's no true master at all.
He's just a lecherous fraud playing tricks.
You...
The Eldest Young Miss is in grave danger.
You've lost all rational judgment.
Think carefully.
Just now,
Mr. Wu sealed your acupoints with a flick.
In the entire Ancient Martial Arts World,
who else has such power?
Can Professor Sun do it?
Besides deceiving people
and telling lies,
what else can he do?
Well,
even if his martial arts are impressive,
that doesn't mean he's a great doctor!
And he's so young.
Seeing is believing.
Then let's go see for ourselves.
But you must promise me,
no matter what you see, don't make a sound.
Otherwise,
I'll knock you out at once.
Fine.
I promise.
Second Young Miss!
Stay calm!
Pervert!
Bastard!
And you said he wasn't a lecher!
He's even got a nosebleed!
This...
must be because
the room is too hot and stuffy.
Yes, internal heat.
Internal heat!
It must be internal heat.
To remove the Soul-Seizing Seal,
one must lure out Guichen's intent.
Seizing this prime chance,
seal its consciousness,
and sever its claws.
Did you see that?
Controlling needles with qi,
Remote Acupuncture.
This is a true divine miracle!
Second Young Miss,
I won't allow anyone to doubt Mr. Wu again.
I, Su Qi, will be the first to object.
Shut up!
Watch carefully.
You...
have finally come.
Though Sword Two was defeated,
he gauged a measure of your strength.
Truly worthy of the Zhongnan Wu Clan.
This Peach Blossom Curse, crafted for you,
is utterly yin, utterly bewitching,
made to break the Pure Yang Body.
I wonder
if your decade-old Primal Yang Foundation
can withstand this bone-piercing rapture.
I eagerly await
seeing your Dao Heart shatter,
and your Primal Yang completely drained.
Nurturing Sirens as Cauldrons.
Guichen's methods are indeed cunning.
What does it matter that I'm a Siren?
What does Su Wan matter?
I am but a devoted admirer of my lord's
masculine vigor.
My lord is yang,
your servant is yin.
Yin and yang should naturally unite.
My lord, why not
join me in carnal pleasures?
Join me in carnal pleasures.
A pity your seduction has no effect on me.
My lord, what a fierce temper you have.
However,
you've fallen into my trap.
Is that all you've got?
So much for Zhongnan martial arts.
Pure Yang Body?
Before the evil, yin Peach Blossom Curse,
it cannot withstand a single blow.
Once the Primal Yang breaks,
the Dao Foundation collapses.
Less than a tenth of your power remains.
Where is A-Yi?
Go.
Kill him.
Yes.
Sister!
You bastard!
How could this happen?
I trusted the wrong person.
I never imagined you'd be this kind of man.
How dare you touch my sister!
You lecherous scoundrel!
I...
I'll kill you!
Don't misunderstand.
Let me explain.
This was a medical accident.
Accident, my foot!
I'll kill you!
Let me explain!
This really was a medical accident.
Something went wrong during the treatment.
My decades of Primal Yang energy,
was just freely given to Su Wan!
They both saw it.
What do I do?
You took advantage and act innocent?
Today, you must answer to my sister!
Or I won't rest till one of us is dead!
Wu Ming!
I never thought you were this kind of man.
Do you deserve the title of master?
I'm so disappointed in you.
Lecher!
Say something!
Nothing left to say, huh?
Where did he go?
That lecherous scoundrel!
Think you can get what you want and run?
Xiao Qi.
Drag him back from the ends of the earth!
We can't let him off the hook!
Right!
Let's go!
That wasn't me.
That absolutely wasn't me.
How could it be?
How could that have been me?
How could I do something so shameless?
Right.
It was all a dream.
It must have been a hallucination.
That scum took advantage of the situation.
Yes.
That's exactly how it was.
He took advantage of the situation.
That goddamn bastard!
I, Su Wan, swear
I'll make him pay the price.
Let's go!
Wait, Brother Ming.
Why are you in such a rush?
Oh, just come on!
There's a man-eating tiger at the Su house.
If we don't leave now, it'll be too late.
The Su family?
You mean the tigress?
Don't we need to investigate Guichen?
Let's wait till Su Wan wakes up.
There's no time now!
Singing so loudly,
Miss Su must have woken up by now.
You...
What on earth happened?
Hurry, tell me!
Brother Ming!
You don't know the situation!
Stop right there!