Delicious.
Mr. Ghosthand.
Please.
Good girl.
Mr. Ghosthand,
I've heard so much about you.
I've heard the Second Young Master is dashing
and exceptionally handsome.
Seeing you today,
your reputation is well deserved.
Care for a game?
I'd be honored to oblige.
The Young Master of the Gambling God Family
truly is extraordinary.
Allow me to show my humble skills.
Brother Ghosthand is truly full of surprises.
Your hand speed is absolutely divine.
However,
his opponent is no pushover either.
That day...
Since he's so skilled at dice,
then,
let's play something he can't control.
We can only bet on
what I do best.
What is Brother Ghosthand best at?
I'm good at everything.
But
what I'm best at
is the Life-or-Death Bet.
There are six bullets in here.
There's still one bullet inside.
Care to play, Young Master?
Sure.
Let's play.
Xiaodao,
you play with him.
Y-Young Master,
I don't know how to play.
That doesn't matter.
Just pull the trigger.
Like this.
Go on.
Young Master, I...
If you don't play,
you die right now.
I...
I... I...
My turn.
The death probability is now 33 percent.
Here goes.
You've got guts.
And good luck too.
But,
my luck is even better than yours.
One shot left.
I'll leave the most thrilling one to you.
Y-Young Master,
this shot means certain death!
The game isn't over.
The winner is yet to be decided.
We must continue.
Mr. Ghosthand,
I admit defeat.
You're far too good.
You predicted this entire outcome.
A true master.
I said,
the winner is yet to be decided.
The game isn't over.
This shot,
let me take it for you.
Brother Ghosthand,
What's going on here?
You all saw it.
Six bullets were loaded inside.
That's right.
I clearly
heard you fire five shots.
But actually,
I removed one while loading.
Brother Ghosthand's hands are so fast!
It was completely undetectable.
Then...
Then how did this shot have a bullet?
Because the moment I fired,
I had already loaded the bullet back in.
Bravo!
Ghosthand truly lives up to his name.
I clearly
watched you with my own eyes.
Yet...
How did you do it?
Because
I am the Invisible Ghosthand.
So relaxing.
So this is the joy of being rich.
Even more enjoyable than I imagined.
Sir,
how's the pressure?
What other services would you like?
We are available 24 hours a day,
dedicated to providing you with
any indulgence you can imagine.
Any indulgence I can imagine?
Then take a guess.
What service do I want?
I'm not as handsome or clever as you, sir.
So of course I can't read your mind.
You're quite a sweet talker.
Your legs are so long,
and your heels so high.
Can you even walk properly?
Sir, I'll go get the door.
Sure.
I...
Rourou.
Brother Qian.
Why are you here?
Aren't you at the hospital?
Everything's settled.
Jingjing is looking after things there.
We hired the best caregiver.
You know what?
We found a donor kidney.
That's great.
I came to thank you.
I told you, no need to thank me.
Just a small favor.
My love and kindness
finally have a place to land.
For me,
that's also very meaningful.
I should be thanking you.
Brother Qian.
You're the kindest and most sincere man.
I sincerely want to repay you.
You...
Did you misunderstand something?
It's not what you think.
I...
I don't want you to repay me.
Don't feel burdened by it.
I know.
You're different from other men.
You have no improper intentions toward me.
It's good that you know.
Then hurry up and let me go.
Men and women should keep a proper distance.
I'm a hot-blooded man,
and if I do something rash,
I won't be responsible.
I'm doing this willingly.
You don't need to be responsible.
Okay.
There's no reasoning with you.
Please, just let go.
Brother Qian.
I'm so exhausted.
Just let me hold you for a while.
Just a little while.
Brother Qian.
You know,
you're like a ray of light
shining into my darkness.
You showed me this world still has love,
and still light.
Why are you crying?
I really can't stand seeing people cry.
Hey,
Cry, go ahead and cry.
All the grievances in your heart,
all the pent-up feelings,
let them all out.
You should feel better afterward.
Brother Qian.
Do you...
Do you look down on me?
Or...
do you simply not like me?
Look down on you?
No, no, no.
Not at all, not at all.
I do like you.
A woman as beautiful,
kind, gentle,
and devoted as you,
what man wouldn't like you?
Then...
I'll go freshen up first.
Wait for me here.
This is moving way too fast.
Saying I don't like her...
I definitely like her.
Well...
Let's just let nature take its course.
Miss.
Mr. Wu has already left.
He asked me to tell you
that you're too exhausted,
and to please rest here with peace of mind.
He said
he doesn't look down on you.
When you're not acting out of gratitude,
and he isn't lusting after your body,
perhaps then,
the two of you can be together.