What's so interesting? Let me see.
Sleeping with my wife?
You...
Oh my god!
You, you...
What the hell are you doing to me?
You sleep with my wife and want to hit me too?
Let go of me right now!
I'm not done with you!
If you want a child, stop yelling.
A child? What child?
You son of a bitch!
What?
You wanna cuckold me right in front of my face?
Let me go!
What are you talking about?
I can cure your impotence.
Impotence? You're the impotent one!
Oh really, you wretched woman!
You even told this pretty boy about that?
Are you done acting crazy?
Talking trash!
Brother Wu Ming is a divine doctor.
He was just performing acupuncture on me.
He can help us have a child.
A child of our very own.
Do you take me for a fool?
Think how much money I've spent,
how many famous doctors I've seen,
how many strong drugs I've taken. Nothing worked.
Now I think there's something wrong with me mentally.
The moment I'm in bed with you, I lose all confidence.
When I first took the drugs, I thought they worked.
Now I'm completely lifeless.
No confidence.
Afraid of failing.
You want confidence?
Fine!
I'll give it to you.
Stop bragging.
I know what I'm capable of.
Let me go!
Or I'm not done with you!
Fatty.
Go to the door, don't let anyone in.
Be careful!
I'm not done with you!
Ignite Shenshu, open the Gate of Life,
let the true energy flow...
Open!
The Eight Liao open and close like a floodgate.
Dragon and Tiger meet, Ren and Du meridians connect.
Twin needles at Huiyang stabilize the great sea.
Yongquan breaks through the nine heavens.
Genuine Qi pours back into the dantian.
Rise!
Honey, you're standing up!
I feel terrifyingly strong right now.
I could punch through the Earth!
So amazing!
Brother Wu Ming, your great kindness...
I'll be indebted to you for life.
But right now,
I have something huge to take care of.
Gotta go, gotta go!
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on, shut the door, shut it!
Honey!
Sweetheart!
I can't wait any longer!
Brother Ming!
Look at this!
The news!
Breaking news!
National goddess Jiang Feifei,
superstar offers a huge reward to save her mom.
An astronomical amount!
Mom and I have depended on each other since I was little.
She's the only support in my life,
and the whole reason I work so hard.
As long as someone can save my mother,
I'm willing to pay any price.
Anything.
Brother Ming,
if you can cure Jiang Feifei's mother,
and get her to endorse our Chinese Daoist Medical Hall,
won't we become famous all over Mancheng,
and take the world by storm?
Plus, Brother Ming,
she said she'd pay any price.
Anything.
Do you know what "anything" means?
Don't you want
Jiang Feifei as a superstar sister-in-law?
To cure her mother's illness,
the root still lies with Jiang Feifei herself.
Her manager's number is on here.
Don't miss this chance!
We're sorry.
The number you dialed is switched off.
Please try again later.
It's switched off.
Makes sense.
With all of Jiang Feifei's fans,
their spit alone could drown a person.
The moment she released that number,
it must've been flooded with calls.
Got excited for nothing.
Alright, alright.
Focus on your actual business.
Tomorrow you're visiting your girlfriend's family.
Shouldn't you prepare some decent gifts
greet your father-in-law & mother-in-law?
Use up all your savings,
give it your all,
and make a great impression.
Don't worry, Brother Ming.
I'll definitely give it my all,
Intimidate father-in-law & mother-in-law!
Wait, no.
I mean, put on a great performance,
and break through the Earth!
Oh, stop it.
Brother Ming,
I still have a bit of savings on hand.
Let me treat you to a nice meal later.
Sure.
Look here.
Account balance: 86.
You call that savings?
Are you going for broke,
or just humiliating yourself?
Brother Ming, no deliveries for months.
I burned through all my old savings.
Who would marry their daughter to you?
Wouldn't that just ruin her life?
Brother Ming,
you can't just abandon me!
I-I promise,
from now on,
I'll definitely work my hardest,
burn the midnight oil,
fear no hardship,
and fill our medical hall's coffers!
B-b-but right now,
I-I don't have a cent.
I...
I can't go empty-handed, can I?
Brother Ming, you gotta help me this time!
Fine.
You've got no fortune in your fate.
Just this once, alright?
The Gate of Life from Qian hides in Dui,
the Wealth Star in Kan meets the Azure Dragon.
Two or three li to the northwest,
where water and fire converge in harmony.
Brother Ming, what do you mean?
If we win money today,
I'll take you to buy a bag later.
You got it, bro!
Brother Ming,
you're gonna make me rich!
Cut the chatter.
Let's go.
Beautiful, lend me a few chips to play.
Security!
Someone's causing trouble.
Misunderstanding!
How many chips for my 3,000-yuan scooter?
Consider these chips a loan.
But you have to pay me back ten chips.
Or your scooter becomes mine.
You're after my little scooter, aren't you?
Fine, ten it is.
Let's go.
Brother Ming,
I'll go look around first.
Qian's White Tiger holds the golden dice,
Dui's Greedy Wolf swallows the jade hook.
Li's fire burns the baccarat tables,
Kan's water claims the roulette wheel.
Zhen's towering wood splits the pai gow,
Xun's wind shatters the slot machines.
Kun's earth breeds gold, dice cup settles,
Gen's mountain crushes all gamblers' woes.
Place your bets, everyone.
Stand next to the pretty lady.
Boosts your luck in romance.
You'll definitely win.
Stand right here. Don't move an inch.
This spot, Kun earth gives birth to metal.
Steady wins the game.
Brother Ming.
What number should I bet on?
The Kun position is solid. Bet whatever.
Even a small bet can win big.
Alright.
Let's give it a shot.
Trade the scooter for a Lamborghini.
I'll bet on 17 points.
Lucky number.
Young man, you must be new here.
Do you even know the rules?
Do you know how rare 17 points is?
Playing all night long,
hitting it once would be a true blessing.
You're throwing your money down the drain.
Take it back.
Buddy.
Take some advice.
Switch it up quick.
Just bet big or small. Much better.
With this,
you're just handing money to the dealer.
Yeah.
Th-this...
Brother Ming.
Should I switch my bet?
No more bets.
Once placed, it stays.
Don't you know the casino rules?
Leave it.
But...
Hey, boss.
Have you made up your mind yet?
Everyone's waiting for the reveal.
Quit stalling. Open it up.
Let this rookie pay his tuition.
Open, open, open!
I'll bet on 17 points.
With Brother Ming here,
fortune favors the bold.
Open it!
Open, open!
Open, open, open!
Open it now!
Open it!
Open!
It really is 17 points!
Brother Ming!
17 points!
No way.
Your luck is unbelievable!
I've never lost when it comes to luck.
Brother Ming,
I think you're terrifyingly strong right now.
Place your bets, everyone.
Brother Ming, what should I bet next?
Stand next to that girl. Bet anything.
What should we bet this round?
I'll bet small.
It must be small.
What do you say we bet?
What are you doing?
This yellow one suits you.
Alright then.
Hold on, young man.
You're getting cockier each time!
Do you know how rare triples are?
Way harder than getting 17 points!
My money, my call.
All in.
You're going all in?
I can't tell if you're stupid,
or just plain stupid.
You know what this is called?
This is called
making big moves.
If triples come up this round,
I'll give you all my chips.
You mean it?
Of course.
With so many witnesses here,
you think I'd back out?
But if it doesn't come up,
you crawl around this table twice.
Deal.
I'll take it.
Alright.
Pretty lady,
why don't you go all in with me?
What if we hit it?
Okay.
Since you're so bold,
I'll bet just a tiny bit with you.
Hey, beautiful
Knees weak from seeing a handsome guy?
Be careful
Don't bump into the table
It would break my heart
Quit stalling
Hurry up and reveal them
I'm gonna make him crawl under the table
What are you waiting for?
Open them, open them!
Fine
I'll open them now.
Open, open, open!