The ancient scrolls say,
the Heaven-Blind Affliction
marks one forsaken by Heaven.
Meant to be born with the Celestial Eye,
yet abandoned by the heavens.
Both eyes shrouded in chaos,
as though stillborn in the womb,
all vitality severed.
Was he already on guard against me,
or did he dodge that strike by chance?
However,
reading your bone structure,
your aura and life lines,
you are not one forsaken by Heaven.
Specks of starlight grace your brow.
On the contrary, it is a sign of great fortune.
Then there is only one explanation.
Someone forced open your Celestial Eye
The failure caused a backlash.
As the saying goes,
incantations must not be rashly invoked,
the Celestial Eye must not be forced open.
The dark art's backlash
scorched your mind and spirit,
sealed off your vision,
and disturbed your senses,
and forged the eyes you now possess,
which seem to pierce through the dark,
yet are bizarre eyes trapped in the abyss.
You said my eyes can be cured.
How?
A rare and precious elixir.
The Flesh Immortal.
What is the Flesh Immortal?
The great cultivators of old,
upon ascending to immortality,
chose dragon veins to inter their bodies.
Their flesh gives rise to
jade-colored feather patterns,
unrotting for a thousand years,
undecaying for ten thousand.
The heart pounds like a rolling war drum,
blood and qi holding boundless vitality,
endless and unbroken.
It sounds like ninth-heaven thunder,
shaking the very soul.
This is
the Flesh Immortal.
The ultimate masterpiece of creation.
Only Flesh Immortal's essence blood,
combined with
Ghost-God Needles piercing yin and yang,
can offer a sliver of hope.
To let you behold once more
after a thunderstorm,
the rainbow arching across the sky.
Absurd.
A baseless legend.
Where in this world is a Flesh Immortal?
You're toying with me.
The Flesh Immortal
is not something ordinary people can see.
The Flesh Immortal, a panacea of the ages,
can revive the dead and flesh the bones.
Its heart never rests,
its sound like thunder.
Truly miraculous.
Even a corpse still has a heartbeat.
I must verify this.
It really is so.
Let me check its blood and qi's vitality.
The patriarch's entire body is a panacea!
You scoundrel!
That is the venerable patriarch!
I...
I'll beat you to death!
Having an elder at home
is like having a treasure.
Talking about this,
I'm really starting to miss home.
We're discussing curing my eyes.
Why suddenly talk about missing home?
Back to the earlier question.
I don't have a Flesh Immortal right now,
but I do have a vial of its essence blood.
A rare elixir.
A priceless treasure.
After all you've said,
are you after my money or my body?
To think I believed a shameless rogue.
How can you have so little self-awareness?
Do you think you look like someone with money?
What's your monthly cut as an assassin?
I'll double it.
Be my bodyguard from now on.
How did you know?
Healers observe, listen, ask, and feel.
In my eyes,
you have no secrets.
Think it over carefully.
Double the price.
Come find me when you've decided.
Best of both worlds.
Forging living people into blind weapons.
Severing one's spiritual roots.
Ruining their entire life.
Such demonic heresy,
I shall eradicate.
From now on, stay away from Wu Ming.
He's dangerous.
Oh, so you know he's dangerous?
Shouldn't that warning be for you?
He's already gone and...
Done what to me?
Anyway, regarding Auntie's treatment,
leave the dealings with him to me.
Don't have any more contact with him.
Wu Ming surely isn't stupid enough
to brag about taking advantage of my sis.
She wouldn't be pregnant, would she?
It's possible.
It's not too late for Plan B, right?
What are you two whispering about?
Nothing.
Then it's settled.
Or I'll cut off your allowance.
What did you say?
No way!
I don't agree to this!
Are you even my real sister,
treating me like this?
Oh, so you remember I'm your sister now?
What are you two sisters arguing about?
Grandpa, you're here!
Grandpa, you're the best to me.
Su Wan is bullying me.
She's cutting off my supplies.
She's going to starve
your cutest, sweetest granddaughter.
Grandpa,
you wouldn't abandon me, right?
help a girl out, slip me some cash.
Your grandpa,
these old bones of mine,
even my meals now
all depend on your sister.
So biased!
You two are in this together.
Xiaoqi, let's go.
Grandpa,
Do you have any leads on Master Tianyi?
Why are you
asking about Master Tianyi now?
Could it be possible that
Master Tianyi is from Zhongnan Mountain?
That is possible.
Master Tianyi's medicine and cultivation
are extraordinary.
Truly transcendent.
Then what Wu Ming said might be true.
Master Tianyi is a Zhongnan traitor.
However,
Master Tianyi has been renowned for years.
I'm afraid Wu Ming is no match for him.
Grandpa,
think harder.
Just a few years ago,
Master Tianyi
overnight
took control of Yushi City.
He reigns supreme there.
If you go to Yushi City looking for him,
you might find some leads.
Yushi City?
That place...
where our Su Family barely holds ground?
Yes.
That place
is treacherous.
If you're going after Master Tianyi,
I'd advise you,
don't get in too deep.
I know my limits.
What's this?
Got your essence drained?
That wasn't just essence-draining,
that was downright inhuman!
From now on,
don't call him Fat Wu anymore.
Call him Hollow Wu.
A truly fitting empty shell.
You're kicking me when I'm down,
rubbing salt in the wound.
Your name's Wu Ming,
mine should be Wu Qian.
So the two of us brothers together
live up to our reputation, don't we?
Even the heavens are helping us make a name.
And you can still laugh about it.
There's still some grease in those bones.
Speaking of essence-draining,
the two of us are
brothers in misfortune!
You've got the nerve to bring it up?
It was your big mouth
that spilled the truth about Su Wan.
Did you think how she'd face the world?
You've stayed in the mountains too long.
Your thinking's way too conservative.
Let me tell you,
people these days,
if they like each other,
they get together.
If they don't,
they say bye-bye.
To Su Wan, you might just be
nothing more than a one-night fling.
Don't go spouting nonsense here.
You're tarnishing her good name.
Su Wan was an untouched maiden before.
Untouched?
Oh my god.
Unbelievable!
What era are we even living in?
And still untouched?
You know what,
A high-mountain flower like Su Wan,
an ice queen goddess
with her eyes looking down on everyone...
Brother Ming,
you should strike while the iron's hot,
marry first, fall in love later,
and just seal the deal!
You,
worry about yourself first.
Look at you.
Lips thin as blades,
a magnet for bad romance.
Corners of your mouth turned down,
your love path as treacherous as a chasm.
And these red marks at your eye corners,
a romantic calamity is upon you,
a deadly fate you cannot escape.
Brother Ming,
you have to save me!
That Black Yama
fed me a worm this big!
She said
even if I hide in Yama's Hall,
she can still drag me out.
Brother Ming,
hurry, take a look at me!
I feel that worm
burrowing deep into my heart!
The Heart-Devouring Gu.
It only tracks, it isn't lethal.
Whoever tied the bell must untie it.
You caused this trouble,
you resolve it yourself.
Resolve it?
How am I supposed to resolve it?
She's forcing herself on me!
I'd rather die than submit!
Brother Ming, I'm afraid of the dark.
You know that.
She's not my type.
Afraid of the dark, yet you eat chocolate?
The trial of love is hard to pass.
Life and death are predestined.
On this matter,
I'm afraid I can't help you.
Brother Ming,
I don't care.
You have to teach me a technique.
Didn't you mention some technique
that gives boundless strength once mastered,
where falling leaves and petals can wound?
And then?
Without the diamond drill,
don't take on the porcelain job.
I'm the head of a great family now.
Without some real skill,
how can I keep my men in line?
If someone comes to challenge me,
do I just drive them off with words?
Your constitution is dull,
your meridians are blocked,
you have no affinity for this.
You can't learn it.
Brother Ming,
you're a divine healer!
You're a living immortal!
You must have a secret method.
Teach me just one technique!
There is one method, actually.
Forcing the Thirteen Ghost-God Needles
to open the hidden channels within you
might defy heaven and change your fate.
However...
Brother Ming, stick me!
Stick me!
Stick me with them!
Stick me anywhere!
Stick me!
Hurry, stick me!
That thick?
Hold on!
Brother Ming,
You're trying to kill your own brother!
Reaping without sowing,
that's wishful thinking.
Without the mindset to wield power,
any power you gain
becomes a death warrant.
It'll only doom you and those around you.
Hey, come on.
You could've just told me.
Why resort to such a vicious blow?
My butt's about to split open!
How else will you learn your lesson?
Fine.
Brother Ming,
I'll remember this.
Lately,
keep a close eye on the Gao Family.
Especially the second young master,
Gao Jin.
Got it.
Only Flesh Immortal's essence blood,
with yin-yang piercing Ghost-God Needles,
can offer a glimmer of hope.
To let you see again
the rainbow across the post-storm sky,
the dewdrops trembling on grass tips at dawn,
the boundless golden wheat waves in autumn,
and in the depths of winter,
the pure, flawless blanket of white snow.
He clearly had two chances
to gravely wound or even kill me.
Why did he hold back?
He's too arrogant.
Perhaps
he did it on purpose.
His aim
was to crush me psychologically.