Oh?
If it isn't President Su.
I'm looking for Wu Ming.
President Su.
You're looking radiant today.
Rosy and glowing.
Absolutely dazzling.
It seems
someone's been Blooming.
What's ailing you today, President Su?
Gynecological?
Or something neurological?
Is this how your medical hall treats guests?
Such Barbed remarks.
Did you swallow gunpowder?
No gunpowder,
but as for aged vinegar,
she drank a whole vat.
Second Princess.
Noda Midako.
What are you doing here?
Is that so strange?
I'm now the Chinese Daoist Medical Hall's
chief herbal supplier
and also
brand ambassador.
The grand Noda Family's Second Princess
stooping to work as an employee here?
You must be joking.
So what?
In a sense,
the Noda Family today
belongs to the Medical Hall.
More accurately,
it belongs to that man.
Impossible.
Even if his medical skills are miraculous,
how could he control the Noda Family?
Then I can only say
you're very shallow, President Su.
You've been so intimate with him,
yet you know nothing about him.
I really envy you.
Or perhaps
President Su Acquired a taste for it
and is craving a man,
so you came here on purpose
to relive an old dream.
How does little Wu Ming taste?
Care to share with us?
Nonsense.
Damn that Wu Ming!
Spreading that kind of thing everywhere!
Bastard!
Wu Ming!
Get out here right now!
If Master favors President Su...
Well, never mind.
Better to get on her good side.
President Su.
This way, please.
You're here.
You knew I was coming?
If you've come to interrogate me,
there's really no need.
I spent foundational vitality to save you.
As for the benefits you gained,
I'm sure you've felt them deeply yourself.
Have you no shame?
Why spread our business everywhere?
Everyone here is looking at me strangely.
I, Wu Ming, conduct myself with honor.
A matter like this,
I wouldn't even bother to mention.
Fine.
Then let this end here.
We'll both take it to the grave.
That suits me perfectly.
I came to ask you
just how deep your medical skills run.
Did I recover because of you,
or because of Professor Sun?
His superficial knowledge counts as
the Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles?
He hasn't even crossed the threshold.
True Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles
pierce heaven and earth,
sever fate and restore souls.
Without the courage to weigh life
and the cultivation to cross calamity,
it simply cannot be performed.
Are you doing some kind of magic trick?
You were never actually sick.
You merely fell into Tian Yi's trap.
He used you as a Human Cauldron
to nurture Mei.
Once the Mei spirit matures,
that's when he reaps the harvest.
Using your foundational vitality
to strengthen himself.
That's impossible.
Grandfather said
Tian Yi is a reclusive grandmaster.
He leaves hardly any trace these days.
How could he have cast Mei on me?
Tian Yi's true name is Guichen,
a traitor of our Zhongnan Sect.
His heart is twisted,
and he specializes in dark arts.
Does your Su family
have any leads on him?
I'll have to ask my grandfather.
If there are any,
I'll let you know.
Many thanks.
This time,
I'm asking you to save my aunt.
She has ALS.
Her condition is rapidly deteriorating.
Top global medical teams are helpless.
I want to know if you have a way.
Jiang Feifei,
is she your cousin?
How do you know?
I've seen her on TV.
In my view,
the issue isn't with your aunt,
but with Jiang Feifei.
That's impossible.
Feifei is in perfect health.
Are you kidding me?
Look at your aunt's facial features.
Your aunt's countenance—
a full and radiant forehead
signifies abundant blessings.
A rounded, fleshy chin
indicates a peaceful later life.
These aren't signs of grave illness.
Are you diagnosing or fortune-telling?
The Five Arts are inherently one.
Face and Aura Diagnosis is also medicine.
Look at recent media of Jiang Feifei.
Her brows grow crossed and reversed,
with scattered ends.
These are Entangled Brows.
Now look at her Yintang.
The Yintang is the Palace of Destiny.
Crimson foretells injury and bloodshed.
A major event will surely occur soon.
At best, her reputation will be ruined;
at worst, she'll end up imprisoned.
I'll grant you got that part right.
Feifei has been plagued by rumors lately.
Your aunt's face shows no illness;
rather, it shows she suffers for kin,
sacrificing herself to ward off calamity.
Her philtrum is deep and long—
her life force is extraordinarily strong.
Her nose bridge is high and straight—
her will is unyielding.
Her smile lines are deeply etched—
this signifies
a profound sense of responsibility,
willing to give all for loved ones.
At some critical moment,
she stepped forward
to take a blow meant for Jiang Feifei.
So the root of the problem
lies with Jiang Feifei.
What nonsense.
You've never even met my aunt.
How can you make such claims?
Do you think you're some god?
If you trust me,
go bring her here.
If you don't,
find someone else.
I don't have time to waste on you.
I can't even convince myself.
How am I supposed to convince Feifei?
How would she let you mess with my aunt?
That's your problem.
As for the favor,
I agreed to help.
In exchange,
leads on Guichen—
take it seriously.
You'd better really have what it takes.
Or face the consequences yourself.
Wu Ming, get out here right now!
You used my sister and ran off!
You owe me an explanation!
Sis.
What are you doing here?
What did you just mean by that?
What I just said was...
Wu Ming, he took my sis...
...ter friend!
Xiao Qi.
He took my dear sister Xiao Qi,
used her, and tried to bail!
Xiao Qi.
Didn't you tell me
that Wu Ming bullied you?
That he jabbed you with needles?
And today,
we came to demand an explanation, right?
Right.
That Wu Ming stabbed me with needles.
We came today to settle the score.
Right.
Wu Ming is just a...
scumbag,
a lecher,
shameless!
We came here to teach him a lesson.
Sis,
what are you doing here?
I came to get Auntie treated.
Auntie's condition is quite serious.
This Wu Ming,
can he actually cure her?
He said Auntie has to come in person.
Wu Ming,
let me tell you,
you'd better cure her.
If you dare pull any tricks,
I'll settle every score with you at once.
Sorry,
I can't cure her.
I'm just a depraved lecher
who only bullies little girls.
How could I know how to heal?
A grown man like you,
So petty.
A little lady like you,
how do you have such a Venomous tongue?
Sharper than a knife.
You hooligan, you pervert!
You called me little?
Me, little?
Where am I little?
What I have,
what I have is...
refined.
This is called fashionable.
Do you understand?
Don't act all mysterious with me.
Answer me.
Enough.
Don't worry about Auntie's matter.
Come home with me.
You just wait.
I'm not done with you.
Wu Ming,
the rumors in the medical hall,
you'd better deal with them at once.
Or I'll make you pay.
What a hassle.
Are you all right?
Odd Eyes.
Is this the medical hall?
Yes.
This is the Chinese Daoist Medical Hall.
Are you
here for your eyes?
Huizi,
help this lady inside.
Yes, sir.
Your eyes are beautiful.
Can you sense light?
Then,
do you know thermal imaging?
In our eyes,
living people appear red.
So in your eyes,
what color are we?
Black.
Strike now.
He's completely unguarded.
One blow will finish him.
Your eyes,
they can be cured.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Just a bit emotional.
They say my Heaven-Blindness is incurable.
Heaven-Blindness.
No medicine can cure it.
No method can heal it.
However...
do not be afraid.
To see this world,
one need not rely on the eyes.
I'll teach you to see with your heart,
perceive with your intent,
and feel all things.
You will see far more clearly
than those who use their eyes,
and far more deeply.
If Master says it cannot be cured,
then it cannot be cured.
How could I be shaken by the reckless words
of such a man as this?
He must die.