Legend has it
that ancient powerful cultivators
ascended as immortals in spirit
while their bodies became sacred
buried in the mortal world
undecayed for a thousand years
with hearts still beating
Ancestral Master
I'll borrow your body to practice again
I'll take your silence as consent
Here we go
Qihai, pierce one point seven inches deep
Guanyuan likewise probes the depths
Yaoyang, half an inch, no hesitation
Huantiao, slant in three inches
Mingmen, straight in eight-tenths
Yongquan, the sensation fills the sole
You scoundrel!
Defiling our Ancestral Master's body again!
Martial Uncle
Our Ancestral Master died a thousand years ago
She's just a corpse now
Besides, I'm practicing the Sunu Rejuvenation Acupuncture
And there are no women on this mountain
Hold your tongue!
Your cultivation has reached its peak
Your grandfather
sent you down to wipe out Guichen traitors
and to find your sister Ling'er
Guichen
Word of Guichen
places them in Mancheng of the Island Nation
Now go, quickly
Alright
Kunlun and Taibai, both half an inch
Withered wood meets spring, returning to the Void
You little wretch!
You dare keep needling?!
Bow
Bow again
Bow once more
Family repays the kindness
Wait
Second Uncle
What's your hurry?
My sister, Noda Tomoko
is the eldest legitimate daughter
and the primary heir
When it comes to repaying kindness,
a side-branch elder like you has no right
to overstep your bounds.
Bitch!
Since when does a junior get to dictate things here?
Noda Tomoko
Be smart about it
obediently sign and hand over the shares.
Wait
The Divine Doctor of Zhongnan Mountain is here.
Where is the patient, Noda Kinoshita?
We're here to save a life and make some money.
Where did this lowly peasant come from?
How dare you speak the family head's name!
Didn't you offer 100 million for his life?
You're too late
My grandfather has already passed away
He's dead?
Then how do we squeeze these foreigners for cash?
Grandfather!
The corpse is moving!
Don't go over there yet.
Sunken cheeks, vanished spirit
Hollow eyes, cracked lips
Cold breath, frozen spirit
But with me here, his time hasn't come.
He can be saved.
What did you do to my grandfather?
I told you
he's not completely dead yet.
He can be saved.
You can truly save my grandfather?
Noda Tomoko, have you lost your mind?
You actually believe this bastard?
Letting him touch the old master's remains
is the Noda family's greatest disgrace!
She's right, sister.
We can't just turn to anyone in desperation.
letting this fraud defile Grandpa's body!
Resurrection does not exist in this world!
Please answer me
I can save him.
If you can save my grandfather,
half the Noda family fortune
is yours to take
Noda Tomoko!
Don't you dare!
You traitor to the Noda family!
I will never allow this!
Whatever the consequences,
I, Noda Tomoko, will bear them alone.
I beg you to save my grandfather
Please.
Could Second Uncle have set this up
to stop my sister from taking over?
You all deserve to die!
Payment first, treatment later.
That's our rule
Fine.
But if you fail to save him
I'll make you regret ever being born.
Baihui opens the heavenly gate
Shenque steadies the central palace
Qi flows through gold needle into Danzhong
Guanyuan locks the fire of life
Zusanli draws the earthly qi
Yongquan connects to the netherworld
Laogong gathers spiritual light
Yintang marks the stars
How is it?
It's a bit tricky.
Is there anything else we can do?
We're missing a catalyst
The purest Yang heavenly thunder.
Within two hours, in this very place,
there will be a thunderstorm.
That's when Grandpa's soul will return.
Utterly absurd!
Sister
He's just fooling you with shaman nonsense.
Wake up!
You just checked the weather forecast?
It clearly says
there will be a thunderstorm in an hour.
Leave the money
and don't let me ever see you again.
Otherwise
The consultation fee I, Wu Ming, accept
is a debt owed to the King of Hell.
Whoever steals from the Noda family
must die!
Mystic forces of the Nine Heavens,
heed my command!
Resplendent heavenly might,
be drawn by this needle!
Why is this old man not responding at all?
We're done for, done for, done for!
Hello
A lead on Guichen has surfaced.
At the Huangji Clinic.
Got it.
Let's go.
Wait
Do you think the Noda family is a place
where lowly trash like you can come
and go as you please?
Kill them!
Ninjas, assemble!
Brother Ming
Where's the thunder?
You have to trust in science.
It was just a bluff.
You...!
What the hell?
Didn't the forecast say
the storm wouldn't hit for another hour?
Why did it start so early?
Oh my God!
I can't believe my eyes!
Grandfather!
Grandfather, you're alive!
Why is Grandfather unconscious?
He's like a vegetable.
Mobilize all the family's resources.
No matter the cost,
find that Chinese doctor from earlier.
Right now!
Please save my daughter!
Save my daughter!
I beg you, save my daughter!
I'm begging you!
Please, I beg you, save my daughter!
Your daughter's rotten leg
deserves to be amputated.
And her wretched life is worthless anyway.
No, no!
Save my daughter!
I'm begging you!
In my eyes,
your life isn't that noble either.
Have some decency.
Miss Su,
Lord Huangji is waiting for you upstairs.
Please go on up.
Don't let this trash dirty your eyes.
Save my daughter!
This is from my lady.
No, I don't want it!
I'm begging you!
My daughter's leg will rot if untreated!
Lord Huangji...
Do you deserve Lord Huangji's treatment?
They say he can raise the dead.
I'm begging you!
Even selling your whole family's bones
wouldn't cover a fraction of his fee.
Keep pestering us,
and I'll break your legs.
Throw her out!
No, no!
I'm begging you!
Foolish wretch.
You just don't know what's good for you.
Don't hit my mom!
This is too much!
I'm begging you!
Please, I beg you, save my daughter!
You have a death wish!
Such beautiful legs,
used for kicking people?
What a waste.
Where did this pest come from?
Causing trouble at the Huangji Clinic!
You!
It's just that your stockings
are of poor quality.
I'll make sure to
buy you a few more pairs later.
Guards!
Drag her out!
Stop!
Miss Keiko,
please give the Su family some face.
I'll handle this.
Very well.
Miss Su,
As for our rules,
I trust you're aware of them.
This card
has more than enough for the treatment.
May we begin now?
Miss Su, please describe your symptoms.
Remember, do not hide anything.
Any omission
is irresponsible to your own health.
Here with me,
there are no secrets.
I've been to every hospital for check-ups.
Everything is normal.
However,
every night at nine,
no matter where I am
or what I'm doing,
I faint without any warning.
And
I have the same dream.
A dream?
What kind of dream?
You may speak freely.
An erotic dream.
The exact same erotic dream, every night.