You're not following us, are you?
Pervert.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Little ladies.
It's fine if you don't drink.
I'll take you to a private room.
For drinks with a bit more kick.
Juice.
This juice...
Guaranteed to send you to heaven.
We don't drink.
And we don't want juice either.
We're leaving now.
Let's go.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm being nice, don't push your luck.
Damp heat in the liver meridian.
Gallbladder qi running rampant.
This hand of yours...
Has touched things it shouldn't have.
It deserves to be crippled.
I'm gonna kill you!
Handsome, you're amazing!
The legendary internal energy!
A true martial arts master!
Punk.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Do you know whose turf this is?
No matter whose turf, there are rules.
You lot are used to bullying everyone.
What?
Can't stand it when someone fights back?
Boys, get him!
I'll be taking my leave.
But... but...
He... he just saved us.
Are you stupid?
Let's go call the police.
Little lady.
Calling the cops on my turf...
Isn't that a bit disrespectful?
Don't you think?
Master Gao.
Gao Jin, God of Gamblers Family's 2nd son.
Keep it low-key.
Master Gao.
These guys were bullying my friend.
And they wanted us both to drink with them.
With me here,
the sky over Manchester
won't fall.
Punk.
Get down on your knees right now.
Crawl between my legs.
And kowtow three times.
Maybe if I'm in a good mood,
I'll spare your worthless life.
Hey, pretty lady.
What do you think?
Will he crawl?
He won't.
You're that sure?
Beat him to death!
Show no mercy!
Impressive.
What skills.
Tendon-splitting, bone-dislocating.
Striking pressure points from afar.
May I ask, sir,
which school you're from?
Would you allow me
to buy you a drink?
We walk different paths.
Handsome.
God of Gamblers Family's 2nd son Gao Jin!
Befriend him,
and you'll rise to glory in Manchester,
soaring straight to the top.
Let's go.
This place isn't right for you.
Stop right there.
What is it?
You beat up my men,
trashed my place,
and now you think you can just walk away?
Where does that leave my pride?
A crooked upper beam
makes a crooked lower beam.
You're really pushing it.
You...
Damn.
Quite the fighter, aren't you?
Are you faster than my gun?
Move one more inch,
and I'll blow your damn head off.
Gao Jin,
put the gun down.
Gambler's Code disputes end by the Code.
Drawing a gun breaks the rules.
Wouldn't that disgrace the Gao family?
Wang Qianqian.
You finally couldn't resist showing up.
What?
Did you
hire him to come trash my place?
You dare to arm-wrestle the Gao family?
With just you and that lousy casino?
You're giving me too much credit.
This gentleman,
I'd actually like to befriend.
Let me formally introduce myself.
Wang Qianqian.
Wu Ming.
You want to protect him?
I was present and witnessed everything.
The host abused his power against a guest,
and Wu Ming stepped in for justice.
If this story gets out,
It'll shame the God of Gamblers Family.
He
beat up my men,
and trashed my place.
If I don't deal with him,
how can I command respect?
Then by the Gambler's Code,
let one bet decide it all.
Bet.
I'll bet against him.
Gao Jin,
you're making things difficult for him.
What?
Don't dare?
Scared?
Why wouldn't I dare?
Just name the terms.
I won't make it hard on you.
The loser
just leaves a hand behind.
No.
Don't bet against him.
It's fine.
As you wish.
Rolling dice.
We compare the points.
One round decides it.
The lower roll wins.
And if it's a tie?
Then we keep rolling.
Fine.
After you, Mr. Wu.
But if you feel there's no hope,
kneel down now and beg for mercy.
Perhaps
I'll spare your life.
A miscalculation.
He inherited the God of Gamblers' legacy.
At rolling dice,
there's no way to beat him.
What are you standing there for?
Too scared to roll?
Wang Qianqian.
So this is the man you trust?
Rolling dice?
More like wagging his tail in your bed.
Will you do it yourself,
or shall I chop it off for you?
Boss Gao.
Boss Gao, I'm begging you.
Please, let him go.
This whole thing started because of me.
If you have to chop,
then chop off my hand instead.
You little bitch.
Shut your damn mouth.
Today his hand comes off,
and you won't get away either.
Gao Jin.
Show mercy when you can.
Name your terms.
I, Wang Qianqian, will protect his hand.
Terms? Now that's more like it.
By the Gambler's Code,
the winning side
can decide whether to hear out the loser.
Here's the deal.
First,
he kneels at my casino's entrance,
wearing a sign that says "I'm trash,"
for three full days and nights.
And second,
you, Wang Qianqian,
accompany me for three days and nights.
Serve me well enough,
and maybe I'll
pretend today never happened.
How about that?
Sister Qian, don't agree to it.
Fine.
I agree.
But Wu Ming will not kneel.
This kid...
You really do treat him special, huh?
Fine.
I'll allow it.
He doesn't have to kneel.
But you...
Open the cup. The game is set.
I haven't even opened the cup yet.
Aren't you celebrating a little too soon?
Did I hear that right?
What's inside that lousy cup of yours
is crystal clear.
Even a blind man could see it.
Twenty-one points.
You still think you can turn this around?
Did a donkey kick you in the head?
Exactly.
You're just a sore loser, a coward.
A wimp who only hides behind a woman.
Wu Ming.
Don't be reckless.
I've already negotiated terms with him...
This is my gamble.
It has nothing to do with you.
Alright.
Today I'll show you
what it means to turn the tables,
and what it means to be
a frog at the bottom of a well.