Showing off really gets you struck by lightning.
Why did I have to show off?
Rourou.
Dating her,
wouldn't that be nice?
Maybe I should go back.
But...
I'm single anyway.
I'll go back.
And have a proper relationship.
Sounds good.
Darling,
what are you two doing?
Is this the man who has you head over heels?
This guy?
That's right.
What's he got?
He's not as handsome as me.
Not as rich as me.
And he can't even dance like me.
You picked him over me?
Why?
You said I'm ugly,
I could take it.
You said I'm poor,
You said I can't dance,
uncles and grannies might take it.
But Master Fat can't take it!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you too!
You wanna fight?
Come on.
Let's have it out.
Fight my ass!
Don't do this.
Come on, fight me!
Bro!
Come on, hit me!
Bro,
let's talk this out, calm down.
Bro!
I'm gonna kill you!
Let's see who's tougher,
you or my gun.
Calm down!
Jack, are you insane?
Damn!
He's serious!
Now he's a dead man.
You'll have to choose me.
You lunatic!
Darling!
Is anyone there?
Anyone?
Help! Is anyone there?
Brother Qian!
Brother Qian, hang in there!
Brother Qian, you can't die!
Brother Qian!
Hold on!
When you shielded me just now,
weren't you afraid of dying?
I was.
But I'm more afraid of losing you.
Brother Qian, you can't die!
You're my only hope in this world.
Brother Qian,
how can I live without you?
Brother Qian, hang in there!
I'm begging you, Brother Qian!
Silly girl.
Brother Qian, Brother Qian!
Brother Qian, don't scare me!
Brother Qian, you can't die!
Go find Brother Ming.
Only Brother Ming can save me.
You can't die!
I'm begging you!
Wu Ming has made his move.
No matter what,
you must stall him for fifteen minutes.
The point of stalling him
is to keep him from saving anyone.
Wouldn't it be better to tear that fat man to pieces,
so there's no one to save.
Are you questioning my decision?
Yun'er wouldn't dare.
Yun'er knows her mistake.
Remember,
at least fifteen minutes.
As you command.
I must've run into a damn ghost.
This is a straight road,
how did I end up back here?
Driver.
This is my stop.
Take this money,
but don't open it.
This...
The fifteenth of August.
A time for family reunion.
On the road of no return,
unwilling to cross the river,
bitterly waiting for my lord.
He hurries here.
Now that my lord has come,
why not follow me
to the underworld?
Come out.
My lord,
we've prepared the song 'Crossing the River of Forgetfulness' for you.
Wishing my lord
an early ascension.
The five tones deafen the ear.
The five colors blind the eye.
Yama's Ten Ultimates: Incantation of Lust.
So that's it.
So much for the heir of Taoist Medicine.
He's nothing special.
Before the sea of lust and sin,
he turns into a puddle of mush.
Master went to such trouble to deal with him,
yet we took him down so easily.
Every man has desires.
He is now drowning in desire, unable to free himself.
Now, let's send him to the underworld.
You broke free from the prison of lust.
Since this technique was perfected,
no one has ever escaped it.
You're not a man.
Desire is the source of all sin.
You ignite others' desires,
making them slaves to sin.
You deserve to die.
Pupils fully dilated.
No spontaneous breathing.
No heartbeat.
No pulse.
Time of clinical death:
23:47.
You...
What are you saying?
What time of death?
Prepare the body.
Yes.
I won't let you touch him!
Ma'am, please calm down.
He's already dead.
What you're doing is pointless.
Please cooperate with us.
The person we're waiting for hasn't arrived.
He said his brother could save him.
None of you are touching him today.
He's already de—
I'm here.
Brother Wu Ming!
You're finally here.
What's the situation?
A foreigner shot him earlier.
Kunka,
take her to give a statement.
Come with me.
Let's go.
Examine the body.
What are you doing?
Who said you could touch the body?
Get your filthy hands off!
Step back immediately,
or I'll charge you with disturbing the scene
and desecrating a corpse.
He's not a corpse.
He can still be saved.
Still be saved?
Captain Meng,
this lunatic is causing trouble.
I'm going to cuff him and take him in.
Assaulting a police officer?
Put your hands up!
Put the gun down.
He's my friend.
He's here to assist with our case.
Captain Meng.
You just...
Put the gun down.
That's an order.
Don't let anyone disturb me.
Don't worry.
Captain Meng.
This is against the rules.
What is he doing?
Is this an autopsy or desecration?
Enough, not another word.
I'll take responsibility if anything happens.
What?
The bullet actually came out!
Can you please tell me...
how on earth did you do that?
Are you some kind of magician?
What's the principle behind it?
Take his shoes off.
Why should I...
Fine.
Let's see what kind of trick you're playing.
This is Wu Ming.
Within twenty minutes,
deliver seven bronze lamps to the Zhonghua Daoyi Hall.
Where'd he go?
Why are you still here?
He...
Where's the body?
How did the body disappear?
Your friend and the body are both gone.
Captain Meng.
Your friend is a bit strange.
I don't have any friends.
You've been on the job for years now.
Are you still this careless with your words?
Get that body back.