What just happened?
This... this...
Ms. Qian.
Am I seeing things?
Qianqian.
Open the cup for me.
Gao Jin.
One point.
Wu Ming.
Zero points.
Wu Ming wins.
By the Gambler's Code,
Gao Jin,
accept your loss.
Young Master Gao,
will you do it yourself,
or have someone do it for you?
Bullshit!
His life is worth more than your family's.
If you want to live,
get the hell out now!
So you're trying to weasel out?
Weasel your ass!
You have a death wish.
I, Gao Jin, can afford to lose.
And I can afford to bet my life too.
A mere hand
is not worth mentioning.
Gao Jin,
you don't have to do this.
You can come negotiate terms with me.
Your little scheme
won't work.
Young Master Gao,
the rule says,
leave behind one hand.
But it didn't say whose hand.
What I'm doing here
isn't unreasonable, right?
Let's go.
Move.
Get going!
Gao Jin.
Now let's talk
about the casino.
Wang Qianqian.
You think finding some
shady backer out of nowhere
can shake the Gao family?
To us,
he's nothing more than
a slightly stronger ant.
Today,
he humiliated the Gao family.
He's as good as dead.
As for you,
if you don't want to die with him,
stay away from him.
Otherwise,
Golden Hall
can prepare to shut its doors.
Never underestimate others' abilities.
Gao Jin,
whatever tricks you've got,
go ahead and use them.
I, Wang Qianqian,
will take them all on.
Young Master.
Useless.
Useless!
Wu Ming.
Do you need something?
Getting to know you
is my honor.
Chivalrous and righteous,
with a heroic spirit,
and divine skills.
An extraordinary man like you
is rare in this world.
To fight by your side
is my privilege.
Ms. Wang,
with your abilities,
you could've stopped those thugs yourself.
Yet you appeared
just when I seemed to need help.
That way,
once the Gao family and I were at odds,
you,
arriving as a savior to earn my trust.
You and the Gao family,
or rather,
its second young master, are in conflict.
The casino,
I've only been there once.
And you happen to follow the Gambler's Code.
You must be the head of Golden Hall then.
You want to use me against the Gao family.
Tonight's game
was also a test of my skills.
So may I assume
you orchestrated this whole situation?
I...
You don't need to admit it,
nor deny it.
If not for your courage at the end,
by risking yourself to save my hand...
know that anyone who schemes against me
never meets a good end.
Don't let it happen again.
Ms. Qian,
this man is terrifying.
Sharp-minded,
impervious to persuasion,
unmoved by carrot or stick.
Hard to handle.
You're wrong.
The stronger a person is,
the greater their weakness.
And his weakness
is precisely his greatest strength.
Defending the weak against the strong,
a chivalrous heart.
If I can grasp that,
then I can make him
work for me.
Don't go to places like that anymore.
It's not for you.
Today was the first time.
And it was my birthday.
I was a little curious.
Rourou insisted on dragging me there.
The world is dangerous.
People can't be trusted.
Don't put yourself in harm's way.
You'd be sold out and never know it.
I'll remember your advice.
My home is just nearby.
Well...
I'll be going then.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Wait.
Something else?
Today's my birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Can I add your contact info?
I promise.
I absolutely won't bother you.
Of course.
Let me add you.
Thank you, Wu Ming.
There.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Fatty isn't picking up again.
So fast.
What an eerie sword.
Form concealed in the wind,
breath hidden in the shadows.
Five Elements escape technique.
Like a phantom.
If I move rashly,
I'll surely take a thunderous strike.
Wu Ming!
Wait!
I have something for you.
Stay back!
Wu Ming!
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have turned back halfway.
It's all my fault.
It's not your fault.
It has nothing to do with you.
They've been waiting here for me a long time.
I'm sorry.
I know you're an extraordinary master.
Your world is full of danger.
And I'm just...
an utterly ordinary girl.
Being friends with you
might become a burden to you.
Wu Ming.
I'm sorry.
It was nice meeting you.
Take good care of yourself.
Wait.
Didn't you have something to give me?
It's just a very ordinary thing.
I made it myself.
This is the most precious gift
I've ever received.
Really?
Do you like it then?
Well, it's like this...
How should I put it...
The knitting is...
But I'll keep it with me always.
Do you mean what you say?
Of course.
A promise is a promise.
It's getting late.
Going back to school alone is risky.
Let me walk you.
Okay.
Then I'll walk in front.
And lead the way.
Okay.
Ling'er.
If she were still here,
she'd be about her age.
She'd be skipping around like this too.
Since Grandma passed,
I haven't felt this at peace.
Like the whole world is gently protecting me.
This moment...
if it could last forever,
how wonderful that would be.