Sweetie, are you alright?
I'm fine.
We're done seeking treatment.
Mom.
What are you doing?
You're so badly hurt!
Stop fooling around here.
Who's fooling around?
My buddy here is a Miracle Doctor.
He's treating the girl's leg.
Miracle Doctor, my foot.
He's obviously a fraud.
Don't let him fool you.
How can a Miracle Doctor be this young?
He's not even a professional con artist.
The girl has a Congenital disability.
Even gods couldn't cure it.
If you keep bullying these poor people,
and the Su Family won't let it slide.
The Su Family?
The biggest Chinese family in Manchester.
The face of the Su Family
is quite a looker.
You!
But that mouth of yours
is as explosive as gunpowder.
Such a fine body, all wasted.
Pervert!
Congenital bone spurs.
Ghost Foot.
Let go of my daughter!
Mom.
Mom!
Bastard!
Let go!
Hey, beautiful.
You frogs in a well,
just wait and witness a miracle.
What's happening?
My body won't obey me at all.
I can't muster any strength.
Yin-Yang Disorder.
Bone Affliction, Tangled Tendons.
Qi Stagnation and Blood Stasis.
Life force severed.
Now, with Bone-Setting,
I shall set things right.
You're just playing tricks.
Let's see what tricks you've got.
Qi flows.
Stop!
Blood circulates.
Affliction dispelled.
You damned monster!
What did you do to my daughter?
I'll kill you!
Every hospital,
every temple,
every master,
we've sought them all.
None could help.
I heard Miracle Doctor Huangji
once cured a similar rare condition.
I beg you, save her.
Illnesses are myriad,
each unique to the person.
Miss Su,
come.
Allow me to give you
a thorough examination.
Miss Su,
your pulse shows no abnormality.
The root of the problem
lies in those bone-deep erotic dreams.
No need for the consultation fee.
Cherish your time with your daughter.
You, stop right there!
You can't leave!
You murderer!
I'll kill you!
Mom.
This...
Mom...
Impossible.
This is absolutely impossible.
It must be some illusion.
It must be sorcery, a trick!
This...
Your legs...
I told you you were frogs in a well,
but you wouldn't believe me.
This is a miracle.
We are the miracle.
Master Huangji declared it incurable.
Now he's been proven wrong.
This severely damages our society's reputation.
I absolutely will not tolerate
anything that harms our society's name.
Miracle Doctor!
A living Bodhisattva!
Mom!
Thank you.
Thank you for saving my daughter.
Please, get up.
The Congenital Ghost Foot can be reversed,
but a lone star's fate is hard to defy.
After you return,
shut all doors and windows tight.
Never go outside after sunset.
There are things
that should be told sooner rather than later.
This...
You saved my daughter,
and I'm truly grateful.
But...
why are you cursing us?
The moment she was born crying,
did her father die a gruesome death,
with no remains left behind?
Mom!
You're lying!
Dad just went somewhere far, far away
to work.
He just hasn't come back yet.
You're a liar!
Mom, let's go.
Thank you for saving my daughter.
Let's go, Fatty.
Stop right there!
In this world,
no medical skill
can ever surpass Lord Huangji's.
Wipe them out.
No matter the cost.
Miss Su,
let me see
the deepest desires
in your heart.
Truly an exquisite beauty.
From now on,
you'll be mine.
Get up.
It's you!
Tian...
Mr. Tianyi!
Who do you think you are,
daring to touch what's mine?
A bunch of useless trash!
Today,
none of you will leave alive.
Master!
Lord Huangji!
It's you.
You deserve to die!
I insulted you so harshly,
why did you still save me?
Whether a life is worthless or precious,
is not for others to define.
Every life is worth cherishing.
You all deserve to die!
Calamity-Crossing Golden Needle!
You're from the Wu Family.
Blood debts must be paid in blood.
Then let me see, youngster,
just what you're really made of.
Mountain, Medicine, Destiny, Divination, Physiognomy.
How many do you know?
All five arts are vast and all-encompassing,
profound and immense.
Countless brilliant prodigies
spend a lifetime barely grasping one art.
Why not follow me?
I can grant you boundless power,
and heights beyond your ancestors' reach.
Open up your mind,
accept me,
and become
a part of me.
I forgot to tell you,
I mastered all five disciplines long ago.