Worthless trash.
Unworthy to be my enemy.
First, I'll smash this eyesore of a sign.
Smash my sign?
You think you're worthy?
Acting tough with such pathetic tricks?
Where did this insolent brat come from?
You really don't know your place.
Tell your hall master to come out and die.
I am Wu Ming.
Master of the Chinese Daoist Medical Hall.
Your complexion is dark,
consumed by violent energy.
I fear a bloody calamity awaits you.
Sir.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Break your own arms,
and perhaps
I'll spare your miserable life.
As for my people,
no one touches them.
Tell me,
how should we deal with him?
It's entirely up to you, sir.
You reckless fool.
Courting death!
Bastard!
Idiot!
My blade is tempered with the Ebola virus
mixed with deadly black mamba venom.
It kills instantly upon drawing blood.
Even if it just touches your skin,
you will certainly die.
Even the gods couldn't save you.
Your brow is ashen,
your cheeks are sharp as blades.
These are the signs of a violent, sudden death.
And it's about to come true.
The Yellow Emperor's Inner Classic states:
Sinews are rigid,
bones are walls,
flesh is energy,
skin is stiff.
With such thunderous strikes,
from now on,
let's see who dares mock the Chinese Daoist Medical Hall.
You have lost all medical ethics.
You are unfit to practice medicine.
Today, you'll taste the agony of torn sinews and dislocated bones.
This is the true orthodox path of medicine.
Sir.
The Ebola virus is highly toxic.
Are you all right?
I am already immune to all poisons.
When it comes to medicine and poisons,
Huaxia is the true originator.
A mere barbaric poison
is not worth mentioning.
Lord Wu Ming!
We're doomed! We're doomed!
The First Princess came in person.
She's here to condemn us.
Sir just established his dominance...
No.
I must defend him with my life.
First Princess Tomoko.
What happened today
was all because Sato and his men provoked us first.
Sir was forced to defend himself.
Please investigate this fairly,
and show mercy.
It's over.
She didn't even look at me.
This time, Sir might be...
I, Noda Tomoko, implore the Honored Divine Doctor
to use your masterful skills
to save my grandfather, Noda Kinoshita's life.
The Noda family
is willing to give everything we have
to repay your great kindness.
Please!
Repay my kindness?
Is the Noda family's way of repaying kindness
sending ninjas to kill me?
Sister!
The assassin ninjas
were sent by Noda Kumaji.
Honored Divine Doctor.
The Noda family
will surely give you a satisfactory explanation.
Since my sister thinks so highly of him,
I will make a fool of him in public
and expose his true colors.
Honored Divine Doctor.
It is indeed our lack of strict discipline
that gave you a scare.
As long as it quells your anger,
I, Medaiko, am willing to accept any punishment.
I am naturally alluring.
I was trained by an Eastern Island master since childhood.
My charm technique has long been perfected.
In this world,
no man has ever escaped my grasp.
Oh?
Interesting.
Then do as you please.
Thank you for your mercy, Honored Divine Doctor.
How could you torment
such a delicate woman like her?
You don't know how to treat a lady.
Get up, quickly.
The ground is cold.
Come.
What's going on here?
He seems completely unaffected.
Impossible.
I don't believe it.
Honored Divine Doctor.
Medaiko truly knows she was wrong.
You...
will forgive me, won't you?
Of course he will.
I'll make this call.
Such tender, delicate skin,
all beaten red.
Your Lord Fatty's heart
aches just looking at it.
Let me help you inside to apply some ointment.
Come on, let's go.
Honored Divine Doctor,
as long as you cure my grandfather,
name any condition.
Wealth, power,
rare treasures,
even...
including myself.
First Princess, you...
Only by saving Grandfather
do I have a sliver of hope.
Second Uncle isn't as foolish as he seems.
He's a viper hiding in the shadows.
Wu Ming,
you are my last lifeline.
The Noda family is a titan of Mancheng.
Have you ever dealt with Ghost Dust?
Ghost Dust?
Who is this person?
Tomoko has never heard of him.
Cautious indeed.
Even the name is fake.
This traitor has hidden himself well.
Then within the past decade in Mancheng,
has any extraordinary genius emerged?
Yes.
Master Tianyi.
He is a legendary figure.
He appeared out of nowhere ten years ago,
mastering extraordinary arts
beyond mortal comprehension.
The five great families of Mancheng pale before him.
Tomoko once
only glimpsed his glory from afar.
Master Tianyi
is Ghost Dust.
Where is he now?
Such secrets
have long been buried.
Aside from the innermost core of the great families,
no one knows his whereabouts.
Perhaps...
Perhaps my grandfather had contact with him.
He should know.
You're quite clever.
Among Mancheng's great families,
I don't have to rely solely on the Noda family.
Honored Divine Doctor,
Tomoko's filial devotion is utterly sincere,
for heaven and earth to witness.
I beg you, for the sake of Tomoko's resolve
to offer everything to save Grandfather,
please save him.
Noda Tomoko hereby swears,
as long as you help,
regardless of the outcome,
the three things I promised you
I will never go back on.
The Noda family and I
will forever remember your great kindness.
Hey gorgeous,
Your skin
is just like mutton-fat jade
crystal clear and translucent.
Hey, handsome
That Brother Ming of yours,
what's his background?
I'm so curious
Brother Ming?
To your Lord Fatty,
he's a god
An almighty god
Devouring heaven and earth,
Raising the dead
It's all child's play to him
Then does he have any weaknesses?
Come on, tell me
Weaknesses?
Yes, yes, yes
On both sides of his ribcage,
there are two bones
Their scientific name is floating ribs
That spot is the most fragile
If struck hard enough,
one strike can be fatal
Bastard
Is this damn fatso messing with me,
or is he just a complete idiot?
Handsome
I'm not asking about physical weaknesses
I mean,
is there anything he fears,
or someone he cares about?
Something he fears?
Let me think
Fatso
If you don't apply the medicine to her wound soon,
it'll already be healed
Oh no
When did he get here?
Has this fatso been playing dumb all along
just to take advantage of me?
He's no good
You're not a good person either
How am I not a good person?
I'm just helping apply your medicine
You really
turn on a dime.
Brother Ming
Why has my talisman turned black?
The evil art of seduction.
Interesting
Honored Divine Doctor,
can you come back with me now?
Your brow has changed three times
A gray pall covers her head like a mourning veil,
This is a sign of a close kin's passing
Noda Kinoshita is already dead
And look at her cheeks and lips,
A faint black-blue aura emerges
Calamity is right before her
Going to the Noda family now
is a den of dragons and tigers for her
Lord Wu Ming,
what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell somewhere?
Your grandfather
is already dead
You
What do you mean?
My grandfather's vital signs report this morning
is still in my assistant's hands
How dare you curse him like that?
The Noda house has become a place of doom
Going there is pointless
No
Impossible
Nothing could have happened to my grandfather
Honored sir,
no matter what you've seen,
or what you've foreseen,
I beg you
Come back with me
If alive, I must see him
If dead, I must see his body
The mountain root is severed
Her life star has fallen
This needle stirs up a sliver of life for you
Whether you can survive this calamity
depends on your fate
Noda Kumaji
Who gave you the nerve to sit in the head's seat?
Get down from there!
The head's seat,
naturally, only the head may sit in it.
And now,
I am the head of the family.
Grandfather...
You...
What did you do to Grandfather?
Oh, the old man, you mean?
Such a tragedy.
For reasons unknown,
he somehow lost his footing
at the Viewing Pavilion and fell to his death.
But rest assured, dear niece.
All those negligent fools
who failed in their duties,
I've sent them all down to accompany the old man.
From now on,
the Noda Family is under my command.
Your authority,
I hereby revoke.
A useless wretch like you, who only drinks and gambles,
wants to be head of the family?
In your dreams!
Slay the traitors!
Heavenly Fragrance Sword Saint,
Noda Tomoko,
Noda Medaiko.
I've long wanted to have a taste
of you twin sister blossoms.
Either kneel and submit,
or die.
Grandfather is dead.
This family,
ruled by a viper like you and these jackals,
has long since rotted away,
clinging to its last breath.
I, Noda Tomoko, would rather die standing.
My only regret
is that I cannot tear you to pieces with my own hands!
Very well.
Then I shall grant your wish.
Lord Sword Saint,
slaughter these beasts!