This girl
After just a few days with Brother Ming,
she's already got such presence.
Brother Ming must have taught her
some extraordinary techniques.
Tingting!
Uncle Pang!
Uncle Pang brought you blueberry cake.
Thank you, Uncle Pang.
How is it?
Is it tasty?
It's delicious.
Super delicious!
Tingting,
when it comes to cultivation,
balance is key.
Your master making you practice here every day,
that's not scientific.
If you ask me,
cultivation must balance work and rest.
Look at your master lately,
hanging around all those pretty girls,
making eyes at them,
no time to oversee your training.
Only Uncle Pang thinks of you.
Uncle Pang makes a good point.
Master has been slacking off lately.
Right?
I'll give him a talking-to later.
Honestly.
By the way,
the techniques you've been practicing,
the Incantation,
and the movements,
show them all to Uncle Pang in detail.
That way,
Uncle Pang can help you
take a careful look,
study them thoroughly,
spot any flaws for you,
and boost your skills significantly.
Uncle Pang,
you're not trying to steal them, are you?
You're even worse than my Master.
Master said you know nothing,
and tell no one the Cultivation Technique,
especially you.
He knew you'd try something sneaky.
I'm going to tell Master right now.
She's really got potential.
Uncle Pang was just testing you.
Tingting,
you passed my test.
Of course I did.
But still,
just wait till Master deals with you.
You little brat!
What a clever one!
Look at her run!
What do you want?
I'm warning you,
I belong to the Second Young Master.
A cheap whore like you
dares mention the Second Young Master?
His women are all
high-born and precious.
You
aren't even fit to tie his shoes.
I...
I'm a virgin.
A virgin.
A virgin!
The Second Young Master said he'd take me anytime.
If you touch a single hair of mine,
he'll chop you up and feed you to the dogs!
Oh, I'm so scared!
Besides, look at the state of you,
two cripples.
In the Second Young Master's eyes,
which matters more: me, this gift,
or you bunch of useless trash?
Take a good look in the mirror.
You think you can act wild here?
You dare threaten my brother?
Believe me, I'll kill you right now,
toss you in a stinking ditch,
and feed you to the rats.
Hold on.
The Second Young Master is a lecher.
Maybe he really does fancy this one.
If she really becomes his woman,
we can't afford to offend her.
Otherwise,
we'll end up dead without a grave.
Brother, don't listen to her crap.
The Second Young Master has many beauties,
why would he want this bitch?
Enough.
You get
that girl named Jingjing
to come out.
As long as you lure her out,
then what happened tonight
we'll pretend it never happened.
You'll still be
the Second Young Master's
gift.
I just met Jingjing by chance at the bar.
We didn't even exchange numbers.
Don't push your luck, bitch!
Hold her down!
Let's sober her up!
Let go of me!
Rourou!
Jingjing!
Jingjing, run!
Don't worry about me!
Just run!
Run!
Go!
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Let her go!
Is it money you want?
If you want money, come at me!
If it's money you want, come at me!
You animals!
Money?
What I want most right now
is revenge.
The condition is simple.
Cripple her.
Make sure she never stands again,
can never hold anything,
becomes a useless wreck no one can fix.
No!
But before we cripple her,
I'll let her experience
what they call
a gang bang.
You beast!
What are you doing?
Animals!
No!
You beasts, no!
Jingjing!
Let her go!
Let go! Let go of me!
Damn bitch!
Jingjing!
Get up!
Quite the party, gentlemen.
In broad day-
On this dark and windy night,
out here in the wilderness,
putting on a live porn show.
You're worse than animals.
Tired of living?
If you don't wanna die, get out of here!
Or I'll kill you.
Hold on now.
I was just passing by,
just taking a look.
You guys carry on.
I'll just go ahead
and capture your heroic bearing
on camera,
to share with all the netizens.
Go to hell!
Bro!
Scared me to death!
Bro.
Who the hell are you?
From the Family of the God of Gamblers,
the Gao Family is on the job!
Hear my name,
and you'll jump in fright.
I am your long-lost,
dashing and elegant,
fresh as an autumn breeze,
justice-dispensing Master Pang,
Wu Pang himself!
You came looking for us, didn't you?
We don't even know you.
And we never crossed you, right?
Evil and justice
have always been mortal enemies.
Today,
your Master Pang
is gonna draw his mighty blade!
I don't care who you are.
Brothers,
kill him!
Wait a sec.
Jingjing!
Jingjing, are you okay?
Today, I'll teach you
what ganging up really means.
It's a misunderstanding, bro.
A misunderstanding!
Bro, you've got it wrong.
You're truly despicable.
Throwing your best friend to the wolves.
They were the ones who stole my phone.
That wasn't what I intended.
Not what you intended?
Look at how you're dressed.
Do you look like a decent person?
All you see is money.
There's nothing you wouldn't do.
You'd even sell out your friend for profit.
No.
It's not like that.
Rourou isn't that kind of person.
You're still defending her?
If you hadn't been smart today
and called Brother Ming beforehand,
do you know what would've happened to you?
You'd have been violated by these animals,
then dumped in some filthy ditch,
your body left on the streets tomorrow.
That's the best friend you keep defending,
and that's the result she brings you.
Open your eyes and see.
For money, she
would do absolutely anything.
That's right.
I did it for the money.
For money, I'd do anything.
Because I just need money.
I need money.
I need a lot of money.
I need so much money.
Is it also because of your
gravely ill mother,
gambling father,
disabled little brother,
and your broken family?
You think it's funny?
Sounds like a sob story, right?
But this is my fate.
This is the truth.
Jingjing.
You didn't tell me you were sick
because you didn't want me to worry.
I didn't tell you about my family
because I didn't want you all
to look down on me.
Today, I'll show you all
what my fate really is.
Come with me.
Fine, let's go.
Let's see what her fate is.
Let's go.
My mom
has late-stage uremia.
The doctor says without a kidney donor,
she won't survive another month.
Our landlady is a kind woman.
She hasn't charged us rent for months.
But her son is also sick now,
and she really needs money.
We can't keep skipping rent.
That gambling addict father of mine,
no idea if he's dead or alive,
nowhere to be found.
Our family used to be quite wealthy,
but he gambled it all away.
I'm just a college girl.
What can I possibly do?
My life isn't like yours.
There isn't a shred of hope,
just an abyss with no light in sight.
Sometimes,
I really want to just go with my mom.
Rourou.
You should've told us sooner.
We'll figure something out together.
Even I have no way out.
What could you possibly do?
You've already seen my true colors,
and you know what kind of person I am.
You can leave now.
You look like a rich guy too.
How about I sell myself to you?
Do you want me?
What are you saying?
People can't be bought or sold.
Rich people like you
probably look down on me anyway.
How ironic.
My greatest asset is my virginity.
I kept trying to find a rich man to save me,
but kept putting myself in danger.
I tried my hardest to protect myself,
yet ended up covered in scars.
I'm so tired.
After she passes away,
I'll have nothing left to live for.
You're being way too pessimistic.
This world
does have light in it.
Even on this pitch-black night,
it can still shine bright.
Look.
Isn't this bright?
You think this is amusing?
You think this is funny, huh?
You'll never understand how I feel.
Let alone empathize with me.
Just leave.
This topic is too heavy.
I was just kidding.
Three million.
Is that enough for the treatment?
What do you mean?
It's for you, of course.
Just tell me, is it enough?
It's enough.
But I'm not worth three million.
You can't be compared to three million.
Every kind, devoted girl in this world
is priceless.
Of course,
this isn't a gift,
nor is it charity.
It's a loan.
As for the repayment date,
indefinite.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Money, to me,
is just a number.
You...
What are you doing?
But I don't know how to repay you.
You can ask anything of me.
There is one request.
Whatever you ask,
I'll do it.
I want you.