Open it, open it!
Holy crap!
No way!
It's really a triple!
How is this even possible?
It's actually a triple!
Triple!
That's 150 times the payout!
Let's go.
Oh my god!
Big bro!
You're absolutely amazing!
Your luck is insane!
Oh my god!
I'm so happy!
I'm rich!
This is nothing to me, peanuts.
But you got one thing wrong.
There's a whole pile over there too.
W-Why should I?
I-I only made you crawl twice.
Fine, I'll crawl under four times.
But my chips,
I can't give them to you.
And now he's running off!
Can't take losing, huh?
This guy's a cheat!
Is the casino gonna do something or not?
Sir,
this is your own private matter.
Settle it yourselves.
As for the chips you won...
Ugh, forget it.
Just let him go.
Don't hold up my winning streak.
Alright.
Get out of here.
Brother Ming!
There's still a whole pile left!
It's getting late.
Let's go, let's go.
Time to head home.
Don't go, handsome!
How about we grab a couple drinks later?
I'll pass on the drinks,
but...
they're on me.
This round's gonna take off!
Cash it all in.
Won this much in just a few minutes!
This is for you.
Alright.
So generous!
Brother Ming.
Handsome.
Your car keys.
For me?
For you to ride.
Oh, stop it.
Can't you be serious?
Let's go.
Ride safe!
We're rich!
Brother Ming.
In a bit,
let's go buy a 200K car.
No,
make it 300K.
We'll park it at their doorstep tomorrow.
Blind those snobby bastards.
With the rest of the money,
let's blow it all on luxury goods.
Buy another
Rolex.
Slam it right down on their table.
Tell me,
would he approve my marriage to Pinru?
Piling up material things
to buy sincerity
is just building a tower on sand.
One gust, and it collapses.
Get it?
I get it.
Of course I get it.
Brother Ming, you're a priceless treasure.
Anchored at the center,
unmoving as a mountain.
Everything in the world
is just fleeting clouds to you.
Am I right?
Mr. Wu.
My beautiful but reckless little fan,
calm down.
Whatever your issue is,
come at me.
Master Fatty will handle it.
Don't disturb my priceless treasure.
Damn it.
Mr. Wu,
Madam Su is in critical condition.
Only you can save her.
Please,
save her.
You want me to heal her,
so she can keep bossing people around
and even threatening me?
Do I look like I'm that free,
or like some bleeding heart?
Right, Brother Ming.
Saving that ice queen only brings trouble.
How about we just—
Shut up.
Mr. Wu,
Madam Su had a misunderstanding with you,
but as long as you're willing to help,
the misunderstanding will surely be cleared up.
And the Su family
is not ungrateful.
As for the fee,
name your price.
Young lady,
you're holding me morally hostage.
If kind words won't work,
then Xiao Qi will have to offend you.
Today,
even if I have to tie you up,
I'll drag you to the Su residence.
Sister Feifei,
you're finally here.
My sister,
my sister fainted again.
I heard Grandpa Su found a miracle healer from Zhongnan Mountain.
Where is he?
Don't even mention him.
Miracle healer my foot.
He's just a fraud.
I exposed him on the spot.
A fraud?
Sister Feifei,
tomorrow we've invited a giant of Chinese medicine,
Professor Sun Siqi,
to personally treat my sister.
He's highly respected and virtuous,
with miraculous medical skills.
When he comes,
have him examine Auntie too.
I've heard of Professor Sun's reputation.
Let's hope for a miracle.
Let's go see your sister first.
Come on.
Cultivated inside and out
Solid foundation
What a pity
Do you yield?
Never!
Bring it on
Do you yield now?
Oh, right
If you want Mr. Wu to come
I'll teach you a seven-word mantra
What mantra?
Mr. Wu responds to softness
Not to force
I didn't do anything to you
What are you crying for?
Okay, okay, stop crying
Pick me up tomorrow morning
With acting like yours
The Oscars
owe you a golden statue
About what happened today
If you breathe a word to Mr. Wu
I'll make you wish you were dead
No, no, no
Beautiful
We have to be reasonable, right?
Saving a life is a great virtue
Brother Ming has a kind heart
And I, Master Fatty,
also care about all living beings
Kind-hearted folks like us
don't talk about money
only about fate
And this fate,
three thousand three hundred eighty yuan
Just a token gesture
I...
Guess we have no fate with her
Mr. Wu, please wait here a moment
I'll go inside and check things out
Professor Sun seems to have arrived
Wait for my word before entering
To avoid any complications
Alright
This is insanely luxurious
Brother Ming
This is what we're working toward
Once we cure that ice queen
We'll squeeze her for a fortune
And get ourselves a place like this
Upgrade our quality of life
Enjoy life at its peak
Control the comments
Highlight Sister Fei's devotion and helplessness
Contact those influencers
Send me the drafts for approval
Amy
Be sure to record the treatment
If Professor Sun can truly work miracles
we must save my mother at any cost
Understood, Sister Fei
Jiang Feifei!
It's really you!
I finally get to see you!
You're my goddess!
Sis Feifei, get in the car first.
I... I finally see you in the flesh!
I can cure your mother's illness.
Miracle doctor from Mount Zhongnan.
Hear me out, come on.
Give me a chance.
Jiang Feifei!
Brother Ming from Mount Zhongnan!
Hey!
He's really amazing.
Just hear us out.
Hey!
So cold!
She didn't even glance at me.
That keep-your-distance vibe...
I love it so much!
You paparazzi just don't quit, do you?
You even tracked us to this hidden place.
You really get in everywhere.
It's really her in person!
Security!
What are you standing around for?
Hurry up!
Get these two troublemakers out of here!
If I see them again,
you're all fired.
You hear me?
Get the hell out, now!
Take a good look in the mirror.
What a sorry sight.
A toad lusting after a swan.
Keep staring,
and I'll gouge your eyes out.
You guard dogs of the rich,
sure bark loud, huh?
Do you know who I am?
I'm a miracle doctor from Mount Zhongnan!
Yours truly, Master Fatty!
The last guy who claimed to be from Mount Zhongnan,
had his legs broken.
If you don't leave now,
I'll make you two crawl out of here today.
Stop!
Sis Qi!
Xiao Qi.
You're finally here.
These two,
they want to break my legs.
And tell us to get lost.
Fine, we'll get lost.
Mr. Wu is an honored guest of the Su family.
Is this how you treat our guests?
Apologize!
We're sorry, Mr. Wu.
We failed to recognize someone so important.
Please forgive us.
Forget it.
Why should wage slaves torment each other?
Am I right?
Mr. Wu.
Please wait in the living room for a moment.
The expert the Second Miss invited is treating the Eldest Miss.