But I don't know how to repay you.
You can ask anything of me.
I do have a request.
You name it, I'll do it.
I want you...
I want you, from this day on,
to live a bright and joyful life.
Wu Ming!
She's been shot!
Please, save her!
Right in the heart, a fatal spot.
Wang Qianqian, have you lost your mind?
Bringing someone who's as good as dead.
To ruin the Taoist Medical Clinic's name?
If I'd taken her anywhere else,
she'd have died on the spot.
Only if Wu Ming saves her
is there a sliver of hope.
A life matters more than anything.
But...
you've practically delivered us a corpse.
Sir, she simply cannot be saved.
Look,
even ordinary people know
a gunshot to the heart is fatal.
Is he being stupid?
This will damage his reputation.
He isn't being stupid.
This is exactly what sets him apart.
I hope he can work a miracle,
a miracle for the Noda Family too.
Oh no!
Her heartbeat has stopped!
She's dying!
I'm sorry, Wu Ming.
Perhaps...
I shouldn't have brought her here.
You owe me an explanation!
Yes!
There's a heartbeat!
Her heart is beating again!
Impossible.
This...
How is this possible?
Tiantu steadies soul, quells spasms.
Wounds reverse, returning to the void.
Five organs' qi expels the object.
Golden Needle Salvation locks the armor.
Telekinesis, perfect and true.
The bullet came out, just like that.
This... how is this possible?
The heart rate is dropping.
Sir!
It's not working!
The wound is hemorrhaging.
The heartbeat has stopped.
Completely stopped.
Blood pressure is at zero.
Sis!
Shenque uses qi to open the Life Gate.
Five organs return to their place.
Six bowels regain their yang.
Eight-Gate Golden Lock Dunjia Formation.
Close the formation!
Her heart is beating!
It's beating!
Blood pressure is rising.
She's alive!
Sir!
That's wonderful!
She came back to life!
Sir.
Miracle healer.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving my sister.
No need to thank me.
It is my duty.
Thank you.
Huizi.
Keep a close eye on the patient.
If anything comes up, call me directly.
Yes, sir.
Wait a moment.
Sis,
I brewed you a Heaven-and-Earth Soup.
Made with the finest spirit herbs.
Best for restoring vital essence.
Have some.
Okay.
Wang Qianqian,
not you too.
I can do it myself.
No.
You drained your energy saving her.
You're weak right now.
I have to take care of you.
Open up.
I really can do it myself.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Quick, quick, quick!
Let me wipe it.
Hold still.
Where do you think you're wiping?
I'm wiping it for you!
What if you get burned?
Aren't you a peerless master?
Why are you blushing like a little boy?
Wu Ming.
You bastard!
Pressure points?
You actually used pressure points on me?
Are you even a man?
Don't you have any decency?
Wang Qianqian.
About today,
if you don't give a proper explanation,
the consequences will be severe.
Huihui is my cousin.
Her husband is a hopeless gambler.
He owes the Gao family a huge debt.
Then thugs came to collect the debt.
A fight broke out,
and Huihui got shot.
I've looked into you before.
Your medical skills are unfathomable.
My instincts told me
that if anyone could work a miracle
and pull her back from death's door,
that person
had to be you.
And as it turned out,
I won the bet.
Thank you.
Gambling
is an abyss of human desire.
Its poison rivals that of vipers.
It will drag people into endless hell.
Wang Qianqian.
Are you still going to run your casino?
If I don't, someone else will.
Everything exists for a reason.
But there must be rules and order.
It can't be allowed to become a cancer.
The Gao family ignores all rules,
treating human life like dirt,
destroying countless families.
What I want to do
is replace the Gao family
and purge this industry of its cancer.
So,
I want your help.
As long as gambling exists,
the cancer will keep regenerating.
Today you replace the Gao family,
tomorrow you become the new cancer.
Hearts change easily.
Desire is never sated.
The heavenly cycle turns.
No one can escape it.
I can guarantee it.
A cancer wasn't always a cancer.
It's desire that breeds it,
and indulgence that makes it grow.
This is the evil of human nature,
which no vow can bind.
All things in this world
have both benefits and drawbacks.
Among physicians,
there are masters who heal the world,
and quacks who kill for money.
Among casino owners,
some, like me, build order from the mire,
doing their best to save people.
Besides, with you around,
under your supervision,
I, Wang Qianqian, would never dare
to act recklessly.
Every venue of mine will follow rules.
A physician saves one,
ten, or a hundred people.
But managing casinos and gamblers
saves thousands of families.
Isn't that a form of salvation too?
Fine.
Then by your underworld's rules,
let's make a bet.
If I could beat you,
why would I need your help?
If you beat me,
it means your fate isn't sealed here.
Then I will help you.
As for what we bet on, you decide.
Alright.
Then let's bet on
whether I'm wearing underwear.
She's so calculating.
What kind of bet is that?
What?
You just said I get to set the terms.
Going back on your word already?
Fine, fine, I'll bet.
I bet you are.
Turn around and take a good look.
But
no taking it back, okay?
If I'm wearing it, I'm wearing it.
If I'm not, I'm not.
No backing out.
No need to bet.
You win.
If everyone bet like you,
nobody would play.
I know what I'm doing.
But
I accept my loss.
Gao family experts will attack in 2 days.
I'll be waiting for you
to turn the tide.
Treating a lady so rudely
is very impolite.
Not gentlemanly at all.
If you do something this outrageous again,
I'll paralyze you too.
Are you even a man?
Or rather,
are you simply
not interested in women at all?
At least,
I'm not the kind of man you imagine.
And I am interested in women.
I'm just not interested in you.
You...
You're so hurtful.
Some things
are better said clearly.
Do you want to know
if Wang Qianqian wore underwear?
I saw it crystal clear just now.
So she was wearing it, right?
I'm not telling you.
What the heck?
Weirdo.