Please wait in the living room for a moment.
The expert Second Miss invited is treating Eldest Miss.
An expert?
You already hired an expert,
so why call us here?
We're not putting up with this crap.
I...
We're leaving.
No, wait.
Mr. Wu,
I trust you one hundred percent,
but the one inside...
It's fine.
As long as someone can save her,
it doesn't matter who it is.
Let's go.
Alright.
This way, please.
The pulse is slippery
and rolling, like beads on a plate.
This is
what the Classic of Difficulties calls
Shrimp-Swimming and Sparrow-Pecking Pulse.
What's worse,
The forehead is dark,
like the sun hidden by clouds.
The light in their eyes is fading,
like a candle in the wind.
Evil energy now occupies the Pericardium,
causing the Three Huns and Seven Pos to drift.
She's on the brink of death.
Professor Sun,
then can my sister
still be saved?
This condition is extremely dire.
Nine out of ten doctors would be helpless.
However,
perhaps only I can defy the heavens
and snatch her from the King of Hell's grasp.
Professor Sun, really?
As long as you can save my sister,
the Su family will pay any price.
A doctor's compassionate heart.
I shall naturally do my utmost.
Bring the needles.
Please.
This is the Jiu Xiao Huan Pei.
A relic from the Su family's great-grandaunt.
It's said that during the Guangxu era,
great-grandfather Su spent half his wealth
to buy this Tang zither from Prince Gong.
There are bloodstains inside the zither.
Legend says...
Brother Ming.
My ears are about to burst.
The five notes correspond to the five organs.
The Gong note enters the spleen.
It should be warm and gentle,
yet this zither carries a killing aura.
The zither is 3 chi, 6 cun, 6 fen long,
symbolizing the 366 days of the year.
This zither is half a cun longer.
Just as I thought.
I've seen this zither so many times,
but I never knew.
Suppression Sorcery.
A Heart-Suppressing Bell is embedded inside.
The five strings tune yin and yang,
silently matching the soul-capturing spell.
Altered Notes.
Is Su Wan's room
located at the Zhen Position?
Yes, that is Eldest Miss's bedroom.
For such a case of evil spirit affliction,
we must use my Sun family's secret art:
the Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles.
Sister Feifei.
Professor Sun is truly skilled.
He's about to perform miraculous acupuncture.
This is the seventh needle,
Dazhui (GV14).
It requires the Secret Method of the Azure Turtle's Probe,
piercing three cun and six fen deep,
to draw out from the Governing Vessel
pure yang energy,
to channel it directly into the Brain.
Only then can the evil spirit be shaken.
However...
However what?
Professor Sun,
name any condition you wish.
This needle is extraordinarily perilous.
The healer must use his essence-blood
to force the secret method into motion,
sacrificing three Years of life,
to succeed.
Three Years of life?
Master.
You absolutely must not!
You're nearly seventy this year.
How many more three years do you have?
Your three Years of life could save many.
The price is far too great.
Professor.
I beg you,
please save my sister.
Three years of life.
I, Su Qianqian,
am willing to offer my own lifespan.
As long as you can save my sister,
our Su family
is willing to pay any price.
I beg you.
The Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles is my family's forbidden secret.
Those who can learn it are exceedingly rare.
Those who can perform the first five are rarer still.
Even with extraordinary talent,
without years of cultivation,
you cannot perform this fate-defying needle.
This...
Today, I
shall give it a try.
Silly girl,
get up.
Today, I will risk it all.
I will spare no effort.
Miss Su,
look how Professor Sun, to save a life,
is willing to risk his own.
A doctor's compassionate heart like his
is clear for heaven and earth to see.
Professor Sun
has always admired you.
If you can forge this good bond,
it will greatly benefit your future
in the field of traditional Chinese medicine.
Professor Sun,
rest assured.
I know how to show gratitude.
Healing the world,
sparing not oneself.
Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles,
the twelfth needle:
Soul Reclamation.
These Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles
are a method of ghosts and gods.
The King of Hell claims lives.
This has summoned
something unspeakable.
Sister Feifei.
A miracle!
It's truly a miracle!
President Su is awake!
Professor Sun is amazing!
Sis.
How are you?
Are you feeling better?
Qianqian.
What happened to me?
Professor Sun revived you with the
Thirteen Divine and Demonic Needles.
President Su,
you're finally awake.
To save you, Professor Sun
sacrificed three Years of life
to perform a heaven-defying needle art
and revive you.
Just look at his complexion.
It's nothing.
Fortunately, I didn't fail the mission.
Saving a life
is better than building a seven-story pagoda.
Bullshit Thirteen Needles!
Your skills are incomplete,
yet you recklessly use sinister arts,
inviting evil into the body,
harming others and yourself.
Incompetent doctors harm people!
Who let you barge into the Su residence?
Xiao Qi,
throw them out.
Eldest Miss,
I'm the one who invited Mr. Wu.
Who told you to act on your own?
I was worried about your safety!
Xiao Qi,
Is this the Zhongnan miracle doctor you spoke of?
He looks even younger than me.
He's nothing but a fraud.
You two are not welcome here.
Please leave.
You Su family folks
really Repaying kindness
with hostility!
If Brother Ming hadn't
just plucked that lousy zither downstairs,
that black mist would have devoured you all.
Would Eldest Miss still be breathing here?
In your dreams!
What nonsense!
Spreading heresy!
Professor Sun exhausted himself
and gave up Years of life to revive you.
Now you come to steal the credit?
Who do you think you are?
This is absolutely outrageous.
Make them leave at once.
Xiao Qi,
kick them out.
Eldest Miss.
Su Wan,
You're not far from death.
Blindly using the Ghost Gate Evil Needles
has drained your Root of Life Force.
You're merely having A final rally now.
Nonsense!
Though President Su's pulse is weak,
her vitality has been restored.
How can you say her life is nearing its end?
You ignorant brat,
are you grandstanding
to get President Su's attention?
You should know your place.
Three.
Two.
What trickery are you pulling?
One.
Eldest Miss!
Sis!
This is impossible!
Get up, you quack!
Guard the door!
I have to save her!
Don't let anyone in!
Yes!
Professor, please leave.
Don't make me use force.
Fine.
Very well.
Miss Su.
If anything goes wrong,
you will be held fully responsible.
Let's go.
You'll regret this.
Just you wait.
For the needle treatment ahead,
no one else can be present.
Fatty, take her outside too.
Let's go.
No way.
Don't you dare go near my sister.
Carry her out.
Xiao Qi.
Why can't I move?
Forgive me, Second Miss.
You!
What spell has he cast on you?
Gui Chen.
What a cunning scheme.