This assassin comes and goes like a ghost.
I can't be on guard every moment.
Only by setting up Qimen Dunjia protection
can I rest easy.
Rest, Life, Wound, Block,
View, Death, Shock, Open.
Eight Gates Golden Lock!
The First White Greedy Wolf guards the Qian Palace.
The Second Black Giant Gate guards the Xun Wind.
The Fourth Green Wenqu transforms Tianquan.
Yellow Lianzhen,
break the central palace!
Qian, Kan, Gen, Zhen,
Xun, Li, Kun, Dui.
Dunjia,
Open!
Hubby.
Why are you hiding in my room?
It's late at night,
with just the two of us alone.
Look at my figure.
Isn't it nice and curvy?
Get out.
Or else I'll...
Don't you have any sense of decency?
I'm just teasing you.
I'm wearing something underneath.
Scaredy-cat.
I have to say,
Wu Ming,
you're way too adorable.
You're blushing all the way down to your neck.
You...
The Great Island people
are way too bold.
Cultural difference.
More like a cultural gap.
It's hard to understand.
You...
I set up Qimen Dunjia. How did you get in?
Sir,
I've been here since noon.
I was waiting to share your bed,
but then,
you hit me so hard.
You...
Are you all right?
Do I look all right to you?
I just wanted to warm your bed,
and you nearly killed me!
We Chinese are very traditional.
We don't do this sort of thing.
Traditional?
How traditional?
You and Miss Su,
within ten minutes of meeting her,
you were already doing that.
Is that your tradition too?
How do you know about that?
Well,
Fatty,
just couldn't keep his mouth shut.
That damn fatso blabs about everything.
That was an accident.
Don't read too much into it.
And don't pull this kind of stunt again.
You can say that again.
I wouldn't dare do it again.
I'd like to live a few more years.
Sir,
get some rest.
Maybe I did
hit her a little too hard.
The Wu family avoids karmic ties.
So I'll drag you into this cage of karma.
From now on,
you'll have a weakness.
Dealing with you
will be much easier.
Let's have a drink.
Come on, dig in.
Mom!
Please, save my mom!
Save my mom!
She's already dead.
You're a miracle doctor!
I'm begging you.
Save my mom!
I'll pay any price.
There's nothing I can do.
Cursed Lone Star
Doomed to harm those close to you.
The calamities in your fate
are far worse than tonight's misfortune.
They will cling like maggots to bone,
slowly eroding all that you cherish,
bringing you pain tenfold, a hundredfold.
But since you've been tainted by my karma,
if you're willing to take me as your master,
then I shall
shield you from this storm.
The dead cannot be brought back to life.
This is the iron law of heaven and earth.
Though I cannot bring her back,
I can
let you see her one last time.
Mom...
Wandering soul,
where do you linger?
In wilderness and wasteland,
in temples, mountains, or forests.
The three souls grow faint,
the seven spirits sink low.
Frightened by strange specters,
the true soul is lost.
The Heaven Gate opens,
the Earth Gate opens,
A soul-guiding boy from a thousand miles.
By the order of the Three Pure Ones,
swiftly, as the law commands!
O soul,
return!
Mom!
Tingting.
What's wrong, darling?
Who... who...
Who's your darling?
You...
Oh my god, this is horrifying!
I must be dreaming.
Darling, I have to tell you,
you're really not dreaming.
Your performance last night was incredible.
You... you...
Stop talking.
Just pretend I was never here, okay?
Are you trying to be a scumbag?
Last night was my first time!
You want money, right?
I... I have money.
I'll... I'll give it to you.
I'll give you all my money.
I don't want your money.
Then what do you want?
I want you.
We... we're not even the same species.
We can't be together.
I...
I'm afraid of the dark!
See ya!
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the chieftain's daughter,
Epona.
I can tell.
Very Ebola.
It's Epona!
You think you're funny?
What exactly do you want?
Where I come from,
a man and woman who sleep together must marry.
Unless you want my whole tribe hunting you down...
Holy crap...
I...
I mean...
I have to go home and tell my mom.
Sure.
But...
What are you doing?
Darling, you may leave now.
Is this how you treat your honey?
Don't worry, it's not poisonous.
It just works as a tracker.
No matter where you hide,
the bond of our love can never be severed.
Today,
your master shall help you Sink Qi to the Dantian.
Hey, guys,
Could you stop following me so closely?
I'm not a national treasure.
With you tailing me like this,
I feel really uncomfortable.
Master.
We're your personal bodyguard team.
Guaranteeing your absolute safety 24/7.
It's our duty.
Guys,
you're really hilarious.
In such a dangerous situation yesterday,
why didn't you protect me?
I went deep,
deep into the darkness.
Pitch black, an absolute mess.
Master, rest assured.
We've conducted a full risk assessment.
It's impossible for her
to pose any danger or harm to you.
Moreover,
last night you initiated
the intimate engagement.
We have no right to interfere
with the Master's private leisure activities.
There goes my lifelong reputation.
Su Wan and I have a pure doctor-patient relationship.
That was just an accident.
Men.
Take what they want, then deny everything.
Turning their backs
faster than flipping a page.
You!
In any case,
your business with Miss Su,
everyone in our clinic, top to bottom,
collectively disapproves.
We don't agree with it.
This is ridiculous.
Ming Ming.
They don't like you,
but I like you.
I made these noodles specially for you.
It's my secret recipe.
I won't eat it.
Might be poisoned.
Why haven't you left yet?
I forgot to officially inform you.
I'm officially moving into the Chinese Taoist Clinic.
Starting today,
we're colleagues who'll see each other daily.
Surprised?
Shocked?
Do you even know medicine?
Of course.
All kinds of impotence and premature ejaculation,
weak kidneys and frail bodies,
I can treat any and all men's health issues.
Ming Ming,
how about I give you
a thorough full-body examination?
It's free.
Be serious.
This is a clinic.
You're no fun.
Let me tell you,
I'm way more useful than an ordinary physician.
In Hokkaido,
at the foot of Nagano's Mount Fuji, I own three herb mountains.
All kinds of naturally grown top-tier herbs,
whatever you need.
Physicians and medicine working together
makes the work so much easier.
So tell me,
isn't that important?
Fine, fine, fine.
From now on, quality control
will be your responsibility.
But there's no salary.
This lady here
is investing as a shareholder.