Kill these beasts!
Midako!
Sister!
Men can never be relied upon.
When it counts, we can only rely on ourselves.
Useless wretch.
Get lost!
Don't let me see you in Mancheng again.
Or I'll make you wish you were dead.
Cowardly piece of trash.
Worse than a dog.
In the end, I bet on the wrong side.
To think Midako hid her true strength so well.
Midako.
Sister.
Today, you and I, the two of us sisters,
shall likely meet our end here.
Senior Tianxiang.
I beg you, spare my sister.
I will pay any price.
Sword Saint.
Since they pose no threat anymore,
why not hand them over
to me?
Beneath my blade lie only departed souls.
Impressive.
Sword aura made manifest.
Wu Ming!
No matter how much sincerity you hold,
or how much scheming,
I, Wu Ming, will not let any woman shield me.
Let me go.
You bastard!
At a time like this, you're still acting tough?
Even I am no match for Sword Saint Tianxiang.
You're just throwing your life away by coming here.
Midako.
Though you seem alluring and seductive,
with venomous words and an arrogant air,
in truth, your heart is resolute and kind.
I forgive your past offenses against me.
Who are you?
To think you could break my Dizhi Congyun.
Who am I?
Do you truly not know?
With your strength,
the shallow waters of the Yedian Family
cannot contain a dragon like you.
Only Guichen can command you,
or as you Mancheng folk call him, Mr. Tianyi.
Young man.
You are worthy of my full strength.
God-Slaying Slash!
I, Tianxiang, in all my life,
bow only to my Master alone.
What manner of martial art is this?
Why have I never heard of it?
The healer's silver needle, though small,
can also be a lethal judge's blade.
Tell me where he is.
And I will spare your life.
I admit you are strong.
But compared to my Master,
you are nothing but an ant.
My lord
I... I don't know anything!
It was Tianxiang who came to me!
I don't know anything else!
Please spare me!
I'll offer up everything of the Yedian Family!
Including both of them!
They're all yours!
Yedian Midako
is at your command, Master
I know you're unwilling deep down
There's no need to pretend
Actually, your true self
is more endearing
Inside, it's me
Outside, it's also me
Aren't I interesting?
Master
Don't call me Master
Yes, Master
This one is quite amusing
I'll take her
Wu Ming, thank you
Today you stood with me through life and death
The Yedian Family will forever be your loyal ally
What are you doing?
If you think I'm using you
you may very well kill me
Don't let it happen again
Such a powerful man of China
is worthy of our submission and allegiance
Young Divine Doctor Wu
Your name has long been known to me
Please examine my Wan'er at once
Very well
Miss Su
Do not fear
Men and women should not touch.
Divine Doctor Wu
Don't tell me you can't even do thread-pulse diagnosis.
Thread-pulse diagnosis
is but a minor trick
My Wu family's ancient medicine is profound
It emphasizes observing, listening, inquiring, and palpating
The four diagnoses unified as one
I must examine in person
to detect subtle changes in the bloodflow
Miss Su
A healer has a parent's heart
Do not hide your illness from the doctor
Wait a moment
And this is...
This is my granddaughter, Su Qianqian.
She studies at the Chinese Medicine Academy.
So this is the second Miss Su.
So young, yet so admirably ambitious.
However...
To become a disciple of the Wu clan,
we must first see your talent.
Floating pulse, light as wood adrift.
Sunken pulse, heavy as stone in a lake.
Slow pulse, fewer than four beats per breath.
Rapid pulse, more than five beats per breath.
What pathology does each correspond to?
Please enlighten us, Master.
What a sharp-tongued little girl,
trying to test me instead.
These basic pulse readings,
they're nothing but...
Well, you see...
Floating pulse indicates exterior syndromes,
and deficiency syndromes.
Sunken pulse indicates interior syndromes.
Slow pulse indicates cold syndromes.
Rapid pulse indicates heat syndromes.
These are the basics of Binhu Pulse Studies.
What's wrong, Master?
You have to think about even this?
Or is it that...
you've just been putting on an act?
Your eyes keep darting around,
you're restless and impatient,
your words are flippant.
You have none of a healer's compassion,
let alone the bearing of a true master.
Grandfather.
Sister.
Open your eyes and see clearly.
This man is nothing but a charlatan.
Insolence!
I, a divine healer, came in good faith
to offer you medical treatment at your home,
yet your Su family is so ungrateful,
even slandering me.
This is utterly outrageous!
Farewell!
Stop right there!
Who gave you the nerve
to swindle the Su family?
Xiaoqi.
Spare me, lady warrior!
I just wanted to scam a bit of money.
I'll never do it again.
I was wrong! I was wrong!
Drag him out of here.
Wan'er.
But what about your illness?
Grandfather.
Don't believe in these so-called divine healers anymore.
I'll find a way to cure myself.
Second Miss.
We just received word.
Huangji Clinic has been renamed Zhonghua Daoyi Hall.
And the master is none other than Wu Ming.
So my guess was right.
He used me to take down Huangji,
and now he's targeting the Su family.
Eldest Miss.
Actually, I think Wu Ming is rather...
Xiaoqi!
You're still blinded by him.
You need to take a long, hard look at yourself.
Sister Xiaoqi
You're just too naive.
That Wu Ming,
first he used my sister's hand
to wipe out his rivals.
Now he's making a big show of opening a clinic.
He's after something big.
How could a man like that truly devote himself to medicine?
Besides,
in this world, those whose medical skills surpass mine
can probably be counted on one hand.
You don't just run into them so easily.
Eldest Miss,
Second Miss,
neither of you believes me,
but I'll prove it to you.
Brother Ming,
are we really not going to the Su family first?
It's still too soon.
Brother Ming,
I've got a favor to ask of you.
No need to be so polite, just say it.
You know I have a girlfriend, right?
Her name's Pinru.
She's a great girl,
treats me really well too.
But her mom is obsessed with money.
Says I'm poor, says I'm useless.
Every day she's trying to break us up.
You,
if you'd just show some real ability,
take yourself seriously,
how could your mother-in-law look down on you?
Brother Ming,
help a brother out just this once.
Come with me tomorrow,
and show that snobby old woman a thing or two.
Fine.
Take me to meet her tomorrow then.
Brother Ming,
I knew you were a true bro.
Bottoms up!
To hell with living together!
Wang Gang, get back here!
Get back here!
I'm not coming back!
What are you running so fast for?
You heartless jerk!
I worked so hard brewing this medicine.
Are you drinking it or not?
I'm not drinking it!
I drink that bitter, nauseating stuff every day.
It's completely useless!
Useless?
But we still can't have a kid!
And whose fault is that?
What's wrong with me?
Are you telling me you don't want this marriage anymore?
If you walk out that door today,
I'm telling you,
we're getting divorced!
Fine!
Divorce it is!
Brother Ming,
this Brother Wang owns the barbecue shop.
He and his wife are good people,
they just have bad luck.
Bad luck?
How so?
He's not so great in that department.
They've been married for years,
but they've never been able to have a kid.
Brother Ming,
this old Wang
is a really loyal guy.
Back when I had no money,
he often treated me to meals.
So, about this...
Alright.
Oh no.
It's almost nine o'clock.
Eldest Miss, what's wrong?
That damn feeling is coming back again.
Come, come to my side.
Drop your resistance and enjoy the bliss.
Get out!
Get out of my head!
Eldest Miss,
how about I ask that Wu Ming for help?
No.
He must have used some method
to put me under hypnosis.
We can't.
We can't fall for his trick.