These days, with him,
I don't even want to talk anymore.
As for me,
Li Mei,
I'll just keep enduring like this.
Until I'm completely worn out,
and it's all over.
Sister-in-law, snap out of it!
You should go to him,
go to Bro Ming!
He's a Miracle Doctor from Zhongnan Mountain.
There's nothing he can't do.
Helping you have a child?
That's child's play for him.
Little brother,
are you really willing to help me
get pregnant?
Sis... Sister-in-law,
you're overthinking this.
You got it all wrong.
I meant the Miracle Doctor,
his Golden needles,
his Internal energy.
Let him treat Brother Wang.
Once he's cured,
won't your future happiness be guaranteed?
Him?
A Miracle Doctor?
Just a green kid.
More like a charlatan, if you ask me.
Sister-in-law, just give it a try.
What if it actually works?
Once Lao Wang is cured,
won't you get to hold those chubby babies,
as many as you want?
What?
You really think I'm that kind of woman?
Trying to flirt with Sister-in-law?
Not afraid Lao Wang will break your legs?
No, that's not it.
Um...
This...
What is it?
The Pericardium Meridian of Hand-Jueyin
Qi is stagnant at the Tianchi point
Conception Vessel cold deficiency at Guanyuan
Three days before your period,
your lower abdomen feels icy cold,
and the pain is like a twisting knife.
Am I right?
You...
How could you know that?
Even Lao Wang doesn't know this.
By the Midnight-Noon Ebb-Flow theory,
the Kidney Meridian governs at the You hour.
At that time, deep within your lower back,
it aches like ten thousand ants gnawing,
the pain piercing the bone marrow.
Am I right?
Incredible!
Truly incredible!
Bro Ming,
even my deadly evening backaches,
you nailed it perfectly.
The exact spot, not off by a hair.
Even Lao Wang never knew about this.
Taiyin, Shaoyin, Jueyin,
where the three Yin meet, qi and blood clot,
hard as solid stone.
Within the womb,
ten years of cold-induced blood stasis
have formed an icy cavern.
All vitality has been cut off.
Sister-in-law,
if you let me use needles to break it tonight,
the problem will be resolved.
There's...
There's something!
I'm so hot!
Something's surging inside my belly,
like...
like fire.
Tell me, are you convinced now?
I'm convinced.
I'm truly convinced.
When Bro Ming makes his move,
divine needles unsheathed,
calm and composed,
shouldn't you treat us to a good meal?
Young man,
Stick them in!
Stick them wherever you want!
Needle the hell out of me!
As long as it works,
I'm telling you,
Sister-in-law will grill 10 kidney skewers.
No,
twenty skewers!
How about that?
Sister-in-law,
the kidneys won't be necessary.
How about finding a quiet place
for me to give you acupuncture and massage?
Let's go, let's go!
Right now!
Sis,
I'll use Golden needles on your Baihui,
Shenting,
and Yintang points,
to force your mind to wake up.
It will be very painful.
Don't hold the pain in.
Baihui opens Yang and clears the mind.
Sis,
What do we do about Second Miss?
Why is her pulse so chaotic?
Xiaoqi,
Go make the call, quick!
Hurry!
Okay.
Sis!
Hello?
Sis, don't scare me, sis!
Sister-in-law,
Your cold-induced blood stasis is severe.
Full-body acupuncture is needed.
If anything seems inappropriate during the process,
please don't overthink it.
A doctor sees no gender.
Sister-in-law trusts you.
A hundred percent.
Don't worry.
Sister-in-law has been around the block.
I've seen it all.
As long as you can cure me,
don't feel any pressure.
Right, Bro Ming.
Sister-in-law is so cool about it.
I'll be your assistant.
I'll hand you the needles.
And wipe Sister-in-law's sweat.
No.
Let me help you.
I can even hold Sister-in-law down.
Get out,
and shut the door behind you.
Oh, right, Bro Ming.
I'll wait right outside.
If you need anything, be sure to call me.
You have to call me!
Forget it.
I'd better check on Bro Ming.
What if he needs my help?
Sister-in-law,
Face away from me and remove your clothes.
Then lie face-down on the bed.
Okay.
Sister-in-law, please turn over.
It's time for acupuncture on the front.
This...
Wow, that works too?
You've been needling me blindfolded?
How can you do that?
If you miss the points,
it could be fatal!
This is truly miraculous.
I'm completely impressed.
But, little brother,
why don't you take off the blindfold?
Seeing where you place the needles
it would put Sister-in-law's mind at ease.
No need, Sister-in-law.
Let's continue.
You really are an upright young man.
However,
if you really can't hit the points,
feel for Sister-in-law's acupoints to needle,
that would be fine too.
Sister-in-law trusts you, you know.
The master is not here.
Come back tomorrow.
Miss Huizi can't wait until tomorrow.
I know President Su was disrespectful before,
but right now, a life is at stake!
Don't you have his contact info?
You could at least give him a call.
I don't have the master's private contact.
Even if I did,
the master has his own reasons for what he does.
Since Miss Su doesn't trust the master,
why come begging him now?
You're so certain the master will save her?
I'm a martial artist.
This feeling cannot be wrong.
Facing the master,
it's like I see towering mountains and deep seas.
I feel as small as a speck of dust.
This pressure is overwhelming.
Is that so?
You feel small as you don't understand him.
Once you truly know him,
you'll realize
that feeling small right now
is just a drop in the ocean.
You'll truly understand
what it truly means to gaze up at the stars,
and feel ashamed of your insignificance.
For someone as proud as you to say such things,
just how powerful is he?
A true dragon will one day soar across the sky.
It hides in the deep only to shake the world.
Once he rides the clouds and rises,
overnight, the whole world will know his name.
Then may I wait for him here?
No matter how late it gets.
Suit yourself.
Help yourself to some tea.
Little brother, you're amazing!
I feel completely refreshed all over.
Like a ten-year burden has been lifted.
My whole body feels nice and warm.
I've never felt so energized.
My infertility problem,
has it been cured?
Sister-in-law.
Though the cold stagnation is cleared,
but your waist and abdomen strain is severe.
I'll massage you to get the blood flowing.
So qi and blood flow smoothly during pregnancy.
Both mother and child will be safe,
and you'll suffer less.
I'll have to trouble you then.
Sister-in-law,
no need to undress for the massage.
Just lie face-down here.
What's so interesting? Let me see.
Sleeping with my wife?!