How could I possibly kill someone?
I was just drugged by hallucinogenic smoke.
You're the one who brought me back to my senses.
You used my hand to kill Huang Ji,
making it impossible for me to treat him.
You came here for the Su family.
I'm warning you,
abandon your twisted scheme.
Otherwise,
your fate will be worse than Huang Ji's.
Su Wan is under Gui Chen's mind control.
As long as we find Su Wan,
we'll have a lead on Gui Chen.
Gui Chen.
Is he really that sinister?
Gui Chen was once an unmatched prodigy.
He was Grandfather's chosen heir.
But he harbored malicious ambitions.
While Grandfather was in seclusion,
he severely wounded Grandfather and Uncle.
He took my sister,
and stole the Wu family's forbidden tome:
The Ten Arts of Yama.
If the Ten Arts are mastered,
demons will descend upon the world!
Ming.
Cleanse our lineage.
Slay this fiend.
This is your destiny!
Grandfather,
your grandson swears here and now,
I will surely slay Gui Chen.
Brother Ming,
so what do we do next?
Should we head to the Su family first?
Su Wan currently misunderstands us.
Chasing her puts us at a disadvantage.
We just need to wait for her to come.
Wait.
I have greatly offended you before, sir.
Yet you helped me with a benevolent heart.
I deeply admire you.
I hope you can forgive my prior rudeness.
There is no grudge between us.
Rise.
Get up.
Though Huang Ji Medical Society is famous,
its prominence has drawn much hostility.
We have offended many.
The master is now dead.
I fear
we will surely be attacked from all sides.
I beseech you to take charge of the clinic.
You've got quite the clever scheme.
You want to use me
to shield you from the storms of your past.
I am willing to submit to China,
to submit to you, sir.
I beg for your mercy.
I've always wanted to open a clinic,
to heal the world.
Its scale and reputation are quite good.
Then I shall accept this karma.
Since you honor me as your master,
you must abide by my rules.
The entire society obeys your commands.
Whatever the rules,
we shall follow them.
First,
no person is high or low, noble or base,
only good or evil.
Second,
abandon all heretical and harmful arts.
Yes!
Come now, come now.
Rise quickly.
Please rename the society,
rename the clinic, sir.
The Chinese Dao Clinic.
The greatest super ninja.
I'll pay thirty million
to kill someone for me.
When I kill,
it takes but one strike.
A Chinese man named Wu Ming.
Torture him to death in the cruelest way.
Sever his head.
And then,
when speaking to me,
more than five words
means death.
Don't kill me!
You've already said thirty words.
If you want to live,
you'll have to pay more.
Three hundred million.
Done.
The super ninja
is truly terrifying.
I suppressed Gui Chen's mark in Su Wan.
He's bound to sense it.
He won't let it go.
A perfect chance to lure the snake out.
Sir.
Let me attend to your bath.
No need.
You may withdraw.
What are you doing?
Since I have accepted you as my master,
I already belong to you, sir.
My body,
my heart,
I willingly give them all to you, sir.
Please cherish me, sir.
My hand.
My hand has gone numb.
You needn't do this.
Assist Fatty well,
and managing the Dao Clinic is your duty.
You are like a true dragon, sir.
I know my humble form is unworthy of you.
I dare not hope for any title.
I only wish to follow you always,
as your servant and handmaid.
Killing intent.
Help me draw out the assassin.
If we're putting on an act,
it has to be convincing.
Right, sir?
Dying in her embrace is too good for you.
Raging Flame Heaven-Burning Slash!
This...
First seduction,
then assassination.
Quite the tactics, Noda family.
No!
I did no such thing!
I swear to the heavens,
this matter has nothing to do with me.
I've planted the Three-Talents Soul-Lock Needle in you.
In all the world,
those who can dispel it are few indeed.
A healer holds benevolence,
but you are of a foreign clan.
I bind you with forbidden arts.
Stir up trouble,
and you shall die.
Second Princess,
it was Noda Kumaji
who forced me to seduce Mr. Wu Ming,
and sent a super ninja to assassinate him.
But in the end,
he was slain in a single move.
Even a super ninja couldn't kill him,
and was slain in a single move?
Yes.
That's impossible!
You're lying to me!
I wouldn't dare.
I dare not deceive you in the slightest.
Mr. Wu Ming has now taken over the clinic.
I beg the Second Princess to show mercy.
How dare you!
Who do you think you are,
to plead on his behalf?
He nearly cost my sister the seat of clan head.
He deserves to die!
Yes.
I was wrong.
The dread that Mr. Wu Ming inspires
can only be felt by those who face him.
You will pay the price for your arrogance.
I vow to follow at his side forever.
Second Uncle never lets a slight go unpaid.
He surely won't let Wu Ming off.
Let's watch the tigers fight from afar.
If anything develops,
report to me at once.
Yes.
I've already sent men riding in haste
to Mount Zhongnan,
to invite a master from the Wu clan.
Once the master arrives,
your strange ailment will surely be cured.
Grandfather,
nine out of ten so-called masters are frauds.
Don't be deceived by them.
Besides, this illness of mine,
please don't trouble yourself over it.
The Wu lineage of Mount Zhongnan
is a hidden clan with divine arts.
Grandfather is well on in years,
and firmly believes in these masters.
Forget it.
Better to humor him,
to spare him worry.
Come, pull that corner back a bit more.
Okay, okay.
Is that good?
Right here.
Who dares approach?
The one who'll destroy Huang Ji Clinic.
Insolence!
Huang Ji Clinic is a thing of the past.
From this day forward,
this shall be the Chinese Dao Clinic.
In Mancheng's medical world,
I reign supreme.
All others shall be wiped out.
Seeing you have some beauty,
I shall take you as my slave
and spare your life.
You're unworthy of enslaving me.
I am the Oshima Medical Sage!
What gives you the nerve
to speak to me like that?
The one who stands behind me
is the source of my courage.
You!
Not a bad feeling.
I'm warning you,
let go of me!
My master is not someone you can cross.
She's been pushed around this badly,
and that Wu guy still won't show himself?
Truly a master indeed,
a master enduring endless humiliation.
Sister, let me handle this.
Keiko is one of our own, after all.
Not just any stray dog gets to take a bite.
No need.
If he can't even handle this much trouble,
then he didn't revive Grandfather.
Wu Ming,
I defied the entire family
and gambled my future on you.
You'd better not disappoint me.
Your master?
Who does he think he is?
Old Huang Ji wouldn't dare speak to me like that.
Once I've killed your master,
you'll belong to me.
Stop it now!
My master will never let you off.
Worthless rabble.
Unworthy of being my enemy.
First I'll smash this eyesore of a sign.
Smashing my signboard?
You're not worthy.