NAZE! Congratulations
on getting first place!
This is all thanks to everyone!
- Thank you!
You've been on a roll
since Producer Azuma's departure.
We heard
he constantly abused his power
and looked down on the group members.
Do you have any words for him now?
Mr. Azuma is no longer
associated with NAZE.
Please keep your questions
related to the song.
We already told them he has
nothing to do with us now.
Why do they keep asking
the same thing?!
Where could Mr. Azuma be?
I've got it! Why don't you move?
You guys can't stay in that
cramped and old house forever.
I agree.
Besides
NAZE is one of the top idols now.
Ms. Nam.
What should we do about the costumes?
I doubt you'll be using the coats
and the kimonos again.
Well, I guess you have a point.
But the performance back then
was great, wasn't it?
Yes, we got to wear
everyone's traditional clothes.
I was so moved when I saw
everyone's childhood photos.
The origins of the ingredients
don't matter at all.
We'll bring out our unique flavor
with our own power.
That's all that matters.
Hey, those are the messages
we wrote back then!
DON'T BULLY TORINNER!
Those kids were so cool, right?
Please don't bully TORINNER!
Instead of the anonymity
of social media
they'll write their true feelings
for TORINNER by hand.
Mr. Azuma came up with this idea.
Wait, what's this?
It's Dad and Mr. Yamada.
I'm glad you made up with your dad.
You came to NAZE's
every live show, didn't you?
Will you let my son join you again?
In the end...
it was all thanks to Mr. Azuma.
He's the reason
we were able to make it this far.
Stop talking about him.
He abandoned us and just ran off.
We know.
Then forget about that horrible,
violent jerk!
That's not it.
What I meant was, we know
why Mr. Azuma acted like that.
He didn't want to get in our way
so he tried to erase his presence.
It's too obvious.
He changed way too suddenly.
Kun, you knew that too, didn't you?
- But--
- It's enough, Kun.
Anyone would have been able to tell.
His attitude changed
way too suddenly.
But Mr. Azuma told us
that it was his job to take
the best course of action for NAZE.
If he had tried to deny the article
and caused a commotion
it wouldn't have been good for NAZE.
Mr. Azuma was the one who let us know
it's okay for us to dream.
Now, it's our turn
to help Mr. Azuma dream.
I want to challenge myself
with even bigger dreams
together with Mr. Azuma.
Me, too.
Kun. You feel the same, right?
Yes.
It must be nice to be young.
But that guy is really stubborn!
He'll refuse to come back for sure.
I agree with you.
Well...
During our first live performance
didn't he say that he would
do anything we say
if we filled up the National Stadium?
- Wait...
- He did.
- He said it. He did say it!
- Yes!
That's 80,000 people.
If you can fill up
the Japan National Stadium
I'll do anything you say.
Let's make him keep his promise.
- Wait, Minase, what do you mean--
- Guys!
- Let's hold a concert there!
- What?
He said he'd do anything if you
filled up the National Stadium.
It's the only way
to bring Mr. Azuma back.
Wait a minute, Minase.
I hate to say this,
but that would be impossible!
That's 80,000 people.
Do you have a good plan?
Azuma is gone now.
You're right. It's too difficult
for us to achieve that on our own.
Are you saying that you can't
do anything without Mr. Azuma?
Mr. Azuma said he'd give up
everything to protect NAZE.
In that case, we cannot let him down.
Mr. Azuma had led us this far.
This time, let's work together
and achieve something
that will surprise him!
What are you guys doing?
Let's have a meeting!
What would Mr. Azuma do
to gather 80,000 people?
Sorry, Ms. Nam.
We'll move another time.
Goodness!
You murderer!
I am very sorry!
It doesn't matter who it is.
Do it at all costs.
Find out what NAZE will do next
and Azuma's current whereabouts.
Hey.
Are you guys not going to work
until I tell you to do so?
Am I the only person here?
Make yourselves useful to me!
- Yes, sir.
Hey, are you taking a break already?
Losers have no time to rest.
Move. Quick.
Is he an amateur?
Nobody makes people
practice nonstop these days!
Hey! What's wrong?
What are you doing? You'll die!
Hey!
He's so dramatic.
NAZE WILL HOLD A CONCERT
AT THE JAPAN NATIONAL STADIUM!
We're NAZE!
We'll be holding a concert,
so please come!
- Please come!
- What? NAZE?
- No way!
Please come to watch!
Don't push!
- Please don't push!
Please don't push!
- Nobody's pushing me, huh?
- Don't push!
- We're NAZE!
- We'll be holding a concert!
It will be
at the Japan National Stadium!
- Please come and watch!
We're making really slow progress.
Is there a more efficient way
to promote?
I've got it!
The video Mr. Azuma made for TGC
was played many times, right?
He said he still
had a bunch of other video footage.
Maybe there's something we can use.
Please go slowly! Don't push!
Right, we worked backstage.
Look!
We also handed out flyers.
Right, that hurt.
Why was this filmed? Who filmed this?
You were horrible.
- Hey...
- Oh, this part!
It's insane,
no matter how many times I watch it!
You guys should forget that exists.
Still, I'm surprised you managed
to stay so calm.
Well, I'm an adult.
Once more. Reina, do it again.
One more time, Reina!
Is this Mr. Azuma's voice?
Reina! One more time, Reina!
It is.
Oh, come on.
I wanted something dramatic.
What did you say?
He's being so mean.
He was just enjoying it.
How annoying.
He had no idea how I was feeling.
- She's impressive, though.
- You mean Minase?
I don't know if you can call it
her passion or obsession.
But she has exceeded my expectations.
She wrote up
that thick stack of information
and visited so many companies.
I asked if she was ready to be
responsible for other people's lives
but I feel like
she taught me a lesson instead
and made me reflect on myself.
Mr. Azuma...
Shall we watch the others?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Oh, it's the riverbed.
I had no stamina back then.
It's so embarrassing.
Yuya can be a little too serious,
but he's resilient.
When he decides on something,
he will stick to it.
He will go far.
Ato is the pillar of this team.
He's always thinking
about what the team needs.
I want him to be
more self-assertive, though.
Younki may appear mischievous,
but he's actually observant.
I can see he's trying to help Ato
see anything he may have missed.
I'm honestly surprised
by Turn's ability.
He has the talent
to become a world-class dancer.
I want to train him carefully.
As for Kaisei...
Kaisei is...
Come on!
Harmony is the most important thing
in a team.
But it's not something
anyone can achieve.
Having him around eases the tension.
That's an extraordinary talent.
Do-hyeok is the youngest,
but he has a mysterious charm.
I'm excited to see
how much he'll grow in the future.
I like Kun's intense,
passionate hunger to succeed.
With that earnest attitude
he'll be the one
to lead NAZE someday.
Why don't you tell them
all that yourself?
I'm not comfortable
with praising people.
What an edgelord.
Continuing to do what you love
isn't always fun.
But nothing you do is ever wasted.
You may hit a wall, and you
don't get the results you want.
When you repeat something
that may seem pointless
you steadily build up experience
over time.
The accumulated experience helps them
create their own unique weapon.
That's why
I won't praise them easily.
They have incredible potential.
Until that potential
is fully unleashed
I want to keep telling them
to aim higher and higher.
Mr. Azuma...
Turning the experience we've built up
into our weapons...
That's it!
It's the special version
of Isn't She Lovely?
Please learn it!
One, two...
What do you think?
- That seems easy enough.
- Right.
I think we can do it if we try.
Let's do a dance challenge together!
An 80,000-person dance relay!
Here we go!
SEARCH, 80,000-PERSON
DANCE RELAY
SEARCH, 80,000-PERSON DANCE RELAY
It's difficult!
But this is our chance
to repay Mr. Azuma.
Don't you agree, everyone?
- Yes, sir.
SEARCH, 80,000-PERSON DANCE RELAY
- Act cute?
- Yes, like that.
I'm going to film! Get closer!
SEARCH, 80,000-PERSON DANCE RELAY
They're doing all this
to ask Mr. Azuma to return.
There's no way Mr. Azuma
would abuse his power.
Ms. Park, we'd like
to support NAZE as well.
But...
I don't know what Mr. Choi
might do if you do that.
It has increased so much!
I'm so happy!
Wow!
- Look! Just look at the sales!
- Yes, I'm looking.
APPEARANCE REQUEST,
COLLABORATION REQUEST
The 80,000-person dance relay
was a great idea.
It's because
Mr. Azuma complimented my dancing.
Wait! Have a look at this!
What? Is there a problem?
I can't believe he made all these
in secret.
He's so sweet.
I just received your title track song
from a songwriter in the US.
I really like it
so I want you guys to hear it now.
He summoned us here in the middle
of the night just for this?
This guy is insane.
That is...
not all I have for you.
- Wait, he speaks Japanese?
- Well...
I used to work in Japan.
It seems that NAZE
will be holding a concert
at the Japan National Stadium.
Yes, we've verified that information.
On the same day
TORINNER will hold a concert
at Tokyo Dome.
- What?
- Tokyo...
Congratulations on your dome debut.
Please wait a minute, Mr. Choi!
We have only a few songs.
That will not be enough
to satisfy our fans!
Besides, we don't have enough time--
Don't talk back to me!
I'm not asking for your opinions.
You're just going to do as I say!
You hear me?
Just look forward to it.
I'm going to crush NAZE for you.
Goodness, the snow is heavy.
It's going to make the roof collapse.
Please let me clear the snow.
There's no reason for you to do that.
Now leave!
I am sorry.
I've been thinking about
what I can do
but nothing comes to mind.
Please, at least let me help--
I don't care about what you think!
GRADUATION CEREMONY
WE'LL WIN THE BEST NEW ARTIST AWARD
AT MAMA!
Riku...
Hey! It's dangerous! Get down!
Just stop it and come down.
Don't worry, I'll be careful.
Hey, sir, who is that guy?
No idea.
It's looking good!
At this rate, we might be able
to fill up the stadium!
What?
At Tokyo Dome?
It's on the same day as our concert.
TORINNER'S CONCERT AT TOKYO DOME!
Darn it! They're here
to get in our way again!
Where is Mr. Azuma?
We mustn't.
We can't rely on Mr. Azuma forever.
I know.
I know, but...
I like NAZE
but there is no way I can betray Ryo!
I was going to go
to the National Stadium!
Why does TORINNER's
first Tokyo Dome concert
have to happen on the same day?
Flowers never betray me.
The more I care for them
the better they grow.
I hope TORINNER will be the same.
Hey, turn on the studio cameras.
What's going on?
Where did they go?
The concert is just days away!
They might be taking a break.
Who allowed them to?
Make them resume their practice.
Yes, sir.
Where are you going?
I've decided to live the way I want.
This is bad.
So many people have canceled
their tickets.
At this rate,
forget about bringing Azuma back.
We'll go bankrupt from huge losses.
Yes?
What do you want?
You're still at it?
Sorry, I couldn't do it properly.
Sir, let him rest inside.
Otherwise, he'll die!
This guy is none of my concern.
Don't be ridiculous!
That would make you a murderer!
I'll fetch you a patch.
GRADUATION CEREMONY
My arrogance drove Riku to his death.
I am really sorry.
I had no idea that he had passed away
so I was late in coming to see you.
Here's a patch for you.
Shall I put it on your back for you?
No, it's okay. Thank you.
Don't overdo it, all right?
There are things you can
and cannot do in a snowy region.
Right, Izaburo?
Hey, do you know about
the Snow Festival's sky lanterns?
No, I don't.
We get so much snow around here,
so there's no risk of forest fires.
That's why we can
send up lanterns like this.
It started as a prayer for recovery
from the earthquake in this town.
But to this day, people continue
to write their wishes on them.
Riku loved this festival
since he was a kid--
Keep your mouth shut!
Come on! What's the harm?
Even after Riku became a celebrity
he would still come back
for the Snow Festival.
And then he'd brag to me.
He said his dream came true because
of his grandpa, who raised him...
and a producer named Mr. Azuma.
He said
it was thanks to both of them.
You are Azuma, aren't you?
Yes.
Take a look at this picture.
WE'LL WIN THE BEST NEW ARTIST AWARD
AT MAMA!
He was really grateful to you.
Stop it!
This jerk killed Riku.
He doesn't look like someone
who would push a person to his death.
I'm sure you also remember
how Riku was back then.
He looked really bright.
WE'LL WIN THE BEST NEW ARTIST AWARD
AT MAMA!
Where did they go?
Where is TORINNER? Answer me!
- I don't know.
- You idiots!
Where's that guy?
I ordered him to look for them!
Where did he go?!
By "that guy"...
who are you referring to?
What?
Is there even a need for me
to memorize your names?
We aren't...
your puppets.
Are you crazy?
You only move when I tell you to.
You're nothing more than puppets!
What was that?
TORINNER IS NOW LIVE
Hello, everyone.
- We're TORINNER.
What's this?
This morning, we announced that
we would be holding a concert
at Tokyo Dome.
I feel so blessed
seeing my favorites together
However, we'll be canceling it.
I love you guys
What are these morons talking about?
Instead, we plan
to make a guest appearance
at NAZE's concert
at the Japan National Stadium.
Wait, aren't you guys rivals?
NAZE are our friends
so please come to the concert.
- We look forward to seeing you!
What the heck was that?!
Are you guys going to be okay?
Who knows? But...
We need to take charge
of our own lives.
You are one of SS's members...
Ji-hoon! Why are you here?
Mr. Izaburo.
Mr. Azuma.
I am so sorry!
I lied.
I was the one
who drove Riku to his death.
Mr. Azuma had nothing to do with it.
Get TORINNER here now.
Now!
What's this?
What are you scumbags doing?
Hey!
Do you...
know my name?
I don't care what your name is!
I am...
Seung-ho.
I am Ju-heon.
I'm Min-gyu.
My name is Kyung-ju.
We've decided that we want to live
like normal humans.
Please excuse us.
Hey.
Hey!
It was Mr. Choi Ki-young
who kicked Mr. Azuma
out of SEVEN SEAS.
Choi did that? Why?
Ever since you became SS's producer
Choi thought about
getting revenge on you.
Revenge?
A big round of applause
for Producer Azuma!
Mr. Azuma already had a track record
of producing another popular group
and he was always the one
who stood out.
On the other hand, Choi often did
the unglamorous tasks
like schedule coordination
and apologizing to business partners.
I'm impressed!
How did you get that filmed there?
Come on, anyone can rent that place.
They allowed it
because of you, Azuma.
As SS became more successful
Choi started asserting
his own opinions.
The company will never allow this!
We've been doing it like this.
But they would always listen
to Mr. Azuma's ideas.
Thank you.
That was when Choi overheard
their boss's conversation.
A boring guy like Choi should stay
quietly in Azuma's shadow.
He made the meeting longer
and wasted our time.
So, Choi fabricated a story about
Mr. Azuma abusing his power.
He filmed us with a hidden camera
during practice
and edited it so that it looked like
Mr. Azuma assaulted our members.
Then, he leaked it to the press.
What were you thinking?
Are you trying to ruin SS?
Before the incident
spiraled out of control
Mr. Azuma had a talk with us.
I'm quitting my job as a producer.
I'm tired of looking after you.
I'm done with you. Do it yourselves.
What are you talking about?
Are you going to abandon us now?
You don't care about SS?
- Are you running away now?
- You traitor!
Are you trying to ruin our lives?
Everything went
according to Choi's plan
and Mr. Azuma was blacklisted
from the industry.
No way. He went that far
out of mere jealousy?
Choi became our chief producer,
and he brought to us...
Are you kidding me?
...a concept completely different
from Mr. Azuma's vision.
So our leader, Riku,
and the rest of us strongly objected.
You want us to perform
such a lame song? Are you serious?
Mr. Azuma wouldn't have
given us something like this.
That's right. It's not going to sell.
Shut up! I am the producer.
Shut up and follow my orders!
We stopped talking
to each other after that.
It was impossible for us
to accept Choi's producing methods.
And then...
For some reason
the other members found out
about my secret.
We had been living together
for ten years
but there was a secret
that I couldn't tell them.
It got out somehow.
My secret is that...
I am gay.
Darn you! Why did you tell them?
So I confronted Riku.
After all,
he was the only one I had told.
It really wasn't me!
I blamed him again and again.
You're the most horrible person.
You don't deserve to live!
You ruined everything.
Get out of my sight!
SS disbanded right after that.
A few months later...
Ji-hoon!
Riku...
Riku died.
I suppose Riku's death
was unexpected, even for Choi.
He promised that he'd hire me
as his secretary
and with good pay.
He made me tell Riku's family
that Riku was a victim
of Mr. Azuma's abuse of power.
He said if I told you the truth
I would be blamed for everything.
- Pull yourself together!
- He threatened me.
That was when I finally realized.
Choi would lie
without batting an eye for his pride.
Mr. Azuma got in his way,
so he drove him out.
SS didn't obey his order,
so he forced us to disband.
Choi orchestrated all of it.
It was my fault...
that Riku died.
I've always wanted to apologize.
I lied to you
and I couldn't forgive myself.
But I didn't have the courage
to stand up to Choi.
I'm truly...
I am truly sorry.
Mr. Azuma.
I am sorry.
It's okay.
The Dark Truth of Choi Ki-young
President of the Global
K-pop Agency Bouquet Music
As Confessed by His Secretary
Alleged Abuse of Power by NAZE's
Producer Azuma Was Fabricated
Please come back, Mr. Azuma.
Everyone in NAZE
is doing their very best
because they want you to come back.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
I couldn't protect Riku's life.
Ji-hoon and SEVEN SEAS, too.
I forced my dreams on them
but then I ran away from them.
That guilt won't disappear.
You're wrong.
Everyone in NAZE said that
they were able to dream
because of you.
So now, it's their turn
to let you dream.
The live concert is tomorrow.
Let's go back to Tokyo together.
I can't go back.
Stupid Azuma!
The boys and I...
We are all fools.
So we want to have
an even more foolishly big dream.
Together with you.
The Dark Truth of Choi Ki-young
As Confessed by His Secretary
Can't believe
his secretary betrayed him LOL
So Bouquet Music
just wanted to destroy NAZE?
Why?
Why is it always me?
Why do things like this
always happen to me? Why?
I don't need these!
No matter how hard I try
nobody appreciates me!
I am Choi Ki-young!
Why is it always me?
Everything that we can do...
We've done it all.
Now, we just need to give it our all.
Let's do this!
Minase! Where's Azuma?
That idiot! Is he really not coming?
Thank you so much for coming today.
That's our line. I'm glad that
you managed to make this happen.
So, where is Mr. Azuma?
We still can't get a hold of him.
I see.
We'll be closing
the entrance door soon.
- How about the guests on the list?
- Everyone is here.
- We'll begin the concert.
- Okay.
No problems here.
- Everything is okay.
It's almost time.
- Okay.
One, two...
- NAZE!
Okay, let's go!
- Let's go!
Starting the countdown!
- Five, four, three, two, one!
Oh, no. It has started.
Darn it!
I've never seen this room so empty.
Are you here to laugh at me?
You have a weird hobby.
You're a self-righteous, distrustful,
bossy, and awful person!
But...
your tenacity in training TORINNER
to become a top artist
is something I acknowledge.
I caved under your pressure
and ran away.
But next time
I will challenge you head-on
as a producer.
I'm waiting for you
to claw your way back up.
Thank you.
Minase! Is that idiot still not here?
You're late.
Welcome back.
YOUNKI, ATO
YUYA, KAISEI
Wow.
Are you ready,
Japan National Stadium?
Wow!
TURN, YOU'RE SO COOL
Younki!
Do-hyeok!
Why did the lights turn orange?
YOUNKI
They showed me a huge dream.
Yes.
Now...
it's my turn.
Yes.
Do-hyeok!
- NAZE!
- Amazing!
I found that one thing filled
with our fond memories.
I'm so happy.
You came, Mr. Azuma.
I get it already.
Look, get off of me.
WE'LL WIN THE BEST NEW ARTIST AWARD
AT MAMA!
Let's go
to that foolishly
big dream stage!
THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL