You can stay with me.
I really don’t mind at all.
Okay.
Is someone waiting for you
in your room or something?
How could there be?
Who’d be waiting for me in my room?
Are you crazy?
Get out now.
The one who falls harder
gets hurt the most.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Sit down first.
Huh?
Let me do it for you.
You don’t have to. It’s dirty.
Let me take them off.
Have you been drinking?
Mm.
The place offered complimentary cocktails,
so I had a little.
A little? It doesn’t look like it.
Here.
Thank you.
Weren’t you supposed to be meeting
with the auditors?
Mm, I really did go meet them.
Here, give me that.
Come to think of it,
we’re not actually dating.
You don’t have to take my words
so seriously.
Uh.
Wine, you’re really drunk.
Why don’t you go take a shower first?
True.
Then I’ll go shower first.
Lal, could I have
this quarter’s client contracts?
They’re in that cabinet. Go check.
Lal, this plant’s basically dying.
Should I just throw it away?
Hey!
Oh shit! How could I forget?!
What do I do?
Just let it go.
-It already fought for its life.
-No!
I can’t!
What do I do?
Water, water! It needs water!
Water, water.
I need to water it.
Ah! I forgot it’s coffee!
Lal, may I have the docu—
Excuse me.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
It can still be saved.
Really?
Yeah.
Just give it more sunlight and fertilizer.
It should recover.
I’m really sorry.
You even bought it for me.
Did you hide it in the cabinet
because you were afraid I’d be mad?
Mm.
Huh?
Mm-hmm.
Seriously?
Mm.
Then how about this?
I’ll take care of it for now,
and once it gets better,
I’ll return it to you.
Mm.
And it’s really not a big deal.
I’m not mad.
Next time, just tell me, okay?
Yes.
Oh right, Numnim said
there’s a new onsen spa that just opened.
Do you want to go together?
No.
What if someone sees us?
Come on, it just opened.
There probably won’t be many people yet.
Besides, it’s far from the office.
Fine.
So you’ll go?
Okay, I’ll make the reservation then.
Mm.
I’d like to book two massage sessions
at 9 PM under the name Lal.
Yes, thank you.
Lal, hello.
Did you make plans with Wine?
Oh, no.
I brought cheesecake for her.
Wine eats cheesecake?
Only from this one shop.
The other day she posted on her story
saying she wanted some,
so I bought it for her.
But she hasn’t replied to my messages yet.
She’s probably busy.
Then I’ll bring it to her myself.
Are you two close?
Well, not really.
That’s what I thought.
Wine never talks about you to me.
I’ll take it to her anyway.
I have to go to the accounting department.
Alright then.
Thank you.
Hello.
I’m Lal. I booked for 9 PM.
Miss Lal,
two aroma massage sessions, correct?
This month we have a promotion.
If you post on your story and tag the spa,
you’ll get a 10% discount.
But you have to follow
our Instagram first.
That’s okay.
Huh? Why not?
It’s 10% off.
I’m worried people will ask questions.
I don’t want any issues.
It’s fine. I’ll post it myself.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You have a private account too?
No. This is actually my real account.
Only close friends follow it,
so it’s fine to post there.
Then can I follow you too?
I don’t accept follows
from people at work.
If you suddenly follow me,
it’ll look suspicious.
True.
This way, please.
Hm?
No!!!
Another one’s gone missing!
Don’t cry.
I’ll take you
to buy a new glass next time.
That makes four glasses this week already!
Four!
Why does this only happen to me?!
How about this?
Next time, let’s put laxatives in it
and catch the thief.
Lal!
Lal, we already know about it.
I saw it yesterday.
Saw what?
I saw…
New meeting with one of our clients
whose contract is about to expire.
The pause timing was freaking terrible.
What was that again?
Are you okay?
I’m fine. Continue.
If it was just a meeting,
there’d be no issue.
But if that client decides
not to renew their contract,
then our suspicions are probably correct.
Here.
Look at this.
I think New has been approaching clients
whose contracts are about to expire
and making deals with rival companies.
But the weird thing is…
how would New even know
which clients’ contracts are ending?
PR staff shouldn’t have access
to that information, right?
There’s definitely a traitor
in our company.
Wine, I’m sorry I’m late.
Traffic was terrible,
so I had to take a motorcycle taxi.
It’s so hot outside too.
But I did exactly what you told me.
I didn’t tell anyone
I came to have a meal with you.
Uh, thanks, but…
that’s Proud’s drink.
And that’s her seat too.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
I’ll just sit over there then.
The reason I asked you to come today
is because there’s something
I want to discuss.
But no one in the office
can know about this.
Sure.
No offense, Wine,
but the more people involved,
the messier things get, don’t you think?
Tangkwa’s worked with me for a long time.
I trust her.
Really?
If there’s anything
you want me to help with,
just tell me.
If it’s for the company, I’ll do anything.
And what if it’s not for the company?
Proud.
What if it’s personal?
Could you still do it?
Proud, that’s enough.
Tangkwa, I want you to help Proud
with something.
Ooh, I was just craving this.
I know you like it.
How do you know that?
You like Japanese food, don’t you?
Tonight I’ll make you
Nanban fried chicken.
But Pu from next door just called me.
She said the repairs are finished already.
Eh?
Didn’t they say it would take two weeks?
Mm.
Apparently they got a repair slot
sooner than expected.
I was actually planning
to move my stuff back today too.
I don’t want to trouble you any longer.
Hey, no. It’s no big deal.
I’ll drive you back.
Mm.
Then I’ll go shower first,
and I’ll come out quick
so I can eat tonkatsu.
This repair guy is really meticulous.
I came to supervise every single day.
From what I can see, it looks fine now.
It just needs a little cleaning.
Thank you so much.
No worries. It’s nothing.
By the way, you two are both so pretty.
Are you dating?
Uh, no.
We’re coworkers.
If you were dating,
you’d make such a cute couple.
Ah, I should get going now.
Pu!
Yes?
Behind you.
Um…
What’s this hole?
Right? I have no idea how that got there.
But it looks like it was made by
a tool or something.
Well, the repair guy already left too.
How about this?
You two just stay here for now,
and I’ll bring something
to patch it up later.
Alright?
Pu.
You can still contact
the repair guy, right?
If you don’t hurry and contact him now
and he disappears
without taking responsibility,
then you’ll be the one responsible.
Pu is so tricky. She has so many layers.
I can’t even tell
if she’s a person or a dragon fruit.
Come on, at least she agreed.
So what are you going to do now?
Guess I’ll have to stay with you
a little longer.
I’m sorry for bothering you again.
Of course.
It’s really not a problem.
Mm.
Hm?
And if there’s anything
that makes you uncomfortable,
just tell me, okay?
I don’t want things to feel awkward.
Okay.
If there’s anything, I’ll let you know.
And one more thing…
I don’t want you to think
I moved in just because of sex.
You overthink too much.
I never thought that at all.
Even if we’re just friends with benefits,
if you’re having a hard time,
of course I’ll help you.
I’m not obsessed with that, you know.
Mm.
Uh…
Are you not okay?
Can we go do it in bed?
My back hurts.
There, there.
Come on, let’s do it in bed.
Go on, hurry.
Go.
Ow.
What? What is it?
Well…
Bas, just say it.
New met with the client
at that new spa place, right?
Yeah. So?
So I checked who else was there
that day besides us.
Hurry up.
Here.
THANK YOU FOR USING OUR SERVICE.
Lal’s face is shocked as hell.
It’s the same as mine.
Lal, you also didn’t think
it was Wine, right?!
Wine— I mean,
she might’ve just gone there for the spa.
You’re way too nice, Lal.
Even though you two don’t get along,
you’re still defending her.
But isn’t it too much of a coincidence
that she went the same day as New?
Well, the world is full of coincidences.
But they used to kind of see each other.
Maybe they’ve got
some secret deal together.
No, that’s too far.
Or maybe they got back together.
If it’s Wine, that’d make perfect sense
because accounting can access
client contract information.
Exactly. And think about it.
If they’re “nothing,”
why would they go
to an onsen spa together?
Maybe it really is nothing.
You two went there together too,
didn't you?
Yeah, true.
Fine, maybe they’re not dating.
But Wine is still suspicious
for going to the spa on the same day
New met with the client.
But don’t worry.
We’ll go snoop around for you.
I mean, we’ll dig more info for you.
Sure thing.
This is way more fun than working.
Alright, alright.
Keep digging for information then.
Got it.
What?!
My phone.
Ah, damn it!
Seriously?
Why did you accept
the spa’s follow request?
I didn’t accept it.
They messaged asking for proof
that I’d posted the story,
so I sent them a screenshot.
I didn’t think they’d post it like that.
Right now, Numnim and the others think
you and New have something going on.
What?!
If those two find out
we were together that day,
we’re screwed.
But there’s something even worse.
My team suspects
New is the traitor inside our company.
What?
We think someone with access
to client contracts has been helping him.
And since you went to the spa
the same day as him,
now you’re the most suspicious person.
That’s even worse than
people finding out about us.
Exactly.
Right now, the best thing we can do
is prove that New really has been using
company secrets to steal clients,
and that you haven’t been helping him.
Is that really enough?
Thank you so much.
Here.
Thank you.
Once your contract expires,
please don’t forget about me, okay?
Of course.
Thank you.
Hey, do you know how hard it was
to land this client?
I think we need to renegotiate
our percentage split.
New, I’m already giving you a huge cut.
But our risks aren’t equal.
I still work at the company.
I could get caught anytime.
Seriously? You always do this.
Damn it.
Lal!
Hey!
You checked my calendar and free slots
just to secretly follow me here?
I just found out
that besides being in sales,
you’re also a detective.
I also just found out
that besides being in PR,
you’re also in sales.
Let’s talk numbers.
If the benefits line up,
then it’s a win-win situation
for both of us.
But you violated business confidentiality
and caused millions in damages.
No amount of money would be enough.
Lal, think carefully.
Even if I get punished or fired,
what do you gain from this?
Wouldn’t it be better
if we came to an agreement instead?
So this is
how you’ve always handled things, huh?
You’re good at this,
but I’m not falling for it.
Lal, wait!
Let’s talk this through first.
Do you know what the client
who switched to the competitor said?
They said that besides you,
no one on your sales team
is actually competent.
I think you know
your team’s been dragging you down.
They made mistakes,
and arrived hungover
before meeting the client.
And if you report this to management,
your team might get dragged into this too.
They could be blamed
for failing to keep the clients’ trust.
Who knows?
Maybe the whole team will get fired.
How about this, Lal?
Do you want to work
for the competitor instead?
I think they want someone talented as you.
You’d earn more money,
and your team wouldn’t get affected.
This sounds fair, doesn’t it?
Hey, Lal!
Wait! Lal!
Come on, let’s talk first.
Wow, his gaslighting skills are insane.
I thought he was a freaking lighter.
How can someone make people
feel guilty that easily?
Basic PR skills.
They’re good with words.
So what are you going to do now?
Report him to HR immediately?
Definitely.
But I want to handle a few things first.
Like what?
He said clients switched to competitors
because my team isn’t strong enough.
So I want to reorganize the team first,
talk to the juniors,
and strengthen things up.
That way, if management calls me in,
the others won’t get blamed too.
And there’s another thing.
I think Winnie, who just left the company,
probably still has company files.
I want to go through
and clear out the documents too.
Eh?
What about people suspecting me?
I’ll talk to the team about that.
But honestly, I’m still not sure
whether only Numnim and Bas
know about me and New
or if other people in the company
know too.
Mm. I understand.
As for your team,
let me say this
as someone who’s also a team leader.
I understand that you love your team.
But personal relationships
as coworkers are one thing,
and doing what’s right professionally
is another.
If you can’t handle this yourself,
then HR should handle it instead.
Hey!
Hey, what’s going on?
What are you looking for?
Lal, the company credit card is missing.
Huh?!
How did it go missing?
I just gave it to her
to pay for a client seminar room,
but she accidentally dropped it somewhere.
What should we do, Lal?
Call accounting to freeze the card now.
Freeze it, freeze it.
Lal, do you have something
you should tell me about?
I understand you’re new here,
so you probably don’t realize that
what you’re doing might be covering up
employee misconduct in the company.
I’m not trying to cover anything up.
I just wanted to handle it myself first.
But aren’t some things
beyond your capability?
I understand that,
but I just wanted to give people a chance.
Give a chance to someone
who’s stealing from the company?
Isn't that accusation a bit too strong?
My team member hasn’t even—
Who exactly are you referring to, Jantra?
New, from PR.
I know you’ve already found out
he violated company rules
and helped a competitor.
Why didn’t you report this immediately,
even though it directly affects your team?
I’m sorry.
I may have been slow to react.
But how did you even know about this?
You don’t need to know about that.
But a team leader covering up
another team leader’s misconduct…
let’s make sure this is the last time.
Yes.
Do you really need to leave today?
Didn’t you tell management yourself
you couldn’t work with me anymore?
I’m not making excuses,
but I didn’t report you.
Lal, listen up.
It’s true the company
wants talented people,
but they keep the ones
who know how to behave.
Someone like you,
who keeps making enemies,
simply doesn’t know how to behave.
Stop gaslighting me already.
I’m not the one
who reported this, seriously.
If it wasn’t you, then it’s even worse.
That means someone around you
can’t be trusted.
Oh, no.
You trust them, but they don’t trust you.
Why the f*ck are you looking at me?!
Who got fired? New or you?
What Lal said is right.
I’ve been the weak link in the team.
I keep messing things up,
so clients don’t renew contracts.
If you want to punish me, go ahead.
Wow, now you’re dragging drama into this.
She hasn’t even scolded you yet.
I’ll take full responsibility…
for the credit card issue
if anything happens.
You can deduct it from my salary.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Lal, the accounting team
gave the card to me first.
Deduct it from my salary instead.
What? Why are you acting like a hero now?
Your salary is as tiny as an amoeba.
You’re still offering
to let them deduct it?
I lost it,
so I should take responsibility.
Come on. We’re a team.
Shouldn’t we take responsibility together?
Anyway, Lal, just deduct my salary.
Oh, seriously, dude?!
Alright, enough.
There’s nothing to worry about the card.
I called housekeeping.
They found the card in the restroom.
I already got it back.
But next time,
promise me you’ll be more careful.
And if you lose a card again,
call and freeze it right way,
so there won’t be any issues.
As for the client not renewing with us…
(Yes, Lal.)
(I’ll renew for another 2 years.)
(The competitor offered a better price,
so I hesitated,)
(but I prefer your team’s service.)
(Your admins and team are nice.)
(They’re always helpful.)
Yes. Thank you so much.
As a team leader, I always ask myself
what matters most for my team.
And I’ve found the answer.
I’m not looking for someone
who never makes mistakes.
I want someone that takes responsibility,
both for their mistakes
and their successes.
If they do well, they get praised.
But if they do wrong, they must own it.
That’s the team I want.
I’m sorry, Lal.
I’ll try not to be a burden
or a weak link to the team anymore.
I’ll improve myself.
Fix your shitty attitude first.
Okay, enough. Stop crying.
You’re back. Are you tired?
Yeah.
Traffic was terrible.
I saw. Have you eaten yet?
Wine,
did you tell HR about New?
Yes, I did.
Why did you do that?
I told you I wanted to handle it myself.
I thought if we delayed it,
New would keep stealing clients.
I didn’t want you to be affected
by this issue any longer.
You already have all the evidence too.
You’re right,
but this also involves my team.
I wanted to deal with it internally first.
But I didn’t report anything
about your team.
But you should’ve waited for me
instead of going ahead on your own.
Lal, you have your own team
to take care of,
and I have mine too.
If management finds anything unusual,
my team will be one of the first
to get investigated.
I had to follow company regulations.
So this is really just
about protecting yourself, right?
Weren’t you the one saying
you were worried I’d get in trouble?
That’s too harsh.
We’re both angry right now.
We shouldn’t talk for now.
Hello, Proud?
Yes, let’s meet at the same place.
I’m heading out.
(You’re still not back yet?)
You’re back. Are you tired?
Damn, did you make this for me?
Hello, Wine, well…
(This is Proud.)
(Wine is too drunk
to talk to you right now.)
-Wine.
-Huh?
Let’s go home. Can you stand?
Yeah…
Let’s go.
Hey, why did you get here so fast?
You were flooring it or what?
You know you can’t handle alcohol well,
so why did you drink so much?
Let’s go.
You probably know
why Wine drank so much.
I’m just kidding.
I let her try my cocktail.
I forgot it was really strong.
She passed out right away.
She gets drunk just from the smell.
Would you like to drink with me, Lal?
Speak clearly
before you go inviting someone else.
You actually didn’t have to come.
I was going to take her home.
It’s fine. I’ll take her.
Excuse me.
Didn’t you say you two weren’t close?
Well, we just happen
to live near each other.
But calling her this late
makes it seem like you’re pretty close.
It was about work.
At 1 AM?
It was urgent.
Are you two dating?
Oh.
No.
We’re not.
I figured.
Someone like you
isn’t even Wine’s type anyway.
We’re not dating… yet.
It’s hot.
Ow…
Wine.
-Huh?
-Let's cover up first.
It’s hot.
Here.
Let me wipe you down first.
I’m sorry for telling Jantra.
But I only did it because
I was really worried about you.
I know.
Let’s talk about it tomorrow.
But I’m sad.
You said I did it for myself.
I’m sorry.
I spoke too harshly.
I’m still not over it.
Then what do I have to do
for you to forgive me?
Come on, comfort me.
Comfort you?
Mm.
-How do I even do that?
-Like this. There, there.
There, there… okay?
Proud, what are you doing here?
From today onward,
we’ll probably be seeing each other
every day, Tangkwa.
I know you don’t like me,
but this is work.
I hope you can separate
personal feelings from work.
Don’t worry.
I can separate them.
What do you want me to help with?
Tangkwa, do you know who Wine is dating?
Are you making rice porridge?
It smells so good.
Mm.
Sit down. I’ll serve you.
Did Proud call and wake you up
to pick me up last night?
I’m sorry about that.
Oh, I was still working at that time.
I was still awake.
Wine.
Between you and Proud,
there’s nothing more than
a senior-junior relationship, right?
I just want to be sure.
Even though we’re just
friends with benefits,
I won’t feel comfortable
if you’re in talking stage with someone
or dating someone.
With Proud?
I really just see her as a younger sister.
And what about Proud?
Does she see you as an older sister too?
She probably used to feel something,
but I already cleared things up
with her honestly.
There’s nothing between us anymore.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Don’t worry about it.
Even if Proud and I were together,
someone like me
would never cheat on my partner
with a friends-with-benefits situation.
Mm.
Wine.
I’m sorry
for speaking too harshly earlier.
I know you were just worried about me
and the company.
I’m sorry too…
for not discussing things with you first.
Lal,
maybe we should talk about work
less from now on.
Sure.
I started it this time anyway.
I’ll be more careful next time.
Actually, I just don’t like it when we fight.
If there’s something we don’t understand,
we should just talk it through properly.
I just want to stay like this with you.
Let’s be each other’s safe space.
Wine.
The rule of friends-with-benefits
is not to talk about personal things.
But I want to talk to you about everything
because I feel really comfortable
telling you everything,
and I want you to feel comfortable
telling me everything too.
Of course.
I want it that way too.
We don’t have to follow the same rules
as everyone else, right?
As long as we understand each other,
that’s enough.
Let’s just be friends with benefits,
exclusively for the two of us.
Mm.
She kept saying,
“Wine is so toxic and annoying.”
This is Wine.
Our company outing activities
are starting now!
Wow, she is even more serious than me.
Something feels off.
Awww. I’m shipping them.
Whoever has the most photos
on their phone wins.
I think I want to try loving you, Wine.
I like you, Wine.