MkvDrama.net
Zen.
I love you.
Me too.
I only want Ryo.
It has to be Ryo.
Sorry.
I've... I've reached my limit.
I was just...
I think I was dreaming about the past.
Hm?
We've really grown up, haven't we?
What's that about? So random.
Hey...
Yeah?
When I was falling asleep
last night, I was a little scared.
Of what?
That us becoming a couple
was all just a dream.
That I'd wake up in the morning...
and you wouldn't be in my arms.
Are you still half-asleep?
Idiot.
I don't think...
I can ever let you go.
Well, can't be helped. I guess
I'll just have to make you happy.
You've got good taste, choosing me.
Right back at you.
Don't...
Stop that.
Morning.
No matter how you slice
it, I won this round, right?
The only thing you won was the KPI.
In terms of profit, it was
a landslide victory for me.
All you did was
put on a routine, large-scale event.
But I brought in all new clients.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
You just don't get it.
The number of attendees
was double last year's.
Isn't that just because you hired
a famous band to draw a crowd?
That's playing on easy mode.
Uh, okay, that's enough, you two.
What?
Yes, sorry.
I can't believe a socially awkward
guy like you could earn an artist's trust.
Huh?
I've had no problem with it so far.
Speaking of which.
You only won back the top spot once.
Are you sure you should
be getting this cocky?
What?
Listen, the competition was
about the KPI from the start.
So I won.
Got it?
I refuse to accept that.
Pretty amazing, right?
Yes, very.
I was just thinking Yotsuya-san
was back from his business trip.
And he comes back to this.
They really fight like little kids.
Yeah.
Especially since they're
both so brilliant at work.
I should get back.
Just one more minute.
- That's enough.
- Ow.
How many times have I told you?
I want to focus on work
when I'm at the office.
I've been away on business.
We've barely seen each other.
A little moment can't hurt, can it?
This has nothing to do with your trip.
I said not at the office.
I've told you before.
If this keeps up, I won't be
able to concentrate on my work.
Then when we get home
tonight, we can continue...
Because of how you just
acted, tonight's canceled.
Just kidding.
Don't you complain, even if
we're up late tonight, okay?
"Fake Fact Lips"
(Episode 6: The "After All" Is Unnecessary)
Yotsuya-san, I've been
looking all over for you.
Sorry, sorry.
Senshin Publisher just sent
over the production schedule.
But it seems a little different
from the one we made before.
Oh, didn't the client
send an email about some changes?
That must be it.
Huh? Let me check.
- Yotsuya.
- Yes?
About the meeting this evening.
I'd still like you to be there.
Huh?
Uh, it starts at five, right?
Would it be okay if I'm a little late?
Not a problem at all.
That's a huge help. Thank you.
Yotsuya-san, excuse me.
I found the email.
See? Told you.
Yotsuya-san.
The client wants to add a few
more options for the brand colors.
Ah, of course.
I knew this would happen.
So I've already made a list.
Um... tell them we can get it
to them by the end of the day.
Okay, I'll let them know.
Oh, by the way.
Tonight.
Saeki-san from Gaisei
company invited me out for drinks.
Would you be able to join me?
Saeki-san, huh?
Yes.
He specifically told me to
bring you along, Yotsuya-san.
- I'll pass.
- What?
Because if he gets a hold of you,
you won't get home until morning.
That's why I don't want to go alone!
If it's just for drinks, you don't need me.
Look, isn't that guy from your year?
I refuse.
Why not?
Because there's a game I want
to play as soon as I get home.
So heartless.
Please don't leave me to fend for myself.
He's your client.
I'll make it up to you, I promise.
- No.
- Why?
Because someone's waiting for me at home.
Someone at home?
What?!
Yotsuya-san, you're seeing someone?
Give us the details!
What is it? Don't all crowd around.
- Go on, shoo.
- Since when?
Where did you meet?
What are they like?
Is it someone from the company?
From the Secretarial department?
Or General Affairs?
From another company?
Are they older than you?
Younger?
What's their type?
So annoying!
Someone respectable and cute, I bet.
You...
Don't say weird things at the office.
What's the big deal?
I just said I have a partner.
That may be true, but...
It's not like anyone
would guess I'm with Zen.
Hey.
Let me finish my drink first.
Stop messing around.
Again?
I've been holding back for so long.
Then you need to hold
back when you're at the office.
I was wrong about that.
It's been so long
since I saw you, I just...
No excuses.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful.
If I can't focus on work because of you,
then we'll have less time
to spend together, won't we?
Zen.
You're trying to make time for me, too?
Of course.
I've also felt bad for being so busy
and neglecting you.
After all, we are a couple, aren't we?
The "after all" is unnecessary.
I can't hold back much longer.
Just let me enjoy my drink a little longer.
If I let you enjoy your drink,
you'll just pass out right away.
Well, that depends on
your performance, Ryo.
Huh?
What did you say?
I'll do my best, so hurry up and drink.
I get it, calm down.
Sit down first.
- I'll do my best.
- I know you will.
So put your clothes back on first.
We're just going to take
them off again anyway.
- Stand up.
- Oh, honestly.
Okay, okay, I get it.
Come on, your hand.
- Let's go.
- Seriously.
Don't you "seriously" me.
Still awake?
Barely.
So, this quarter...
Zen won, right?
Yeah.
Is there anything you want me to do?
Uh...
I don't think so.
What?
How boring.
Competing with someone who isn't even
that upset about losing...
is pretty boring for me, too.
You're the one who came up
with the rule in the first place.
I never had anything I
particularly wanted you to do.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Because no matter the outcome,
it's a reward for you either way, right?
That's true.
You know me so well.
Ah, but if I had to say something...
Hm?
I want to know more about you.
Huh?
Ryo, you know a lot about me.
But I know almost nothing
about you from college.
That's because you never asked.
Also...
I'm also still hung up on you
saying you like sleeping with men.
No, that's not it.
I was just bluffing.
I'm sure that's not true.
I don't mean to bring up old stuff, but...
This whole arrangement
is skewed in your favor.
It's not fair at all.
But...
There are so many things I want Zen to do.
If I didn't do it this way, you
never would have agreed.
I didn't have a choice.
What else do you want me to do?
Hmm...
Make you list 10 things you like about me.
Who could even come up with that?
See? Again, it only benefits you.
Then think of something that
would make me uncomfortable.
Ah.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I just thought of something
completely unrelated.
What is it?
What's this?
Rid Randal?!
Why?
It's nothing. I got them from a work event.
- Want to go together?
- Huh?
Did I ever tell you I like them?
Oh, really?
Huh? It's just a coincidence?!
Yeah.
Seriously?
I've been a huge fan
of theirs since college.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
They've gotten so popular lately.
It's impossible to get concert
tickets, even through the lottery.
I didn't win the lottery back
then, so I'd already given up.
I can't believe you managed to get tickets.
They were a thank-you gift
for helping with a dispute.
Seriously?
Wow, that's amazing.
It's been so long since I've been to one.
You know, this is our
first proper date, isn't it?
If this is a date, it's
going to be a blast.
The energy is going to be insane.
Rid Randal.
Actually, I tried to
book them for our event.
But their schedule was completely full.
They're my absolute favorite right now.
Lately, I've been singing
Rid Randal at karaoke.
Rid Randal, Rid Randal...
I just can't stop.
Okay.
Okay, I think the file
should be shareable soon.
Okay.
- Okay.
- The documents just arrived.
Yes, I'll send it to you now.
Okay, goodbye.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh, by the way.
How's that proposal coming along?
Ah, well, there's about 80% left.
Huh? You've only done 20%?
Ah, I misspoke... Um...
I've finished 80%, so
there's only about 20% left.
I see. Show it to me when you're done.
Okay, I'll finish it right away.
No rush. Take your time.
Yes, sir.
Do you have plans later?
Nothing in particular.
Are you going on a date?
Huh?
First Yotsuya-san, and now you're
going on a date too, Shido-san?
What if I am?
What?!
Shido-san.
Are you even competing with Yotsuya-san
over who has a girlfriend?
I would never do something like that.
But the timing is a little
too perfect, don't you think?
It's just a coincidence.
You're even busier with work than we are.
How did you get a girlfriend?
Please, teach me your ways.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
We broke up.
Huh?
Seriously?
Weren't you together for about three years?
Yeah, since we were students.
Work has been too busy lately.
It's amazing how
quickly you can drift apart.
I hate to admit it, but
that's pretty common.
Yeah.
You should be careful too, Shido-san.
The time you get to
spend together is precious.
I know.
More importantly, Higashino.
I said no rush,
but get back to work.
Yes! Sorry!
That's right, Higashino.
No need to rush, just hurry up.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Okay.
Okay, it's done.
Shido-san.
Yeah?
Could you please check this?
Ah, one second.
Yeah, just swap this part
and this part, and it'll be fine.
Got it.
Thank you very much.
- I'll be heading out then.
- See you.
Hello, this is Shido.
Ah, thank you for your help the other day.
Yes.
I see.
(A client called me in last minute. I probably
won't make it until after the show. Sorry.)
Yotsuya-san?
Ah, Shido.
You actually made it.
Sorry, I missed it.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
By the way...
Oh, right, right.
I just ran into
Kiritani-san and her friend.
Yeah.
We bumped into each other at
the entrance. It was such a surprise.
Oh, so that's what happened.
- It's been a while.
- It has.
Long time no see.
Huh?
Could it be Shido-san?
Huh? What do you mean?
Ah, Yotsuya-san just mentioned
that someone couldn't make it today.
We thought it might
have been his girlfriend.
No, that's not it.
It's a shame you couldn't be
here for the show, Shido-san.
The chorus of the fourth
song was incredible, wasn't it?
- Totally incredible.
- Right?
You know, that song from the album.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- The intro was completely different.
- Different.
- The arrangement was amazing.
- Amazing.
- I know, right?
- Huh, you noticed?
Well...
Don't tell me you're a fan too, Shido-san?
Huh?
Oh, no, I don't know them at all.
It's just that Yotsuya seems to
have been a fan for a long time.
Yeah.
She's a huge fan too.
We had a great time
talking with Yotsuya-san.
And they both know even
more about them than I do.
Is that so?
This was my first time really
talking with Yotsuya-san.
He's a really interesting person.
That guy didn't say anything rude, did he?
Of course not. Not at all.
He even apologized, saying...
that you were the
one who got the tickets.
Oh, I see.
By the way, since we're all here...
Want to go for a drink later?
Oh, sure...
What do you think?
Ah...
Um...
- Hey, but...
- Oh, sorry.
Oh, no, it's really okay.
But maybe next time.
Let's do it again sometime.
Yeah, you're right.
Shido-san, you have to
come with us next time.
Okay.
I'll do my homework before then.
Okay, well, we'll get going then.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Matsushita-san, the
one with Kiritani-san...
is hilarious.
During the most hype song of the concert...
she suddenly started headbanging.
I teased her, like, "This
isn't that kind of song."
And Kiritani-san was just stunned.
The look on her face was priceless.
Zen?
Hey? Zen?
What's wrong? Are you mad?
I'm not mad.
You sure don't look like it.
What's wrong?
Huh?
You're not... jealous, are you?
What?
No way.
You totally are.
Is it because I was having
fun talking with them?
Give me a break.
It's not that.
Honestly, I didn't think
you'd get so jealous.
Whatever. I'm just a petty guy.
I'm going home.
If that's the case, then I'm sorry.
I'm not mad at you.
Huh?
I... I can't believe I didn't know
what kind of music you like.
No, that doesn't matter at all...
I thought I wouldn't care
no matter who you were friendly with.
You're nice to everyone.
Such a charmer.
See? You are mad at me.
No.
It's just...
Getting jealous over
something so trivial at this point.
I can't even control my own emotions.
I feel so pathetic.
Let's just call it a day.
I'll probably calm down after a while.
There's no way I'm leaving you like this.
Morning.
Yo, Shido-kun.
Long time no see.
Futami?
Futami... you...
(Next episode)
(Episode 7: Let Me In On This Match!)
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
Futami's transfer was so sudden.
Now that he's back...
Looks like things are
about to get lively again.
Hey, Shido~
I look forward to working with you again.
Yeah, same here.
You two are still in touch?
You're still as close as ever.
We even go on trips
together, just the two of us.
Trips?
Let's have a drink, just the two of us.
Why are you going this far?
Do you really have to
make this a competition?
Because I'm a better match
for Yotsuya-san than you are.
You're staying the night, right?
MkvDrama.net