The food here is actually pretty good.
Yeah, not bad.
Can you pour me some water?
Eating at a place like this,
with zero atmosphere...
It's actually kind of relaxing.
Thanks.
You know...
Right now,
I wish time would just stand still.
If only Fukami
felt the same way,
that would be nice.
Want some?
- I want this one.
- No, not that one.
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
(Episode 8)
A transfer...?
Actually, the Hokkaido branch reached out.
Sales are down over there,
so they want to send someone talented.
Hokkaido, huh?
Plus, it's a promotion to section chief.
It'll be great for your career.
It's pretty far away, though.
Kaji-kun,
surely there's someone
you'd hate to leave behind.
Ah.
It's not really like that.
I think it's a good chance to settle down.
A lot of people get married when
they transfer. Just look around.
It's hard to find the
right timing otherwise.
At our company,
unless there are special circumstances,
you can't really turn down a transfer.
Kaji-san.
The new product catalogs are here.
Oh.
- These are for the expo. I'll take them.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
The most important thing
is what you've built at this company.
If it were me,
I'd never say no.
Who doesn't want a promotion?
[Signs hanging in the back showing
Kaji being the top salesperson]
Lately,
we've been meeting every week we're free.
Today, we're just chilling at
his place making dumplings.
But...
to Fukami,
it doesn't seem like we're actually dating.
To a guy like him,
what does "dating"
even mean?
Ah.
I don't get it,
but I want to try to understand.
But for that to happen,
we need to be close to each other...
Hey, you're terrible at this.
You're putting in too much filling.
It all tastes the same anyway.
What do you mean "the same"?
Huh?
I have to tell him.
About the transfer.
If I go,
what's going to happen to us?
It's not like we're dating.
And it's not like
we've made any promises about the future.
Doing it in the kitchen is a bit...
That's not what I meant!
It's out.
Yeah.
I don't want to let go.
I can't let go.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
You're being really clingy today...
Hey.
Can we go again?
We're all out of condoms.
Then never mind.
It's fine.
I've never tried it before,
but let's give it a shot.
Kaji.
Tell me if it's too much.
This...
So fast.
What should I do?
Like this.
This is like porn.
We have terrible chemistry.
True.
It's warm and feels a bit naughty,
but the pleasure isn't that different.
What are you, a sex sommelier?
You idiot.
Honestly.
You seem fine.
I thought you were feeling sick again.
Um...
Fukami.
My sister's pregnant with her second.
She's due next year.
Sorry.
Did you have something to say?
I forgot what it was.
What would Fukami say?
If I...
wasn't around anymore?
I heard from the manager
that Kaji-san is transferring.
Kaji-san is transferring?
He's so talented.
Why would Sales let him go?
But the manager said it's a promotion.
If it's a promotion,
he can't really say no.
I'll miss him.
(Network connection under repair)
Fukami.
The internet's out.
It's resetting?
It's back up now.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling okay?
Is anyone still here?
It's getting late.
Wait, is no one here?
If we don't finish this,
we won't be able to work.
Hey, we're at the office.
Are you out of your mind?
Maybe.
Wait.
Shower.
No.
You're acting really weird today.
I said wait.
You're transferring
somewhere far away, aren't you?
You...
How?
Where did you hear that?
To you,
I might just be one of many.
But I only do this with you.
Right now, you're the only one for me too.
Then shouldn't you have told me first?
I haven't told anyone.
About the transfer.
I couldn't say anything
until it was official.
I don't want to hear your excuses.
You're the one leaving.
What do you actually want?
Just tell me the truth.
Don't think you can play it cool with me.
I...
don't have the confidence.
With the distance...
and the physical stuff...
If we lose the one thing
keeping us together,
it'll never work.
Someone like me,
who wasn't even loved by his parents...
(To Aki-kun)
Wait, what are you talking about?
Your parents...
That's not true at all.
You wouldn't understand.
Looking at you and your sister,
it's obvious you had a great family.
You were raised with so much love.
Kaji-san, please get
along with my brother.
It's like a constant reminder
that I'm not like you guys.
It hurts.
I'm the one who hurt you.
No.
- That's not it.
- I've been happy.
Doing all those things with you.
But if being with me hurts you...
Fukami.
No, I don't want this.
I don't want to be apart.
Don't leave me.
I've had enough too.
I'm tired of you messing with me.
This is perfect.
You're transferring.
It's been fun,
but I didn't know how to end it.
I'm ready to try someone new anyway.
Are you serious?
With your looks,
you'll find someone else in no time.
Let's end this...
between us.
(Preview)
He's someone important to you, right?
That guy...
isn't happy with me.
Thank you for everything at HQ.
Are you just looking for one last lay?
Idiot.
I'll be waiting for you.
Their final night...
begins now.