Where did this brat come from?
How dare you steal from
the Crown Prince's camp?
Beat him!
Beat him to death!
For stealing!
I'll kill you!
Wait!
Greetings, Crown Prince.
Some beggar from who knows where...
sneaked in here to steal steamed buns.
He deserves to be beaten to death.
Come here.
Thank you.
Thank you, Crown
Prince, for saving my life.
Please take me in.
I'll do anything as long as you
give me food to eat.
I'll do whatever it takes.
What's your name?
Why?
I've already gotten rid of
my third and fourth brothers,
but Father still won't pass the
Crown Prince position to me.
Your Highness,
eat something sweet,
and your mood won't be so gloomy.
Do you think you can please
me with such petty tricks?
I'm an orphan.
I've endured all kinds of hardships
to survive since I was a child.
I've suffered so much.
But you took me in.
From now on,
I'm willing to live for you.
As long as it makes you happy,
I'll do anything.
Your Highness,
Have some hangover soup.
I'm new to the imperial city.
No one knows who I am.
I want to transfer from being a gate guard
to the Fifth Prince's Yunhe Palace
and spy on his every move for you.
If he has any improper ambitions
for the Crown Prince position,
I will report to you immediately.
Very well.
Since you have the heart for it,
then stay by Yin Qi's side.
Do a good job.
I won't let you down, Your Highness.
When you ascend to the Eastern Palace,
I...
will be able to...
return to your side openly.
"Journey With You"
(Episode 5)
I wonder,
could you give me a guarantee
to make me believe
that you're truly willing to
help me achieve my wishes?
It's so late.
Where have you been?
I thought
you trusted me
and wouldn't associate
with Yin Zhou anymore.
But why
are you still going to him?
I'm just a lowly hostage.
I can't make my own decisions.
It's all because.
I have to follow the orders of you princes.
Yanzhi,
let me ask you,
no matter how hard I try to keep you,
you'll still work for Yin Zhou?
I'm not only a hostage in the Daxing Palace
but also a prince of Talhan.
Yin Zhou
is very likely to be the
future emperor of Daxing.
Working for him
what's wrong with that?
If you're determined not to turn back,
then
we're no longer on the same path.
Then, Fifth Prince,
farewell.
Could it be that they've already...
I'm the only one who can
make the decisions for you.
It seems A Qi has really misunderstood
my relationship with Yin Zhou.
Well, never mind.
Your Highness,
haven't you been resting properly lately?
This wound keeps reopening after healing.
Don't you want this arm anymore?
What has Yanzhi been doing lately?
I haven't seen him around for a while.
There's definitely something
going on between them.
Your Highness should
take care of your body.
Nowadays,
our relationship with Talhan is uncertain.
You're being so open
and sincere with the prince,
but in the future,
if something goes wrong,
how will you handle it?
Nanxing,
thank you for your kindness,
but
I've been doing something
with Yanzhi lately
that can't be known by outsiders.
Don't worry,
I'll definitely rest and recover.
Your Highness,
Well?
Did you follow him?
Forgive me, Your Highness.
I still couldn't find out
the prince's whereabouts today.
Also,
Duan Yi said the Crown Prince
has also been missing all day lately.
I see.
You may leave now.
This subordinate takes leave.
Your Highness,
Lately, you've faced dangers
several times for the prince.
Have you ever thought
that he might be someone
who could bring you danger at any time?
But
he's also
the most special one.
Your Highness must rest properly lately.
This wound was poisoned,
and it's hard to heal.
If it keeps reopening
like this, it'll easily fester.
This...
is what Concubine Chen
always missed—Longjing cakes.
She always said the cooks in the
palace didn't make them authentically.
You've always said since you were a child
that you wanted to taste
authentic Jiangnan cuisine.
Come and try it. Is it good?
The prince has to take
care of so many princes.
It's so tiring for you.
You still remembered what I said before.
It cant be easy.
Come and take a walk with me.
I thought
we had cleared the air
that night at Zhou Bridge.
But why
do you come close to me one moment
and then distance yourself the next?
A Qi,
I...
I'm sorry.
I was too impulsive that day.
One day,
you'll marry your own princess consort.
I shouldn't be an obstacle to you.
Didn't you know I was
a prince from the start?
I'm not afraid.
What are you afraid of?
Yanzhi,
I've never asked you
for any promises.
I just hope you won't push me away anymore.
Just this small request.
Can't you grant it?
The gap in our statuses
is like heaven and earth.
I can't just ignore everything
and stand by your side without a care.
Enough!
You're sure I won't do anything to you,
so you keep hurting me without restraint.
We really can't seem to communicate.
Did Yin Qi and Pei Yanzhi
really have a falling out?
Could it be just childish temper tantrums,
and they'll be inseparable
again in a few days?
This subordinate truly
heard Yin Qi say harsh words to Pei Yanzhi.
Even if it's not a complete breakup,
it's still serious.
I don't care about their
closeness or distance whatsoever.
But seeing Yin Qi
upset because of Pei Yanzhi.
I am quite pleased.
I heard from De Shun
that Father is hosting a
banquet at Yanbo Tower tonight
and has invited Yin Qi and
Yin Heshu to accompany him.
This old fox.
He's been favoring Yin Qi lately
and ignoring me.
He wants to reprimand me like this.
Yanbo Tower.
Your Highness,
didn't you also arrange
to meet Pei Yanzhi and
Su He at Yanbo Tower?
Yanbo Tower
will be the stage
for Pei Yanzhi and Yin Qi
to have a complete falling out.
Yanbo Tower.
Yanbo Tower is very famous in Jiangnan.
The owner is very mysterious.
It's said that his businesses
are all over the Central Plains.
It seems Yanbo Tower
is connected to the Piaoxiang
Pavilion in the capital.
Yanzhi is acting so strangely today.
He must be meeting someone at Yanbo Tower.
Your Highness,
Then we...
Fifth Prince,
His Majesty instructed
this old servant to tell you
that he's hosting a banquet
at Yanbo Tower tonight
and has invited you and
Sixth Princess to attend.
Just the two of us siblings?
Yes.
His Majesty said Yanbo
Tower has beautiful scenery
and it was Concubine Chen's
favorite restaurant when she was alive.
So he only invited you and Sixth Princess.
Okay.
I understand.
You may leave now.
Yes.
This old servant takes leave.
Your Highness,
Why would the Emperor
invite you to Yanbo Tower alone?
Could he have found out something?
Judging by De Shun's demeanor,
Father is probably just
inviting us to Yanbo Tower
for a simple banquet.
Nothing else.
What about the person the
prince is secretly meeting?
No matter who it is tonight,
we must be extremely careful.
Duan Yong.
Come with me to Yanbo Tower.
Ziming.
Let him rest for the night.
Yes, Your Highness.
Oh well.
Take Ziming with us.
This chess piece arranged by Elder Brother
It's time to play its part.
Ziming?
How could it be?
It's really unexpected.
Treat him just like before.
Don't show any flaws.
Yes, Your Highness.
Farewell, sir.
Come in, sir.
Please sit here.
Senior.
Today, we'd like to use the
Jinling Spring private room.
We have important matters to discuss.
Okay.
Xianyue,
take them there.
Be careful.
My dear nephew.
You've suffered in Daxing all these years.
Now it's finally time
for you and I, uncle and
nephew, to take the stage.
Don't worry.
After things are done,
you'll have all the riches and honors.
You won't have to endure
humiliation anymore,
pretending to be a hostage.
Uncle is joking.
Riches and honors
are just fleeting clouds to me.
What I truly care about
is the rise and fall of our grasslands.
By the way,
the Fifth Prince
has been kind to me.
When the time comes,
I've agreed with the eldest prince
that after things are done,
he'll be allowed to live a
life of leisure and wealth.
A proud prince of the grasslands
can't be trapped by love and affection.
You should look further ahead.
If you really like
that fair-skinned prince of Daxing,
when the time comes,
just bring him back to the grasslands.
Uncle
approves.
In terms of great talent and strategy,
I definitely can't compare to you, Uncle.
The Crown Prince.
He'll come later.
He ordered me to entertain you well.
Please.
This meat from the Central Plains
is far inferior to ours
from the grasslands.
It seems Uncle has made up his mind
to assist the eldest prince
in achieving his goals.
The queen has a vast
network of power in the court.
She has deep roots.
If I become a core member
of the crown prince's faction,
there will definitely be
benefits for me in the future.
The crown prince
can give this Khan what I need.
Helping him ascend to the throne,
why wouldn't I help?
The Concubine Chen's
skill in playing the qin.
Heshu has learned a bit of it.
She’s somewhat decent.
Qi'er, do you know?
Your mother back then
also liked Yanbo Tower very much.
The way Sixth Princess
sits and plays the qin
reminds this old servant
of the Concubine Chen.
Father.
I've told you many times.
I'm now
just an ordinary wealthy merchant.
I'm used to it.
Father.
The scenery at Yanbo Tower is really nice.
It's different from the
bustle of the capital.
Jiangnan is small and elegant.
It's quite charming.
Here.
Let me toast you, Father.
Oh, Father.
I've heard that Yanbo Tower
has many seasonal Jiangnan dishes.
I'll go to the kitchen to take a look
and see what fresh dishes are available
so that Father can enjoy a delicious meal.
It's rare that you have such filial piety.
Go quickly.
Aunt,
you've been standing
here for quite a while.
Is the girl's piano
playing really that good?
The piece she's playing
lacks some of the freedom her mother had,
but adds a touch of playfulness.
You're not saying that
they are the children of your
old acquaintances, are you?
She...
Your Highness,
I just saw that
the young master entered a private room
opposite Yanbo Tower
with a foreigner,
presumably
to meet with his clansmen.
If I'm not mistaken,
that foreigner
is his uncle.
Yanzhi has been
working for Yin Zhou and Su He.
I tried to persuade him with kind words,
but I couldn't stop him.
Whether he lives or dies in the future
will have nothing to do with me.
Your Highness,
you and the young master
have had a ten-year friendship.
So what?
Hasn't he still been secretly working
for Yin Zhou behind my back?
Ziming,
from now on, you don't need to report
any news about Yanzhi and Yin Zhou to me.
It has nothing to do with me.
Father,
I've arranged everything.
Good.
Come.
Let's drink.
Dear guests,
I'm the owner of the Yanbo Tower.
I see that you distinguished
guests have extraordinary bearing.
From now on,
please take care of our business.
This is Jinlingchun presented by our shop.
Please have a taste.
Is it brewed by the wine shop
across from the Yanbo Tower?
Exactly.
This distinguished guest,
you look unfamiliar.
And your accent doesn't sound like
that of a Jiangnan person.
Yet you're so knowledgeable.
You must be a big shot who
has seen a lot of the world.
Back then, your mother
sat right in this seat,
playing the same tune that
Heshu just played on the qin.
I didn't expect that after
she finished the piece,
she picked up her wine cup
and took a sip of this Jinlingchun.
I never thought that
such a gentle Jiangnan woman
would have such a bold side.
In the blink of an eye,
it's been twenty years
since I first met your mother.
Look at your son and daughter.
They're so handsome and beautiful.
I bet your wife
must also be a great beauty.
We in Jiangnan
had a famous beauty
twenty years ago
named.
Su Tang'er.
What?
Do you know her?
I've heard that
she later entered the palace
and became an imperial concubine.
Such a heavenly beauty
is not someone a vulgar person like me
could ever get to know.
I think
you,
a woman,
can run such a big tavern so well.
You must be an outstanding person.
If the madam doesn't mind,
would you like to
have a drink with us tonight?
My two children
are also visiting
Jiangnan for the first time.
Since Yanbo Tower seems to
have a fateful connection with you,
I'll have a drink with you.
Good.
You're truly a heroine among women.
Come.
Sit down.
Let's drink slowly.
Thank you for your kind offer.
But my little shop
has a lot of things to take care of.
I'll take my leave first.
Has Father taken a fancy to this madam?
Don't talk nonsense.
I think this madam is
definitely not simple.
Why?
Don't worry about that for now.
As your elder brother,
I'll give you a task.
Father,
Such a nice place as Jiangnan,
and this is the first time
you've brought us here.
You should be punished
with this cup of wine, right?
Okay, okay, okay.
I deserve the punishment.
This cup
is from your daughter to you.
You've been so good to mother and us.
You're the best father in the world.
Come on.
Since Jinlingchun tastes so good,
of course we should have another cup.
You.
Always teasing your father.
By the way,
Aruna is also fourteen
years old now, right?
Is she doing well at uncle's place?
She's doing great.
Don't worry.
It looks like
she's approaching
the age to get married.
I've already found a
suitable candidate for her.
The Khan of the western grasslands,
Urhtu.
Isn't he almost sixty years old?
Even if uncle wants
to win over their tribe,
he shouldn't make Aruna
marry that old man.
I don't agree with this.
Your elder brother is incompetent.
The whole Talhan tribe
has to rely on me to take care of things.
Fengsun,
You've been living a
peaceful life in Daxing.
You've gotten used to it.
Have you forgotten that on the grasslands,
one has to fight to survive?
You.
The Jinlingchun is right across the way.
Back then,
your mother and I
often came here to buy wine.
Khan, let me go have a look.
After all these years,
I wonder if there have been any changes.
This bridge,
your mother and I
used to walk across it together back then.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry,
but the Jinlingchun is booked
for a private event today.
We're not accepting outside guests.
This place
was where my wife and
I often came back to.
So I thought I'd come back for a visit.
It was rude of me.
Father,
We all know how devoted you are to mother.
Then let's come back tomorrow.
You.
How dare you make fun of your father?
You deserve a punishment.
Then punish me by making me drink
with you every day.
Okay.
Let's go back.
You Central Plains people
are so cautious in your words.
It's really annoying.
The Crown Prince
has deep roots in the court.
That's true.
But he relies on
the maternal clan of the Empress.
As far as I know,
the Emperor has no intention of
sharing power with him.
I'm afraid that
if the Emperor's preference
is not the Crown Prince,
that Uncle has chosen the wrong person.
Yin Zhao, that old fox,
doesn't even trust his own son.
What kind of hero is he?
However,
what do you mean by this?
Back then,
it was you who sent a secret envoy
to ask for my help
for the Crown Prince,
So it was Yanzhi wo was behind inciting
Yin Zhou and Su He to rebel together.
He's the one who started all this.
How is that possible?
Back then, I had the same idea as uncle.
To help the Crown Prince ascend to
the position of Crown Prince.
In this way,
we could gain the upper
hand in the Daxing court.
But recently,
the Emperor has also shown great favor
to the Fifth Prince.
If the Emperor's preference
is for the Fifth Prince
to be the Crown Prince,
it's also a possibility.
You don't have to test my determination
on behalf of the Crown Prince.
We grasslanders keep our word.
Since.
I, the Khan,
have promised to cooperate
with the Crown Prince,
I will never go back on my word.
The crown prince has sent me to
deliver this message to the Khan's hands.
It seems that I
won't be able to see the.
Crown Prince this time in Jiangnan.
Indeed.
Breaking promises
is something those Central
Plains people would do.
The Crown Prince is
cautious in his actions.
He's probably afraid that
the Emperor is here
drinking and having fun,
so he doesn't dare to show his face easily.
Central Plains people always do things
so cautiously,
afraid of wolves in
front and tigers behind.
In a few days,
I, the Khan, will set off back to Talhan.
As for the Crown Prince,
Uncle, don't worry.
I won't let uncle's trip be in vain.
I've been keeping an eye on Yin Qi.
His expression hasn't changed at all.
It seems that
he's really given up on Pei Yanzhi.
After all these years of deep affection,
in the end, they still have
to go their separate ways.
I thought Yin Qi had
changed his temperament
because he wanted to
compete for the throne.
But now it seems that
he only cares about.
Pei Yanzhi.
What good can come from
someone born to the Concubine Chen?
But we still shouldn't let our guard down.
I understand.
Your Highness,
are you really not going to meet Su He?
Let his uncle and nephew have a good chat.
If I go so easily,
Su He will only think that.
I can't do without him.
My lord,
judging by what Fengsun said,
the old Emperor of Daxing
may not want Yinzhou
to be the Crown Prince.
What Fengsun just said,
I, the Khan, already knew.
Who becomes the Crown Prince in Daxing.
I, the Khan,
don't care at all.
I only know that
the more chaotic the Daxing court is,
the more we can reap the benefits.
If the Fifth Prince
comes to cooperate with me,
I, the Khan, will also consider it.
My lord,
What does this mean?
Tiele Suhe gave the
military token to Fengsun.
I, the Khan, came to Jiangnan this time
because I wanted that
military token in his hand.
I think.
Yin Zhou can't wait any longer
to ascend to the throne.
As long as he makes a move,
we can
use his hands to get rid of Fengsun.
My lord is truly far-sighted.
To my lord.
A Qi,
what are you doing here?
I thought you were forced to do things
for Yin Zhou and Su He.
But I just found out today that
the mastermind behind all this
is you.
You heard everything.
A Qi.
Su He has imprisoned my younger sister,
using her life as a threat.
Enough, Pei Yanzhi.
The conversation you just had with Su He
didn't sound like you
were being threatened.
Since
you've already chosen to go against me,
then,
A Qi,
listen to my explaination.
Do you want everyone in the palace
to know about your dealings with Yin Zhou?
A Qi,
A Qi, don't be like this.
Why don't you just kill me?
It would be better than all these years
of you compromising and
enduring humiliation for your tribe.
Can't do it?
I'll help you.
A Qi, calm down.
I did this for a purpose.
Things aren't like what you think.
You should have known that
even if you help him
ascend to the position of Crown Prince,
he won't let me go.
Rather than dying in his hands,
you might as well kill me now.
Tomorrow, you can take my body
and claim credit.
Promotions and power will be
within your grasp. It's that simple.
Do it, Fengsun.
Am I just someone
in your eyes
who is greedy for power
and willing to betray
friends for fame and gain?
Then tell me.
Why did you do this?
Not for power.
Could it be
for Yin Zhou?
I did it for you.
Su He
is eyeing the Khan's
throne on the grasslands.
Yin Zhou
is determined to kill you.
I had to find a way to
eliminate the threat forever.
I've been planning this for so long.
I already have a chance of winning.
As long as you
do nothing.
So,
you deliberately let Su He and Yin Zhou
form an alliance,
and incited them to rebel,
to expose their ambitions
in front of the Emperor.
Are you crazy?
I had no better way.
I only had
to make them die without a burial place
to ensure your safety and freedom.
If I had to choose again,
I would still do it.
No.
That's not right.
In a past life,
Yanzhi went to save the Emperor,
not to kill him.
So that's what happened.
A Qi,
As long as I plan everything carefully,
it will definitely work.
At that time,
I can give you
the freedom you want.
Isn't that good?
What if
you fail?
If I fail,
then it's fate.
What about me?
Why don't you understand by now that...
I do want freedom,
but the freedom I want
shouldn't be given to me by you.
Pei Yanzhi,
you have the guts to do
all these crazy things behind my back,
but you don't have the courage
to admit
your feelings for me.
Pei Yanzhi,
you coward.
Now,
you're not running away anymore.