♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 14=
♪Someone I've been looking for♪
♪Don't have to keep searching anymore♪
♪I've never thought I'd have it all♪
♪But everything changed,
and anything is possible♪
♪I found what I've been looking for♪
♪Someone I've been looking for♪
♪Don't have to keep searching anymore♪
♪I've never thought I'd have it all♪
♪But everything changed,
and anything is possible♪
♪I found what I've been looking for♪
Come.
Welcome to my secret spot.
Your secret spot?
Yeah.
Only Zichen and I know this place.
When we were kids,
my dad used to make things hard for us.
Grandma would bring us here
to play fireworks.
I told her back then
that when I grew up,
I'd only bring someone here
if they really mattered to me.
I feel like
I still haven't caught up.
My head's a mess.
Nange.
You need
to face the facts.
What facts?
We're really together now.
From now on,
I want you
to tell me everything.
Anything at all.
Don't hide it.
Just tell me.
I'll do everything I can
to help you through it.
You're not bothering me.
That's what
a husband is supposed to do.
Since
we've chosen each other,
I'll handle
my own problems too.
You already run Huo Group.
That's already a lot.
You have enough pressure.
I don't want
to dump my stress on you too.
And
what if one day
you stop treating me this well?
That would really hurt.
I won't.
Nange,
no matter what you're dealing with
or how you're feeling,
I'll face it with you.
Besides,
I like being good to you.
I like surprising you.
In your words,
that's called...
adding variables.
What variables?
♪Darling, I'm guide with compass♪
Hey, hurry up.
Nange and I are waiting.
It's beautiful.
So pretty.
That one's huge.
Look!
♪Cause it's hard to travel alone♪
Look at that.
♪Cause you wouldn't be the only one♪
It's beautiful.
♪You might as well have company♪
Do you like it?
Look.
That one's huge.
♪It wouldn't be the worst thing♪
♪Cause you wouldn't be the only one♪
I do.
Good.
♪The only one♪
♪Cause it's hard to travel alone♪
So beautiful.
Yeah.
Beautiful.
It's getting late.
So...
Should we get some rest?
Rest?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I thought you said we should rest.
I was just walking you back.
Nothing else.
Then get out.
Hurry.
Move.
Get out.
Nange.
Out.
Okay.
I'll go check on Grandma.
Tomorrow night,
sleep in my room.
Grandma,
I finally found someone
I can share
my secret spot with.
Xu Nange
is really wonderful.
Scarf...
finished...
Nange...
warm...
Grandma,
I know you like Nange.
You always
have the best instincts.
Grandma,
I made progress today
with the Dr. X case.
A real breakthrough.
This way, Mr. Huo.
Over there
is our newly built
advanced biomaterials center.
Inside is a dust-free cleanroom.
Shen Yan.
Climate-controlled, too.
Shen Yan,
come here.
Look at this.
Hurry.
Mrs. Huo, I got it.
It's extremely dangerous.
We need to move fast.
Give me.
This is the latest edition
of Everything About Huo Beiyan.
Diet, routines,
warning signs, facial tells,
even his preferred coffee temperature
depending on his mood.
It's all in Chapter 3.
Do not share this.
Especially
the last page,
with my pencil rants.
Got it.
Accurate data is the foundation of research.
A relationship without solid data
just isn't scientific.
Mrs. Huo, I totally agree.
Shen Yan, you're the real big data.
Shen Yan.
I'll send you the money.
No.
We don't talk money.
You're going places.
Come here.
Let me tell you about Mr. Huo.
He's ridiculously picky.
Every morning,
he has to have coffee.
Too hot? Nope.
Too cold? Nope.
The ice cubes?
Too many today,
too few tomorrow.
He's impossible.
Seriously,
you have no idea.
Honestly,
Mr. Huo is such
a nightmare.
Who's a nightmare?
What's that?
My research data.
Research?
What do you know about research?
I...
Mrs. Huo left this research data
at the office.
Right.
Research data?
Everything About Huo Beiyan.
Ultimate edition.
(Volcano mode)
If Huo Beiyan's been working
for over 72 hours
and smiles at your request,
you're about
to get rejected
and handed more work.
Back away slowly.
Survival first.
How dare you.
How is this
my research data?
What did you even write?
In ancient times,
this would be treason.
You're done.
Mrs. Huo,
how could you...
Volcanic morning temper,
ridiculously picky,
and won't admit it.
Terrible jokes,
even worse delivery.
And a serious
cleanliness obsession.
Well, Shen Yan.
You really know me well.
Mr. Huo, wait.
Let me explain.
Impressive.
You've really studied me.
And you write well.
I remember
there's a mining project in South Africa
needing a site lead.
Book your ticket.
One-way. No return needed.
I... I'm not going.
I'm serious.
No way.
Absolutely not.
Shen Yan!
I'll deal with you tonight.
Shen Yan,
I won't forget this.
If this is just
about getting back at him,
we don't need to meet again.
It's childish.
Their marriage is real now.
I don't stand a chance.
That got to you.
Doesn't feel good, huh?
Your turn's coming.
Listen to this.
Hear what my cousin really wants.
Me?
Ye Xin,
you need me now.
My goal
is to kick Huo Beiyan out.
Then we split Huo Group.
Keep treating me
like a kid,
and you're dead.
Listen first.
Then we'll talk.
Grandma,
the truth is almost out.
You got worse
because someone gave you
an experimental drug.
Code name, NIT-33.
It's from United Pharma.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪