♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 8=
Huo Beiyan,
yesterday you said you didn't like me.
But now you keep bringing me food
every single day.
Do you...
It's like this.
Because
there are a lot of people watching us.
We have to sell the act completely.
Otherwise,
everything we've done so far
could fall apart.
But let me be clear.
I'm extremely busy.
I can't exactly help you provide
all that emotional value stuff.
Do you feel like you're losing out?
I never asked you to provide it.
Just focus
on playing the role of Mrs. Huo properly.
Fine.
You said it yourself.
Eat.
(Li Wanru)
Ugh.
What now?
My stepmother, obviously.
Ever since she found out I married
into the Huo family,
she's been clinging to me
like a fly that won't go away.
I'm telling you now.
If she brings Xu Yin to bother you later,
do not engage with them.
Relax. I'm not that free.
Yes?
Nange, sweetheart,
it's me, Mom.
Are you busy?
Yes.
Nothing important, really.
I just wanted to ask.
You see,
now that you're married,
when are you bringing
Mr. Huo back to the Xu family
for a meal?
Who was it again that threw me
out of the Xu family?
I'm never going back there again.
Let bygones be bygones.
Now that you're married,
you should still come back for a visit.
It's basic etiquette.
Don't think I don't know
what you're really after.
I'm telling you right now, impossible.
Well, look at that.
Now that she's climbed the social ladder,
she thinks she's untouchable.
Don't say that.
I refuse to believe
there's no way into the Huo family.
Come on, Mom.
Even I can see through your tactics.
You only know how to play easy wins.
What would you know?
Right now, I'm waiting
for the perfect opportunity.
Who is it?
You are…?
You must be Auntie Li Wanru.
That's right.
I'm Huo Beiyan's cousin.
My name is Huo Zichen.
Mr. Zichen?
Quick, come inside.
Look who's here.
Mr. Zichen,
this is my other daughter, Xu Yin.
Ever since Nange got married,
she's the only one still single
staying by my side.
Hello.
Auntie,
you can just call me Zichen from now on.
I picked up this gift on the way over.
My cousin's been very busy lately,
so as the younger one,
I thought I should come visit instead.
Zichen,
you're too thoughtful.
Please sit down.
Come, have a seat.
Really.
You didn't have to bring gifts.
I just got back from overseas,
and the first thing I heard was
that my brother got married.
Honestly, I was shocked.
Tell me about it.
Nange's always been independent
since she was little.
Even we only found out
about the marriage two days
before they registered.
Right, Yin?
Yeah.
I guess when fate arrives,
there's just no stopping it.
Fate really is mysterious sometimes.
But my brother's personality
has always been pretty cold and distant.
For him to care this much
about his wife,
she must have something
truly special about her.
Of course she does.
Exactly.
Oh right.
I heard someone mention
that her doctoral thesis
is extremely difficult this time.
My cousin even bought out
an entire lab at Linhai for her.
She never really tells us much
about her research anyway.
My mom and I
can't understand a word of it.
She acts mysterious all day long.
Yin.
I-I didn't mean
that in a bad way.
No, it's fine.
You two are sisters after all.
My brother and I
are like that all the time too.
Right.
Yin, stop sitting there.
Pour Zichen some water.
Okay.
(A research topic ordinary people
can't even understand)
(and she still insists
on being so secretive?)
(Xu Nange,)
(I'm getting more and more curious.)
So the final conclusion is,
after verification
by a third-party laboratory,
all of Dr. X's experimental data
can be successfully reproduced.
There's no possibility of fabrication.
By the way, Mr. Huo, I also had someone
look into Dr. X's background.
Although this person
is extremely mysterious,
their reputation in academic circles
is impeccable.
Oh right,
this is the investigation report.
Same as before,
find them as soon as possible.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Mr. Huo, look.
I understand you invested
in a private laboratory for Madam's sake.
But did you really need
to rent out
the entire building
next to the lab too?
It's not like she can use
that much space anyway.
Is there a problem?
No problem at all.
Mr. Huo is getting
more lovestruck by the day.
Less nonsense. Go make the arrangements.
Right away.
(I'll pick you up later.)
(Family dinner tonight.)
Beiyan,
how's the company's
medical-industry transition going?
I've already collected
the board's opinions.
More than half of them
oppose the transition.
So what are you planning to do?
I think
the only way to convince everyone
is with an absolutely authoritative
transition plan.
That's why
I've decided to work with
Dr. X,
the expert in neuroscience.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, really.
Go on, continue.
Dr. X?
We don't even know who this person is.
Wouldn't partnering
with them be too risky?
Dad,
they may be
Grandma's only hope.
Normally speaking,
an expert at that level
wouldn't need to hide their identity.
If they refuse to show themselves,
could they actually be a fraud?
I just think
what you're discussing
sounds very important.
So everyone should probably
be more cautious.
Nange makes a good point too.
But I already had someone
run a background check.
Dr. X's research results
all hold up under scrutiny.
And their reputation is excellent.
How about this?
Nange,
you're also a medical PhD.
Once I find Dr. X,
I'll arrange a meeting between you two.
You can evaluate
their professional level yourself,
then we'll decide whether
to cooperate with them.
Sure.
You all continue talking.
I'll go upstairs
and check on Grandma first.
Alright.
Our Nange has worked hard for this.
You're going to help me
find the best doctor?
Grandma, don't worry.
I'm actually the Dr. X
Huo Beiyan has been searching
for all along.
I'll definitely do everything I can
to cure you.
But right now, I'm thinking...
How can I keep my identity hidden?
Why do you need to hide?
Because,
I have a secret that can't be told.
(One year earlier)
My name is Xu Nange.
Today is December 17th, 2025,
8:52 in the morning.
Starting today,
I will begin efficacy testing
on the so-called
Alzheimer's miracle drug, NIT-33.
Based on my prior investigation,
this drug is clearly harmful
to the human body.
Yet NIT-33 has already become
a massive overseas bestseller,
earning billions in profit.
So starting today,
I intend to expose this enormous lie.
And to achieve that goal,
my life
may be placed in considerable danger.
My experimental data
and research materials
require the highest level
of security clearance.
Without my biometric authentication,
(Clause 2: Data Security)
no one is allowed to touch anything.
That includes you.
I can't finish my thesis anymore.
I don't need money.
I want the entire laboratory
at Linhai Medical School.
So,
I'll use my doctoral studies
as a cover for my real identity.
Under the anonymous name "X",
I'll publicly release the progress
of my experiments.
This matter is too important.
I'm recording this video as evidence.
If anything happens to me,
rule out the possibility
of suicide entirely.
Mrs. Huo,
Madam Li Wanru has arrived.
What is she doing here?
She's here for the family dinner.
It seems Mr. Zichen invited her.
(Huo Zichen?)
Understood.
Grandma, I'll be right back, okay?
Is this for me?
Okay.
Thank you, Grandma.
I'll be back soon.
What are you doing here?
Nange,
you're Mrs. Huo now.
Of course we had to come visit.
With the Huo family
supporting us,
the Xu family's future
will definitely soar.
Whether I'm Mrs. Huo or not
has nothing to do with the Xu family.
Watch your tone.
Weren't you raised by the Xu family?
Just say a word to Huo Beiyan.
Do you know how hard it is
to secure projects these days?
If any suitable projects come up,
just let the Xu family handle them.
The Huo family has its own standards
for partnerships.
I won't interfere,
and I don't have that authority anyway.
The Huo family's standards?
Wouldn't Huo Beiyan
be the one setting them?
Besides,
doesn't he have another cousin?
Li Wanru,
I'm warning you.
Stay away from Huo Zichen.
Our dear in-laws have arrived.
Forgive me
for not welcoming you properly.
This must be our in-law,
Old Mr. Huo himself!
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪