ظآزLove's little quiz
takes seven parts sweetظآز
ظآزAnd three parts bitter,
till you and I meetظآز
ظآزI pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stayظآز
ظآزWaiting for youظآز
ظآزWe've got so many
romantic dreams to unfoldظآز
ظآزFinally hearing
the I love you I long to holdظآز
ظآزFalling fast
into the swirl of your eyesظآز
ظآزIt's just too tempting, so temptingظآز
ظآزNever could I have guessedظآز
ظآزMy heart's rhythmظآز
ظآزHow beautiful it is, meeting youظآز
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 9=
Our dear in-laws have arrived.
Forgive me
for not welcoming you properly.
This must be our in-law,
Old Mr. Huo himself!
Really now, dear in-law,
for such an important visit,
you should've told us ahead of time.
Thankfully Mr. Zichen
was thoughtful enough to arrange it.
So it was Zichen's doing all along.
Uncle, it was my own decision.
I wasn't sure whether it was appropriate.
Of course it is.
Very appropriate.
Nange, entertain the guests for now.
I'll head to the kitchen
and make arrangements.
We'll chat more later, in-law.
Sorry for the disturbance, in-law.
Uncle, I'll help you.
Let's go.
Xu Nange,
you'd better give me some face here.
Because if you embarrass me,
you'll only make things unpleasant
for yourself.
After all, this is still the Huo family.
Dear in-law, your presence
truly honors this humble home.
These dishes
were specially prepared
for you by the Huo family.
I just hope they suit your taste.
Please.
Mr. Huo,
you're far too kind.
Auntie,
please try this.
As the head of the family,
you work so hard every day.
You should nourish yourself more.
Xu Yin, come.
You should try some too.
Thank you, Zichen.
Zichen is such a thoughtful child.
To be honest,
Nange's had a hard life.
Her biological mother passed away early.
When her father left her in my care,
she was only this tall.
Over the years,
I truly devoted myself to raising her.
I was both mother and father to her.
If other children had something,
then Nange had to have it too.
And if other children didn't have it,
I'd still do everything I could
to get it for her.
Nange, do you still remember
that princess dress you wanted
back in elementary school?
I had to go to three malls
before finally finding it for you.
You've probably forgotten by now,
haven't you?
You still want a new dress?
From now on, just wear
whatever your sister's done with.
Mom, you're way too good to Nange.
I remember when she was living
on campus in high school,
Mom would make soup every weekend
and have me deliver it to her.
That's nothing.
As long as our Nange is doing well,
everything I do is worth it.
Right?
Stop kidding yourself, Xu Nange.
You think someone like you
deserves friends?
From now on,
stop embarrassing me at school, okay?
I already transferred
your allowance to Yin.
Whatever she has left over,
that's what you get to spend.
You won't starve.
And from now on,
stay out of sight around the house.
Seeing you annoys me.
You're bad luck.
This in-law really hasn't had it easy.
Nange,
- from now on you should...
- I understand.
Good.
(I already figured the Xu family
dynamics out back in college.)
(I just didn't expect
they'd become useful now.)
(Nange,)
(how much longer
are you going to endure this?)
(And does Beiyan know any of it?)
(Interesting.)
It's just a pity.
The Xu family is worlds apart
from the Huo family.
Now that's not true at all.
From now on,
we're all one family.
If you ever
have difficulties or requests,
just say the word.
Auntie,
we should spend more time together
from now on.
Zichen's right.
We should pay each other more visits.
Absolutely.
We'll keep in touch often.
(Hurry up.)
(I'm waiting for you to lose control,
Xu Nange.)
Judging by the time,
it should be here soon.
Did you prepare some kind
of surprise for everyone?
Everyone, apologies.
This surprise was prepared
for Nange alone.
Mr. Huo.
Madam.
These are the gifts
Mr. Huo personally prepared for you.
First, the premier collector's piece
from Paris Haute Couture Week.
Second,
a limited-edition set handcrafted
by Italy's national master artisan.
Third,
the final archived treasures
from Paris's last pearl atelier.
And here
this is the Corridor of Time
personally opened for you by Mr. Huo.
Every piece of jewelry inside
holds its own legendary story.
And now,
they're all waiting
to meet you once again.
Oh,
and Mr. Huo specifically instructed us.
There was no need
to choose the most expensive gifts.
What mattered was that each piece
could gain a brand-new life
when worn by you.
(Beiyan.)
(It's only a paper agreement.)
(Do you really have to play her knight
in shining armor too?)
(Can you stop using this fake-love act)
(to disgust me?)
Nange, do you still remember
that princess dress you wanted
back in elementary school?
I had to go to three malls
before finally finding it for you.
You've probably forgotten by now,
haven't you?
Auntie,
you just said
that whenever Nange wanted something,
you always found a way
to give it to her.
I'll remember that.
And what I can promise is,
from this day forward,
whatever Nange wants,
whatever she deserves,
I can give it to her.
Today, in front of our parents,
I want to make three requests of Nange.
First,
stop locking yourself away
inside the laboratory all the time.
I know many talents and experts
in the medical field.
You should go out more,
meet people, make friends.
And those meaningless social circles?
You don't have to force yourself
to deal with them.
ظآزAll that I can
to just stand where I standظآز
Second,
treat yourself better.
Whatever you want,
whether it's clothes you want to buy,
places you want to visit,
or restaurants you want to try,
you never need to look at the price tag.
As long as you live comfortably and brightly,
your heart will naturally become brighter too.
And,
I'm willing to pay any price
for your happiness.
Because you deserve it.
Third,
whenever someone
or something makes you frown,
don't carry it alone.
Tell me.
As your husband,
it's my duty and responsibility
to make sure the people who trouble you
quietly disappear from your sight.
I'm willing to protect this bond
of family for you.
The dress fitting can wait.
Come on.
Let's eat first.
Alright.
Delicious.
Let's stop just sitting here staring.
Everyone dig in.
Dear in-law,
this is premium deep-sea fish maw.
Great for beauty and skin care.
Thank you.
I made myself clear, right?
From now on,
the Xu family and Huo family
can maintain appearances publicly.
But those two women,
do not let them appear in front
of Nange again.
Not even once.
Understood?
Understood.
Thanks for tonight.
It was nothing.
You're pretty impressive, you know that?
Li Wanru had barely started putting
on her fake act about dresses,
and within five minutes,
you already had Shen Yan
bring in all the props.
More accurately,
three and a half minutes.
How do you even do that?
How I do it isn't important.
I'm only responsible for making decisions
and fulfilling the promises I make to you.
Being your special assistant
sounds exhausting.
It's much better to be like me.
Being the wife is easier.
I...
I mean...
you should give Shen Yan a raise.
Don't worry. I already have it in mind.
Actually, besides tonight's dinner,
he also made progress on something else.
He tracked down Dr. X's email.
The network address
had triple-layer encryption,
but my tech department
already broke through two layers.
At the latest,
I'll have the final result tomorrow.
(That fast?)
(They already traced the IP address?)
What's wrong?
I-I just remembered
I still haven't finished
revising my thesis.
I'm heading back to work on it first.
(Not here.)
(Not here either.)
(Where did they put)
(that IP trace report?)
(If I don't find it soon,
Huo Beiyan will be back any minute.)
Mr. Huo.
Mrs. Huo,
these are the urgent files
Mr. Huo requested.
Just leave them there.
Understood.
Why is this place such a mess?
I'll help him tidy up a little.
(IP Trace Report)
(So it hasn't been delivered yet.)
(There's still time.)
(IP Trace Report)
Good afternoon, Mr. Huo.
Tell the marketing director
to wait for me.
I'll be there shortly.
Hello.
Wait.
Why are you here?
Weren't you supposed
to be revising your thesis?
Iظخ
I wanted to come see you.
Is that not allowed?
Wait for me a second.
I just need to finish up some work.
Hang on.
ظآزWhat destiny brought us to meetظآز
ظآزTwo different worlds, a love so sweetظآز
ظآزA wish we made
in a past life, it seemsظآز
ظآزDestined to cross time and dream ظآز
ظآزLike a fairytale story toldظآز
ظآزA gentle breeze feels so boldظآز
ظآزAs your hair brushes past your earظآز
ظآزI long to kiss your cheek, my dearظآز
ظآزAll my longing, all my love for youظآز
ظآزHas never changed, it's forever trueظآز
ظآزIt's the hand of fate
that we meet againظآز
ظآزLet me hold you once againظآز
ظآزResting against your chestظآز
ظآزYour warmth shines like stars at nightظآز
ظآزLet me kiss you once againظآز
ظآزNo reason neededظآز
ظآزMy heart belongs to youظآز
ظآزI'm not afraid
to cross time to find youظآز