♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 16=
Nange,
the site investigation report is in.
Nothing was taken from the lab.
So, it's hard to say what this even was.
(On-site inspection)
(Findings & Recommendations)
What's wrong?
You haven't been yourself
since you got back from the lab.
I'm fine.
Are you scared of something?
Are you afraid of whoever broke in,
or afraid of what might come out
if something was taken?
No.
I've just been tired lately.
Beiyan, please just let me handle this.
Nange,
we're married.
I need you to trust me.
Just because we're married,
I...
I think some things
are better left unsaid.
What do you mean by that?
Beiyan, please stop asking.
Why can't I ask?
Just call me stubborn if you want,
but let me deal with this myself.
Do you really want this?
Beiyan!
Uh, am I...
interrupting something?
Zichen, what are you doing here?
Uncle Beixiang wants to celebrate
Grandma's birthday early.
Just a small gathering at home.
He sent me to invite both of you.
Mrs. Huo, you're looking a bit pale.
I'm fine.
Beiyan and I will be there shortly.
Great.
I brought some bird's nest
for you, Mrs. Huo.
I'll leave it here.
Oh, right.
The old mister has been bringing up
grandchildren again.
He sent me to drop the hint.
Good luck. I'll leave you to it.
Nange,
whenever you're ready to talk,
I'm here.
Don't forget,
you are married to me.
Whatever it is, I can help.
(Still not going to confess?)
(Fine.)
(Then, I'll handle it myself.)
I, Xu Nange,
on this day,
December 17th, 2025,
at 8:52 in the morning,
hereby declare that I
will begin testing
the so-called Alzheimer's drug NIT-33
for its true efficacy.
Based on my prior investigation,
this drug is clearly harmful.
Yet NIT-33 has been sold overseas,
generating billions in profit.
Starting today,
I will expose this massive fraud.
I will use my doctoral studies
as cover,
and publish my findings anonymously
under the alias Dr. X.
The stakes are high.
(Xu Nange.)
(So, you really are Dr. X.)
Mom,
today is your 70th birthday.
Going by the rules
you set for our family years ago,
we're keeping it simple
this year.
Everything our family has today
is all because of the Old Madam.
She built it all from
a single box of medicine.
Without her hard work back then,
none of us
would have the lives we have now.
Come,
let's raise our glasses
and wish the old madam
a very happy birthday!
Back then, the family had nothing.
Grandma
worked as an apprentice
at a nurse's station by day,
while at night,
studied medical texts by lamplight.
Eventually,
she saved enough money
to stock affordable medicines herself
and sell them to neighbors
who couldn't afford the expensive ones.
And little by little,
the idea of going
into medicine was born.
Grandma always used to say,
medicine is for saving lives,
not for making money.
She was right.
And even as the years went on,
and our family business grew,
Grandma never lost sight of her roots.
Mom, do you remember?
You used to instruct the finance team
to make anonymous transfers
specifically to fund
promising students who
couldn't afford medical school.
Grandma did that kind of charity work?
I never heard a word about it.
Neither did I.
What I know
is only the half of it.
Grandma's always kept
a low profile.
She never let me ask
or tell anyone.
All I know is,
there's always been
a fixed outgoing payment
from the company,
and on the transfer slips,
no real name was ever written.
Just a single
letter of the alphabet.
X.
(Nange, I hope this finds you well.)
(Linhai Medical University
is where you should be.)
(Don't worry about tuition
or living expenses.)
(It's all been taken care of.)
(Focus on your studies.)
(You belong here.)
(I know a little)
(of what you've been
through with the Xu family.)
(Being overlooked was never your flaw.)
(It's proof you learned
to stand on your own.)
(Don't underestimate yourself.)
(It has nothing to do
with anyone else's approval.)
(Exhaustion is just part of the climb.)
(But I saw it in your eyes.)
(A flame that refuses to go out.)
(True talent)
(never stays buried.)
(When opportunity comes knocking,)
(I hope you'll be ready.)
(So you remembered me)
(because you already knew)
(who I was.)
(An anonymous letter from years ago.)
(And the tuition and living expenses.)
(Those words that got me through
the Xu family's cold shoulders)
(and all those sleepless
nights in the lab.)
(The mysterious alias I inherited,)
(X.)
(It was Grandma all along.)
Nange,
how did you figure it out?
X is an unknown.
It felt exactly like the kind of thing
Grandma would choose
if she wanted to stay hidden.
That makes sense.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Grandma.
Happy birthday.
Beiyan,
I've made up my mind.
There's something
very important I need to do,
and I can't afford
to lose a single minute.
Give me two weeks.
After that,
whether my research is finished
or this matter is resolved,
I'll tell you everything.
I promise.
So what are you planning
to do for these two weeks?
Probably just in the lab,
I guess.
There's a test
I have to run myself.
Okay.
I'll wait.
If you need space, I'll give you space.
If you need time
to sort out what you want to say,
I'll be patient.
But I have two conditions.
First,
make sure you're
eating and sleeping properly.
Second,
if things get dangerous
or too much to handle alone,
call me.
I promise.
Then, I'll
leave you to it.
This is where my brother
and I used to play.
How is it?
Not bad, right?
I have zero interest
in childish things.
Let's get to the point.
Fine.
It's time for the two of us
to come to an agreement.
Once it's done,
we split Huo Group fifty-fifty.
Don't even think about cutting me out.
Honestly, I'm not sure your abilities
are worthy of your ambitions.
Fine then.
Let me give you something concrete.
Xu Nange's research
is targeting Ye
Pharmaceuticals' new drug.
She
is Dr. X.
Proof?
You'll have to verify that yourself.
After all, we're
in this together.
Are you threatening me?
Of course not.
I came in good faith
to propose a partnership.
I'd hate to see my own partner,
Ye Pharmaceuticals go down.
It all depends on whether
Miss Ye is willing to help.
And besides,
I've already identified
the right person to back
and the right moment to move.
Who?
My cousin.
Huo Beiyan.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪