♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 12=
(Reserved for Dr. Xu Nange)
(Shen Yan)
(Mr. Huo,)
(the tech team analyzed a ton
of early related texts, including word choice,)
(narrative logic,)
(Shen Yan)
(and even punctuation preferences,)
(and confirmed that Dr. X)
(is left-handed.)
(Also,)
(by looking at handwriting pressure
on surviving drafts,)
(it seems she has a pretty unique grip.)
(The index finger joint digs in deep,)
(and the pressure is uneven.)
(We don't know)
(if this info will actually help,)
(but it's a breakthrough.)
(Anyway,)
(Dr. X is scary smart.)
(She basically erased
every single trace of her existence.)
(She's still tough to track down.)
What's wrong?
I was just trying out the pen.
Why are you acting so freaked out?
It's nothing.
I think
my brain just short-circuited.
Anyway, thank you so much.
I really
love this gift.
Glad you like it.
What did you write?
Nothing.
Just doodling.
Let me see.
(Huo Beiyan)
Consider this
my thank-you note for your gift.
You're welcome.
(Four months ago)
This is my 83rd log.
Since the Dr. X persona
has been drawing way too much attention,
starting today,
I'm going to practice writing
with my left hand.
Going completely off the grid
might actually be counterproductive.
So I'll purposely leave behind
Dr. X's handwriting,
signatures,
and a few blurry photos from behind.
That way, I can create a smokescreen,
throw them off the scent,
and protect myself.
(Yi Home)
Dad,
have you seen Beiyan today?
He left for the office
early this morning.
Today's a big day.
He'll be in board meetings all day long.
Nange,
it's kind of my fault.
I'm the one
who piled all that work on him today.
But don't worry.
I'll be more mindful next time.
It's totally fine, Dad.
I was just feeling a bit hungry
and thought I'd ask him
to whip up something to eat.
That's no big deal.
I'll take care of it for you.
It's okay, Dad.
Don't worry about it. It's fine, really.
Stop being so polite.
Just sit tight.
It'll be ready in ten minutes.
Got it.
Don't worry.
I received the gift
you sent for Beiyan.
As soon as he gets back,
I'll hand it over to him.
Okay?
I know.
(Ralph Lauren)
Okay, got it.
(For Huo Beiyan,Ye Xin)
Ye Xin?
Who's Ye Xin?
Well...
It's a bit complicated.
What's so complicated about it?
Just tell me.
She's Beiyan's childhood friend
and former fiancée.
After all these years,
she still remembers what he likes.
But don't worry.
The engagement is ancient history.
Beiyan called it off
six months ago for you.
(For me?)
(But six months ago,)
(Huo Beiyan and I hadn't even met yet.)
Uncle Beixiang, is breakfast ready?
Dad,
I suddenly lost my appetite.
I think I'll skip breakfast.
Zichen, you should've stopped her.
How could you let her
leave the house on an empty stomach?
It's fine. I'll eat it.
Oh, you'll eat it?
I'll have to fry up more eggs, then.
Hang on.
Ye Xin.
Huo Beiyan.
(Perfect match.)
(The dream team.)
(FM98.7 interview?)
(The date of this interview)
(is really a few years ago.)
(Beiyan and I
didn't know each other back then.)
How did I accidentally hit that?
(Question.)
(Miss Ye, as everyone knows,)
(you and Mr. Huo Beiyan from Huo Group)
(grew up together.)
(The public has always been
very curious about your relationship.)
(Could you tell us)
(what your ideal type is?)
(Is it based on Mr. Huo?)
(Beiyan is indeed incredibly talented.)
(We grew up together.)
(Judging by her voice,
she's probably pretty good-looking.)
(But when it comes to an ideal type,)
(it's hard to narrow it down
to just one person.)
(If I had to describe it,)
(I admire someone who's
emotionally stable, dependable,)
(and who can stand by my side)
(as a true partner in business.)
(It sounds like you're
describing Mr. Huo himself.)
He's not like that at all.
(I hadn't really thought about it,)
(but Beiyan is a great guy.)
(He remembers little things
like how I don't drink coffee)
(and only drink black tea.)
(That's a huge plus.)
Wow, what a great memory he has.
Well, I like coffee.
Coffee is my absolute favorite.
(Sorry.)
(The number you have dialed)
(is not reachable at the moment.)
(Please try again later. Sorry.)
Okay.
It's fine.
He's working.
He's just busy with work.
What's this?
Where did this Ye Xin person
even come from?
Huo Beiyan.
Miss Ye.
You're here so early today.
(It's her.)
(Ye Xin)
(Ye Xin.)
(CEO of United Pharma.)
(The main mastermind
and the biggest profiteer)
(behind the NIT-33 global strategy.)
(Ye Xin)
(Turns out)
(you're the one I've been looking for.)
Why don't you go chat with Mr. Huo?
I'll take you up.
(This is the woman.)
(She wraps poison
in shiny presentations)
(and uses corporate backing
to push a flawed drug)
(onto the global market.)
Oh, Miss Ye,
- this is...
- Let me guess. You must be Ms. Xu.
You're exactly how I pictured you.
Very academic.
Well, they say scholars
are usually broke.
Don't mind me, Miss Ye.
I've actually heard a lot
about you and your company elsewhere.
A small company like mine
can't compete with Huo Group.
Are you here to see Beiyan too?
Want to go up together?
Sure.
Let's go.
(We can settle all our scores at once.)
Oh no.
This is going to end badly.
Miss Ye.
Long time no see, Beiyan.
You two know each other?
We just met.
We bumped into each other in the lobby.
What brings you by today?
Didn't I say I'd pick you up?
I figured you'd pick me up every day.
I've been way too busy today.
You know, as women,
we need to learn to give men
plenty of space for their careers.
Don't just act up and throw tantrums
over nothing.
It's my bad.
I'll make you something good tonight.
Deal.
Huo Beiyan,
since when did you become...
Have you been
waiting for me for a long time?
Just a little long.
I promise
I'll definitely pick you up
on time from now on.
Okay?
Okay.
Sorry about that, Miss Ye.
When my wife
is lecturing me,
you'd better
keep your mouth shut.
Nange,
I might be a bit tied up today.
You head back first.
I'll get home as soon as I can.
You go do your thing.
After all,
I need to give you some space.
Mr. Huo.
The meeting
is all set up.
We're waiting on you to start.
Alright, I'll go take care of that.
Ms. Xu.
I didn't expect
you two to be so close.
There are a lot of things
you wouldn't expect.
Just don't go
throwing yourself at him later,
or he might have to call you out again.
You're something else, young lady.
What kind of tricks
do you have up your sleeve?
I didn't have any tricks before.
But from here on out,
you're going to see a lot.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪