President Huo
The Old Madam is having an episode.
Quick, go check on her.
Old Madam, please calm down.
Old Madam!
Grandma!
Don't worry, I... I...
I'm Huo Beiyan.
Look at me.
I'm Beiyan.
Who are you?
I won't take the medicine.
Grandma.
I'm better now. Grandma is fine.
We don't need the medicine.
It's okay, let me take a look.
Patients experience hallucinations
because vague sensory inputs
and memory fragments
get incorrectly bound together.
Due to impaired frontal lobe function,
these erroneous responses
can't be identified or suppressed.
There's nothing wrong with these two medications.
Come on, Grandma.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
Extensive contact between water and skin
can rapidly lower body temperature.
It's raining.
Wind and rain.
That's right.
After the rain, a rainbow will appear.
Okay.
There's no rainbow.
The cause of the hallucination is unclear,
but guiding its direction
can be effective.
Go find me a watering can.
A watering can?
Trust me, go quickly.
Grandma, it's okay.
Look, a rainbow!
A rainbow.
Grandma, look.
Nange.
My good Nange.
Thankfully Grandma's okay.
That's so strange.
Grandma can't remember anyone,
but just now,
she only remembered your name.
This kind of thing does happen,
but it's extremely rare.
I'm increasingly convinced
that my initial instinct was right.
Perhaps
you really can help the Huo family.
Don't get your hopes up too high.
Alzheimer's disease
isn't that easy to cure.
But I'll do my best to help.
President Huo.
Senior Chairman Huo told me to bring this.
Do you know Chinese medicine?
A little.
Epimedium
Rehmannia
Deer antler slices
Dodder seed
Atractylodes
Eucommia
What are they for?
Isn't it obvious?
Yours is an aphrodisiac.
Mine is to prevent miscarriage.
Um...
My dad,
he loves researching these things.
Health and wellness.
Good for him.
Well...
I still have a paper to write.
I'll get going now.
Make sure to take your tonic.
Dr. X.
You know him?
Of course I do.
I'm a medical doctor.
I read dozens of papers every day.
What I said just now
was a quote from Dr. X's paper.
Didn't I say last time
that we should consider Zichen's feelings?
Our relationship
should last as long as possible.
I have a proposal.
Go ahead.
The agreement between us,
let's extend it to five years for now.
Five years?
Keep your voice down.
My dad hasn't gone far yet.
Huo Beiyan.
President Huo.
Don't tell me you're playing for real
and have actually fallen for me.
Whatever I, Huo Beiyan, like
or want,
I always go straight for it.
Why beat around the bush?
What kind of man would that make me?
Aren't you a bit too full of yourself?
You sure?
Fine.
Then I want to add a condition too.
Let's hear it.
I can't finish all my papers.
I don't need money.
I want Hai Da Medical School's entire lab.
Done.
Chairman Huo, Mrs. Huo.
The paperwork is all settled.
This is the new nameplate for our lab.
Thank you, Professor.
That was incredibly fast.
Got it done overnight?
That's Chairman Huo's efficiency for you.
However,
by tradition,
the unveiling ceremony
has to be done by you personally.
The air on campus is so refreshing.
From your shabby little rental,
to hauling all kinds of lab equipment
into our marital home,
and now taking over
the entire medical school lab.
At this rate,
world domination is around the corner.
Dr. Xu.
I'll be relying on you, President Huo.
But I've always been curious,
what's the logic behind your business plan?
Alzheimer's disease
is one of the toughest challenges
in the medical field.
Pouring in so much real money,
aren't you afraid of losing it all?
This matter
has nothing to do with profit.
My parents were busy when I was little,
It was Grandma who took care of me.
Every time I came home,
Grandma would happily wait at the door.
But later,
she started to forget.
The way she looked at me
was like looking at a stranger.
You probably don't understand how I feel.
Businessmen always chase profit,
but Huo Beiyan,
no matter how cold he looks on the outside,
deep down,
he's actually quite loving, isn't he?
Yes.
I know that in this world,
no one truly feels another's pain.
But I think
if one day
someone who loved me deeply
suddenly stopped loving me,
I'd be very sad too.
I'd probably also
try my hardest to get that love back.
I knew it.
It really is Grandma's birthday.
Temporary Marriage Agreement
Both parties, due to special reasons,
shall enter into a marital relationship,
valid for three months.
The wife
must cooperate to play the role of a wife.
Brother.
You destroyed my relationship,
so don't blame me for taking Huo Group.
I have to win at least once.
What are you doing?
I'm stewing this for Nange.
Look here.
The way you're handling the heat,
you've really got the knack.
I think it's highly necessary
for me to give you some pointers,
and to taste-test it.
I'm just afraid your seasoning
isn't quite enough,
and my daughter-in-law won't like it.
Don't worry.
My cooking skills
have surpassed the master.
They're definitely better than yours.
You sound so sure.
Then I've got to try a bite.
I've got to try a bite no matter what.
I'll stew some for you next time.
When did you get so stingy?
Got a wife and forgot your dad, typical!
Nange.
Here.
Get some energy in you.
Your timing is perfect.
I'm starving right now.
Here.
Fo Tiao Qiang.
Try some.
It's delicious!
You can even make this?
Teach me when you have time.
How am I supposed to teach this?
I'm pretty smart, you know.
Just give me the formula,
and I can learn anything.
Cooking doesn't have formulas.
I wonder who it was
who read research papers to cook a dish.
I'm afraid you'd blow up the kitchen.
That makes sense.
Then I'll just sit back and enjoy.
Eat up.
Huo Beiyan.
Yesterday you said you didn't like me.
But now you come feed me every day.
You...