♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 15=
Grandma,
the truth is almost out.
You got worse
because someone gave you
an experimental drug.
Code name, NIT-33.
It's from United Pharma.
It's tiny, almost undetectable.
But it builds up over time
and speeds up aging.
Ye Xin thought she left no trace.
I won't let her get away.
Grandma,
I only bought
into United Pharma
to get their books,
lab records,
buried emails,
and approval files.
Don't worry.
Ye Xin won't be charged
with malpractice.
It'll be attempted murder.
And Dr. X.
He was one of the first to study NIT.
He wasn't just watching.
He was part of it.
He's faster than I thought.
NIT...
He even found the code name.
Huo Group
is now United Pharma's
second-largest shareholder.
It became official last week.
You let the wolf right in.
At least we're hidden.
Well,
this should prove where I stand.
Here's to our partnership.
One thing still bothers me.
Dr. X.
Why is he after you?
Did you fall out?
I don't even know him.
What I don't get
is how a total stranger
knows so much
about NIT's old research.
I already checked
every contractor on the line.
What about temps?
Interns?
Huo Zichen, don't be ridiculous.
This is a cutting-edge
drug research.
What intern
would know that much
and be that academically sharp?
You have a lead?
I need to confirm it.
Shen Yan,
move tomorrow's board meeting
for 8 a.m.
I have an announcement.
♪Darling, you go far away♪
♪Why don't you take me too?♪
♪We could go on a journey♪
♪I could take you in♪
♪Garfunkel's got Simon♪
♪Batman's got Robin too♪
♪Everyone's got a partner♪
♪Trained to help them through♪
♪Cause it's hard to travel alone♪
♪So you might as well just take me♪
♪You might as well have company♪
♪And if you should fall in love♪
♪It wouldn't be the worst thing♪
♪Cause you wouldn't be the only one♪
(Nange,)
(once I find Dr. X,)
(I'll give you a wedding.)
Zichen.
Ever since that family dinner,
we've felt that...
We're family now.
We should be closer.
But whenever we call Beiyan,
he's either busy
or his assistant picks up.
They're polite enough,
but they never let anything slip.
We get nowhere.
Is that how in-laws act?
Shen Yan
works closely with my cousin.
He's just careful.
Please don't take it to heart.
How can we not?
We're trying to be close.
Now we look pushy.
Yin says the same.
She wants to learn
from the Huo family, but...
Actually,
that's why I came.
I know a few
private clubs and art salons.
They're good for networking.
If you're interested,
I can take you there.
Sure.
That sounds great.
Young people
should go out more.
Why stay with us old folks?
Alright.
Zichen, don't just sit there.
Didn't a new
dessert shop open downstairs?
Take Zichen there.
- Okay.
- Go on.
Then I'll excuse myself.
Go on. Have fun.
I'm going.
Don't rush back.
If Yinyin can win over Zichen...
Not bad.
Zichen, try some.
This place is famous.
Forget dessert.
I'm interested in you.
Xu Nange is impressive.
You must be too.
How can I compare to her?
Don't say that.
I was abroad for years.
I'm curious
what you and Nange
went through.
You two
must have had
interesting internships.
Well,
I studied fashion design
with a Milan designer.
My mentor was...
What about Nange?
Who cares about her?
I...
I didn't really notice.
She...
was always so secretive.
I think
she interned at a big pharma company.
Uh...
The famous one...
United Pharma.
That's all I know.
(United Pharma internship?)
(Xu Nange,)
(one secret)
(leads to another.)
(Interesting.)
Zichen,
let me tell you
about my internship.
My mentor
came to China for the first time.
Her company was hard to get into.
When I first met her...
Okay.
My mentor...
I just remembered something urgent.
I'll take you
to the art salon next time.
I should go.
Zichen, the dessert...
Zichen!
Morning.
(What happened?)
(He was in a meeting.)
(I was waiting.)
(Then... what happened?)
Breakfast is ready.
Chinese or Western.
Your choice.
(No way.)
(I was so looking forward
to our first night.)
(Such a perfect night,)
(and I slept right through it?)
Xu Nange, what's on your mind?
Nothing.
You slept well last night.
I know.
Xu Nange,
were you expecting something?
No.
No?
- No.
- Really?
Really.
I need to take this.
Hello?
Nange,
did someone break into your lab?
What?
The lock was picked.
The footage is gone.
Nange, you're finally here.
What a mess.
Did you call the police?
Yes. They just left.
They found nothing.
Okay.
I'll check it myself.
Okay, then I'll go to security.
Okay.
They left no trace.
Nange,
why care so much about this paper?
I've read it.
It's a normal topic.
It is.
But I...
You can delay graduation
or change topics
if it isn't working.
I've put
too much into this.
I can't just change it.
I can help.
You've got me
and the Huo family.
Beiyan,
to me,
this isn't just a dissertation.
I...
It...
No.
I think
you care too much about this.
Is there another reason?
I can help.
No.
I'm just stressed.
I'll go find Professor Liang.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪