ظآزLove's little quiz
takes seven parts sweetظآز
ظآزAnd three parts bitter,
till you and I meetظآز
ظآزI pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stayظآز
ظآزWaiting for youظآز
ظآزWe've got so many
romantic dreams to unfoldظآز
ظآزFinally hearing
the I love you I long to holdظآز
ظآزFalling fast
into the swirl of your eyesظآز
ظآزIt's just too tempting, so temptingظآز
ظآزNever could I have guessedظآز
ظآزMy heart's rhythmظآز
ظآزHow beautiful it is, meeting youظآز
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 11=
(Dr. X IP Trace Analysis Report
Behavior analysis, Digital timeline)
Mr. Huo.
Here's the latest paperwork on Dr. X
from the tech department.
I'll leave it right here.
Shen Yan.
Yes, Mr. Huo?
Book a restaurant
for my one-month contract anniversary
with Nange.
Find somewhere quiet.
She hates noisy places.
Wow, you're actually celebrating?
Alright, on it.
By the way, Mr. Huo,
since it's an anniversary dinner,
should we
get her a little something?
You really think
I'd miss a chance to look good?
I've already got it covered.
Alright, Mr. Huo.
Sorry.
Something just crossed my mind.
Ye Xin just got back to the country.
Ye Xin?
What's she back for?
Look, Mr. Huo.
I don't mean anything by this,
but since she's been
living abroad for ages,
she probably has a lot
of academic connections, right?
Maybe we could
ask her to sniff around a bit
about Dr. X?
Don't bring her up again.
She might be a business partner,
but after all...
After all, we used to be engaged.
Don't worry.
I won't make things
awkward for Mrs. Huo.
Since I've decided to come forward
as Dr. X,
I shouldn't get him
or anyone else dragged into this.
As soon as the research wraps up,
the paper gets published,
and United Pharma goes under,
this will all be over.
I'm going to crush United Pharma
and their academic fraud over NIT-33.
I'll send the paper trail of evidence
straight to the federal regulators.
(Let's eat out today.)
(I'll pick you up.)
(I booked a restaurant.)
Is my
makeup today
still uneven?
Um...
Don't get too close to me right now.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
Oh, really?
Don't.
We're at school.
So?
What are you talking about?
You asked me to check
if your makeup was uneven.
So, is it?
Your makeup looks great,
and so does your outfit.
Finally, something nice.
I thought
you wouldn't wear this outfit.
Well, I respect the contract.
I...
I have to do my best
to play the part of Mrs. Huo.
Shen Yan.
Here, Mr. Huo.
Come here.
ظآزSometimes we roll the diceظآز
ظآزTo see what the future hidesظآز
ظآزSpinning us round and round
like a never-ending rideظآز
ظآزBut I gave you everythingظآز
ظآزEven the songs I loved to singظآز
ظآزNothing can change the way
that a heart gets igniteظآز
ظآزCuz I know you give your heart
to me every dayظآز
ظآزAnd sometimes I know
the words can be hard to sayظآز
ظآزI know you feel itظآز
ظآزI feel it tooظآز
ظآزThis loveظآز
ظآزIt's me and youظآز
Miss Ye,
long time no see.
Just cut to the chase.
I'm not the one asking for favors here.
You're the one who called me out
asking to team up.
I already told you plenty
of the backstory
over the phone.
Are you sure
Beiyan
and Xu Nange are in a fake marriage?
You know how my family works.
(Temporary Marriage Agreement)
Without a marriage,
Beiyan can't get
full control of the business.
(Temporary Marriage Agreement)
But
this stunt of his
ruined my relationship.
Tell me your plan.
We can figure out the plan together.
I just feel like
you're the best fit
as the lady of the Huo family.
But my engagement to Huo Beiyan
was called off six months ago.
As long as you work with me,
I'll set everything up in advance
and make them hate each other.
I can clear all the obstacles
and pave the way
for your return.
Without any real, valuable intel,
don't expect me to place my bets.
I'll keep an eye out for intel.
But isn't my attitude
the most valuable thing here?
Honey,
take a seat.
Hey.
Enjoy your meal.
I don't see anyone spying on us here.
Calling me honey
startled me.
That brings us to today's main topic.
As they say, walls have ears.
So I think
we need to add a supplementary clause.
We need to constantly make sure
we address each other and act
like a married couple
at all times.
What a capitalist.
Slipping hidden clauses
into the contract again.
A supplementary clause
is still a clause.
Fine.
I got it.
Let's just eat.
I'm starving.
I'd like to see if this place
is better than your cooking.
Sir.
Ma'am.
Thank you.
(Angelica and Red Date Braised Lamb)
I'll get the wild mushrooms chicken
the peppercorns scallop soup,
and the angelica
and red date braised lamb.
Alright.
Just a moment.
Are we really eating this healthy
in the middle of the day?
Beiyan,
you have to strictly
stick to this medicinal diet.
No matter how busy you young people get,
you need to take care of your bodies
and start working
on expanding the Huo family tree.
You sound exactly like your dad.
Whose dad?
My bad.
Our dad.
Our dad, alright?
Here.
This is for you.
It's a little gift to mark
our first month together.
ظآزDarling, you go far awayظآز
There are two names on it.
One is Florence Nightingale,
and the other is you.
ظآزWe could go on a journeyظآز
ظآزI could take you inظآز
ظآزGarfunkel's got Simonظآز
ظآزBatman's got Robin tooظآز
ظآزEveryone's got a partnerظآز
ظآزTrained to help them throughظآز
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Huo?
You might need to find a place
where you can talk freely.
Make it quick.
I'm in the middle of a moment here.
Mr. Huo, this is huge news.
Listen.
We followed a clue
from a paper Dr. X
published three years ago
and tracked down
a defunct academic forum.
By cross-referencing
their old registration info
and posting habits,
we managed to find
the only existing photo
of Dr. X from behind.
And guess what?
Our initial search direction
might have been completely wrong.
Dr. X is a woman.
Are you sure?
Ab...
Absolutely sure.
Send me the photo.
And sync me on the details.
Got it.
(Mr. Huo,)
(this is the photo
of Dr. X from behind.)
(Reserved for Dr. Xu Nange)
ظآزWhat destiny brought us to meetظآز
ظآزTwo different worlds, a love so sweetظآز
ظآزA wish we made
in a past life, it seemsظآز
ظآزDestined to cross time and dream ظآز
ظآزLike a fairytale story toldظآز
ظآزA gentle breeze feels so boldظآز
ظآزAs your hair brushes past your earظآز
ظآزI long to kiss your cheek, my dearظآز
ظآزAll my longing, all my love for youظآز
ظآزHas never changed, it's forever trueظآز
ظآزIt's the hand of fate
that we meet againظآز
ظآزLet me hold you once againظآز
ظآزResting against your chestظآز
ظآزYour warmth shines like stars at nightظآز
ظآزLet me kiss you once againظآز
ظآزNo reason neededظآز
ظآزMy heart belongs to youظآز
ظآزI'm not afraid
to cross time to find youظآز