You're supposed to support me,
not dictate how my life should go.
- Well, it's because you--
- Let's talk later.
We're here to take him
on a trip, remember?
WHEEL ALIGNMENT
SUSPENSION CHECK
Mr. Thee!
Mr. Thee! Kongkwan!
Kongkwan, honey!
You should know
what you're supposed to do.
You can't get distracted like this.
And about Veluree too.
You--
Dad, please stop! Dad!
You have no right to do this!
Dad! Dad!
You ran off to Thailand again, didn't you?
I already told you,
stop doing stupid stuff like this
and start focusing
on our business already!
I'm an adult now, Dad.
Can you stop forcing me already?
An adult, you say?
Yet you still can't provide for yourself.
Should I provide for you till you die?
Keep drawing your stupid art,
and you'll starve to death for sure!
You need to get married
and help me run my business.
And stop it with this nonsense!
I'll prove it to you
that my passion isn't some nonsense.
I'm going to be a successful designer.
Just watch!
Hello, Anna?
Dump everything on that desk!
Sorry, I need to use the restroom.
Let's go.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
That was totally not okay.
He was touching my leg!
Yeah, but please stay with me!
Please?
Come on. Bottoms up.
Drink up.
- Are you having fun?
- Yes.
PLOY
What's up? Is something wrong?
I'm at my condo.
Khim,
I want to meet you and Mook.
Can we meet tomorrow?
Of course. I happen to be off tomorrow.
I'll hurry and call Mook tomorrow.
I miss you.
I miss you both too.
I'm hanging up now.
Let's meet at our usual spot tomorrow.
Eat plenty, so you'll stay healthy.
Is something wrong, Mook?
Well…
Just tell me what's on your mind.
Stop hesitating already.
It's Mr. Thee.
He told me he wanted
to eat your cooking again.
My, my, that's it?
I thought it'd be something serious.
Is he out of the hospital already?
He told me he could leave today.
Well, let me know when he's coming,
so I can buy some groceries.
Nice! I want to play with Thee again.
So you're fine with him
coming to our house now?
Well, of course!
And ask him if he wants
to eat anything in particular.
Okay, Mom.
Don't hold back, okay?
I've got a whole nother pot of that.
I'll be right back, Mom.
What's up?
Ploy agreed to meet with us.
Really?
She said to meet
at our usual spot after work.
Okay. I'll hurry up and finish work,
then I'll be right over.
Mook, she's going to be late!
Okay, Mom!
I'll talk to you later.
I've got to drive my kid to school.
See you this evening.
See you. Bye.
Coming!
About Mrs. Anna,
I must apologize again, Mr. Thee.
It's alright. I understand.
It was my mother's orders.
By the way,
how much does she know about Mook?
Just the basic details
and her family situation.
So, my mom knows Mook has a daughter.
Yes, sir.
Where are you going, Mr. Thee?
To go see Mook, of course.
Don’t we have a meeting
to finalize the campaign today?
Yes, we do. I already arranged
for a meeting room.
Come on, Mr. Pitak. I miss my girlfriend.
For our campaign with The One,
our team at A Round Trip Travel
has come up with many special campaigns
so that the customers who are couples
may come to The One's hotel
for all services concerning weddings.
We'll show you our slides
for more details.
Our customers may wish
to travel to Singapore,
to other countries,
or also here in Thailand.
For Thailand, we tried to find
only the good spots
that are hidden gems,
but also trending online currently.
THANK YOU
I'll leave you in charge
of our production and PR.
As for the promotion, I'll have
my hotel's marketing team handle it.
Sure.
As for the location for the honeymoon,
I was hoping we could use
one of The One's hotels.
And where's that?
Narin Beach Resort.
Narin Beach…
Oh, the one we've been to, right?
Great. A beachfront hotel's perfect
for the honeymoon campaign too.
But I never knew your group
also owned that hotel.
Yes, I'm signing a contract
to partner with them.
I've had the chance to meet Mrs. Narin.
She seems pretty sweet.
Enough about work.
Let's talk about your mom.
What did your mom say
about me dining at your house?
She said yes.
Let me know what day you'd want to come.
How about today? I miss Kongkwan.
Not today.
I've got an important meet-up
with my friends.
How about some other day?
I'll introduce you to my friends too.
Then sure.
Hey, don't worry.
I'll talk to Ploy.
Why isn't she here yet?
I wonder if she's okay.
She's supposed to be here an hour ago.
Should we call her?
I'll call her then. Okay…
Sorry, the number you've dialed
is currently unavailable.
She turned off her phone.
Sorry, the number you've dialed
is currently unavailable.
Maybe Top already knows?
SCUMBAG
Don't bother waiting for her.
She already knows
about when we had our fun.
Khim.
What happened?
Why? Are you telling on me
to your friends?
Listen, if you want to have friends,
maybe find better ones.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You're such an idiot.
That's why Khim
could fool you for so long.
Take a look at this.
Is this your oh-so-nice friend?
How could you do this to me? How?!
How could you?!
I didn't start it.
And actually,
she slept with me
the night before we got married.
Did she tell you that?
You think you can rely
on a horrible friend like her?
You're dumber than I thought.
Ploy must hate me so bad.
I'm sure she'll cut me off.
Calm down, okay?
I'll find a way to talk to her.
We've been mad at each other,
and we've fought,
but we've never stopped being friends.
But this time, it's seriously bad.
I should've listened to you all along.
I should've stopped being such a playgirl.
What's past is past. Don't blame yourself.
Top is the one to blame.
I won't let him ruin your lives
or any other woman's life anymore.
Thank you for understanding me, Mook.
VETERAN POLITICIAN RUNS FOR LOCAL OFFICE
INVITES SON-IN-LAW TO ENTER POLITICS
MINISTER PANSAK IS PAVING THE WAY
FOR HIS SON-IN-LAW TO ENTER POLITICS
- Are you for real?!
- Hot, hot!
Hey!
What got you so shocked?
Our boss is entering politics!
- Mr. Suetrong.
- Yes?
Did you know
about our boss entering politics?
May I see it?
"Veteran politician runs for local office,
invites son-in-law to enter politics."
Huh? I don't think so.
He never wanted to enter politics.
I think this was a misunderstanding.
But that's what the reporter wrote.
"Minister Pansak is paving the way
for his son-in-law to enter politics."
If he's really entering politics,
then what about our company?
You got everything right.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Is Mr. Pat really entering politics, Prao?
Not yet. But I'm going
to have him do it for real now.
He'll never be successful
with his stupid travel agency.
He's lucky it's not bankrupt yet.
I wonder how he'll avoid it this time.
Ploy never showed up today.
We can't get a hold of her either.
Do you know where her condo is?
I heard she moved to her husband's condo,
but I don't know where it is.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Yes, Mom?
I'm sorry?
Have some roselle juice, Ploy.
Thank you, Auntie.
I happened to have made some today.
You and Khim used to always ask for it.
Try it and let me know
if it's still as good.
Sure.
It's as good as ever.
Mook told me you got married.
How has it been?
Are you having a child soon?
Marriage is nothing
like I imagined, Auntie.
Calm down, honey.
It's normal that you'd have to adapt
in the beginning after you get married.
Every couple has this problem, Ploy.
Try to stay calm and work it out, okay?
Auntie…
Ploy!
So you know about everything?
Khim told me everything.
Ploy!
Khim, how'd you get here?
I called her.
I think it's time
we opened up to each other.
Ploy…
I'm sorry.
I never knew
being pleasure-seeking
would bring me so much pain.
You can be mad at me.
You can hate me all you want.
I understand.
At first, I was really shocked
at what I saw,
but the more I thought about it,
you were probably suffering
as much as I was.
I really didn't know
Top was going to marry you.
But when I found out,
I tried to come clean with you
so many times.
But…
Top threatened me.
He said if I told you about it,
he'd leak the video he took of you.
Khim told me
that apart from you two,
he also has videos of other women.
A scumbag like him
doesn't belong in our society.
If it hadn't happened to me, I'd find it
hard to believe Top's that kind of guy.
In front of my parents and everyone else,
he comes off so good-hearted and polite.
There's plenty of people
who are like him in our society.
In front of people,
they act like a good person,
but they secretly save their devilish side
for people who can't fight back.
No one dared to fight him back.
That's why he's still out there
doing these horrible things.
So what are you going to do?
Maybe you should tell your mom.
If I told Ma, at most,
we'd just get a divorce.
So what's your plan?
We need to stop him together,
so he can't hurt anyone else.
I'll tell the police.
Have you seen the news, Mr. Pat?
What news?
I'm sure Prao's behind it.
I thought so too.
PRAO
What is it, Prao?
Sure. I wanted to meet you anyway.
Who knew it'd always be so hard
to meet my son-in-law?
Last time, you just up and ran off.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm not used to being around
that many people.
Well, learn to get used to it.
Soon, you'll enter politics
and work with me.
You'll have to meet lots of people.
My dad invited you today
because he really wanted you
to officially work with him.
There's about to be a local election.
Dad wants you to run.
I already told you, Prao,
I don't want to enter politics.
I'm really not fit for it, Dad.
You should find someone else.
How long will you keep on struggling
with your agency?
I heard you've been in the red
for two years now, haven't you?
I'm working on fixing it,
and we've been doing better.
You can cash however much you'd like.
Think of it as a bonus
I'm paying in advance.
Then, come work with me officially.
As for your travel agency,
if you want to keep running it,
that's fine by me.
But do it as a hobby,
or find someone you trust
to run it for you.
See? Dad just wants what's best for you.
Please accept it.
Because if you don't,
who knows when you'll finally solve
your company's problems.
I really can't accept it.
Not this check
and not the job in politics.
I can deal with my own problems.
If you'll excuse me.
Pat!
With photos and videos secretly taken,
if only the victim or the plaintiff
appears in them,
they cannot indicate
who the perpetrator is.
But my husband
really took those videos, Officer.
- It's true!
- Then, I can file a report
and look for more evidence for this case.
In the meantime, if you two
have definitive proof
that he committed the crime,
please report it right away.
What should we do now? If we keep waiting,
Top will surely catch on to us first.
I'm going to find the evidence myself.
I'll make sure
that scumbag won't get away.
You sure have changed a lot, Ploy.
I don't want to run away anymore, Khim.
Me neither.
If I can help in any way,
please let me know.
Let's deal with that scumbag together.
Alright.
Whoa, hey!
We're just having dinner.
You didn't have to buy a gift basket.
Your mom's making me something delicious,
so, of course,
I couldn't come empty-handed.
Okay, let's go.
What? Why are you handing me that?
Go give it to her yourself.
Please just hold it for me.
I have to grab Kongkwan's gift.
Let's head inside. My mom's
made lots of delicious food.
This way.
Thank you.
Please save your money next time.
I'm just happy to have dinner with you.
Okay.
- Careful!
- Thee's here!
Good evening, Thee.
Good evening. I got you something too.
What is it?
Here it is! A huge box of colored pencils.
Thank you, Thee.
Can we color together sometime?
Of course.
Let's eat before the food gets cold.
- Sure.
- Let's go, Thee.
Go on.
Let's go.
Is it this way?
Here? Okay.
- There.
- Not like that.
- Yeah.
- Let's finish this part first.
You can color this part blue.
Can I help you, Mom?
Those two are still playing together?
Yeah. They're stuck together like glue.
Kongkwan seems very happy today.
She must be happy to have a new friend.
Where there's joy, there's also sorrow.
I want you to be prepared.
Yes, Mom.
I'll remember your words.
When the day comes,
I'll be prepared to handle it.
Thank you.
The food was so good.
It's been a while
since I got to eat your cooking.
Come again anytime.
You're always welcome here.
Thank you.
Ma'am,
would you and Kongkwan
like to go to the beach with me?
Mook and I are planning to go
and scout the venue for our campaign.
Yay! The beach?
I want to go too.
I want to go to the beach.
Please, let me come with you. Please?
Please join us, ma'am.
I'll take that as a yes.
Then, if you'll excuse me. Goodnight.
Goodnight.
Kongkwan, I'll be going now.
Goodnight, Thee.
A promise is a promise, okay?
I promise.
Come here. Sit with me for a minute.
Come on, I'll walk you.
Kongkwan's really happy today.
Thank you so much.
I'm the one who should thank you.
It's been a while
since I had a home-cooked meal.
Your mom and Kongkwan are so sweet too.
Your family really feels like a home.
Of course.
Once I'm done handling things,
I'll take you to meet my family too.
And
why do I need to meet them?
I just want to take my girlfriend
to meet my family.
Would you mind toasting with me?
How annoying.
It's just a toast. Don't be so stuck-up.
- You want to say cheers that bad?
- Yes.
You bitch!
- Hey!
- Let go of me! Let go!
What's going on here?
It's you!
Let's get out of here.
It's dangerous. Let's go.
Trying to run?
If you get any closer,
prepare to spend nights in jail.
- Give me that!
- Stop!
‪Let's go.
Careful.
- Where are you going?!
- That way!
Stop running! Stop!
Where are you going?
Don't be afraid of them.
What's going on here?
These two were harassing this woman.
- It's you two again? When will you learn?
- Let go!
- Come on!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Can't we ever meet in a normal situation?
My name is Bella.
You can call me Bell.
I'm Anapat.
Hey, it's fine. He works for me.
Miss, you should've let me
come inside with you.
Just now,
if something happened to you,
your father would've killed me.
I'm not a prisoner.
I don't need someone
to watch me all the time.
And don't tell Dad.
I don't want to bother explaining.
Understood.
I hope we can meet in a normal situation
someday, Mr. Anapat.
Yes.
Everyone!
- Wait.
- Don't you dare!
- Throw me that ball.
- No!
Thank you, Mr. Thee,
for bringing Mom and Kongkwan along.
It's been a while since our family
got to travel out of town.
It's nothing. You don't have to thank me.
- Hello!
- Hello, Mr. Thee!
What's up? Are you tired
from working so hard?
Mook, we'll be checking out
the ballrooms and the other areas now
for our presentation.
Okay. Oh, don't forget to take pictures,
so we can send them to the event team.
Sure.
What's wrong, May? Do you need to pee?
Mr. Thee, we'd like to thank you
for inviting us on this vacation.
Mr. Thee invited you here to work.
- It's not a vacation!
- Stop interrupting me!
Thank you.
You're welcome. Think of it as working
out of the office and also a vacation.
Okay.
In that case, let's get to work.
- Yeah, go.
- Please excuse us.
- Let's get to work.
- Don't forget to take pictures!
- Come on!
- I know!
Thee, come play with me!
- I've got to go.
- Okay.
Inviting him to get sand all over, huh?
Don't do that. It'll get in your eyes.
I'm coming!
Careful, you'll get sand on you.
That's alright.
- Here.
- What's this game?
What's this game? Go on, tell Mr. Thee.
Let's see, between you and Thee,
who will do better?
Oh,
off to work already?
Yes.
If I take any more days off,
I'm sure they'll fire me.
Have you made your peace about Khim?
I really didn't mean it.
And also, I wasn't the one
who made a move first.
You believe me, right?
With bad friends,
I just have to cut them off.
I don't have time for that nonsense, Top.
That's more like it.
I like it when you're this easy
to deal with.
I'm meeting up with my friends tonight.
I might not come home.
Just go to bed without me.
You can do whatever
and go wherever you want.
It's good that we both
stay in our own lane.
I'm off to work now.
LET'S LEARN ABOUT IPO
My unit isn't so big.
‪You're okay with it?
‪Of course. No problem at all.
Let me give you a tour.
This is the kitchen.
- Back there is the laundry room.
- Okay.
And here…
Here's the restroom.
This is the storage room.
And then this
is our bedroom.
Isn't it lovely?
It is.
It's got an en-suite bathroom
and a walk-in closet.
What about this room, Top?
It's my office.
It's so messy, though.
Please don't tidy up in there,
- or I'll lose track of my stuff.
- Okay.
Are you fine with living here?
Yes.
I left something at my condo.
I'll meet you in a bit. Okay.
How'd it go with the police?
I'm okay. Don't worry about me, Mook.
I've got some evidence now,
but we'll have to plan really well.
Top's a cunning guy.
We'll need to catch him red-handed.
Okay. Well, if I can help
in any way, just let me know.
Be careful, Ploy.
I won't let him hurt me anymore, Mook.
Talk to you later.
Okay.
Is something wrong?
You seemed pretty serious.
My friend called asking for some advice.
Is it Ms. Khim?
It's Ploy, another best friend of mine.
I'll introduce you later.
Where's Kongkwan and my mom?
Kongkwan got tired, so your mom
took her back to their room to rest.
Do you want to eat? I'll order something.
Hello, Mr. Thee.
This is Mr. Chadchai.
He's the manager here.
This is Mook.
She's my girlfriend.
Hey.
Hello. I'm Mook. I'm Mr. Thee's assistant.
Hello, Ms. Mook.
I've already taken care
of that thing we talked about.
Let's talk in the meeting room.
Sure.
If you'll excuse me.
HOUSE NO. 12/3 - TWO METERS - ONE MINUTE
What do you need Preaw's address for?
My friend's opening a coffee shop.
She's looking for someone to help her,
so I wanted to ask Preaw if she'd be down.
Why not call and ask her? It's easier.
She must've changed her phone number.
I can't get a hold of her.
I went to her house,
but she wasn't there either.
She must've moved back
out of town to her other house.
That's why I came to ask you if you know
the address of her house
that's in another province.
I think I may have it
because Preaw's asked me
to mail something there before.
Let me find it first,
then I'll send it right over.
Okay. Thanks.
Khim? How'd you get here?
Take this money
and take your son to the doctor.
Don't worry about your work.
Take care of him until he gets better.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you, I don't think
my son would make it, Mrs. Narin.
Thank you.
Oh, Ms. Mook!
- Hello, Mrs. Narin.
- Hello.
Is that housekeeper okay?
Her son's sick,
so I told her to take some time off
to look after him.
That's so kind of you.
You sure take good care of your staff.
My staff are like my family.
If there's something
I can do to help, I'll gladly try my best.
Are you here on vacation?
Did you book a room yet?
Oh, I already checked in,
but I'm not exactly on vacation.
I'm here with Mr. Thee
to scout the venue for an event.
So Mr. Thee's here too?
Yes, he said he'd use this place
as the venue for our campaign.
He said it's one of his group's hotels.
Did he not notify you in advance?
- I'm really sorry.
- Oh!
I thought he already notified you,
so I had my staff scout the hotel.
No worries at all.
Mr. Thee will become
the hotel's partner anyway.
How about this?
Let me give you a tour of my hotel,
so we can talk while we walk.
Sounds good! Thank you so much.
- Let's go. This way.
- I really appreciate it.
How long are you staying with us?
Uh, I'm not sure yet, but…
This is the small ballroom.
It seats up to 50 people.
The main ballroom
for activities is just upstairs.
I see.
Let's take a look, shall we?
Oh, Mrs. Narin.
It's good that you're here.
Mr. Thee's here to scout the venue
for The One's new campaign.
I was just about to let you know.
Hello, Mr. Thee. Welcome.
I've gone over the contract with Mr. Thee.
Did you find any issues with it?
If everything looks good,
we can sign it soon.
Everything looks good.
Let's set a date for the signing.
Let's go eat. I'm hungry.
Let's not keep
your mom and Kongkwan waiting.
Then, if you'll excuse me.
Thank you for the tour, Mrs. Narin.
I should go read the contract again.
Okay.
Why are you so cold towards Mrs. Narin?
Is there a problem between you two?
Not really.
It's just my work style.
I need a clear boundary.
Why'd you want to invest in this place?
After all, in this economy,
a hotel won't be able to make much profit.
Because what I'll get
is more than just a profit.
I'll get to do
what I've been longing to do.
I'm not ready to face
the same problems again.
You should go back to be
with your fiancée and your mom.
Mook…
- Boss!
You told me to compete with you, remember?
…that Bell is the fiancée of Thee,
an executive at TJ Group.
We also have some great news
to share with you very soon.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya