My name is Bella. You can call me Bell.
I'm Anapat.
Hello, Mr. Thee. Welcome.
I've gone over the contract with Mr. Thee.
A hotel won't be able to make much profit.
Because what I'll get
is more than just a profit.
I'll get to do
what I've been longing to do.
Enough about work.
I need to rest my brain.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Good.
I wanted to talk to Joe about our kids.
RECENTS - BELLA BELL
- Hello.
- Bell!
Hello.
How's Thailand this time around?
It's quite fun.
The people here are smiley and sweet,
and there are tons of cool new spots.
I just hope you won't find
anyone sweeter than Thee.
There you go again with that nonsense.
What you see as nonsense is my happiness.
Is something the matter, Dad?
I just wanted to tell you
to get ready to marry Thee.
I've talked to his parents.
Dad, I already told you,
I've got nothing against marrying Thee,
but just don't forget our promise,
that you won't stop me
from doing what I love
and that you'll stay out of my life.
You're just as stubborn as your mother.
Did you do what I asked, Pitak?
Yes.
Mr. Thee still doesn't know you're here.
Good.
I'm taking Bell to surprise him.
Are you ready, Bell?
Yes.
Mr. Thee sure is nice.
He gave us a nice room to stay,
and he hosted this beach party for us.
I'd better give him
the Best Husband award.
Why don't you pray for it
in your next life?
Because in this life,
Mook already bagged him.
You're right! Mr. Thee
spoils Mook in every way.
He clearly loves her a lot.
I swear to do only good deeds.
Please bless me with someone
good and caring in my next life.
As for this life,
I'll remember to pray for my enemies,
so they can stop bugging me!
Pray for the shrimp too.
He really needs it.
- Calm down.
- "I'm so cooked!"
- Auntie!
- Are you hungry?
Are you hungry, Kongkwan?
Auntie.
- Yes, dear?
- You're here just in time.
We're almost done grilling the seafood.
Please have a seat.
Can I help you with anything?
No, Mom!
You two can just wait over there.
- Follow me.
- Please.
- Yes.
- You look pretty.
Thank you, Auntie.
- You can sit there at the end.
- Thank you.
Go ahead, Kongkwan. Up.
- Look! You hungry?
- Where's Mook, though?
Mook said she's inviting Mrs. Narin,
the CEO of the hotel, to join us.
She'll be back soon.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Doesn't it look delicious?
It smells so good that I got hungry.
Then don't hold back, okay?
If it's not good, blame the chef.
Please, Mrs. Narin, join us.
It'll be fun. I promise.
- Please?
- I don't know.
I wanted you to meet my team too.
Mr. Thee.
I'm inviting Mrs. Narin to join our party.
I don't want to bother him. I'd better go.
Please feel free to join.
We rarely get to eat together.
Let's go, Mrs. Narin.
Thank you. Let's go.
You're here!
- So many people!
- There they are.
Kongkwan, look, they're here!
Look!
What's up, honey?
This is Mrs. Narin, the owner here.
- Good evening.
Good evening.
Mrs. Narin, this is my team,
and that's my mother.
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
Oh, and this is Kongkwan.
She's my daughter.
Oh, really?
Kongkwan, say hello to Mrs. Narin.
Hello, Aunt Narin.
Hello, dear.
Aren't you cute?
My son's just as cute as you.
You have a son too?
Yes.
Why don't you sit with me?
- Come on.
- I see.
ANAPAT
Sorry, I have to take this.
Please, go ahead.
Please have a seat.
Thank you. How's the food?
It's very good!
- Thank you.
- It's great. Thank you.
Where are you, Boss?
I'm almost there, Mook.
How's the location?
The rooms and the ballrooms are good,
but they'll need more decorations
to fit the concept.
You should hurry.
The party's in full swing.
Okay. I'll be right over.
Okay. Drive safe.
So Thee's here, Aunt Anna?
They're all here.
There are others too, Mr. Pitak?
Yes.
Who are they?
It's a long story, Ms. Bell.
There's nothing we can do now.
You'd better hurry.
- And drive me to work.
- Oh.
Mr. Thee,
is Mr. Pitak not here with you?
Why haven't I seen him?
He said he had an important event
and he couldn't come.
But he actually handled
this party and our accommodation.
You even noticed Mr. Pitak's not here.
How come you never care about me as much?
Sorry about that.
Mook sure is taking her time
with that call.
Right?
That's Mr. Pitak!
I thought he had an event?
Mom.
Everyone, this is my mother.
- Good evening.
Good evening.
I heard Thee was hosting
a party for his team,
so I wanted to greet all of you.
This is Bell, Thee's fiancée.
Mook.
Mommy.
Come.
I take it you're Ms. Veluree.
Thee told me you work with him
and you're very talented.
You look pretty young.
It's hard to believe
your daughter's this big already.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
I should go to bed.
Sure.
I usually don't stay up late.
Mook,
please walk me.
Let's go.
But I don't want to go yet, Grandma.
Can I stay with Thee?
Kongkwan,
listen to Mommy, okay?
You promised me, remember?
Let's go, honey.
Thee!
Aunt Anna.
What's all this about? Who's that woman?
If you don't answer me,
I'll go tell my dad.
Bell, wait!
Bell!
Sorry for killing the mood.
It's okay.
Well then, please enjoy.
- Okay, thank you.
- Good night.
What on earth is going on?
This is real, right?
Am I dreaming?
Can you slap me awake?
Of course.
Did it hurt?
- Did it hurt?
- Yeah.
I'm not dreaming!
I feel bad for Mook.
Mook. Mook.
Mook. Hold on.
I'm tired of running away, Mom.
I need to talk to him.
Then, I'd better take Kongkwan to bed.
Okay.
Kongkwan,
go to our room with Grandma.
I need to talk to Thee first.
Bye-bye, Thee. I have to go to bed now.
Let's go, honey.
How come you never told me
about your fiancée?
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect my mom to do this.
But I did plan
to straighten things out first,
and then I'd tell you.
But your mom did that
to warn me to stay away from you.
I won't allow it to go
according to my mom's plan!
What about your fiancée?
What can you do about that?
I do believe…
that you've been sincere with me.
But I'm just not ready to face
the same problems again.
Please just return
to your fiancée and your mom.
I won't let you go.
We need to accept the truth, Mr. Thee.
Even if it hurts…
we can't keep running away anymore.
I won't give up!
I really love you, Mook.
Kongkwan's really happy today.
Thank you so much.
I'm the one who should thank you.
It's been a while
since I had a home-cooked meal.
Your mom and Kongkwan are so sweet too.
Once I'm done handling things,
I'll take you to meet my family too.
Why do I need to meet them?
I just want to show off
my girlfriend to my family.
This is Bell, Thee's fiancée.
Mook.
Boss.
What happened, Mook?
Why are you crying?
Mr. Thee has a fiancée.
I made the wrong decision again.
Do you know what you've done?
I did what any mother should do.
I told you, Thee,
you'll have to marry Bell, no matter what.
When it comes to work,
I never got involved in your decisions.
But this, I can't allow it,
especially when that woman
already has a child.
But Bell and I don't love
each other. You know that.
It doesn't matter.
What matters and has to happen
is that you need to marry Bell.
Everyone's agreed to it.
We've agreed to plan a wedding
as soon as possible.
I used to agree to it
because I never thought
I could love someone,
but then I met Mook.
She made me realize
that I must do everything
for the one I love.
And I won't reluctantly do
what I'll regret later.
Do you really love that woman, Thee?
I'm sorry, Bell. I really love her.
Mom,
stop trying to force our breakup
because it'll never happen.
Well, let's see who'll win!
If you keep making stupid decisions,
I won't go easy on you anymore.
I built you up,
but I can take you down too.
Thee, come back here! Thee, come here!
Uh, I'll talk to him for you.
Aunt Anna,
you should sit down and rest.
He really went too far.
I've never seen him act this way.
Bell, you won't leave him, right?
You still love Thee, right?
Mr. Thee.
If you keep this up,
you'll only make it harder for Ms. Mook.
You know Mrs. Anna well.
The more you care about Mook,
the more she'll have to face trouble.
But I have to explain myself to her!
Tomorrow,
Mrs. Anna is flying back to attend
an association event with Mr. John.
Once she's back there,
you can go meet Ms. Mook, okay?
Please believe me, Mr. Thee.
If you really want to fight for her,
you have to be very patient.
Please get some rest.
As for your mom,
I'll deal with her, so don't worry.
Mom.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I made the wrong decision again, Mom.
It's okay, honey. It's okay.
Mrs. Anna left Thailand.
She said she'd call you later.
What are you going to do now, Thee?
Aunt Anna seemed really angry.
I won't let her do as she pleases anymore.
If I hadn't seen it for myself,
I wouldn't have believed
that you're a guy
who can fall in love this hard.
I really love her, Bell.
And I'll do anything
to show Mom that I really love her.
I won't marry anyone
other than Mook. You understand me, right?
I'm not sure I understand
because I don't believe in love
like you do.
But as for our wedding,
I'll let you decide.
I'm just using it as leverage
against my dad anyway.
If you want to call it off,
I'm fine with that.
Anyway, good luck.
I'll get going then.
Mr. Pitak's driving me.
Okay.
Ms. Veluree and her friends
already checked out of the hotel.
Thank you.
MOOK
Ms. Mook and her friends
already checked out this morning.
Please give her some time.
What she faced last night
was really serious.
Thank you for your advice,
but I can deal with this myself.
Thank you.
Mook already went to work.
She said she had an important meeting.
With everything that happened,
I apologize, ma'am.
You should apologize to Mook instead.
But speaking as her mom,
I don't want to see her
in that state again either.
I'll make sure everything's sorted out.
Even if you've dealt
with your fiancée situation,
honestly,
I don't think there's any way
you can deal with your mother.
I've seen it time and time again,
kids like you, who believe
love always wins.
I'm serious about Mook. I really love her.
I'll prove myself to you.
If you can't keep your promise,
please stop hurting Mook.
You just had to be there.
When Mr. Thee's mom showed up
to the party with his fiancée,
there was this really intense energy.
- I almost couldn't breathe.
- Whoa.
So, how's Mook doing?
She took Kongkwan
and her mom too, didn't she?
I really feel bad for her.
It must've been a real shock.
Oh, Mr. Thee, if you're already engaged,
why fool Mook?
Aw, man. I got so happy
that she found a great boyfriend.
Turns out he's even worse than her ex!
What did Boss say?
He was comforting her last night.
But he's got to be so mad at Mr. Thee.
Thank God they didn't meet last night,
otherwise it would've been…
Would've been what?
A mess, of course!
Where's Ms. Mook?
W-wait! Mr. Thee!
- Mr. Thee!
- W-wait! Mr. Thee!
Are you alright?
Please go home and rest.
I'll meet our client with Whan.
I'm alright, Boss.
I can separate my work and personal life.
I'm worried about you, Mook.
Don't push yourself.
Mr. Thee! Mr. Thee!
Please don't go in there, Mr. Thee!
- Mr. Thee, please listen. Please.
- Mr. Thee!
I need to talk to Mook urgently.
I have nothing to say to you.
Mook.
Please listen to me.
We need to talk this out.
Mook.
- Boss!
You told me to compete with you, remember?
Don't worry. I'm serious about Mook.
So, if you also like her
and wish to compete with me,
then by all means.
But if not,
get out of my way.
If you can't make Mook happy,
then get out of her life.
Mook.
I want to scream and apologize to myself
For being too stupid
It hurts so bad I could die
Yet I keep pushing myself…
Why is my life
so messed up right now, Boss?
I understand
that happiness can disappear so fast…
but isn't this a bit too fast?
That's just how life is.
You can never predict
what will happen to you.
I think…
I'd better stay
as far away from him as I can.
No talking, no meeting, no contact.
Maybe it'll help me move on more easily.
Don't worry about that.
I'll talk to Mr. Thee.
Thank you, Boss.
MR. PITAK
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
I'm sorry, Ms. Mook.
I'm just doing my job.
I understand.
Good luck, Ms. Mook.
Have a seat.
Thank you for meeting with me.
Let me just get to the point,
so I won't keep you for too long.
Sure.
You know Thee's got
a bright future ahead of him,
and I've found a perfect partner for him.
I don't mean to disrespect you,
but you've been married before,
and you're divorced at such a young age.
You're quite talented at your job,
but to me,
it's nothing special.
Plus, I don't see any way
you can support Thee
to help him succeed in life.
I'm sure you understand
how a mother feels.
Mothers like us always want
what's best for our children.
No, I don't understand.
I don't understand
why you look down on others
and only see your son's worth.
If I have to break up with Mr. Thee,
it's only because I can't stand having
a boyfriend whose mom behaves this way,
not because I'm divorced
or because I don't have
an outstanding career.
But don't worry,
because I have to choose
what's best for me too.
Hopefully, we won't have to waste time
discussing this again.
Is something the matter?
I'd like to handle
The One's project in place of Mook
because Mook is no longer comfortable
to meet you like before.
I won't allow it.
She has to continue handling it.
Please don't do this, Mr. Thee.
Don't use work as an excuse
when you can't even protect her.
You're not even in a state
where you can protect her.
Please let her go.
Mr. Anapat.
I suggest you take another look
at our contract,
because what you're trying to do
will affect the contract we signed.
How's Mook doing, Boss?
She's still devastated.
She'll need more time.
As for her work,
I've talked to Mr. Thee.
We'll continue our project,
but I'll handle it in place of Mook.
But in the contract,
it clearly specifies
that Mook has to be in charge.
Won't this cause an issue, Boss?
If that's what the contract says,
I'll keep being in charge until it ends.
Mook.
I'll show them
that we're only where we're at
because we're professional enough.
- Are you fine with meeting Mr. Thee?
- Yeah!
Sooner or later, I'll have to move on.
It's no big deal.
Mook, you rock!
Stop.
Please keep a distance between us.
- Mook.
- Stop trying. It's pointless,
because every time you step closer,
I'll keep stepping further away.
I'm really sorry
about what happened.
I never meant to hide it from you, Mook.
I just wanted to solve the problem first
before telling you.
Which problem?
Your fiancée
or your mom?
Mr. Pitak told me
my mom spoke with you today.
Are you okay?
I'm pretty good.
Your mom's quite straightforward.
She keeps things simple.
She made it very clear
that there should be
a distance between us.
But don't worry about our work.
I can separate my personal life…
or rather,
nonsense, and my work.
- Mook, listen to me--
- You should do the same.
To start with,
stop coming here.
This has nothing to do with work.
If you'll excuse me.
You've talked to Mr. Thee, right?
He was parked there waiting for you
since early in the evening.
Yes.
Don't worry, Mom.
I can get through this.
What's up, Ploy?
I have the evidence
to hold Top accountable now.
Are you sure?
Yes,
but I'm worried that it won't be enough.
Send me all of his information.
I think I know how to deal with him.
Take a look at this.
Is this your oh-so-nice friend?
- Excuse me, Mook.
- Come in.
- Here's your coffee. Careful, it's hot.
- Okay.
Is Boss here yet?
He won't be here this morning.
He said he's going to a party at The One.
What party? Why haven't
I heard about this?
It's a welcome party
for Mr. Thee's fiancée.
We were invited too, but Boss told us
not to tell you.
Hold on, Whan.
Yes?
Call an urgent meeting.
I have a new project for our team.
Why didn't you tell me
before hosting an event?
Why'd you need to host this party
and make a big fuss?
Well, Mr. Joe
is about to sign a contract
for a megaproject with TJ Group.
He wants some certainty from us.
I'm sure you know
that signing this contract
will greatly increase our company's stock.
But we could've just announced
the signing and the project details.
What if they ask about you and Bell?
What do I tell them?
Don't you fall in love so hard
that it affects TJ Group.
Please cooperate with me.
You just need to stand there and smile.
I'll handle everything else.
What?
Do you not know how to drive?
Hey.
It's you again?
Thank God it's you.
I'm really late, and I'm in a big rush.
Would you mind parking my car for me?
I'm not very good at it.
Call me when you're done.
I'll be at the party at this hotel.
Bye. Please do it for me.
- May I take a picture?
- Sure.
Move closer, please.
‪Perfect.
- Good.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you very much for coming today.
- Of course.
- My pleasure.
- Hello, Mrs. Anna.
Hello, Mr. Joe.
Welcome to The One.
Thank you for hosting
this welcome party for my daughter.
It's to celebrate our success.
To catch a criminal?!
Yes, and we must make no mistakes.
We need to catch him
successfully in one go.
How are we going to do that, Mook?
Who is he?
He seems so nice and polite.
If you didn't tell me,
I'd never take him for a bad guy.
He's my husband.
Ploy, have a seat.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
This is Ploy, my best friend.
Hello.
His name is Top.
On the outside, he seems nice
and polite.
He likes to make merit and help people.
PIAMSUK ORPHANAGE
But he has another side
no one knows about.
A dark side, if you will.
You see, he likes to get close to women
and when they agree to sleep with him,
he'd secretly film them to blackmail them.
And even worse,
he likes to beat women.
I can confirm it
because I've faced it first-hand.
If he did all this,
why didn't you go to the police?
I did.
But I don't have proof
that he filmed those videos.
Plus, if I just wait
for the police to handle it,
I'm scared he'll catch on to me
and destroy the evidence.
Then he'll never be arrested for sure.
MOOK
It's time, Mr. Thee.
Ms. Bella's arrived.
Do I really need to do this, Mr. Pitak?
I'm sure you were prepared
for this to happen.
Mrs. Anna won't back down so easily.
I won't either.
We didn't really have to come.
Our company's got nothing
to do with The One.
I just wanted to see it with my own eyes,
the kind of face she'll make when she sees
his actual girlfriend.
Mr. Pat.
I can't get hold of Mook.
Do you know where she is?
No, I don't.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
First of all, TJ Group
would like to thank you all
for taking the time
to come to our party today.
Today, I wanted to host a humble party
to welcome Thee's bride-to-be.
‪Who?
Without further ado,
I'd like to introduce you
to Bella, Thee's fiancée!
But before, you told the press
that you were dating Ms. Veluree.
There's been a little misunderstanding.
So we hosted this party today
to provide the press
with accurate information,
which is that Bell
is the fiancée of Mr. Thee,
an executive at TJ Group.
We're also about to have great news
to share with you all very soon.
- Actually--
- Our families
are co-investing in a megaproject.
And I assure you, it's a project
that'll make everyone go, "Wow."
Please give a big hand
to Mr. Joe, an executive
of Victoria Industry Group
and also an important partner of ours!
- This camera, please.
- Thank you.
- This camera too.
- Perfect.
- One more, please.
- Thank you.
‪-Good!
‪-One more, please.
‪Perfect!
- This camera too.
- Smile, please.
- Perfect.
- Thank you.
Sorry.
You never called me, but I saw you
back there, so I waited here for you.
Hey. My car key, please?
Thank you. You saved me again.
I didn't know you were Mr. Thee's fiancée.
And?
Why'd you have to hide from his mom?
Well, it's enough family time for now.
I have things to do.
Wait!
Here.
Do you know this address?
I'm not quite familiar
with the roads in Thailand.
Now you're asking for it!
‪-Let go!
‪-Ploy, stop! Don't help me!
Let go!
How come you got here
with Mr. Pat last night?
It's a long story, Thee.
Yesterday I saw Mr. Anapat and Mook.
They seemed really close.
Does he have a crush on her too?
I'm really worried about you.
Don't risk your life like that again.
I wouldn't know what to do if something
were to happen to you.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya