I bought a chair.
My room is small, so I got a folding one.
(Episode 9: Sheltering from
the Rain and Huddling Close)
The first person to
sit in this chair was...
Phew...
Tokyo is as crowded as ever.
- I'm exhausted.
- My mom.
This morning, Takako
suddenly said she couldn't drive.
So I had to rush and
call a cab to the bus stop.
Then I had to switch from a bus to a train
just to get here.
At that Shinjuku station, ah...
You know, what's that place called?
The one with all the buses.
- The bus terminal?
- Ah.
Right, right, right.
You have a hospital appointment
at nine tomorrow, right?
I'll go with you.
By the way,
are you sure you can go home the
same day as your cataract surgery?
You don't have to come with me.
I'm staying at Fumi-chan's tonight.
She's going with me tomorrow.
Oh, how's Kuji-san?
Ah...
Yeah.
He's doing well.
You know,
I've always wanted to be with you.
With you, Kuji.
Nothing much has changed since that day.
Our heartbeats pound together,
making it impossible
to tell whose is whose.
It's as if our bodies have become one.
But I also know
that we can never truly merge.
And that alone makes me anxious.
"Life In Smokey Blue"
"The Bouncing Ball and
the Land I Want to See"
What made you decide
to translate it this way?
Since it's a children's book,
I thought it would be good
to use engaging words
to convey how fun the story is.
So for you, Azuma-san,
this was a bit of a departure?
Yes.
While your past translations
have tended to be stiff
due to their precision,
they're gradually starting to change.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
There's also this.
A translation competition...
Competitions can be a matter of luck,
but there's no harm in trying.
That's what I think.
What should I do?
Should I enter?
Delicious!
This must have been expensive.
It was half-off.
It's okay to splurge every
once in a while, right?
It is from a department
store food hall, after all.
Did something happen?
Hm?
No, it's just...
You seem really happy.
I can't hide anything
from you, Shizuka-chan.
Want to hear about it?
- Not really.
- Come on, let me tell you.
Okay, okay.
Today...
my teacher said my
translation style has changed.
That it's not so stiff anymore.
Oh.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
Then Hara-san and I were talking
about entering a translation
competition together.
It's just a small one,
but since you took on that essay job, Kuji,
I thought I'd give it a try too.
Ah.
Sauce.
Oh.
Beef bourguignon?
Wait, isn't this from the Imperial Hotel?
Nukita-san brought it by earlier.
He came to check on
the progress of the essay.
Wow.
What a cool guy.
It used to be my father's favorite.
How's the essay coming along?
I haven't made any progress at all.
I see.
Today,
I went to see Mikami-san.
Yeah.
Mikami-san...
it seems she's moving into a nursing home.
And so...
Once you're all settled in,
please let me come visit
you at the nursing home.
Shizuka-san,
I'm afraid I must decline.
Huh?
I'm very grateful for your
kindness, Shizuka-san.
But...
I want to forever remain in your memory
as Mikami-san the housekeeper.
I see.
That's her way of being
considerate, I guess.
Yeah.
It feels a little lonely,
but at the same time,
I'm also a bit relieved.
It was the same when my father passed away.
I feel like when I'm
trying to write this essay,
the weak and heartless side of me
is being brutally exposed.
It's ready.
Thanks.
- Here, this is for you.
- Hm?
What's this?
Tamaki...
He said he wanted to
borrow an interesting book.
Thanks, I'll give it to him.
Are you eating properly?
How old do you think I am?
Don't worry.
I'm eating well, sleeping well,
and working well.
That's good.
Sis, is everything okay over there?
We're all fine, but...
Mom...
her health hasn't been great lately.
But she seemed so
energetic just the other day.
I guess it's partly her age.
She's become forgetful,
and her movements are a bit unsteady.
So I think she's feeling a little anxious.
I heard she's planning
to get a checkup soon.
I had no idea.
That's because Mom
didn't want to worry you.
Can you keep an eye on her?
Sooner or later, I won't be able to
handle everything on my own.
Yeah.
I understand.
You didn't have to come
all the way from Tokyo.
I had the day off.
How's work at the cram school?
It's... fine.
- Azuma-san, this way please.
- Okay.
Should I take that?
It's okay.
You said you're not feeling
well and are feeling down,
but the tests didn't show anything serious.
I see...
But I get heart palpitations
when I wake up in the morning.
As for feeling down, I suggest
you see a psychosomatic specialist.
Psychosomatic?
- Is that...
- We don't specialize in that field here.
We can do an MRI or other tests,
but we can't diagnose symptoms like these.
So, do I need the tests?
That's up to you.
Up to me...
Then what am I supposed to do?
Like I said, it's your decision.
Um, I...
Then we won't.
- We're not getting treated here.
- Huh?
Mom...
- Let's go home.
- Doctor...
Mom.
Let's go.
Sorry for cutting the
appointment short like that.
Don't be.
It's my fault for not being
able to explain myself properly.
I just caused trouble for
the doctor and for you.
I really hate being like this.
Watch the steps.
Thank you.
You've in your own world.
Oh, be quiet.
How's your mom doing?
You went to the hospital with her, right?
It's a real headache.
That doctor was clearly
impatient with my mom.
No, I actually get it.
We weren't there for a therapy session.
And doctors are only human.
But still...
when I think about my
mom when I'm not around,
I wonder if she's always
been treated like that.
Do you want me to recommend
the hospital my father used to go to?
I know the director there pretty well.
It's a bit far, in the city,
but I think they'll be more thorough.
Hmm...
Thanks, but I'll keep looking for a
hospital that's easier for my mom to get to.
The doctors there are great.
The staff is very kind.
The care is excellent.
- I'm sure your mom would...
- Kuji.
Do you really think
just any old woman
would get the same treatment as
'Kuji Yoshiharu' wherever she goes?
That's not...
Thank you
for being so thoughtful about my mom.
For now, I need to focus on
preparing for the translation competition.
- Azuma, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I know you meant well.
Let me give you a ride.
No, really, I'm fine.
Good luck with your essay.
[He's looking up hospital reviews,
specifically related to psychiatry]
Sensei.
There's something I don't understand.
What is it?
Right here.
Sensei, is something wrong?
Hmm?
You seem a little down.
I'm perfectly fine.
I was just lost in thought.
Oh, good.
You're so considerate, Takechi.
Now you just need to master the grammar,
and you'll be perfect.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh, this question...
It looks like it might be right...
I always used to think
I would never become like my father.
As a scholar and a translator,
I respect him.
But I never admired
his arrogant personality.
I thought I was different from my father.
I've always believed that.
Do you really think just any old woman
would get the same treatment as
'Kuji Yoshiharu' wherever she goes?
Azuma, I'm sorry.
Ma'am, are you alright?
Take your time. It's okay.
Well, you caught me in a cool moment.
Yeah, that was really cool.
I just did what anyone would do.
How's studying for your
entrance exams going?
Is it going well?
Yeah.
It's going okay, I guess.
You know,
I want to be a cool adult
like Kuji-san and Saku-chan.
I'm honored that you'd say that.
But I'm not that cool, really.
Huh?
Really?
I think being a translator is super cool.
It must be a tough job, right?
It's not so much that it's tough...
Well...
In the field of medical translation,
there's something called an
'informed assent form' for children.
It's a document given to children when
they're invited to participate in trials
to test a drug's effectiveness and safety.
While you're trying to figure out how
to translate it so a child can understand,
you also think about the
children who are battling illnesses.
And it just breaks your heart.
Behind the words are real people.
With their own lives.
I always remind myself
never to forget that.
That's so cool.
Kuji-san, you really are the coolest.
So, Tamaki, what kind of
adult do you want to be?
Oh...
My mom once told me
the meaning behind my name.
The character for 'Tamaki'
means 'ring' or 'circle'.
It means 'a circle that connects people'.
I see.
I hope I can become someone like that.
You're pretty cool too, Tamaki.
Huh?
You think so?
Oh, shoot.
I have to get to cram school.
Oh.
This is...
I've been reading it lately. I heard
Saku-chan read it in middle school too.
I got the dried sweet potatoes.
They're delicious.
Could you give them to Kuji-san for me?
Sure.
And...
I found a new hospital for you.
We can go check it out together.
Oh.
That's all taken care of.
What?
My neighbor recommended
some herbal medicine.
I've been drinking it,
and I feel much better.
You could have told me.
I was so worried.
Sorry, sorry.
Well, I'm just glad you're okay.
We were just talking about
how, when it gets a little warmer,
we're going to go to the rose
garden with the neighbors.
Mom, you seem happy.
I am. I'm very happy.
What about you?
Are you happy?
Yeah, I am.
(Hoshi no Monogatari
Translation Competition Office)
Please...!
[Kuji is working on a draft
of the essay about his father]
Yes.
I've finally started writing.
Okay.
Huh?
(Sakutaro: Working from home all day?)
(Kuji Shizuka: Yep.)
(Sakutaro: If it's on my way
back, I was thinking of stopping by.)
(Kuji Shizuka: Roger that.) (Sakutaro: I
submitted my entry for the competition.)
Oh, Azuma-san.
We both made the deadline
for the translation competition.
That's great, isn't it?
It really is.
I actually pulled an all-nighter at the
last minute and redid the whole thing.
Did something happen?
Well... Kuji and I...
Azuma.
Azuma... Sakutaro!
Huh?
Kuji?
Let's go right now.
To the hot springs.
What?!
Hot springs.
I even booked us a room.
Are you serious, Kuji?
You're the best!
Ah, this is amazing.
This is pure bliss. It's heaven.
I didn't realize you'd be this happy.
Then we have Nukita-san to thank.
Huh?
Nukita-san gave them to me.
These gift certificates.
He said he couldn't
make it at the last minute.
What a cool guy...
By the way,
asking me out on the same
day is pretty sudden, don't you think?
About your mother...
What I said was so insensitive.
I'm truly sorry.
I've been thinking about it ever since.
But I couldn't stand it anymore.
I just really wanted to see you.
Shizuka-chan, it's rare
to see you so honest.
Asimov.
Hmm?
I heard it from Tamaki
when I saw him the other day.
That Asimov book you used to read,
Tamaki is reading it now.
Yeah.
I actually read it in middle school, too.
We're so alike.
I wish we could just
freeze everything about us,
on a winter night like this.
(Final Episode Preview) I wish I
could tell my past self all of this.
I've gotten to you.
There are good days and bad days.
That's just how life is.
I don't want to go back.
Want to stay another night?