"Lost To You"
(Episode 5)
Some secrets tear people apart.
Some secrets bring people closer.
But our secret... brings
light to the darkness.
Xiao Yuan.
Getting two servings today?
Can you eat all that?
He's definitely getting it for Zhan Wang.
Zhan Wang gave him so many things.
He has to at least get
him breakfast in return.
No.
I've just been eating more lately.
Oh, come on.
Mom said your appetite
hasn't changed at all.
It says in novels...
When you worry if someone is hungry,
if they're cold,
or if they're unhappy...
it means you've fallen for them.
Xu Nuo.
You should read less of that nonsense.
Aren't you getting two?
Take this one, too.
So stubborn.
This one's extra.
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it. You've already had breakfast.
No, I haven't.
This place isn't very good,
so I didn't eat.
Is this...
for me?
There was also extra.
This must be Auntie Meixi's cooking.
It looks delicious.
You can have the bad one.
Thanks.
Come on, come on.
Pass it to me.
Here, one more.
Let's get warmed up.
Your dribbling isn't bad.
I practice on my own sometimes.
Then it looks like you
mainly need to practice
your shooting and passing skills.
We need one more on our team.
I'm not playing.
Then we're not playing either.
Then forget it.
I've got something to do. I'm out.
How are we supposed to play with him?
Exactly.
We might break a leg just playing with him.
Anyone else?
Bend your knees.
A little lower.
Raise your hands.
Support it with this hand.
Guide it with this one.
Then aim for your target.
Then, like this,
three fingers.
Right.
This hand is just for support.
Then, once you've aimed...
Just the two of you practicing?
Why don't we all play together?
Yeah, come on, everyone.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go. Hurry.
Everyone, join in. Quick.
Alright, serve the ball.
Is there something wrong with this hoop?
Don't be so dramatic.
Forget it. Let's go practice passing.
Let's not shoot here.
Let's go, let's go.
This basketball hoop...
Didn't someone say last time
that the screws needed tightening?
Did no one report it?
It's fine.
I'll go get some tools.
Isn't that the captain and
class committee's job?
Why are you going?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Try moving your ankle.
See if it's okay.
If not, I'll take you
to the nurse's office.
I think I'm fine.
Come on, up you go.
Alright, alright.
Don't be so dramatic.
Everyone, be careful.
See that?
I was closest to you,
but I'm perfectly fine.
You don't have to go out of your way.
I just want to show everyone
that you're not a jinx.
Come on.
Let's keep playing. Keep playing.
Play ball, play ball, play ball!
Pass it to me.
Here.
Nice one!
Great shot!
Awesome!
Not bad.
Let's go again.
Give me the ball.
Let's call it a day.
I'm too tired to play anymore.
Alright, let's wrap it up.
Okay, okay.
Let's go. Bye.
Leaving. Bye. Let's go.
Bian Ye.
You're not on your game today.
A-Ze intercepted you so many times.
I think I pulled a thigh muscle.
Are you okay?
It's not fatal.
Should we go to the nurse's office?
No.
Avoiding Zhan Xu.
Let's go.
Sprained leg, huh.
How did you know?
I went to watch you practice.
You came to watch me practice?
Lie down.
It's not too bad.
It's just a mild sprain.
Not a torn ligament.
Plus, you've also pulled a thigh muscle.
Let me put some ice on it for you.
Rest for a couple of
days, and you'll be fine.
Ow.
Endure it.
You seem to be good at this.
I'm a doctor.
I mean,
your hands are very
steady when you touch me.
I'll go get more ice.
[Doctor's Without Borders Treatment
Initiative, Yunnan Mountains 2020]
Put it down.
You were part of Doctors Without Borders?
I never would have guessed.
That's pretty cool.
That was a long time ago.
Who's the other person in the photo?
A colleague.
Just a colleague?
You can go now.
This thing in your ear,
is it for listening to
music while you work?
It's for work.
There are some subtle sounds
that I need to hear more clearly.
Like what sounds?
Like...
whether a machine is running properly.
a patient's breathing rate.
Like...
the sound of your
footsteps as you leave now.
You came to watch me practice.
I'm the school nurse.
Caring about the
students' physical condition
is my duty.
Then why only watch me?
Just now,
I saw your reaction.
Is it hot in the nurse's office?
Your hair is all wet.
See you at the clinic at 5 p.m.
Don't forget to do the test paper.
Let's take a break.
Your stamina is pretty good.
Your coaching is pretty good, too.
Here's your prize bottle.
I'll come to you to claim
my prize next time, too.
You're actually not a bad player.
A long time ago,
my dad taught me how to play.
He was really good.
And then?
Then he died.
I'm sorry.
Don't be scared on game day.
I'm not scared.
Then stop your hands from shaking.
They're not shaking.
Like this.
Every time you're about to shoot,
just imagine
that you're holding onto something.
Holding what?
For example...
wringing an enemy's neck.
More like wringing your neck.
Come on, I'll treat you to a meal.
I have money.
You have money? Then you can treat me.
Deal.
Next up,
we have Class 2, Grade 12,
facing last year's champions,
the Grade 11 United Team.
The pressure is on for Class 2, Grade 12.
This is going to be a bloodbath.
Let's welcome both teams to the court!
Victory!
That Jinx is actually playing?
Is Grade 12 out of players or something?
Just wait for them to lose.
Don't be cowards!
We'll win even with the jinx on our team.
Xu Yuan is not a Jinx.
That's right.
He's our class's lucky star.
Go, Xu Yuan!
Xu Yuan! Zhan Wang!
Class 2, Grade 12, will win!
Go!
Offense!
Defense!
Nice shot!
Awesome!
Hurry up! Faster!
Great shot!
He's so cool!
Go, go!
You're amazing!
Xu Yuan!
That was beautiful!
Xu Yuan! Xu Yuan! Xu Yuan!
Awesome!
We won!
We won! We won! We won!
That was so cool!
Great game.
We won!
We won! We won!
Xu Yuan!
Come on up!
Xu Yuan, go on! Yeah!
Go, Xu Yuan!
Get on stage and get the award, Xu Yuan!
Xu Yuan!
The championship is ours!
Yeah!
Three, two, one!
Be careful, don't fall.
If I fall, you'll be
there to break my fall.
Bro.
Let's go.
I'll kill you!
I told you to get lost!
Mr. Chen said he's taking this land.
You have to be out by the weekend.
Are you deaf or just stupid?
The contract says...
It doesn't expire for another three years.
Contract?
My word is the law around here.
Playing tough guy, huh?
To hell with you!
I'll kick you to death!
Get off!
Mom!
Stop fighting!
Another one?
Get lost!
Stop fighting, all of you!
If anyone touches my son again,
I'll die right here with you.
She's a fucking psycho.
Let's go.
Mom.
It's okay. It's okay now.
Help your mom inside first.
It's okay.
Let's go inside.
You need to get that injury looked at.
I'm fine.
Zhan Xu should still be at the clinic.
Go on.
You have such a gentle touch.
It doesn't hurt.
You can get up now.
Let's have dinner tonight.
I know a new Japanese
place that just opened.
Sorry.
I have plans tonight.
Xu.
You always turn me down.
Are you done staring?
If you are, you can leave.
Bian Ye.
What are you doing here at this hour?
What?
Did I interrupt something important?
And this is...?
My student.
Right.
A student.
The teacher needs to tutor his student now.
So you can leave.
Get out. I said, get out.
Students these days have no manners.
Bian Ye.
Don't be like that.
Like what?
And what you two were doing was so great?
He touched your hand, and you just let him.
Zhan Xu.
Isn't your student a little out of line?
Say that again.
Bian Ye.
Let go of him.
So this is your type now?
A little brat.
But, Zhan Xu,
a little "wolf pup" like this...
is fine for a fling.
Just don't get too serious.
I'll come back another day.
You come back here
again, and I'll kill you.
Bian Ye.
You've gone too far.
I've gone too far?
What did he mean by all that?
What did he mean, "your type"?
And what was that about "just a fling"?
You should go.
I'm not leaving.
You need to tell me the truth.
Do you like men?
Do you?
With him?
That's right.
I like men.
Are you happy now?
Then why can't it be me?
You're my student.
And I'm your teacher.
Do you even know what
it means to like someone?
This is just a passing crush.
I don't understand?
Then you tell me.
Who is it that makes
my heart race like this?
Who makes me rush here to do
homework every day after class?
Who is it?
Who makes me want to hit
someone just for touching your hand?
Who is it?
Zhan Xu.
Look at me.
You really want to tell me
you feel nothing for me?
Then why did you help me?
Why did you give me money?
Why did you fix my tooth?
I saw you in the nurse's office that day.
I saw how you reacted.
Your ears turned red.
Are you going to deny it was
because I was close to you
that you got hard?
You... your ear...
Hearing damage in my right ear.
Basically, I'm half-deaf.
So now you know.
I'm not just some freak who likes men.
I'm a cripple, too.
Are you satisfied now?
Just go.
I'm not leaving.
That's them!
Run!
Get them!
Don't run!
Stop!
Where'd they go?
This way! They're fast.
Little punks.
Check over there.
I'll kill you when I catch you!
Alright.
Go check over there.
Find them yet?
Where are they?
Where are we?
My dad's old fishing boat.
Let's check over there.
Let's go.
Alright.
There are stalls down there.
There's no way they can escape.
Where are they?
They're not over here.
Alright.
Nothing.
Go, go, go.
Let's get out of here.
What happened to your ear?
Is it because of the person in the photo?
In high school, because I liked men...
my dad slapped me more than a dozen times.
My right eardrum was perforated.
What happened after that?
We ran away from home together.
Traveled the world together.
Provided medical aid
around the world together.
And where is he now?
He got married.
His kid's starting
elementary school this year.
Xu... I won't.
What?
I won't get married.
I won't leave.
When I commit to someone, it's forever.
You're only nineteen.
Forever is a long time.
So...
I have a long time to prove it to you.
Tell me...
If I fell from here...
would you save me?
You definitely wouldn't [fall.]
But what if?
Really?
Really.
Then I'll give it a try.
Zhan Wang!