"Lost To You"
(Episode 4)
We run towards the light
but we see the shadows behind us
growing longer and longer.
Xu Yuan.
That guy...
Aside from being a total jinx,
he's actually a pretty good person.
He's good-tempered,
gets good grades,
and I've never seen him get mad at anyone.
It's not that we intentionally exclude him.
It's just that he...
never tries to hang out with us either.
When the teacher said to
make a class group chat,
he said he didn't have WeChat.
It's not that he doesn't have WeChat.
He doesn't even have a phone.
No phone at all.
We all think that's pretty weird.
Yeah.
He sounds like an old man.
Look who it is.
What's wrong?
Stomachache.
You're a pretty convincing actor.
Spit it out.
What is it?
How did you know I was faking?
You've been like this since we were kids.
Whenever you lie,
you touch your ear.
I just wanted to ask...
about Xu Yuan.
Why the sudden interest in a classmate?
I'm curious.
He's my deskmate.
If I don't understand him,
I can't focus on my studies.
Fine.
His family situation...
I don't know much about it.
But there is someone...
who might know.
Who?
Bian Ye.
Bian Ye?
You mean that kid with the red hair?
The one who's always fighting?
Yeah.
He helps out at Xu Yuan's
mother's noodle shop.
He should know a lot.
If you want to know about Xu Yuan,
you could probably ask him.
You seem to know a lot about Bian Ye.
Are you close with him?
I'm tutoring him.
In exchange, he has to stop
hanging out with that crowd.
Why are you so nice to him?
Wang-wang.
Some things...
don't need so many reasons.
Being good to the people you care about...
is nothing to be ashamed of.
Whether they're friends...
or something else.
Just like you...
you seem to care a lot about Xu Yuan.
Trying to bribe me?
I don't smoke.
You want to ask about Xu Yuan.
His family...
is dirt poor.
A little better off than me,
but not by much.
Auntie Meixi doesn't make much in a month.
And she has to raise two kids.
Then why are you the only one helping out?
Why doesn't he?
With his jinx-like nature,
who would dare get close to him?
The most he can do is run
some deliveries for his mom.
And I mean literally run.
Making deliveries on foot?
What was he thinking?
It's hilarious.
Who makes deliveries on foot these days?
I've set him up with a few part-time jobs,
but they all bailed when
they heard he was a jinx.
Now, the most he can do
is move cargo at the docks
or help people mend their fishing nets.
But he's been really short on cash lately.
I think it's for his sister.
Xu Yuan.
There's a shipment of
glass to unload tomorrow.
It's a bit dangerous, but it pays well.
Fifty. You in?
I'm in.
What time?
Same time as always tomorrow.
But...
let's be clear.
If you break the glass, you pay for it.
Okay.
Here.
Thanks, Uncle.
Look!
Isn't that Zhan Wang from
the high school division?
He's so handsome.
It really is him.
What's he doing over in
the middle school section?
See that?
That's my brother's friend.
He's here to see me.
Brother Zhan Wang, I'm over here!
Taro boba tea.
Half sugar.
Thanks, big brother.
Brother Zhan Wang is the best.
What did you need me for?
Are you here to ask about my brother?
Just a quick question.
Your brother is so old,
why doesn't he have a phone?
Well...
My brother...
he doesn't talk much.
I'm always the one pestering him to talk.
And when we communicate at home,
we just write notes to each other.
Actually, I think...
he just can't bear to spend
money on a new phone,
so he says that on purpose.
He's that short on money?
It's kind of embarrassing to say,
but my brother is doing all this...
for me.
For you?
I want to take acting classes,
but the ones in town are too expensive.
One session costs over ten thousand.
After my brother found out,
he secretly took on a bunch of odd jobs.
And he's kind of a dummy.
The last time he was moving glass,
he cut his hand all up.
When I asked him about it,
he just said he fell by accident.
I see.
I'll take care of the acting classes.
This is for you.
But it's not free.
From now on, if anything
happens with your brother,
you tell me immediately.
Deal.
These three are brand new releases.
Don't worry.
I'll tell you everything I know.
Besides, when it comes to my brother,
I know everything.
Last night,
he stayed up late helping
Mom with the account books.
His shoes are getting a little old.
He needs a new pair.
Got it.
I'm heading out.
Bye, Brother Zhan Wang.
Get on.
This bike is for you.
Don't you have to make
deliveries for your mom?
Running is too slow.
This bike is fast. You
can make more deliveries.
I don't want it.
It's not a gift.
The condition is...
you have to take me to
and from school every day.
I don't want to walk every day.
It's exhausting.
No.
It's dangerous for me to ride a bike.
Just try it.
I'm a seasoned veteran.
I'm not afraid of your jinx-like nature.
Get on.
[A full dossier of information on Bian Ye]
So, after I check in with you today,
is my debt to you paid off?
Sit.
Let's talk.
About what?
About why you left Jingzhou...
and chose to come back to this dump?
Or should we talk about your rich old man?
Let's talk about your father.
None of your damn business.
Bian Jianguo.
Age 42.
Five years ago, at a casino,
he racked up 300,000 in gambling debt.
He packed his things in the
middle of the night and ran.
Leaving you and your mother behind.
And a bunch of debt
collectors at your door.
Zhan Xu.
You've been investigating me?
What are you trying to do?
Come on.
I'm taking you somewhere.
I'm not going.
If you come with me today,
your debt will be cleared.
The path you take from here on...
is up to you.
Why did you bring me here?
You'll see.
Limpy Li.
Back in the day, he
fought for turf at the docks
and got his leg broken.
Now he gambles every day,
and is up to his ears in debt.
When are you ever...
going to get a real job?
So what if I don't have a job?
Am I just sitting around doing nothing?
Have I ever let you down?
Wang Wei.
He was a notorious thug back in the day.
Brawling,
running protection rackets.
Now he lives off his wife.
He drinks every day,
and beats his wife when he's drunk.
Old Zhao the Third.
Used to be the big shot of Hong Town.
Now he picks through trash for a living.
What's your point in showing me all this?
To show off how much you know?
Or are you trying to tell me
I'll end up just like these losers?
Bian Ye.
You're a lot like them.
You think school is useless.
You think being tough is all that matters.
You think you can just worry about tomorrow
when it comes.
I'm not like them.
How are you different?
Maybe your father
said the exact same thing back in his day.
I'm not...
I just...
Just what?
Just occasionally
collecting debts for loan sharks.
Just occasionally moving some smuggled
goods.
Bian Ye.
With things like this,
if you do it once,
you'll do it ten times.
The stakes will just get higher and higher.
And eventually, you could end up in jail.
Have you ever thought about your mom?
Then tell me what I'm supposed to do.
If I don't do this stuff,
how am I supposed to pay off my debts?
How am I supposed to buy my mom's medicine?
School?
Can school turn into cash overnight?
Make a deal with me.
What are you up to now?
Starting tomorrow,
you report to my place every day.
I'll give you a test.
When you finish,
I'll give you 300.
Are you kidding me?
I'm a man of my word.
If your score is higher than the last one,
I'll give you an extra 500 as a bonus.
That way,
you'll make more than you
do hustling on the streets.
And it's safer.
If you can stick with it until
you graduate high school,
I'll even help you pay for college.
You can learn a real trade,
and support yourself and your family.
Don't you want to escape
a life like your father's?
This is the first step.
Making money with your brain,
not your fists.
Bian Ye.
I've been looking all over for you.
We've got a job tonight.
Let's go.
The choice is yours.
You can keep cowering in the dark,
or you can step into the light.
Bian Ye.
Bian Ye, I've been
looking all over for you.
I'm not going.
300 a day, right?
Right.
And a 500 bonus for a higher score.
Yes.
300 on the first day.
800 on the second.
The third day...
In one month,
that's a total of 23,700 yuan.
What time tomorrow?
And where?
After school.
Meet me at the clinic.
See you tomorrow.
The doorknob is fixed, too.
The yard is all tidied up.
And the swing...
The swing is hung up, too.
Did you do this?
No.
Wasn't it you?
Could it be
we have a secret helper?
New shoes!
I wonder if it's because I
told Zhan Wang yesterday...
and he...
He even got me a pair!
He's so thoughtful.
Bro, let's try them on.
Is Xu Yuan wearing the latest model?
Xu Yuan must have struck it rich.
Those shoes are crazy expensive.
Zhan Wang's are too.
Morning.
Zhan Wang.
Those shoes at my doorstep...
You left them there, didn't you?
What shoes?
I don't know what you're talking about.
And...
the gate to the yard,
the clothesline,
the faucet holder...
What are you talking about?
I have no idea.
Then maybe someone left them by mistake.
Then I'd better put them away tonight.
The owner might come looking for them.
Wait.
I heard
there's some kind of
community outreach program.
They give supplies to students in need.
The community outreach
program gives out this brand?
The brand was having a sale.
A clearance sale.
Clearance?
Giving away one pair of men's
shoes and one pair of women's?
And they just happen to
be mine and Xu Nuo's sizes?
Whatever.
Since someone gave them to me,
I might as well wear them.
They're pretty comfortable.
You've got good taste.
I'm done.
These questions are impossible.
Your score is higher than last time.
But I still didn't pass.
So no bonus.
But you still get the base pay of 300.
Here you go.
Your tooth is bothering you again?
None of your business.
I'm a dentist.
Let me take a look.
You have a cavity.
It's a pretty deep one.
And it looks like this tooth here...
is cracked.
Is it this one?
Ow!
The power's out.
Let me just file down the tooth for now.
Okay, open up.
Does it hurt?
All done.
That's all we can do for today.
Remember to come back for a follow-up.
You can't water mint like that.
You'll cause root rot.
I was just passing by.
It looked a little dry.
Just passing by with a full toolbox?
I have to fix Bian Ye's bike.
I'm in a hurry.
I gotta go.
Have you had dinner yet?
Not yet.
My mom made seafood congee today.
Want to join?
Drink it while it's hot.
I made extra congee today.
Xu Nuo, time to eat.
Coming.
Thank you, Auntie.
It's nothing.
Zhan Wang, you're here.
You're amazing.
Mom.
Zhan Wang signed me up
for an online acting class.
I looked it up.
The teacher is from Jingzhou.
A professor from the drama academy.
He's taught so many big stars.
I'm going to be a big star too.
An acting class?
How much did that cost?
Well, Xiao Wang...
Auntie.
It didn't cost much.
You see,
Professor Li happens to
be a friend of my mom's.
He said he wanted to
take on a few students.
Xu Nuo is talented.
But we can't let you pay for it.
Mom.
Please just let me take it.
Professor Li said...
the first month is just a trial class.
If I'm not a good fit,
he won't even accept me.
Xiao Wang.
I don't know how to thank you.
It's nothing, Auntie.
Where's Xu Yuan?
Zhan Wang.
Did you forget?
My brother is the infamous jinx...
I'm used to eating alone.
Hurry up and eat.
Did you sneak some extra food?
Let me see.
Come on, eat over there.
No.
Come on.
Let me see what's in your bowl.
Look at those two.
Eat up.
You're pretty good at washing dishes.
I've been doing it since I was a kid.
Do you have a phone charger?
Can I borrow it for a bit?
My phone is dead.
I don't have a phone.
No phone?
Is your mom usually that strict with you?
I don't need one.
Then how do you contact your classmates?
I don't.
What if you need to?
There's nothing I need
to contact them about.
There's a class group chat.
They post everything in there.
A-Ze tells me.
What if A-Ze can't reach you either?
Zhan Wang.
I don't have any friends.
And no one I need to contact.
The most important people to me...
are all in this house.
Does that include me?
Auntie.
Let me help you.
No, it's fine. I can do it.
It's okay, I'll get it.
I'll wipe it.
Don't.
Zhan Wang.
You and my brother are a good match.
Thanks for your help.
Zhan Wang, you can leave it here.
[Lending this, [so you're] easy to reach]
I'm not giving it to you.
I'm lending it.
Why?
I want to add you on WeChat.
Besides, you have to
be my training partner.
I need to be able to find you anytime.
Thanks.
Do you know how to use a phone?
Class.
Next month is the all-school sports meet.
This will be our last group activity.
The basketball tournament
is the main event.
Our class has to make us proud.
So, sports representative,
get a headcount.
Okay, teacher.
Everyone, please sign up enthusiastically.
I'll sign up.
Zhan Wang.
You have to sign up.
That three-pointer you
made the other day...
we all saw it.
It was a perfect shot.
Yeah, yeah.
You have to sign up.
You have to. Sign up, sign up.
We're counting on you.
Yeah, we can't win without you.
Alright.
But I have one condition.
What is it?
He...
has to be on the team too.
Him?
Him on the team?
Zhan Wang.
You can't be serious.
Basketball is a team sport.
How can we let him on the team?
Zhan Wang.
The sports meet is about our class's honor.
You can't treat this like a joke.
Exactly.
I mean,
what if something happens on the court?
Who's going to be responsible?
Right.
If he gets hurt, whose fault is it?
I won't join.
I'm not suited for team sports.
And I don't like playing basketball.
Oh, that's great.
Then I'll sign up, I'll sign up.
Okay, okay. Anyone else?
You guys sign up.
You're joining with him?
Let's just get the others signed up first.
We'll discuss the
basketball tournament later.
I've been looking all over for you.
How did you know I was here?
Xu Nuo told me.
About the basketball tournament...
don't worry about it.
Those guys are idiots.
They're scared of everything.
They're not wrong.
I'm not suited for team sports.
Xu Yuan.
You can't keep running away.
What right do they have to call you a jinx?
All that talk about curses...
it's all nonsense.
They were the ones who had it coming.
You don't know anything.
You don't know what it's like
to watch your own father drown.
You don't know what it's like to see
your only friend get into a car accident.
Every time I try to be good to someone,
something bad happens to them.
Once is a coincidence.
Twice is an accident.
What about the third and fourth time?
You tell me.
Besides accepting my fate,
what else can I do?
I don't know exactly
what happened to you in the past.
But I do know...
what it feels like to
be treated like a monster.
In my family,
my second brother was that monster.
Because he likes men.
In my dad's eyes,
he was a disgrace.
I was also afraid of
becoming a disgrace.
Later, I realized that no
matter how hard I tried,
I could never satisfy him.
So,
there's no difference
between my brother and me.
We're both just useless
embarrassments to him.
Xu Yuan.
I'm not trying to compare
sob stories with you.
I just want to say...
that after my grandma passed away,
a lot of things...
became clear to me.
I just want to be me.
And I hope you can be, too.
You were never the jinx
that people see you as.
You...
are just you.
But...
And to me,
you're not the person
who brings me bad luck.
Instead, since I came here,
you're the one who's made me feel warmth.
What if...
I end up hurting you too?
It was never your fault.
Besides,
I'm tough.
I can take a hit.
On the basketball court,
you'll be there to protect me, right?
Honestly,
that dive you took...
was pretty cool.
Alright.
I'll give it a try.
But you have to promise me one thing.
Name it.
Study hard.
And take your homework seriously.
Deal.
Bro.
I can't believe you're
playing basketball again.
Did hell freeze over?
Didn't you say
all sports that require teamwork
were a huge pain?
I'm just dribbling.
It's because Zhan Wang
asked you to join the team, isn't it?
The power of love is a great thing.
Xu Nuo.
See? I was right.
Bro,
you and Zhan Wang
are the talk of Shude High now.
Every move you two make,
nothing gets past me.
Why are you keeping tabs on me?
Just focus on school.
It's just that you've
changed so much lately.
I can't help but pay attention.
Zhan Wang.
Are you really putting him in?
Yeah.
Why not?
Is he any good?
Yeah.
Can he really play?
Does he even know how?
He's not actually going
for a three-pointer, is he?
There's no way he's making that.
See that? See that?
Incredible!
When it comes to shooting,
none of you can touch him.
I'll say it again.
I'll only join if Xu Yuan joins.
Otherwise, find someone else.
Got it?