[One year ago]
I don't have time for this, Jae Min,
so just answer my question.
Is it true?
Was there something between you two?
I don't see what you're getting at.
Haven't you heard?
There's even a petition to kick you out.
What I'm asking you is,
if there really were any mutual feelings...
between you and that idol.
Huh?
You're a contestant, what were you thinking?
Whatever.
I can't believe you got into a scandal!
The agency...
just made a statement.
What are they saying?
The romance rumors are entirely false,
and Jae Min's persistent attention
caused our artist discomfort...
and even fear.
That's it.
Wait, what?
Fear?
This could come off as stalking.
What do we do?
Sir!
It's fine.
Your number.
Hey.
I don't give my number out to just anyone.
That's not who I am.
- I don't know what you thought of me...
- Give.
Give me please.
That was bold.
Hey, wait!
Hey!
You should... return your tray.
And did he just take my number and run off?
Who even does that? I need his, too.
[One year ago]
- Break a leg! - Good luck!
What's that?
Oh, this? Just a lucky charm.
I passed every audition I took with it on.
So I always keep it on me.
Really?
Do you want to try it on?
Can I?
The final stage is starting soon!
Let's go.
Hyun Jae, who is it?
Is something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
- Hello?
- Hello.
I'm... uh...
the guy from...
Hey.
You were pretty close by.
Yeah.
This.
What is it?
Take it.
But what is it?
- T-shirt.
- A tee...
Ah, no, you don't need to.
I'm sorry.
No, it's really fine. I'm serious.
Take it.
If you're really sorry,
you could buy me dinner instead.
Take it!
Ah, wait!
Hey!
I don't even know what his name is.
[Ketchup]
- Good work.
- Great work.
- Good night.
- Good work.
- Great work.
Huh?
Excuse me.
Good night.
[Ye Eun]
Hey, Yoon Soo An,
are you trying to tick me off?
Come over right now before I lose it.
I can't.
You didn't answer my texts! Where are you?
- I'm at home.
- What?
I saw him.
You should get back to training.
I can't be an idol.
Why not? You didn't do anything wrong.
You shouldn't have stepped down.
We should've told the truth.
You went out with him because he liked you.
How could he just frame you as a stalker?
What a jerk.
I think... I saw Soo An.
At the studio.
I think he's working as a staff member.
What? No way.
He's the ace of Unicorn. He'd be practicing.
Why would he be working?
Why not just ask him?
[Soo An, can we call?]
Can I?
- Whoa!
- What? What is it?
Hey, where did you get this?
It's from a luxury brand, right?
- Uh, no, it's not.
- Yes, it is!
It must've cost a fortune.
- What, really?
- Did you buy it yourself?
- No.
- Did you steal it, then?
- No!
- Well?
How much is it?
What?
- 850,000 won?
- 850,000 won.
- What do I do?
- Do what?
I can't do this. Wait here!
You think they'll take it back?
Oh, you're here.
Well, look who it is!
I'm back.
You did a great job.
It's nothing, sir.
We've been waiting for you.
We've got big plans for you, so rest up.
Manager Kang, take him home.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
What? Are you waiting for someone?
No, of course not.
Don't slack off just because the group's done.
Plenty of eyes are on you.
I know, sir.
Let's go.
At the tone, please record your message.
Come on, answer already.
Oh, hey!
Hey, wait!
[Notice]
[No outsiders are currently allowed in]
Working hard to meet you on stage.
Oh!
Hey!
Hello.
Did I scare you?
You scared me with how jumpy you are.
I just wanted to see you about this.
Is this an expensive shirt?
Expensive?
Um... It's just...
Normal.
Normal?
I'm sorry.
For what?
You don't like it?
Ah, this shirt is...
Expensive. Too expensive.
You know?
It's nothing.
I said that's okay.
But...
Let's take this back.
Take... back?
Refund. Okay?
But...
I didn't even wear it much.
It's basically brand-new.
Have a bite.
Aw, dang it.
Kim Hyun Jae.
Well, now what?
- It's okay.
- No, no!
I'm not comfortable with this.
Let me see what I have on me.
I'm empty-handed now,
but I'll do anything.
Your body.
Come again?
You can pay me back...
with your body.
[Hotel LUXE]
This doesn't feel right.
What is he even thinking?
You left this for me to find, didn't you?
Why did you cut me off?
We used each other for fame.
You even got to debut. Isn't that enough?
Want me to warm it up?
Do you really feel nothing towards me?