At his age, he doesn't need to work.
Just sit around, and that's it.
Right. He can barely even walk now.
You can go now.
We've come as far as we can.
Hmph.
Come on now.
Your friend still not talking?
Grandpa, are you good now?
I'm sleepy.
Aw.
Then go to bed, Snow.
Okay.
Ow...
Ow.
Huh.
Ugh.
Ouch...
Oow.
Ow. Ugh.
Father's still not up?
Father.
You awake?
Yeah, I'm up.
Oh? Father.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just...knocked it with my hand.
What about you? Anything wrong?
Everything is all right.
I thought it was odd
that you weren't up yet.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
- I was just about to get up.
- Okay.
Father. Oh...hmph.
Tell me where it hurts.
It's not that bad.
Don't tough it out, Grandpa.
Tell me so I'll work
on the right spots.
My whole back is killing me.
Not just his back.
Last night, he had me massage
his shoulders too.
There you go.
So where exactly does it hurt?
All of it.
You always tell me
not to be difficult. Now you.
Fine. Everything hurts.
Elbow, shoulder,
the muscles, the arms...
Let me see.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh?
- Dad.
- Hmm?
It's getting serious.
Let's go to a doctor.
No, some balm and a massage will do.
Then let's rub the balm on now.
If it doesn't get better,
I'll take you myself.
Hmm? What is it, Father?
Your back brace. You done with it?
Let me use it.
Oh, Father.
What, Grandpa?
You're just catching up
with the office syndrome trend.
Come here. Let me massage you.
Easy now.
Gentle, son. Light pressure.
Not too hard.
Okay, okay.
Nice and easy.
Okay, Dad.
Ooh.
Hey, Pipe.
Yeah, Phi Save?
Wanna play with my doll?
No.
I'm here to trade.
This one...is a secret character.
And this one...is super rare.
I'll give you two for it.
Trade for this one. Deal?
Sure, Phi Save.
Two-for-one is always a super.
Hmm? A massage balm?
It reeks.
Yo, boys. New toys.
What is it?
- Let me see.
So cool.
Awesome.
"Got what you gave me."
"It's so cute. Thanks a lot."
"Unread message"
Well, well...
What?
Don't let me catch you
sneaking up to write.
- Hmm?
- Hehe.
- I'm awake. Hehe.
- Hmph...back in there.
Just rest, okay?
So? You patched things up
with him yet?
Sounds like he's cut you
out of his life.
Think so?
Well,...
you went at him pretty hard first.
Yeah.
I messed up. I know.
Oh-ho. Ho.
Look at you.
It took you long enough
to admit you were wrong, huh?
That big ego?
I must have gotten it from you.
Then how about
trying a little harder?
Like how?
Make him something.
Handmade.
Correct. Hey, a story for ya.
I once made a friend angry.
I made something for him.
It's a gun box. He was into guns.
The moment he saw it,
he lit right up.
Ah-ha.
But...I don't know
how to make anything.
- Can I just buy something?
- No.
When you make it yourself,
he'll see how much
you really mean it.
And the harder it is to make,
the more he'll know
you're truly sorry.
Got it, Grandpa.
Thanks so much. I'll be back.
Yeah...
You rest.
Hmm...rest, okay? I'll be back.
"'Geez, how can I
make peace with Nan now?'"
"He mutters and vents
to the empty room."
"'I shouldn't have run
my mouth like that.'"
"The young man
going back and forth,"
"thinking of a way to
make things right with his friend."
"He hopes to restore the friendship,
the way it used to be."
"DIY gift, hardest to make"
Knitting.
"Easiest knit craft"
No, no. Wrong.
What is the...
hardest thing to knit?
Knit a sweater.
Let's do it.
Huh.
- There you are.
- Ah.
Up writing again.
Well...the pain's gone.
How can I just lie here?
That's enough, Dad.
Come here. Get up. Let's go.
Ow, ow, ow...
You said the pain's gone.
It's back
because you're carrying me.
Come on, come on. Easy.
No writing. Enough is enough.
Don't squeeze my arm.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Sorry. Come on, come on.
Easy. Here, sit down.
Okay. Watch your back and lie down.
Ow, ow, ow...
- My legs. My legs.
- Okay, got it, got it.
Lie down, Dad.
See, all curled up like a shrimp.
- Alright, now. Rest, really, Dad.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Whatchu doing?
Hey, where are you taking that?
I'm putting this away.
You don't need to. I won't write.
I don't believe you.
Let me hold onto it.
When will I get it back?
After you recover. Now, rest.
Sorn.
- I'll hold onto it. Bye.
- Sorn. Sorn.
Sorn.
Sorn. Oh-ho, ow.
I was just on a roll. Dang it.
Here, Pheem, take it. Ready?
- Hey, guys.
- You in, Messi?
I'm not playing today.
Oh?
- What's wrong with him?
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Oh, another one.
Guy, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What I said was out of line.
You actually know that?
I got frustrated with Grandpa,
and I took it out on you.
Just as I thought.
That was on me.
I own it.
You know? Some things, once said,
cannot be taken back.
I know.
You said
we came as far as we could.
Then, we are no more.
Guy.
Ow.
I'm fine. Just go.
Save, you idiot.
A kick that hard
probably broke a toe.
You still mad at me?
Yeah.
Can you get up?
Thanks, man.
Take it off.
What?
Your shoe. Take it off.
Ugh.
That toe must come off.
What? Are you serious?
You believed that? Silly.
Aren't you waiting
for the teacher?
Easy. I can handle it.
Whatchu doing?
Uh...
I'm just...
exercising my hand.
Oh-oh. Easy, easy.
Ugh...
Oh-oh.
Easy.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah.
- Phi Sorn.
- Hmm?
Save says the channel's back.
Oh, really? Let me see.
Okay. Let me look.
Hey, it's actually back.
"Sanae Chan by Auntie Mart"
Good.
Should we do a livestream then?
We can't do it ourselves.
We already tried that.
That's true.
And Guy, my boy,
isn't coming anymore.
"My boy"?
Since when is he your child?
This is on you.
You didn't want him coming.
Got what you want, huh?
Hey, I've got an idea.
- Hello.
- Hi, hi.
Ma'am, these are Sanae Chan sweets
by Auntie Mart.
They're good. Watch, watch.
Hoo.
- Look amazing, let me try.
- Soft and chewy.
Of course.
Watch me, watch.
Oh wow, they're really good.
Made from mochi flour.
Not too sweet.
Healthy-delicious.
Click, pay, done.
Click, click, click now.
Click away...
Well? Is my idea working?
Hehe.
Well, well. Snow could do this too.
Why did you say that?
All she does is dance all day.
She never reads anything,
except those BL novels.
See? This might just be
our daughter's special talent.
Today, we also have
a dance performance.
3, 2, 1.
Sanae Chan sweets by Auntie Mart.
Sanae Chan sweets by Aunt Mart.
Ow, ow, ow.
Ow.
Grandpa.
What happened to your foot?
I came to tell you something.
Guy still won't forgive me.
Just wait. He's still hot.
Try again after he cools down.
Will that day even come?
Let me ask you.
Do you want to make up with Guy
because you need him for the novel,
or because you...
can't stand the thought of him
not being in your life?
Your novel or not,
he's someone I want to keep around.
That means you care about Guy a lot.
Care? No way.
Your story's got my hands itching.
I really want to
get back to writing.
Right now, you need rest.
Or your back will get worse.
But the ideas are flooding my head.
You have to take care of your body.
For a writer like you,
your fingers, wrists,
arms, back, and shoulders
do need your attention.
You know that?
They're your bread and butter.
- Yeah, look at that.
- Ouch.
Haha.
Coming from the guy
who just kicked a tree.
Come on, Grandpa. Trust me on this.
Some manga artists
push themselves so hard
they have to take a year off.
Take care of yourself,
then get back on the novel.
Getting old. Everything's a hassle.
Have you tried this app
on your phone?
You just speak
and it writes for you.
No. I like reading
my own handwriting.
What about recording?
You can capture a lot of ideas.
No. Can't go back
and edit a recording.
Grandpa.
Just pick something.
Do whatever works for now.
Fine. Fine, I'll do it.
Your phone.
Alright.
Right here. Press here.
Hello, check, check.
Done.
"Hello, check, check."
Hey, that's not hard at all.
See? Told you.
What's in that bag?
This?
I'm just...following your advice.
Ow.
Ugh, why is this so hard?
Come on.
'I'm sorry,'
Somporn says.
The guilt was written
all over those eyes.
I'm sorry.
Don't bother.
If you meant what you did,
don't apologize.
Man, it was just a moment of anger.
I promise it won't happen again.
I know you like dogs.
Carved this for you all night.
You didn't clean it?
Uhm...I did a little.
Not mad anymore?
Still am.
Yo, guys,
any good spot to study tonight?
There's a cafe near my place.
Open 24 hours.
Cool.
Guy, Save, you two coming?
They got into uni already.
They don't care.
Yeah.
I'll go.
Guy, come with us.
I'm busy. You guys go.
Hey, what's going on with you two?
Seriously, are you two in a fight?
- No.
Both of you, come here.
- Get up.
- Come here.
Get up.
Guys, excuse us, please.
Alright, you talk.
We'll handle this.
Dudes, this awkward vibe.
It's killing us.
Any beef between you two,
just let it out. Come on.
Ask Save yourself.
Yeah, I was the one
who made him mad.
When I tried to make up,
he wouldn't.
Try him, will ya?
What did you do to him?
Is it about me teasing you guys?
No.
So what is it about then?
Look, if you can't talk
with us around,
then just the two of you.
If you can't work it out,
don't come out.
We go, guys.
I've got nothing to say,
except sorry.
That's all you've got?
It's what I genuinely feel.
Guy.
Can we give this another shot?
All this time, you were just
playing around.
I was the only one who was serious.
I should just let you go.
I don't want to fall any deeper.
Hmm.
Ow.
Oow.
Hrr.
Oops.
Hmm.
Hey.
Grr.
Good thing nothing's broken.
- Ouch.
- Easy, easy.
Sorry, sorry.
Serves you right.
Told me not to work.
Now you're the one who barely slept.
Dang near wiped out on that bike.
That teach ya?
Aw, Dad.
I've got bones of steel.
Gonna hit me hard to finish me off.
Hehe.
Ow.
Oh. Ow.
Look at this.
We're all down for the count.
Is this a home or a hospital?
Huh.
And today Auntie Oui called in
to run some errands.
What do we do now?
Alright. Watch your six.
Watch your six.
Be careful.
Hey, food's coming.
Jedi, slow down.
Put them right here.
Whew. That was a workout.
Let's see.
Okay, line up. Quick.
Hmph.
Quick.
- Yeah...
- Get in line.
Okay. Okay.
Pipe, hurry up.
- Okay, go.
- Got it.
Just a sec.
Here you go.
Come, come.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Water.
- Get water.
Wow, I wouldn't have guessed
the kids would make
fried rice and egg.
They did.
You didn't help, did you?
How could I?
Even moving hurts right now.
Kids these days are smarter
than we give them credit for.
Yeah, good stuff.
Hi, everyone. Will you throw
this guy some support?
With these Sanae Chan sweets,
you're gonna love them.
You won't be disappointed.
"Where is Phi Guy?"
Have you ordered yet?
Try one box.
And you'll love them.
And...any questions, just ask.
Order now. They look amazing.
Super delicious. I promise.
All this time, you were just
playing around.
I was the only one who was serious.
I think I should just let go.
I don't want to fall any deeper.
Ugh.
Somporn yearned to
make things right with Nan.
Something was slowly taking shape,
like...a whirlpool.
"Even though Nan kept
that cold, stiff wall up,"
"in one unguarded moment,"
"their eyes locked for just
a fraction of a second,"
"and Somporn knew instantly that..."
"Nan wanted the same thing."
His eyes gave it away.
Hmph.
Grandpa.
Ow.
- Hello.
Ma'am, these are Sanae Chan sweets
by Auntie Mart.
This is a royal court recipe,
with a Japanese twist,
because it uses mochi flour.
That gives it a chewy texture
unlike anything else.
- They're flying off the shelves.
- Yes.
- If you buy now, you got a three...
- get 1 free deal.
Price? Just as sweet.
Super wallet-friendly.
Just 60 baht a box.
Let's do a taste test.
- 3, 2, 1.
Ting.
- Yum.
- Oh.
- So good. Unbelievable texture.
- Soft and chewy like a dream.
Nothing else comes close.
Come in.
Here you go.
"5"
"Between Us in the Deep Forest"
Give it a read for me.
"Lacerating yearn" means what?
You don't know that word?
Tell us, Director.
It means what, Grandpa?
Simply put, it means
to miss someone.
But on a deeper level.
Hmm?
So deep it burns.
- Woo.
-Hoo.
Wanting to see that face every day.
- Heh.
- Sweet.
Wanting to hold them,
wanting them near always.
- Argh.
- Raah.
Yes, you've hit the sweet spot.
Perfect.
Yes.
I love it so much, Grandpa.
Is there more? Please, please.
Yes.
I need to read more.
So? Fun, right?
So much fun, sir.
So your publishing house
will print it for me?
Yes, the writing is beautiful.
Mm-hmm.
- The style is great.
- Yes.
But it's a bit much
for young readers.
Not at all.
The kids at my place read it
and all understood it fine.
And to make sure,
we can explain in footnotes.
So readers who don't know
the vocabulary can learn as they go.
Here's the thing, sir.
I'm not saying
it's not a good novel.
But I'm not sure it'll sell
in the current market.
I think it's a bit niche.
It's not...quite mass.
Mass?
Meaning it won't appeal to many.
And like I mentioned before,
it needs NC scenes.
But yours maxes out at a hug.
Hmm.
My suggestion, sir.
Maybe try submitting it
elsewhere first.
I'm rooting for you.
Huh.
It's okay, Grandpa.
They can't see it, but I can.
We don't need a publisher anymore.
I have a way.
These days,
people post novels online.
People publish on their own.
You can do an e-book
or a print copy.
Does that cost a lot?
Posting online is free.
But if you want a print copy,
I will chip in.
You have money?
Sold some game accounts.
Got a decent amount.
You actually make money
tapping on your phone all day?
Hmm, not bad, huh?
But...how can I take your money?
No.
Grandpa, I want to use it
to help our family.
Oh, don't cry.
Ooh...I'm not crying.
Now.
Here.
And Grandpa, I paid someone
to design a cover.
Nice, isn't it?
- Really nice.
- Mm-hmm.
And if I upload this now,
by tomorrow, it may be out. Perfect.
It's a holiday.
People will have time to read.
So...what pen name do you want?
Harn Chanprai?
Hmm? No, no.
Then what?
Anything. Help me think of one.
Something people won't
trace back to me.
Yeah.
Save, get over here now. Right now.
What's going on?
Guy's leaving today.
Today? Why? Where's he going?
America on an athletic scholarship.
We're at the school field.
Get here fast.
Grandpa, I have to run.
Have Snow come help, okay?
Okay?
Ow.
- Where are you rushing off to?
- I'll borrow the bike, Dad.
Sure, ride carefully.
I just had it fixed.
Where's he going?
Save, jeez, you took forever.
Where's Guy?
He already left.
What?
Didn't you pass him on the way?
Guy.
I made you something.
You did this yourself?
Yeah.
I don't want it.
Just take it.
Don't turn down a gift, man.
Use it as a rag if you want.
We're parting ways, right?
What do you mean?
You're leaving today.
Leaving where?
America.
What America?
Forget it.
I want you to have it,
know that I'm sorry,
and consider it my apology.
You don't want us anymore,
that's okay.
But can we go back to how we were?
You told me things can't go back
to the way they were.
Forget it.
Okay.
So you don't want my apology
or to be friends?
Mm-hmm.
Pipe, hurry up. Big mission today.
I'm already walking fast.
Hmph. I get stuck on duty with you
of all people?
It's not like I like this.
Whatever.
Hey.
What?
It's blooming.
Oh...
Grandpa, please help me.
Come on everyone, quickly.
Come here, this way.
- Go, go.
- Grandpa, here.
Here, I checked the auspicious time.
At 8 AM sharp, you hit publish.
- Oh wow, she came prepared.
- Oh...
Trust me on this.
Got it.
7:59.
Hey.
It's up, everyone.
- Yeah.
- Yay.
Hmm...
Hey, one.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Everyone.
- What, Snow?
- That one was just me.
- Oh...
I thought it was someone else.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Right.
- I was so excited.
- That's true, Aunt Mart.
Sorry.
Everyone, the views count
is now five.
- Hey, five already.
- Yay...
Hold on. Any of you, though?
- No.
- Not me.
- That wasn't me.
Yeah, okay. Great, great.
Real readers are coming in.
- Yes...
- Yay...
The numbers are climbing again.
- Yes...
- Yay...
Grandpa, look.
People are reading it.
- Yes.
- Yes...
How many now?
Eleven now.
Hey, everyone, eleven.
- Yes...
- Yay...
Honey Cheese Pie, author of
"Between Us in the Deep Forest."
If word got out that I wrote this,
my peers who look up to me
in the industry
would lose respect for me.
I read his novel
up to the latest chapter.
That makeup scene, you gave him
everything between us to write.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?