Good work.
Um...
Has the Takeichi Masaten
family contacted us?
Oh...
They haven't especialy reached out.
Nothing today either.
Yeah.
Something that's always been there...
(Store Closing Notice)
Doesn't mean it'll be there forever.
I think there was one over there, too...
He's so handsome it's infuriating.
Shizuka.
- Sorry I'm late.
- No, it's fine.
Let's go.
Shizuka?
"Life In Smokey Blue"
(Episode 8: Hope)
Is this a book club?
Yeah.
I thought that besides our classes,
it'd be nice to have
another place to learn.
We're happy about it,
but aren't you busy, sensei?
Well...
Getting more books into the
hands of Japanese readers,
even if it's just one more.
I used to think that was my mission.
But passing on the knowledge
and skills I've learned so far
to your generation
is also an important part of my job.
Passing it on...
For the first meeting, I was thinking
we could discuss Nesbit's work.
I'll contact you with the details later.
Nesbit, huh? I'm looking forward to it.
Are you a fan of hers?
When I was a kid, I was
captivated by the stories themselves.
But as I got older, I often found
myself relating to the author.
I heard she went
through a lot of hardships.
I see.
Her various childhood memories
seem to have become
the foundation of her work.
In the face of a harsh reality,
she might have been writing
to protect her own sense of belonging.
A sense of belonging...
I don't mind being alone.
But family,
lovers,
friends,
hobbies,
work...
I understand that feeling of
searching for something to hold on to.
I also know the happiness
of being held by someone.
But...
there's also the anxiety
and fear of losing it...
I'd be lonely if you weren't here.
It's lonely when someone's gone, isn't it?
Here, this is for you.
The berry tart you like, Shizuka.
Thank you.
- You have a good memory.
- Of course I do.
Minoru likes cheesecake.
Sensei likes savory rice crackers.
And Mikami-san likes coffee jelly.
I guess that's right.
I'd completely forgotten.
And also that when Nukita-san
brings someone's favorite food,
you need to be on your guard.
Since you understand that much,
this should be easy.
Mm, what's this?
Delicious.
I hear it's a popular shop.
Editors always know the best places.
Oh...
So that handsome older guy is an editor.
What do you mean, "that guy"?
Kuji Shizuka, you were on a
date last week, weren't you?
With that handsome older guy.
Huh?
I actually happened to see
you two on the street last week.
Why didn't you say hi?
I was in a hurry.
But I'm surprised you recognized him.
That the person from then
is the same one who brought this.
It was the umbrella.
Ah...
Nukita-san.
He's very good at his job,
but he's pretty clumsy.
So his name is Nukita-san.
He's always losing his umbrellas,
so he deliberately picks
a color that stands out.
Oh...
An ex-boyfriend?
He used to come to our house a lot.
He was my father's editor back in the day.
Now that I've inherited the copyrights,
we see each other occasionally.
Oh...
Are you jealous?
Of course not.
You've got some nerve.
No, it just seemed like it.
I'm glad if I was mistaken.
Come here for a second.
Did you used to like him?
I guess so.
Probably.
Probably?
I was in middle school back then.
I had love, lust, and admiration
all mixed up.
Oh...
That's pretty honest.
I'm past the age of telling pointless lies.
Well,
I guess you're right.
I can understand how a
young Shizuka must have felt.
That guy is super charming.
Seems like he's still got it.
What do you mean, "still got it"?
He's married.
So?
And now he's reappeared in your life
as the editor for your father's work.
No wonder you looked so lost in thought.
Lost in thought?
Don't even try to deny it.
If that's how it looked, you're mistaken.
How am I mistaken?
They're planning to release my father's
essays on translation as a paperback.
He asked if I would write an
essay for the end of the book.
Oh, isn't that great?
Is it?
He said I could write about anything,
but I have no idea what
to write or how to write it.
True, "write about anything"
is the hardest prompt.
Before that, when it comes to my father,
his work, and everything he taught me,
I don't even know if I
want to write about it or not.
Worrying over just a few pages.
Oh...
Since you're struggling with it,
why not just give it a try?
That's one way to approach it, right?
Regardless of whether
you publish what you write,
once you start writing,
you might be able to sort things out.
Kuji Yoshiharu, the translator.
And Kuji Yoshiharu, the father.
The scent of the time
spent together in that study.
Shizuka.
Sensei said he was going to
the university. I tried to stop him,
but he insisted he had a class to teach.
I'll walk with him wherever he wants to go.
It's okay.
His steps are steadier than usual today.
I'll be right by his side,
watching over him.
It's all gone now.
My sense of belonging here.
Let's go home.
Dad.
I'm so glad.
It looks like your work has wrapped up.
Yes, thank you so much
for your help back then.
Not at all. We should help
each other in times of need.
Hara-san.
I'm sorry.
I suddenly remembered...
what happened during the earthquake...
I see.
Hara-san, you mean back in Miyagi...
Let's find a place to sit down and rest.
Hara-san, are you okay?
Take your time. It's
okay to take your time.
Hara-san, if you don't mind...
I'm so sorry.
It's been over ten years,
but sometimes I still get like this.
But I'll be fine after
resting for a bit like this.
Azuma-san, please don't worry about me.
No.
It seems the trains won't be
running for a while anyway.
Oh no...
What are we going to do...?
Hara-san.
I have a friend whose house
is just a short walk from here.
Can I call him and explain the situation?
You could at least
rest there for the night.
He's a translator who mainly
works in the medical field.
He's a trustworthy person.
Um...
I don't mean anything by it...
I know someone like you, Azuma-san,
would never have any bad intentions.
And you can call me a
presumptuous old woman,
but I really can't go to a man's house.
I'm sorry.
How embarrassing.
You were just worried about me.
I'm truly sorry.
Not at all.
I'm the one who should be sorry.
I was being thoughtless and insensitive.
I'll go look for a 24-hour place
nearby.
Wait here for a moment.
Hello?
It looks like the trains
are still out of service.
Hara-san.
I've looked, but every place is full.
It looks like we still don't know
when the trains will be running again.
I think it's best if you find
someplace warm to rest for the night.
I contacted that friend
I mentioned earlier.
He said you're welcome to come over.
I know this might be a bit forward of me.
But I consider you a very
important friend, Hara-san.
I hope you can trust me.
Huh?
Is that Kuji Yoshiharu sensei?
Yes.
So...
My father was the one who
first taught me literary translation.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I've read almost all of his translations.
This one, for example,
when I was getting divorced...
it brought me so much comfort.
I've been divorced once.
It's a bit embarrassing to say.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Everyone has their own story.
That's true.
Ah.
Azuma, can you check on the pot for me?
Yeah, sure.
Milk?
That's unusual.
Hm?
(Receipt for milk)
Is this for Hara-san...?
This is delicious.
I'm glad.
I need to become stronger.
Both mentally and physically.
I can understand why you'd feel that way.
But please don't push yourself too hard.
You might think I'm
acting like I know it all,
but I've been through something similar.
You're right.
Don't push yourself.
No matter how hard you try,
the ones who are gone won't come back.
You just have to carry that
anxiety, sadness, and regret,
and keep moving forward, right?
For those of us who were
lucky enough to survive...
Thank you so much for everything.
Of course. Take care on your way.
I will.
Thanks. See you around.
Yeah, about that thing...
We'll talk later.
Well, I'm off.
See you.
Azuma-san and Kuji-san
are really close, aren't you?
We used to push each other away.
But he's a good person, really.
He is.
It's the first time I've seen
Azuma-san so relaxed.
It's refreshing.
You two have a great relationship.
Hara-san, you may have already noticed,
and if I just leave it as is,
it wouldn't be fair to
let you keep wondering.
So I'll just be direct.
The thing is,
we're gay.
That's why I took the liberty of assuming
that bringing you, a woman, to Kuji's place...
wouldn't be a problem.
Or rather,
I was being naive and inconsiderate.
It's just that Kuji understands
everything about me,
so I feel comfortable around him.
I see.
Now that I've told you all this,
I feel like I might have just given you
an unnecessary burden.
Not at all.
That's not true.
Kuji also said it would
be best to tell you.
We're not trying to hide it.
We just don't bring it up.
Yes, I understand.
Oh, this is my way.
Okay, see you in class.
Okay.
Why am I only getting nervous now?
Takechi!
Azuma-san.
I'm sorry.
I haven't been in touch.
I'm so glad.
You were willing to come back.
I'm going to work hard here.
Besides,
there's nothing else
I can do for Tajimi-san.
Let's do our best together.
Here, this is from Hara-san for you.
She said it's a thank you for last time.
Oh, a Sendai specialty.
This stuff is delicious.
Let's dig in, let's dig in.
We'll need some beer to go with this.
Oh, by the way, I've
decided to give it a try.
The afterword essay.
Oh?
What, did the sun rise in the west?
Looking back now,
the reason my dad so readily agreed
to let me pursue translation as a career...
was probably because he wanted to
leave something for me through his work.
The only thing I can pass on...
is that sentiment.
Passing something on...
Hm?
It's nothing.
So you'll be seeing that
handsome older guy a lot more?
Using the essay as an excuse.
It's not an excuse, it's work.
Legitimate work.
I know, I know.
I'm not young enough to get the
wrong idea over something so silly.
Right, right.
But still,
it's nice to have something to pass on.
Yeah.
Kuji.
Have you ever thought
about getting married?
Never.
I hope same-sex marriage becomes legal,
but I don't have the desire
to get married myself.
Me neither.
A comfortable distance,
a comfortable relationship.
It's nice to be at ease.
Is this what you call a
'comfortable distance'?
Yeah.
Stay by my side.
You yeti.
What part of me is a yeti?
Isn't there one in "Rex's Adventure"?
The farewell with the yeti.
Oh, right, that part.
When I was a kid,
I used to wish there were no goodbyes
and we could all stay together forever.
I just suddenly remembered that.
You can never see them again.
You can never go back.
I wonder if the future is just
an endless series of losses.
Sometimes I suddenly think that.
Time, people, and places.
Someday, will you also...?
Kuji.
Hm?
You know,
I always want to be with you.
With you, Kuji.
Huh?
Oh.
Hey, why the sudden declaration?
I just thought it's better
to say these things clearly.
Well, thank you for the
special announcement.
For the record, this isn't
a confession, it's a report.
Is that so?
Yeah. Message received.
Connected hearts.
Beyond that,
I believe there must be something.
Something that won't easily disappear.
A place where I belong.
What should we eat tomorrow?
(Next episode)
You can't be serious, Kuji.
Competitions can be a matter of luck,
but it's worth a shot.
I'm counting on you.
Always connecting people.
I wish I could be someone like that.
What are you spacing out for?
You're so annoying.