And what is this?
Didn't I tell you to ask me before doing anything?
Can I just have my own life?
You are Tao Sor, you love Kim.
He is your boyfriend.
I'll be right beside you.
What can I do to get Kim out of Tao Sor's life?
Do you want him to have memories?
Or are you afraid that his memories will come back?
Let's make a wish together.
And if I asked "Who is Kim?" how would you answer?
You know the person in this drawing?
I just dreamt that this boy saved another boy from drowning.
You don't have to go, I'll take the clients myself.
Hurry back!
Is there a problem? What did KIm do?
I just want to know where my brother is.
If anything happens to him,
I won't be doing any more business with Siam Sea.
Sang, go check.
Okay, Dad.
It's true, Dad.
There's one ship out right now.
It's the one with the issues.
What did you say?
A faulty ship?
And you just let my brother go?!
I just found out as well, like you!
Let's do this, Dad.
I'll hurry and get some people to go look for them.
Get to it!
I'll go too!
What the hell did you just do? You know what you did?!
Tao Sor's terrified of the ocean, you never knew that?!
If something happens to my brother, how will you take responsibility?
I'm sorry...
I won't accept your apology!
People like you never learn.
Otherwise you wouldn't risk Tao Sor's life over and over like this.
But this was an accident!
And another thing.
Tao Sor wanting to remember things,
that's what he needs.
Don't be making excuses!
Everything that happened is because of you, and only you!
Hey!
Kim already said so,
that your brother went to go see him on his own will.
You can't just blame us for this incident.
So you're gonna protect a guilty person?
You're protecting your brother,
I'm protecting mine!
There's no difference.
We truly apologize for this whole situation.
I might not fully understand how you feel,
but I think...
Kim's feelings...
knowing that he's the reason
someone he loves is hurt...
it would hurt so much.
Okay. From now on, don't ever let these two meet again.
Otherwise we're going to take legal action.
And The Treasure will nullify every business deal with Siam Sea.
Starting from today.
Okay.
My professor says he's in a stable condition, but he's not awake.
Let's go check on Tao Sor.
Hey, you still don't get it?
You have no right to go see him ever again.
Go home.
Please wake up, Son. DOn't let go.
How many times to I have to lose you? I can't lose you again!
Mom?
You shoud go back and rest.
I'll help look after him here.
Okay?
Tao Sor...
you can hear me, right?
Forget everything.
And come back to being my brother, okay?
It's been cleared up, Dad. But...
they won't be doing any more business with us from now on.
This isn't called 'cleared up', we just lost clients!
How are you doing, Kim?
What are you asking him for?! All he's done is cause trouble!
But we're not the only ones at fault here, Dad!
Their son came on his own, boarded the ship on his own,
most importantly, they're above the age of consent!
I don't care! Just go apologize already!
Sang.
I'm sorry.
If you really feel bad,
then I beg you.
Quit messing with that family's son!
Let's go, Dad.
Take your meds and go to sleep.
Calm down, Kim.
I'm on your side, you know?
Thanks...
Happy Birthday to you....
You know the person in this drawing?
Are you okay?
I just dreamt that this boy saved another boy from drowning.
Tao Sor.
It's me.
Your older brother.
I drowned, right?
Someone made you drown.
And someone drowned along with me too, right?
No.
But I saw...
a boy drowning...
and another one came to help...
You must be confused about things.
And...do you remember anything else?
It's okay.
Just forget about all this.
We're gonna go back to being a happy family.
I won't let anything hurt you again.
You're really gonna go through like this?
Yeah, I am.
Anything that is a picture of our parents or me, get rid of it all.
Tao Sor has no need for these memories.
If it isn't of us.
You think by doing this, Tao Sor will truly be happy?
We must clear out anything that can destroy his life.
Let's go.
Chef Mochi, how are you doing?
Who are you?
I'm Chef Daiji, I'm your buddy!
Who's Chef Mochi?
I'm Tao Sor.
Whatever.
Look!
See? I brought you your favorite!
I also brought this!
Here...
So you can draw to pass the time.
Thank you.
You're doing fine, right?
Someone left a parcel for you.
It's gonna hurt a bit, okay?
If...
this will be the only thing that will let me remmber today, I'll glady do it.
Blue whales are sybols of solitude.
But when two blue whales meet,
it's like meeting a certain person, where even in a world so large...
there'll be someone that truly understands us.
It's so you'll know...
that you'll always have me by your side.
Talay?
This tattoo, how did I get it?
Oh, it's just that the other day...
you said you wanted to get a tattoo, so I took you.
And...
why did I choose the design?
Well, the owner gave you some designs to choose from,
and you thought this one was nice, so you picked this one.
Okay.
We've been here before?
Back then, you were so afraid of the ocean,
so I took you here.
I'm the one...
who will be your memory for you.
Tao Sor.
I'm Talay.
I'm your older brother.
Is something wrong?
I wanna sleep some more.
I wanna dream about him and who he is.
Tao Sor,
aren't you gonna eat?
Talay?
Do you know the person in this picture?
Why...
did I draw him so much?
That means...
he means a lot to me, right?
That's not it.
You were just..drawing from experience.
Oh!
Mor Kluen once said that,
if we do things repeatedly over and over again,
our bodies will remember....
That's why you...
That's why you draw these pictures over and over again.
Mor Kluen...
who's that?
Mor Kluen's...
is your regular doctor.
I really don't know this person?
How about this?
I'll get Mor Kluen here,
try talking to him.
Maybe that might ease your mind.
Okay.
Thank you.
Shall we go eat?
Mor...
is there any way...
that we can get Kim out of Tao Sor's memories?
You're talking about something that even renowned doctors and professors can't do.
You can stop anyone from doing whatever you want,
but the one thing you can't stop anyone from doing...
even yourself, is thinking.
Mor, I know!
My family's not ready for that kind of loss again!
Fine, I'll talk to him.
But right now, I'm busy.
There's doctors here for seminars everywhere.
Can you get Tao Sor to come see me in the city?
Let him go outside for a change, it might help with his mood.
These dreams are the only things I can remember.
Also...
I dream about this man...
I've drawn so many pictures of him...
That means...
I've dreamt about him many times
but...
I ask Talay, and he says that I don't know him.
I want to see him.
I know, but I'm not ready yet!
My family's not ready for any more risks.
And what if in the end...
everything was just a thought?
Like how?
In psychology...
sometimes the things we dream or imagine...
might come from deep desires that we can't experience in the real world.
In your case,
some things are similar to some triggers known as:
Daydreaming in Compositon.
It's using the images in our heads and dreams to replace our desires,
but they don't really exist.
Sometimes...
it could point to a phenomenon called:
Conafabulation.
It's when we fill our memories with certain images, while we are unaware of it happening.
Which could come from incomplete memories...
or feelings of emptiness inside.
That means..
all of this is a lie?
It's not a lie, Tao SOr.
But it's your brain trying to create the perfect image.
So you can feel like there is continuity in your life through drawings.
Or maybe it can deeply reflect
how you want an intimate relationship
how you might want a lover
but since there's nothing in your life that is similar,
you expressed that need through drawings.
And...
did I ever love someone?
You love your dad,
your mom,
and Talay.
And everyone around you,
they all love and care about you very much.
Shall we try being happy with the present?
Is that better?
Thank you.
Anything else? I'm gonna leave soon.
Hold on, Daiji...
I can't remember anything...
but...
dreams are the only thing that I can remember.
I always dream about that man.
But he isn't real...
It's like I...
have nothing left.
I don't want to dream of him anymore.
But...
I can't help but feel...
like I want to see him all the time.
Calm down for now.
I'm sorry for...
venting to you.
- It's okay.
I understand, I really do.
Umm, wait a minute.
Please...throw these away for me.
Because in the end...
these aren't my real memories.
Like Kluen said...
we should be in the present.
Get rid of it?
Yes.
Because in any case,
when I wake up...
I'll just forget it all.
Wait a minute.
Hold on to them.
Eitherway, they're still your memories.
I'm off.
What's the matter with Kim?
He's been acting like this for weeks.
When is it going to end?
If it's gonna be like this, I think we should send him back to Bangkok.
I'll try talking to him, Dad.
I'll leave it you. I'll go take care of business first.
There's 2 ships coming in tomorrow,
take your pick, the Western clients or the Chinese ones.
Are you just gonna be sitting and sleeping around like this?
You must be glad.
When I first got here,
you wanted things to be like this, didn't you?
You should just move on, Kim.
Once you get back to Bangkok, you're gonna get to start over!
Forgetting someone for you,
is so easy for you, right?
What do you mean by that?
Like how you don't talk about when we were young.
You act as if he was never in our lives.
Even someone you grew up together with,
you're still able to forget them.
If you don't know anything, then don't say anything.
But isn't it true?
We lived in this house together for so long,
But since I came back here,
I'm asking you for real,
have you ever thought about him?
Some things, though we never talk about them
it doesn't mean that we've forgotten!
Why wouldn't I remember?
That the other day was his birthday?!
How could I forget?!
What he liked to eat...
But some memories...
can destroy us, you know?
Sang, are you okay?
I'm okay.
You don't have to go, I'll take the clients myself.
But this job's...
- Go home.
It's okay.
You've been tired all day,
if I get any tips, I'll share them with you.
Okay, bro. Thanks so much!
I wanna have Mie Hokkien, Sang. Can you get some for me?
I'll eat when I get back home.
Sure, I'll get you 3 servings!
Great. Then I'll get going, okay?
Look after yourself!
Hurry back, okay?
The truth is...
the one who should have died that day...
it should have been me!
It should have been me!
- Sang!
It should have been me that died!
I should have been the one that died!
Sang!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too!
I'm sorry!
I'm the one...
who never knew how you felt.
I'm sorry....
I'm sorry, Sang...
Something going on?
Little bit...
Siw...
Can I have you look after the office for Sang?
We're closing, please come back tomorrow.
Then I'll come back tomorrow.
Nao!
Why didn't say you were coming? I could've picked you up!
I'm here to surpise you.
Here, I got you some snacks from Bangkok.
Thank you!
So are you here on a trip?
How many days will you stay?
This time might be a bit long, I got a new job too.
A job?
Yes, I was thinking of asking you to help too.
Remember Future, the mall owner's daughter?
Her dad had me tell their fortune.
After talking for a while, we got to the topic of natural disasters in Phuket.
So he wanted to create content to inform people about natural disasters
that affect people greatly.
So I told him that I knew a Content Creator that's also a local.
Me?
Yes, but I'll be your assistant.
Actually, that's a good idea.
We can promote Siam Sea as well.
So people can know that Siam Sea...
promotes safe tourism.
And can we handle doing this on our own?
It's actually 3.
I think...
we can start from looking at Siam Sea's past ventures?
Look for reports of storms, accidents, and the like.
About the people who've had direct experience,
would there be anyone still alive?
In that case, I'll make some calls and see if we can get some info.
Yeah, speaking of...
The youngest son from the Precious Resort family, has also been through an accident.
Hmm, should we go interview him?
Even if you asked,
Tao Sor wouldn't remember anything.
As for Talay...
he won't tell us anything.
You're right about that...
But the people there might know something?
What about Daiji?
The one that's always with Tao Sor.
Well, that person could be possible.
Shall we go try and interview him?
I think...
you should go by yourselves.
Huh? Why? You don't wanna see him?
Up to you then. If you wanna just let time pass by you,
then go back to Bangkok, act as if nothing happened...
that's your choice.
Let's go, Nao. Don't give him any attention.
Siw-chan!
It's been a long time, Prof!
Get anything today?
Not yet...
And... Tao Sor didn't come today?
He didn't.
He had soemthing else he wanted to do.
Umm, Daiji?
- Hmm?
I have something I wanna ask.
Of course...
Me being able to meet you...
is one of the best things that's ever happened to me.
And...
how would you know if you've ever experienced anything good before?
Some day, I'll take you to my studio.
if I remember to.
Deal! Because if you don't remember,
I'll go to your place myself!
Kim. When I wake up,
will I remember you?
I told you already, you don't have to worry about that.
Even if you won't remember,
I'll be here, re-introducing myself each time.
Trust me, okay? Get some rest.
I love you, Kim.
Kim!
Tao Sor!
You remember me!
You remember me, right?
Not really.
I can't remember...
But...
your tattoo and mine...
I know you, right?
And we also have memories together...
right?
Yes!
That means I'm not really your son, right?
I don't know why...
I'm even alive.
You're here so we can love each other.
Why the fuck are you helping Kim?!
The perosn that destroyed everything....
isn't me...
but you!
I still want to see you...
Please don't leave me.