SOLD OUT ON YOU
Hae-seok. So I… double-checked the
ingredient list, and the allergy
content is missing.
Oh, sorry about that.
The labeling rules are always changing,
so you have to be extra careful.
According to my calculations…
Oh, look at Chang-ho keeping his
junior in line.
Oh, how about I keep that trap of
yours in line? Never mind. I feel
like I… shouldn't be touching your face.
Yeah, that's a bit…
That's actually pretty hurtful, man.
Hey, are you guys hungry? Dubikimchi?
-Call!
Oh, I'm not finished with this just yet.
All right, but what if there's makgeolli?
Yes, makgeolli.
Oh, perfect. Sounds perfect.
Call.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
I doubt there'll be a table.
-Oh, they always have a table for me
-Come on, let's just get going.
There.
Okay, calm down. Let's talk about this.
Why couldn't you have listened…
to Woo-su's final words?
What words are those? All that pointless
bullshit about responsibility? Huh?
It isn't that you've changed. You've
always been this way.
Hae-seok, if it wasn't for me, The
USU… it would've gone under before you
even joined.
Who do you think made it possible
so you could focus on your research,
clueless about how the world works? I'm
the one who brought in all the
development investments!
But that guy, Choi Woo-su, he
abandoned me. How was I suppposed to
feel about that?
I haven't had a chance to tell Chang-ho
yet, but I'd like you to be team leader
this time.
Wait, what?
For the new project,
NEW PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT PLAN
I'd like you to be the one to
take the lead on it.
But, Chang-ho should be the leader.
He has way more experience, and more
knowledge too.
You're right. Chang-ho sees the forest of
the USU, but you tend to the trees.
And right now, I really need a researcher
who cherishes each and every tree.
The mass appeal Chang-ho keeps
insisting on, honestly, I'm a bit
concerned about it. I feel like it
might become an excuse to leave someone
behind.
Enough excuses…
You little bastard.
Woo-su ending up like that was no one's
fault but his own!
Mechoori.
It's too cold to be out here.
You wanna take a walk?
FINAL EPISODE
You've worked so hard.
And that goes for the both of us. I feel
like that's something we both deserve
to hear that.
If there's anything you still want to
say to me, come on. Let's get it all out
right here and now.
I've got nothing to get off my chest.
I've already said it all.
After that incident five years ago,
I went to the bus station… and got
aboard the first bus I could find.
I got off at a place I'd never
heard about, and I…
just kept walking.
That's how I ended up all the way
in Deokpung.
Looking back I believe… it was Woo-su…
that took me all the way out to Deokpung.
I'm so glad
that Woo-su was… the man I knew.
Here, let's go.
Come on.
This is uncomfortable.
Well, then, like this.
DAM YE-JIN
JI YUN-JI
The Good Morning Cream incident that
shook the cosmetics industry five
years ago, due to a number of toxic
ingredients contained in the cream,
JI YUN-JI'S CONFESSION: TRUTH
COMES TO LIGHT AFTER 5 YEARS
was closed following the suicide of
CEO Choi Woo-su. But today, a new
Ms. Ji Yun-ji, a home shopping host,
blew the whistle on the real culprit
-responsible for changing the ingredients
-Whoa, it was Ji Yun-ji?
Contained in the Good Morning Cream.
It was revealed that she had been
Poor Dam Ye-jin, she was set up.
Did you know about this?
No, I had no idea.
Paid to keep quiet by Mister Son
Chang-ho, the CEO of H.O. Cosmetics.
Wow.
Additionally, Mister Son has been
accused of obtaining a list of pre-launch
SON CHANG-HO SUSPECTED OF
BRIBING NOORI CREAM TESTERS
is damaging. Ms. Ji Yun-ji claims
to have made this confession amidst a
barrage of threats from Mister Son
Chang-ho, and police have secure the
relevant recordings and have now
launched a full-scale investigation.
The number you have dialed is not…
Here's your coffee ma'am.
Oh, hot!
How many times do I have to tell
you to bring my coffee with cold
foam? How many times? God!
My apologies.
That Mister Cha guy finally got the
temperature figured out.
SON CHANG-HO
Should I handle him?
Just take care of it, ok? I wanna
get this over with and go home. Clear my
schedule here and book a flight.
And what about Mister Seo?
You said Mister Cha took the dash cam
memory card, right?
We'll have to deal with the factory
manager.
Understood.
This is my chance. Now I can make an
impression on the vice president.
Compassionate Bohdy saht Vah.
M-Mister Seo.
Um, Father, I only did what the vice
president told me to. Paid well
for it, but I couldn't spend anything
because I've been on the run.
The Lord loves you, my son.
Does that mean I'm forgiven?
Only if you confess your sins
at the police station instead of here.
-Mis-Mister Seo.
-You scared us dissapearing like that.
Ah shit.
And thus, the Lord has forgiven
you first. Now, let us hold hands
with our brothers and sisters next
to us and pray to the Lord.
Oh, Lord.
JOONG-HOON AND ERIC WERE HERE
There's a full recording of the Michelle
ordering the addition of microbes into
the essence. I'm gonna turn myself
in right now, so let's never meet again.
Shall I proceed?
Yeah.
Goddamn it.
Oh, why? Why would you eat that?
Michelle Desruets, the vice president and
presumed successor at the global
skincare brand, L'Etoile, was revealed
to be involved in criminal activities in
connection with this battle for
succession. It has been discovered
that Ms. Desruets bribed a factory
manager to use microbes to contaminate a
batch of products scheduled for launch in
Korea, to sabotage Executive
Director Eric Seo's Korean expansion
project.
You happy now?
Michelle…
That innocent face of yours. It's all
over now, so cut it out.
Things…
weren't always like this with the two of
us.
When we first became family, you
taught me all about the world.
And protected me from the kids
who made fun of the way I looked.
You have it wrong.
I never liked you even for a moment.
If you believed I did, it's because my
father showered me with praise
whenever I took care of you Eric.
The moment you and your mom showed up,
my life became miserable.
Yeah, because what little time I
had to spend with my father…
I had to share with you.
I just…
wanted to be loved by Dad like before.
I'll pretend I didn't hear you say
you never liked me, even for a moment.
The way I remember it Michelle, you
acted the same, whether our father…
was around or not.
GOOD MORNING CREAM
INCIDENT COMPLAINT
L'ÉTOILE VICE PRESIDENT MICHELLE
You have to do something for me.
What the hell?
Oh, for god's sake, come on! Hey you,
come on, back up!
Oh, you all must not be from around here.
This is a one-way street!
Yeah, yeah, stop yapping. Is the
mushroom farm nearby?
Um, tell me why you guys want to know.
Hey, if you don't know, just beat it.
Come on, just back up! We're busy,
you bastard.
For god's sake… What?
Oh, no. Mechoori.
Well, well. So here you are. Wow.
So these are mushrooms, huh?
Looks pretty interesting, eh?
Who are you people?
None of your business. If you just get
lost, we won't touch that pretty face of
yours.
He wouldn't hesitate to use violence
if he doesn't get exactly what he wants.
Get out of here.
Whatever, I guess we'll just have to
get rid of these. Get back!
Hey, move it! We have ten minutes to
finish.
Yes, sir!
Stop it. Stop it!
Hey, what the hell is wrong with you?
You trying to pick a fight?
-Who are you?
-If you lay one finger on that man there,
you're going to regret it.
Hey!
Mu-won!
Get him damn it!
Come on, pick up.
Hitting someone in the back of the head?
That was a dirty move.
Goddamn it!
Mister Park.
Mechoori, you just leave it all up to
us now.
We got it.
-Leave it to us.
Really?
-Ow, that hurts, dammit.
-Hey, move. Just move.
Well, look at this motley crew. You made
it back alive.
Ugh, come on. I told you. That right
there was a one-way road!
When you break the rules, you suffer the
punishment. That's how things work
here in Deokpung.
That's right. Stop yapping.
-Hey… go get them!
-Let's go!
Get in there, come on!
Oh, are you okay?
-Watch out!
-Ahh, that hurts!
Stop! Please stop!
What is wrong with my voice? That hurts!
What the hell?
Damn it! Come here, you bastard.
Ow! Stop it, you bastard!
Retreat, retreat!
Take that!
Retreat!
Okay. Everyone, get up! That path
from earlier! That is the way out.
Got it?
Yes.
Hurry up and leave. These country
backroads get pretty dark. Okay?
Okay everyone. We did it!
We did it! We did it!
-We did it!
-We did it! We did it! We did it!
All right! We did it!
We did it.
Hey! Shut up, damn it!
Hey, what's with that bus?
Hey, it's a one-way, it's a one-way!
Where do you think you're going? Hey!
Want some corn before you go? Huh?
Ahh! Seriously? Hey, get it together!
Those guys have to back up.
Come on, move it!
Hey you, back up.
Ah shit!
Kwang-mo. Over here.
Looks like you're gonna have to be
the one to keep him safe…
I don't think I was wrong.
But still, I'm sorry.
I think I made you that way. I'm sorry.
I'M SORRY
IT'S ALL ON ME
Chang-ho!
Chang-ho.
You had to come all the way here?
Making me miserable to the very end.
Hey, don't do this.
Get down and we can talk about it.
It's all over.
Hey, It'll be alright. Everything's
alright. So just get down from there. I
understand how you feel…
No, you have no idea.
Chang-ho!
Tell me, why'd you do it? If you
were just gonna end it like this?
Live.
You have to.
You have to stay alive. To try… and make
amends. Chang-ho, let's go downstairs.
Please.
-We did it!
-We did it.
-We did it! Hey, we did it!
-We did it! We did it!
We finally did it!
Chang-ho!
God, Mechoori.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mechoori!
Who're you?
Oh, I'm sorry. Where is…
Dam Ye-jin?
Mechoori.
What're you doing here…
Hey, you really scared me!
What's wrong? Did I hurt you? Are you
okay? I'm sorry.
Huh? Just kidding.
Seriously?
Cut it out.
That one actually hurt.
Oh, really? Let… let me see. Oh my god,
I'm so sorry. What should I do now?
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Mu-won.
Ae-ra.
Are you all right?
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
Ae-ra. My Ae-ra.
Ae-ra, you're incredibly strong.
Shouldn't we take him to a hospital?
This whole thing's just weird.
It really is.
Mechoori's here!
Hi.
What are you all doing here?
Hey, we have to clean up the farm quickly
so you can make cosmetics again.
-That's right!
-These are no ordinary mushrooms.
They're the mushrooms that protect our
village!
-Yes! You're right.
-Okay. Let's all work together and finish
this up quickly, then.
Okay. Once we all wrap up here. Why don't
you ome on over to my house, and
we'll have makgeolli!
Mister Son Chang-ho, do you admit to
hiring men to illegally enter and
sabotage the mushroom farm that's located
in Deokpung Village?
Yes.
Hey friend…
CHOI WOO-SU
I'm here. I came way too late, I'm sorry.
Woo-su…
I'll make sure we do well. For your
sake, too. Watch over us.
The broadcast is in two weeks with
Noori Cream. We'll stick to the
original schedule.
-Good luck.
-Thanks, I appreciate it.
Did… you know that the Good Morning Cream
incident happened right after I became a
director? Ignoring the executives'
calls to fire Dam Ye-jin was the first
decision I made in my new position.
So, Dam Ye-jin, you are Dong Hyun-ki's
success story. I'm not hyping you up, I'm
putting pressure on you.
So, did you and your mother have a good
talk?
What?
She's the only one who could have
persuaded Yun-ji.
I'm sure she talked about you. Yun-ji has
a daughter too. Song Myeong-hwa may be a
proud woman, but she's not as strong as
she looks. Reach out to her first.
Have a seat.
Yun-ji. Why are you doing this for me?
You… should ask your mom about that.
I heard the broadcast for Noori cream has
been confirmed.
Why did you call me?
I have a favor I want to ask.
What?
I said, let's do the Noori Cream launch
at the mushroom farm.
So does that mean the whole crew has to
clear their schedules for the day.
Will that work?
What do you think? Huh? The first one?
I mean, come on. I'm begging. Let's just
-do this one at the studio. Please.
-Pease? Pretty please?
What's the reason? You can at least
tell us the reason why.
As both of you know, Noori Cream was made
from ingredients with a story.
So?
It's authentic. That place will explain
Noori Cream without me having to
say a word.
-I mean, she does have a good point.
-Come on, really?
Go over there tomorrow, and check the
equipment layout.
Yes, all right.
I can hear the sound of my life span
shrinking.
You know how much I love you guys, right?
What's all this?
I know I'm making more work for you,
so I picked up some of these delicious
and healthy treats.
Hey, where did these all pop up from?
Hey, how did you know how much I
like these? These two are my absolute
favorites.
Of course.
Ms. Eom, you really need to lighten up
a bit.
It's good.
Okay, I'm letting you off the hook.
-All right, good work. Cheers!
-Cheers!
Cheers!
-I just realized something.
-What?
Nothing goes with a drink like an
eight-hour meeting. Tastes so good.
All right, time for another drink.
Sung-mi, I'm really sorry. Mister Hwang
sir, I'm really sorry.
I'm just so grateful to be able to have a
drink with you like this. It's true.
Sung-mi.
I just can't believe it.
I know, me too. I'm so happy, so
happy to be drinking with you.
So, um… you guys can make it home safe,
right?
Listen, I have someone to pick me up.
Me as well.
With just one phone call.
Mister Rigid? Are you drunk? Why are you
spreading fake news?
And how is Mister Park supposed to
get here this late?
If I tell my honey potato, "I miss you",
he flies right in from Deokpung.
Mechoori would come get me at
three in the morning.
Yeah right.
Wanna bet? Who's gonna get here first?
You're on. If you lose?
Golden bell.
Call. Mister Hwang, join the pool.
-Join in.
-What? But I don't even have a girlfriend.
It doesn't matter, just call someone you
can trust. I'm doing it.
Come on, we all have to call at
the same time, so hurry up and find
-someone.
-Yeah, get ready.
Ready, set, go!
Okay, ready. Go!
Oh! Mechoori, where are you right now?
Honey Potato, where are you? I
really miss you.
Did someone call for a car service?
Ugh, why isn't he picking up?
Oh, honey. I'm sorry, but, um,
my girlfriend's here so I have to go.
Sir, is this you? I called you
so many times. There's an extra charge
for this.
I'm so sorry. God, I'm really sorry.
Come on.
Golden bell, let's call it a tie.
-Let's do that.
-It's a tie.
Let's move it out a little so the two
don't overlap. The table bring, the
table here.
Both sections, yea. Just be careful with
that spot over there.
Okay, got it.
-Hey, just… hold on for a second okay?
-Come on, now. Seriously?
-Let me just put this…
-Mister Park.
Ms. Eom.
Let's bring it over there.
Coffee from the Moon Cafe is here.
Coffee!
-Come and get it!
-Wow.
This coffee has been made by the world's
finest barista, have some.
Come on.
Have one of these. Please have as many as
you want. Oh, hi there.
Macarons, too.
Thank you.
Wow, Mister Kang really just opens up
his wallet doesn't he? He's really cool.
Tomato, did you really just call another
guy cool?
Uh, no, I just meant… he is very
generous. He's a generous man.
-Made by the world's finest barista.
-Oh, not there. To the left.
Have some macarons.
We hope to see you at the Moon Cafe.
Great job, today.
Thank you for doing this.
Oh, don't mention it.
Ae-ra, I'm gonna help them with the heavy
lifting.
Oh, be careful.
Hold on. I can do it. Yeah. Go back to
what you were doing.
Mister Park, that's dangerous. We should
lift it together.
A man should know how to use his body,
not just how to use his money.
The body?
Yeah.
This body is the product of exercise.
You might be exaggerating there.
This body looks like crushed garlic.
Mister Park, please help me out, how old
are you?
Forty.
Oh, same age as me. Which month?
I was born in September.
Well, I was born in March. Turns out
our Mu-won is just a little kid.
Little kid?
You come with me!
My pleasure.
Hey there, wanna go watch?
-With you?
-It's my pleasure.
Um, okay.
I think it'll be fun. Come on, let's go.
Looking good!
INSANE STAGE PRESENCE
DON'T GIVE UP
You have some pretty fancy gear on.
Kwang-mo!
Looking good! Looking good!
-Ae-ra!
-Oh, damn.
Wahoo! Wahoo!
The real winner is whoever isn't
watching this mess.
STOP IT
Yea. We're the losers.
Tomato!
Tomato, where are you going? Did you
see that?
-How does a cappuccino sound to you?
-Tomato, did you see that?
Cappuccino?
-Where are they going?
-And what about lunch?
-Hey, you peeked, didn't you?
-Of course not.
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY ONE
NOORI CREAM LAUNCH BROADCAST D-DAY
Starting today, I'll be coming to you
every Saturday at the same time on
"Dam Ye'jin's Only One." This is
your host Dam Ye-jin, hi.
Maybe you're wondering, "what's with
all this greenery?" This is the
very farm where the White Flower
Noori Mushroom grows, the key ingredient
of the cream I'll be showing you today!
To celebrate the launch of Noori
Cream, we have a special guest today.
The eternal first love of our lives, the
actress, Ms. Song Myeong-hwa.
Good evening, Song Myeong-hwa here.
Would you be on the launch show as a
special guest?
THE GODDESS HERSELF!
WILL THIS CREAM MAKE ME LOOK LIKE HER?
And I must say, your skin really
does look amazing.
Oh, I've been trying to keep it
looking nice. But the real reason
my skin looks like this is truly all
thanks to this Noori Cream.
I've been using it for less than a week
and already, several people have asked
-what I've been doing differently.
-I want to see, I want to see that
But I've only done one thing
-differently. I've been using this
-too. Come on, over here, let me see it.
Noori Cream.
I've tried so many different
facial creams and I think this is the
-first time I've come across one
-Look at that, all right.
With such a soft texture.
You're right. One of the things you
experience for yourselves is
this amazing texture. Take a look at how
smoothly it absorbs into the skin
after only a few light strokes.
The reseachers at Gojeuneok Bio
developed a cream with this texture
for people with sensitive skin who
wanted to reduce even the slightest
irritation that can occur as you're
rubbing it in.
So it doesn't irritate your skin at all,
and it's extremely mild.
That's right, but that doesn't mean
it feels like it just evaporates when it
soaks in. The moment you apply it
to your skin, it feels light, but also
really nice and present.
That's because it contains a new
ingredient extracted from the White
Flower Noori Mushroom, which is great for
skin barrier regeneration. Everyone,
take a look at these clinical test
results and see how much of a
difference our cream made after just
two weeks of use. As we all know, many
people out there struggle with skin
issues. For those of you who have
problems with ordinary creams because of
pain and discomfort,
this Noori Cream was created just
for people like you. The real
strength of this cream is how well
it works for every single skin type.
All the sincerity and integrity of
Mister Lee Hae-seok is bottled
inside this one jar of cream.
The positive results from the live
application trial are only the beginning.
VEGAN FORMULA, GENTLE ON SKIN
At the end of the day, the way your
changes after using this cream
is what matters the most. That's why
we would confidently like to offer you
a free sample. Try it for yourself and
decide. Customer Oh-eight-two-seven,
I love to see that you are excited to
try our product on your child's skin.
And you can feel assured it's all safe.
Everyone, we have just sold out of our
stock of product for today!
Thank you so much for your overwhelming
love and support. Thank you so much.
Thank you for watching.
Cut!
-Really good work.
-Great job today.
-We did it.
-Nice work.
You were great.
Nice job everyone. Good work! Thank you
all. We did it!
Amazing work everyone!
Som Myeong-Hwa, you wanted to say
something?
I don't even know where to begin to
untangle all these threads.
Did you really believe me when I told you
that…
I wanted revenge?
Ye-jin,
Back then, I was so young, and
too selfish…
to understand what was really important
in life.
I know it's not my place to say this,
but please don't hate your father.
He really did try his best… to keep you
from getting your heart broken, Ye-Jin.
I owe both you and your father…
My sincerest apologies.
I'm so sorry. So sorry.
My daughter. I'm sorry. I'm sorry,
my daughter.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry.
HONEY, HEALTH IS EVERYTHING.
EAT, EVEN IF YOU'RE BUSY
HONEY, I CAME TO VISIT
DON'T SKIP YOUR MEALS
WRITE DOWN WHAT YOU WANT TO EAT
SONGHYEON MARKET
I was surprised to hear from you.
I just… felt like eating something
that you cooked.
Oh, well then, I'll have to whip up
something special.
Sir, I think the one on the right
looks better.
-Yes, you're right.
-Okay, then I'll take that one.
Should we grill some pork jowl?
All right.
I'll take some pork jowl too.
-Auntie!
-Oh, my. Ye-jin? Is that you?
Have you been well? The rice cake you
make here is so good.
Should we get one?
I'll take one.
Thank you for cooking.
-I love it.
-Please enjoy.
Um, dad?
Why aren't you asking me about it?
I assume you watched the show.
Because I feel guilty.
Oh. About what, now? Why are you always
apologizing?
I'm just…
sorry for everything.
All this time,
I treated you so bad, dad.
All because you hurt me first. And I
wanted to hurt you the…
same way I was hurt.
I never should have done that.
And I want to say I'm sorry.
Ah, Ye-jin, I-I'm the one who's sorry.
By the way,
are my side dishes too salty?
-What?
-Is that why you didn't eat them?
No, no, he likes bland food, is the only
reason.
Oh, really? Really?
Uh-huh!
-Such a relief.
-Has that really been bothering you?
Yeah, I guess it has.
Today, we're going to be making manduguk,
using bone broth for an even
deeper flavor. Does anyone
have experience making dumpings
from manduguk? One person? Oh, today's
class won't be easy.
What are you working so hard on?
I was trying to… make these for Ye-jin,
but it is pretty hard isn't it?
Are you nervous?
Oh, you do this.
All right, you do it.
Together.
Press on the count of three. One, two,
and three!
BUY ONE NOW
IF YOU HAVEN'T
NOORI CREAM IS PERFECT
FOR SENSITIVE SKIN
MY SKIN IS SO DIFFERENT
I HIGHLY RECOMMEND
MY WHOLE FAMILY USES
THE NOORI CREAM
This item keeps selling out, and it's
becoming an absolute must-have among all
your favorite hot K-pop stars. Give it a
try.
The color's pretty. So many colors as
well.
-I know.
-Oh, it's so pretty.
This color here is famous for being a
K-pop boy band item.
I love these. We need more of these.
Well I like it.
Come in.
-Oh, Ms. Jin-yi.
-Hello!
I'm Na Jin-yi. I'll be your assistant
host for "Dam Ye-jin's Only One." I'm
looking forward to working with you.
Hello, Ms. Jin-yi. Game time.
Yeah.
-Sweetie?
-Yeah?
I want to buy this.
Oh. Get it. Get it.
-I love you.
-Oh, stop it.
I missed you.
Really? What a load of bullshit.
Whoa, Ae-ra. Please wait here a second.
Oh, hi, Ms. Paeng is it? Wow, it's
been a long time. It's me, Kang Mu-won.
Oh, yes, Mister Kang, how have you been?
I've been well. How about we have a
little chat? I'm afraid the man
you're with, is involved in marriage
fraud.
What do you mean, marriage fraud? Is that
true?
I-I I just I-I just. Who are you, anyway?
Huh?
Bastards like you would never understand
how much more valuable Ms. Ae-ra's
affections are than all the clothes
you're wearing. Go ahead.
Hey, take off everything I bought you.
I-I I just I-I just wanna…
-You bastard.
-Come on, you old hag!
Old hag? You scumbag.
Oh, you don't need to see this.
You wanna die? Huh?
Hey. Hold on. Just call the police!
-Police? Yes. Call the police.
-No no not the police, I take it back!
-Hey, I think that's Park Kwang-mo.
-Are you serious?
He's even more handsome in person.
Come on, let's go say hi. Excuse me,
are you Captain Deokpung, Park Kwang-mo?
Well, I would be lying if I said I
wasn't him.
Do you think I can maybe shake your hand?
Oh, sure, of course.
I'm Park Kwang-mo, the Captain who lives
and dies for Deokpung.
Me too.
I suppose you two are fans of the show?
Yes, we are.
Well, hello.
I think there's something wrong with her.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
See you.
Should I just take down your channel?
It does bother me a little bit though.
Now the whole world knows how
cute you are.
But why would it? The only thing that's
cute to me is my Tomato.
Close your eyes.
Open them.
PARK KWANG-MO TV
What is this?
Park Kwang-mo… I'll get you a gold
button inside of a year. Let's live
together.
Tomato.
Does that mean you're moving to Deokpung?
Oh.
Don't worry about that.
My little Bong-chan. I made all
your favorite things to eat.
Happy birthday.
Mister Seo. We have another meeting with
a magazine tomorrow evening.
What? As soon as we arrive in France?
Oui.
It's the same, here or there.
People are very interested in
the new CEO, so I pulled a few
questions I think they might ask.
Where'd it go?
Are you sad to leave?
Not really. I just don't think I'll be
coming back for a while. Although, I
learned a lot. We'll be very
busy from now on. I'm excited.
Me too, Mister Seo.
When used with Noori Cream, it showed
excellent regenerative effects.
So this is the first sample, right?
I think this will sell even better,
Don't you?
Yeah.
Love it, but…
Oh, my god!
No, seriously, it's all good. All good.
When it comes to serum, texture is
very important. Cause if it
doesn't absorb well, whatever you put on
next will just sit there. This texture
is extremely fresh and lovely, but
maybe the absorption could be just a
little bit better.
-Dam Ye-jin.
-I'm listening.
It's because you're trying to rush it.
Here.
If you pat it a few times like this, it
absorbs.
When our custiomers are getting ready for
work, it's a matter of every second.
I think if you just add a little bit
of an ingredient that helps with
absorbtion, the market response will
be much better.
Okay. Noori Serum is a product
that's made with fermented
ingredients for absorbtion. If we add
synthetic ingredients, it will
interfere with both the texture and
the efficacy. Dam Ye-jin, you're saying
we should reduce the efficacy?
Lee Hae-seok sir, you must know I'm not
saying that.
Then tell me, what did you mean to say?
I'm saying you need to respect the
opinion of the host. After all,
-I'm the one who has to communicate
-Leave them alone. They're just talking.
Directly with customers!
Just continue what you were doing.
Don't you know the saying, "speak to
others as you'd want others to speak to
you"?
No, I don't. But I do know "do unto
others as you'd have them do unto you?
Uh, whatever. How about the law of
WANNA GO GET MALATANG LATER?
action and reaction?
I was the one who what?
You said… Listen lady!
Listen, lady?
No I meant, I meant Dam Ye-jin!
Yes, Mechoori?
It's Matthew Lee. Matthew Lee!
Oh, for god's sake. From now on,
let's just communicate through email.
You nitpick at everything I say.
Huh? I did my research and gave my
opinion after careful consideration.
Okay.
-That's three times.
-What?
HAE-SEOK AND YE-JIN'S WEEKEND RULES
You talked about work three times.
So, three kisses.
But we're in the yard.
It's part of my house.
That's not the rule.
Yes, it is. Come on. Three of them.
No.
But the rule, it's rule number three.
All right.
Okay.
Come here. Come here.
Wait a second.
No matter how much I think about
this, I'm still curious.
What is it?
When did you know I was the one?
I'm not sure.
I asked you something, come on. When
should we say that we first started
dating?
Why does that matter?
Lee Hae-seok, come on. Just tell me when
you knew I was the one.
Som-yi told me that if you find yourself
wondering if somebody ate well, or
slept well, that's when the stanning
starts.
I think that's when it began.
From the day I started to worrying
whether you had slept well.
I like that.
So, did you find anything in this book
that touched your heart?
Well it says here that modern science has
yet to find a sedative more effective
than graditude.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
DEOKPUNG COMMUNITY CENTER
Here we are. See you tomorrow.
Yea, see you tomorrow. If you're lucky.
JEON WON-TAEK:
SEO JIN-WON
SO JONG-IL:
YANG HEUNG-JU
Ladies. Here you go.
You're really the best!
I'll come see you soon for another one.
WON-TAEK'S WIFE:
JUNG SU-JIN
Keep staying healthy, okay?
JEON JUNG-MUK:
KIM JUNG-HWAN
Um, can I buy you dinner tomorrow night?
What?
I said, let's have dinner tomorrow as
well!
Oh, yes!
HWANG KI-HONG:
YOON JAE-CHAN
Why are you smiling?
Na Som-yi, go to sleep.
I will in a second.
NA SOM-YI:
AHN SE-BIN
NA JIN-YI:
KIM SEO-AN
Mom, I'm sleepy.
You are?
Mom, Good night.
I love you Seo-a. Nighty-night.
I love you.
JI YUN-JI:
PARK AH-IN
Thankyou all for your hard work today.
I look forward to more of it soon.
DIRECTOR DONG:
SHIN DONG-MI
A WARM DAY OF HOME-COOKED COMFORT
Tomorrow… I'll try harder.
What you did for today is enough.
SONG MYEONG-HWA:
WOO HEE-JIN
DAM SEOK-GYEONG:
KIM YOUNG-JAE
You were great today.
I'll love you even more tomorrow
than I do today!
PARK KWANG-MO:
JO BOK-RAE
EOM SUNG-MI:
PARK YE-YOUNG
When should we have our families
officially meet?
Sorry?
This coffee's delicious. This cappuccino
is really very good. Very delicious.
It's decaf, so it doesn't even keep me
awake at night.
MOON AE-RA:
JO WOO-RI
Good night.
KANG MU-WON:
YOON BYUNG-HEE
Good night.
I hope to see you in my dreams.
YANG SANG-GEUM:
GOH DOO-SHIM
I feel like I don't want to leave.
Thank you for everything that you've
done.
CHA JOONG-HOON (MR. CHA):
KIM JOONG-DON
Okay then,
Goodbye.
ERIC SEO:
KIM BUM
MATTHEW AND FRIENDS:
MY FRIEND IS SICK
And he lived happily ever after with
Matthew was no longer alone,
his friends.
The end.
Som-yi gave me this book.
So that's Mechoori, huh?
Matthew Lee, already.
Sweet dreams.
Don't just dream, just sleep well.
DAM YE-JIN: CHAE WON-BEEN
LEE HAE-SEOK: AHN HYO-SEOP
SOLD OUT ON YOU
THANK YOU AHN SANG-WOO AND SEO HYUN-WOO
FOR THEIR SPECIAL APPEARANCE
SON CHANG-HO:
CHAE DONG-HYUN
FACTORY MANAGER: JO WAN-GI
SECRETARY SHIN: EUN SUN-WOO
BUS DRIVER: AHN SANG-WOO
BONG-CHAN: NOH SEONG-EUN
YOUNG SANG-GEUM: KOH SEO-HEE
GI-BOK: JO JIN-HYEONG
MS. OKPO: NAM GWON-A
GI-SUN: JANG EUN-SIL