National Radio. And Telvison Administration
Go away.
Let go of me!
It's upside down.
It's the opposite.
How dare you!
What are you doing?
What?
How dare you hit me?
I'll kill you.
Let me tell you.
You've gone too far.
Tie it up.
Eagle.
Mr Five.
Stop!
Why are you here instead of drinking?
You guys.
It’s Leader’s family business.
It’s none of your business.
How rude.
Brother Zhen San, you mean...
we are not family?
I mean
The boss didn’t say anything.
No one is allowed to make trouble.
Alright.
Stop arguing.
Golden tooth.
What kind of disguise is this?
It's all upside down.
He Xiaopian, why did you hit me?
Look at this place.
What day is it today?
Talk nicely.
Are you sober now?
Brother.
You have to help me.
Look how those outsiders beat me.
Look at my ears.
What happened?
Brother, say something.
Boss.
I hurt him.
Untie him.
Hurry up.
Brother.
Lingbao Ba Liang has been your family for years.
If that's the case,
it would have been more than ten years.
Except for Huo Er and Meng Si,
I'm probably the longest.
You came here today
just to take advantage of your seniority?
Brother.
Since you said so,
let me make it clear today.
I'm here for your daughter.
I'll give you
and betrothal gifts.
Why are you stopping me, uncle?
Don't make trouble for your father.
He's already like that.
Didn't you see
are looking for trouble?
Golden tooth.
Do you really want to be my son-in-law?
Whoever gets in my way today,
I'll kill his whole family.
Looks like all these years of education
all these years.
Brother,
Stop talking to me
with benevolence and morality.
If anyone dares to go against us,
stand out.
Mr Five.
I cut one of your ears today
to teach you a lesson.
Remember,
Humans are just three bowls of noodles.
This kind of scene
You're shameless.
I won’t show you mercy.
I only have one daughter.
Although my daughter is naughty,
but no one can covet my daughter.
My marriage
is not up to anyone.
It's up to her.
Eagle.
You tied this button to death today.
That's why you're the only one who can undo it.
I'll kill him now.
It won't be that easy.
We need a perfect plan.
Think about it.
If you had a son-in-law now,
you wouldn't be so arrogant.
Shangguan Bao.
Sooner or later,
I'll return these three bowls of noodles to you.
A wrong has a source, a debt has its debtor.
I broke your ears.
Do you want revenge or revenge?
you can come at me.
Madam said
these three bowls of noodles
I’ll do you a favor today.
Take what I said
as a fart.
I was wrong today.
But what do we
do we have?
With a knife.
I'll take your life.
How dare you!
Young Master of Qinglong Fortress.
took one of your ears.
for your sake.
Does what you said count?
What?
You said
I have the final say in my marriage.
I won't force you.
to do something you don't like.
Okay.
I'll tell you now.
The person I like
is him.
What's going on?
Eagle, think carefully.
Marriage is a serious matter.
Jintooth, don't just stand there.
Go back.
I want one of your ears.
It's a good deal for you.
Wu Zhen.
You are now the son-in-law of Qinglong Camp.
Not to mention one of his ears,
even if I kill him,
no one dares to say a word.
You want me to fight with him, right?
Give him another chance.
I'll spare your life today.
If you do it again,
you will die.
Brother.
Don't be so arrogant in the future.
One ear is missing.
Don't bite your tongue again.
I have to remind you again.
Remember.
From now on,
if anyone goes against Leader,
he’s going against our army.
Wu,
if you can’t do it
because of your feelings,
My men can do it.
This is my family matter.
It's none of your business.
Get lost.
I'll remember you.
I'll be back.
Mr Five.
I must avenge him.
If my father didn’t spare his life,
he wouldn't have left Qinglong Hideout alive.
right?
I'm talking to you.
Ni, I'm talking to you.
What are you doing?
Don't do this in my room.
It's not a festival.
Why do you make fun of them?
Sooner or later,
It will be useful.
What is it
Min Ja.
I knew she was here.
I'm exhausted.
Come here.
Go help.
Look
What help? I'll go.
Come on.
Stay in your room.
Wait for regret.
Hurry, regret it.
What should I regret?
Young Lady Zhen Zhu, you just want to be happy.
You saved that Wu.
Haven't you thought about
about his background?
What will you do in the future?
Who are you? I brought him here.
Besides,
It's fake anyway. It's okay.
It's okay. It's fake.
Except you think it's fake,
who else would think it's fake?
Who would take it seriously?
Who else
will take it seriously.
Sister.
I think
Actually, Wu Zhen is quite good.
At worst, you...
Go away
Wait, Min Ja.
So you mean
I lost a lot.
Young Lady Zhen Zhu, you've turned around.
No, no.
I have to talk to him.
Me too.
Silly girl, why are you getting involved?
I'm so tired. Go work for me.
What is Shangguan eagle trying to do?
Brigade Commander Cui.
Mr. Wu.
Congratulations.
I know today's wedding
is a bit tricky.
What are you going to do?
What else can I do?
How about this?
I think you're good.
It won't take long
Soon,
I promise I’ll be your leader.
We can be a match then.
We just met.
You're allowed to be the commander.
Brigade Commander Cui.
You're short of people.
I am.
But I need someone who can
and capable to fight Japan.
I have no good impression of your army.
You should find someone else.
It seems you have some misunderstanding
the National Party.
Tell me.
I can explain it to you.
Father.
Come back!
Come back.
Let's go.
Wu Zhen!
Wu Zhen.
I need to talk to Wu Zhen.
What happened today doesn't count.
I know
you did it to help me.
Help you?
You think too much.
I was trying to help my father.
I didn't see the roof was on fire.
I know.
Why do you know everything?
Do you know
those people outside have taken it seriously.
Think of a way.
It has to be over.
What is it?
Why are you asking me? Think about it.
I...
What else?
I helped you once.
It's your turn now.
I can't think of anything.
Are you trying to take advantage of me?
Don't worry.
I never thought about it.
Immediately.
Find a way.
Mr. Tian.
I'm in Yuxi.
I can't say that I'm very capable.
But here,
If there's any celebrity or something,
I'll probably know.
You came here today
to do this business.
is not an ordinary person.
This is my first time in Shanzhou.
I have some friends
some of my friends
It's easier to walk with more friends.
It’s easier to do business.
But the munitions business
is a capital offence.
That depends.
I want no one
no one
show respect to you.
So,
the first thing I came to Shaanxi
is to visit you.
As the saying goes,
to pray to the mountain.
Please keep us safe.
Our Xidao
to protect our peers.
and the poor.
If you make a fortune like this,
like you.
Madam.
Don’t be so full.
Like this.
you can choose
on this list.
What do you think?
I despise the Korean Republican Party army.
But I don't want to embarrass them.
If you want to be rich,
please go to where I can't reach you.
What you said today
in return.
If I meet you again,
I won't be so polite.
Master.
See the guest out.
Please.
Okay.
In that case,
I'll take my leave.
Master.
Find two quick-footed men
and keep an eye on them.
Understood.
Brother, are you really
to help Wu Zhen and Eagle?
Isn't that your idea?
The situation was critical.
I didn't expect Eagle
she would really do that.
Can you take back
Can you take it back?
Brother, it's my daughter.
You have sharp ears.
Although what happened today is irreversible,
I'm not confused.
I can't let an eagle
to a stranger
a stranger who doesn't even know his background.
This is the reason
for the time being.
and suppress your vigor.
You're right.
But I'm always worried
the golden tooth is holding a fire.
The fire will be on fire sooner or later.
What we need to think about now
how to finish
to the end.
If not,
I'll go down the mountain to find my father.
Tell them I’m dead.
Madam just said
Without his order,
no one is allowed to go down the mountain.
Sister.
Sister
Say it.
Sister.
When I passed by the accounting room,
I heard my father
about your marriage.
Oh no.
If my father knows I'm lying to him,
he will be furious.
Sister.
You're in big trouble this time.
Are we still getting married?
No.
If it doesn't work,
I'll go out alone.
I won't implicate you.
In that case,
you’ll lose your face.
Stop dawdling.
There is only one way.
The best way is to leave.
Let's go down the mountain together.
Say something.
I'll listen to you.
Okay.
But the problem is the mountain is closed.
How do we get down?
What's your plan?
Let's go back to the county first.
Let's wait for Mountain Queen to return.
What should I do
What should I do?
Master, Madam wants to see you.
Please come in.
Master.
Madam. Master.
You must know Brigade Commander Cui.
Yes.
Wu,
To be honest,
when I saved you yesterday,
you look like an old friend of mine.
A childhood friend of mine.
His surname is Cai.
Wen Kui.
Lower your voice.
Why are you here?
I'm looking for Wen Kui.
My father lost his temper just now.
saying your father is an accomplice.
and wanted to send someone to catch your father.
My father is not.
Lower your voice.
Don't talk.
Go and tell your father.
or it'll be too late.
Go through the back door.
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
My name is Wu Zhen.
Wu Zhen.
You saved Eagle today.
and you didn't kill Golden tooth.
You did well in these two things.
Of course.
Since you're a bodyguard,
you should act like a bodyguard.
Since you became a swordsman,
you're going to be my son-in-law.
Do you know the rules in the mountain?
I know
I already know.
I'll do it according to the rules.
Oath?
That's right.
That's the rule left by the ancestors of the swordsman.
Every swordsman
must go down the mountain to kill a person.
and bring this head back.
There's no turning back.
Fine.
I have a rule.
Go ahead.
I only kill demons.
You can write this down.
Next time you meet a devil,
a few heads will do.
Madam.
I can testify for that.
If he didn't kill the devil yesterday,
I wouldn't be sitting here.
Okay.
I'll remember this.
Since Eagle likes you,
I want to discuss with you.
Do you agree?
There is only one way.
The best way is to leave.
I’ll listen to you and Madam.
What if I let you get married right away?
I'm afraid not yet.
Why?
Madam.
I should inform my father
about this marriage.
You're right.
Where is your father?
In Shanzhou.
I'll tell him when I get down tomorrow.
Master.
Yes.
Listen to Wu Zhen.
Go get his father.
Okay.
I’m on it.
No, Madam.
What if my father disagrees?
What?
My daughter doesn't deserve you?
Not really.
My father has to think about it.
I think
Mr. Wu didn't mean that.
Marriage is important.
The order of parents and matchmakers
you should follow the rules.
Wu,
If you don't mind,
I can be a matchmaker.
Bring your father here.
Cui Wenkui!
How dare you mention my father to me?
It's getting late.
Go get some rest.
Yes.
Wait.
This jade pendant
is for you.
No matter what happens in the future,
come to me with it.
I will do it.
Leave now.
Wen Pei's father said you're an accomplice.
and wanted to arrest you.
I know.
But I can't leave.
Why?
You still don't understand.
In this world,
in this world.
Thank you.
Major.
Looks like Shangguan Bao doesn't trust us.
We have to find another way.
Major.
Lieutenant.
Did you see Golden tooth?
Lieutenant, you're so clever.
That fool will not only cooperate with the Imperial Army,
but also incite other people who are dissatisfied with Shangguan Bao.
We'll follow your orders.
Good.
Where is he?
Here.
So you are all in cahoots.
Two living people
They didn't know someone was following them.
Chief.
I... I saw nothing.
But I saw it.
Thank you, Mr. Golden tooth.
Who are you?
We do arms business.
arms business?
He said you can avenge me
and give me guns and money.
Is that true?
Yes, I did.
And I will fulfill it.
But we don't know each other.
Why are you helping me?
Someone will help me.
If the road is not fair, someone will do it.
There is justice in everything.
Mr. Golden tooth is handsome
and handsome.
Why can't you be
the son-in-law of Shangguan Bao?
Don’t mention Shangguan Bao.
When I mention Shangguan Bao,
I think of their family.
I just want to kill them. I...
Why should I believe you?
I saw everything
at the birthday banquet.
Not only Qinglong Fortress,
no one can help you
can help you?
If you agree to cooperate with me,
not only can I avenge your ears,
I can also help you
the leader of Qinglong Fortress.
Really?
Yes.
And that girl Shangguan Eagle,
to me.
If I catch her, I...
I'll make her suffer.
By then,
everything in Qinglong Camp
Leave them
whatever you want.
Okay.
I'll work with you.
Happy cooperation.
Brigade Commander Cui.
Sorry for what happened today.
Madam is tolerant.
No wonder you can command one side.
Got it.
I think
Brigade Commander Cui should be
you should leave immediately and take office.
I won't keep you.
Master.
Yes.
See him out.
OK.
Madam, goodbye.
Brigade Commander Cui, please.
Sister, what are you doing?
You make me dizzy.
Come on.
Have a seat.
No.
My father is looking for Wu Zhen now.
at this time.
Tell me.
Are they really
discuss the marriage?
I don't understand.
Is my father in such a hurry to marry me off?
About this,
you can't blame me.
Who is it?
Tell everyone
I like him.
I did that to deal with Golden tooth.
I shouldn't have done that.
Pour me a glass of water.
It's useless to say these now.
Besides, didn't you two agree
I don't care if he's dead or dead when we go down the mountain.
Once you come back,
once you come back.
I need to think about it.
How about this?
What?
Look.
Since we're down the mountain,
Why don't you play a round before you come back?
What do you mean?
I mean,
he went down the mountain to visit his father.
You have to embarrass him.
We are thinking the same thing.
Madam,
you know very well about being generous.
But why do I feel like
Why do I think it's driving us away?
He has ruled a place for 20 years.
He has tens of thousands of swordsmen.
Do you think he's that simple?
Why are you still defending him?
I'm not defending him.
Think about what he said on his birthday today.
and what he did.
He's not that simple.
Let's not talk about this.
Meet Captain Li first.
Are you ready?
I have to go.
Otherwise, even if I can't leave,
I have to invite my father here.
Are you ready?
We're waiting for you two.
Let's go.
What are you looking at? Let's go.
Can you go out in this?
Change your clothes first.
Look
Look at him.
So considerate.
What are you doing here?
Close the door.
You agreed so easily.
Be good to her.
I said be nice to her.
You...
She's carefree.
You should go easy on her.
No need. Just one day.
Don't worry.
I like the well-educated
is not your heroine.
But she likes you.
Alright.
Madam.
Master.
Miss Leng and Young Master.
and Master Xi.
They have left.
Okay. Go back.
Yes.
Brother.
We need people now.
Do as I say.
Add more cards.
I've arranged it.
But, brother,
what are you up to?
I don't understand.
You just let them out?
Eagle should go out and see the world.
I also want to know
who I am.
Captain Li.
It's late.
What brings you here at this hour?
My security team
was reduced to Youxi independent Brigade.
[as an independent Brigade?]
I don't know.
You really don't know?
I'm a big parent.
How would I know that?
Brother.
You can ask the commander of the first war zone.
He must know
what happened.
I went to Qinglong Hideout today.
I met a man surnamed Cui.
who claimed to be the Brigade Commander of Yuxi independent Brigade.
Brother,
What a good thing.
What's good about it?
Think about it.
He's here.
The Japanese are here too.
Let him fight the war.
He'll take the responsibility.
You are familiar with this area.
and take the responsibility for collecting military provisions and provisions.
The bullets can't be hit.
And oil.
Killing two birds with one stone. What a good thing.
You didn't see him today.
He doesn't look like a good guy.
Not to mention oil,
we won't even be able to get water.
Think about it.
It's cold.
How long have you been up the mountain?
Qinglong Fortress.
It's been five or six years.
It's been so long.
Why didn't you tell her?
What?
Say you like her.
If you told me earlier,
you wouldn't have made a scene.
What a piece of wood.
All right.
Let's call it a day.
I should go.
You can't leave.
We had a deal.
I'll leave and you'll go back.
Okay.
You can leave.
You can tell her yourself.
Okay.
It's just one night.
Stand guard for a while.
There are a few households in front.
Let's go eat something.
That's great. I'm starving.
It's a deal.
After eating,
I'll go find my father.
Who told you that?
We had a deal before we went down the mountain.
I'll go find my father.
Go back to the fortress.
when you came back?
Why don't I remember?
What do you mean?
I want to see your father and be filial.
Wu Zhen, come here.
Actor table.
Lee Seung-yup.
Choi Bo-wol.
and actors.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile. Wang Lu.
Yue Wang Yang Ziyi Tian Chenzhe Deng Kai Mei Liang Dong.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin. Wang Yukun.
Jungle.
and Wu Jianyu, Zhang Guangyan, Sun Yuanwen.
Qin Haosen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Liangliang, Lin Nan. Liu, Yu.
Yuan Guangming, Liu, Fei, Du Geng, Yuan Zhongchuan. Wang Zhiwei.
Li Jinyang, Zhang Jianing, Liu Rong Qi.
Staff table.
Director team.
Yun Lihua.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Tian Shuizhou.
The clothing team.
Han Yuchao.
Wang Jin-sung.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Props team.
Ye Youth.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian Qiao Chunsheng Yang Tao Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong Xi.
Zhang Chenggui, Su Mingxin, Liu Hongxing, Di Yuping Xu Guanglle.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li Zhang Changchang.
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Chou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping
Yang Shuli, Chen Yongsheng, Liu Junfeng, Liu Fumin.
Yeo Yeong-Jeon, Yang Soo-ri, Jin Yongsheng, Yoo Joon-bong. Yoo Fu Min.
Cut.
Wu Xiaobo.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Ma Jun Nan.
Thank you, Hong.
Dubber.
Zhou Xiangning.
Music Producer.
Theme song, Hero.
Cheng, Spear.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple, Village Cave Scene.
[Seobu Village Committee of Lingbao City]
The village committee of Shanzhou District,
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Legal consultant Zhu Yongpeng.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
There are three gates in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong County Commission.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
Shandong Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
[Henan Movie Development Co., Ltd.]
[Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.]
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
joint production unit
Provincial Committee PR Department.
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Gansu Lanyi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Three Daododong Movie Development Co., Ltd.
Media is limited.
I'll reward Zhang Bing first.