National Radio. And Telvison Administration
No.
Why did you stop him?
Wu Zhen is going to win.
How dare you!
What are you doing here?
Can't I just take a look?
Let's go back.
Let's go.
You hit me too hard. You need to keep three points.
I didn't expect you
at such a young age.
Madam, you flatter me.
Okay, I'll listen to Eagle.
Follow her.
Great.
Madam, actually I’m not…
Let’s go.
Dad, I have good taste this time, right?
Not bad.
Who could it be?
So what?
We are in such a remote place.
Why would the war come to us?
Mr. He,
Weren't you happy
to fix the airport here?
Now you know it's hot.
Brother, cut the crap.
You've earned a lot for fixing the airport.
Right?
Don't be sarcastic.
Let me tell you.
If anyone wants to go to the airport,
who wants to go to the airport.
Me?
I'm the one who suppressed the people.
I was the one who caught the peasants.
Even in a few days,
I was the one who negotiated with the bandit Shangguan Bao.
Look at you.
Open the door and be an upright official.
Close the door and get some dirty money.
It's very comfortable.
Brother.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I just want to tell you
be nice to me.
Otherwise, no one will work with you.
Guards!
Yes
Give me half of the things
half of them as military pay.
and the other is ready to load the car.
to Qinglong Fortress.
Yes.
If Shangguan Bao is willing to cooperate,
how many years can you stay here?
If he doesn't want to,
The Japanese is calling.
It's not too late for you to run away.
Nini, come here.
Cheers.
Pour some wine.
Boss.
This guy is obviously from a wrong background.
Just arrange him for me.
This...
I let him stay to find out
He's not from a bad background.
He's a big shot.
You mean his martial arts
not only martial arts.
I heard that
the Japanese have occupied Luoyang.
I'm afraid there won't be
in the future.
You have 100,000 swordsmen
and is deeply supported by the public.
There's no need to worry.
I'm just the head of a small fortress.
Can I resist the great situation?
What do you mean?
Besides the swordsmen,
who else are there down the mountain?
Demon.
The army
and the Republic.
I've dealt with
with the Republic.
Their way is simple.
is to beat the devil
to feed the people.
But these two
are the hardest thing we can do now.
Report!
Madam.
Master Zhu just sent a message from the fortress
the army came to the village.
I heard them talking about bandits
They said they would come to pay their respects to you.
The Zhu family is grateful for your kindness that day.
so he came here to tell you.
Okay, you can leave now.
I was going to touch the pole a few days later,
I didn't want to make a big fuss.
It seems impossible now.
It's nothing.
I'll ask my men
to surround the surrounding area.
Let’s see who dares to make trouble here.
No need.
I can't guarantee anything else.
They came to me
I don't think they dare to make trouble.
Let's drink.
Drink
Let's go, Nini. Let's go home.
I didn't drink.
Why did they arrest you?
We can't afford to pay the bandits.
they took us to fix the airport.
The airport needs food.
Don't you know?
They only give us half a nest a day.
We can't eat or sleep well.
We have to work so hard.
We can't hold on.
The guards are tight.
You'll get beaten if you slow down.
We sneaked out
so we ran out.
The airport is still closed.
Yes.
He's in the room. He doesn't need to work.
There are guards at the door.
And the security captain Li
went there every day.
Do you know what he looks like?
No.
He's so mysterious.
Someone delivers food and serves pots.
They said
has something to do with the Communist Party.
When will you grow up?
Stand there.
How dare you ask her to drink?
Have you forgotten what Madam said?
What if he gets into trouble after drinking?
You'll pay for it.
Where?
Let's go.
The front. Okay.
Here.
Okay, let's go.
Don't talk back.
The threshold.
Here. Okay. Be careful.
Min Ja.
Oh my god
Why is there another one?
You...
Who are you?
He's Miss Leng's new bodyguard.
Why did the bodyguard
Why are you here?
I'm new here. I don't know the way.
She leads the way.
Okay, come on.
Hold it
Hold it well. Okay.
Be careful. Hold tight.
Come with me.
No.
Don't go there.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Stop laughing.
Hurry up.
Take me to her place. Okay.
Let's go.
Step.
This way.
Be careful.
My head.
Stop it.
Sir, wait.
Qinglong Fortress is closed. You can’t go in.
I’m here to congratulate Madam.
Your lady
loves the magnolia I play for her.
This one.
I can't do this.
The mountain is closed. No one can enter.
This is a token of my gratitude.
Look, I'm here.
No, no, no.
Stop talking. You can't go in.
Please go back.
Madam.
Follow me.
Close the door.
Where did you get this dagger?
This is the dagger Wu gave me.
It seems that this dagger has an important meaning.
But we don't know the enemy.
I can't reveal my identity yet.
I picked it up.
Where did you pick it up
On my way back.
Why are you here?
It's chaotic now.
to make a living.
With your skills,
the army and the army can feed you.
Why do you have to be a swordsman?
As long as you don't do it,
but to be a ghost.
Anyway,
would you
would you like to be the army
or the Republic of China?
What do you think?
I...
I don't know.
Brother.
What is it?
The Zhenshan Liang of Black Tiger Mountain
and Wu Laoliu from Qingfeng Camp are here.
Wait for me at the Gathering Hall.
Yes.
Madam. Madam.
Have a seat.
Didn't you receive the golden sword token to seal the mountain?
Yes.
Wu Qiusheng came to me.
He said something.
I think it’s necessary to tell Leader.
I hope
make a decision for us.
Madam.
Say it.
Here's the thing.
Recently, many refugees
many refugees came from Shanxi recently.
They are all dragging us down.
My village can’t accept it.
Now that the mountain is closed,
the refugees are even missing.
A few days ago, I heard that
Baliang's golden tooth
and kidnapped these refugees.
So I want you to give us a solution.
Yes, Madam.
I also heard that Wang 12 from Chunli Ravine
Sun Jiu Huan from Eagle Cat Mountain.
and Wei Chase Lee from the long worm Ridge.
They also killed refugees
rob the soft and kidnap the women.
Are these all true?
Yes.
My brother
for saving my life.
I dare not lie to you.
If these information are true,
why don't we take the opportunity
In the past two years,
I may have lacked discipline.
The Japanese
might end up here one day.
I don't want my brothers who risked their lives together
and don't worry about our country.
Let's turn against each other first.
You too.
If you meet
please advise me.
Without my order,
without my order.
Yes.
Who is so good?
You're awake.
It's rare.
It's my first time drinking water.
It's warm.
You did it yourself?
What? I did it myself.
Didn't you do this?
And this.
I just woke up.
I still have a headache.
You didn't do it.
Looking at Shangguan Bao,
the mission is not
as easy as I thought.
We must find a chance to go down the mountain
to discuss the next move with Wu Jingyuan.
I'll be Shangguan Ying's bodyguard.
I have to find a way
to
to the organization.
You're awake.
About today...
What is it?
The water and the tea.
Thank you.
It's just a bodyguard.
What I said doesn't count today.
Did I say too much?
You said you could still drink.
What else?
You promised me
after your father's birthday banquet,
Let me say hello to my father.
I remember this.
This one
It's called Three Daggers.
This place is so beautiful.
Where else have you been?
I've been to many places.
Really?
Is there anyone better than here?
There are good ones.
and bad.
But good or bad
is our home.
We can't let the Japanese harm us.
The Great Wall of Qin is like a steel prison.
I don't dare to cross the tomb.
Although the clouds are linked in thousands of miles,
[is as high as the Yao level.]
Sir.
Why do you say the cloud in a million miles
is not as high as the Yao level?
Let me ask you.
What is the Great Wall for?
You said to fight against foreign enemies.
Yes.
Because with the Great Wall,
the army won't dare to cross Linzhou again.
But have you thought about it?
Although the Great Wall blocked the enemy,
but it also blocks us.
Like a prison.
As the saying goes,
As the saying goes, there is a law.
It's not just a high wall.
I see.
Thank you, sir.
Go home early.
Don't let your parents worry.
I don't want to go home.
Every time I see my father,
I feel that he is immoral.
Since Shangguan Bao
has been
he has controlled us
like the Sun monkey under Five-Finger Mountain.
It's almost done.
Tell me.
We are bandits. We don't kill or rob.
What is this?
17 is right.
We are bandits.
Don't try to be a swordsman.
and tie us up.
Guys, listen up.
Today, I will let Shangguan Bao
to marry his daughter to me.
Once the old bastard dies,
What am I?
The head of the stick.
Mr Five.
It's good,
But we've sent messages
to Mr. Huo and Meng Si.
Forget about them.
They are all cowards.
Let me do it today.
Come on.
Put it here.
Hurry up, everyone.
Be careful.
Hurry up. Be careful.
Put it here
Hurry up
Move the wine here
Coming.
Hurry up.
Here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Please come in.
Thank you.
A bolt of white cotton with golden teeth.
What does it mean?
What's going on?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Please come in.
Two gifts boxes for Chairman Lin of the Chamber of Commerce.
The security team has 1,000 yuan.
Nian Nian.
Li, the captain of the security team has just paid 1,000 yuan.
Captain Li.
Do you know me?
Isn't this Young Lady?
We just met two days ago.
How can I not know him?
How is it?
Is my birthday gift okay?
How long did it take
How much money did you receive from the people
to gather a whole box.
My lady.
That's not pleasant to hear.
You have to listen to it.
Go down the mountain.
There are many in the theater.
We don’t serve you.
Miss Leng.
Today,
to celebrate your father's birthday.
Please do me a favor.
Sure.
Take off your gun.
You...
Put your guns there.
What?
You broke the rules here.
Put it down.
Brigade Commander.
I think this girl is quite tough.
Really? Yes.
Why do I think the security team
are so useless?
Brother.
Who does she look like?
It's right to let her kill Li Gang.
That's right.
Accountant.
Coming.
Take your gift.
Remember to ask our men
to return their money tomorrow.
Okay.
Please.
You returned the money to the people.
What if they take it back? Stay there.
Yeah, what should we do?
Mark each money.
As long as you see them spend,
I'll kill them all.
Accountant, mark all the money.
Cut a corner down.
When you see the security group,
kill one by one.
Okay.
She's quite smart.
How could she think of that?
He’s a bit cunning.
Boss.
Congratulations.
I didn't expect you to come to Qinglong Camp.
Welcome.
Did your daughter
learn this from you?
I've been lacking discipline since I was a child.
Don't be angry, Captain Li.
Then we can't talk.
That depends on what we talk about.
Okay.
Please support our security team every month.
500 silver dollars
plus the heads of two bandits.
From now on,
I won't make things difficult for you anymore.
I understand.
So the silver you gave me today
to return the money in two months?
You're really scheming.
How about this?
I'll take a step back.
200 silver dollars.
and 200 people per day.
to fix the airport for me.
No matter what you do in the future,
I'll pretend I didn't see it.
and do evil.
Who did this?
This is the clam on Baldy's head.
I, Shangguan Bao, lead 18 swordsmen
to reorganize Moyun Ridge.
I've been in the Three Durds for 20 years.
No one has said I did evil.
How about this?
we invite the people down the mountain
and tell them something bad about you.
I'll cut you into pieces.
and say something bad about me.
I'll make up half a kilo for you.
and see who dies first.
Fine.
Come on. Come on.
Brother.
Good idea.
Since you can’t get in touch with Leader,
I’ll leave now.
The Shanzhou Security Corps.
Keep reading.
I appoint Cui Wenkui
the independent Brigade Commander of Yuxi, the 5th Warfare Army.
From today onwards, the Shanzhou Security Corps
will be deposited to the first battlezone, Yuxi independent Brigade.
I'll also send you ten guns.
Independent Brigade Commander Cui Wenkui
Send ten gifts to Hanyang.
Choi Moon-Kui.
Wait here.
Mr. Shangguan, congratulations.
Brigade Commander Cui, nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
I came in a hurry
I didn't bring anything.
I'll give you the gun of the security team.
But Yuxi independent Brigade
Mr. Shangguan, wait a moment.
I need to deal with family matters.
You're Captain Li from the security team.
They told me before I came.
you're quite capable.
Why didn't you defeat a woman just now?
Brigade Commander.
I've never heard of it before.
I'll let you know when I get back.
I wanted to ask you a few days ago.
what kind of official is Brigade Commander?
Who is the Brigade Commander?
I'm talking to you.
Bad temper.
Fly up and down
Are you playing tricks with me?
From now on,
there are only swordsmen in Shaanxi,
No bandits.
Anyone who can fight against the Japanese with us
are brothers.
Do you understand?
Come back.
When I went up the mountain,
I saw many guards down the mountain.
Let them go back.
I don’t need protection here.
20 new books.
Ten calligraphy and paintings.
I didn't expect Choi Moon-Kui to be here.
What's his purpose
to come here?
To be honest,
I came up the mountain this time
to discuss something with you.
What you said just now was so good.
As long as we fight against the Japanese, we are brothers.
As for this,
won’t be confused.
Madam.
Have you seen our battle with the Japanese?
What do you mean?
I know.
all your swordsmen
are all warriors.
But the Japanese are well equipped.
If we fight them with a knife,
it's no different than death.
The army is holding guns.
They also suffered heavy casualties.
So...
We're all like that with guns.
Let alone holding a knife.
This is not the past.
The Shanzhou Security Corps has a bad reputation.
And there are only thousands of people.
I’m a hundred thousand swordsman.
You made the national army
with just a few words.
Who should be the Brigade Commander?
Who are you?
A scholar from Shanzhou
to become a legal executive in Qinglong Fortress.
The so-called literature can’t rule the country.
and martial arts can't stabilize the country.
A name is not worth mentioning.
He Xiaopian, the number number of No.1.
He Xiaopian.
If you don't follow Miss Leng,
instead of following her?
Pee
What about you?
Stare at you.
Okay, keep an eye on him.
It's Prince Liyang's birthday today.
Seven sons and eight sons-in-law are at the banquet.
They are paired and matched.
Only our son-in-law...
Okay.
One more.
Everyone, calm down.
Everyone!
Brothers,
Thank you.
Qinglong Fortress has been
for years.
As you all know,
today is our master’s 60th birthday.
Originally,
not to be so grand.
But I don't think
won't agree, right?
Yes.
Now, on behalf of our Patriarch,
to all of you.
Mr Five.
Thank you for your concern.
Thank you.
I wish you all the best.
and longevity.
Wish you happiness and longevity.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Here you go.
Good for you.
You've worked hard too.
Let me pour it for you.
Okay.
Come on
Drink as much as you want.
Drink. Don't be shy.
Come on. Again.
Bottoms up.
Let me tell you.
More.
No problem.
I'm happy today. Come on.
Come on.
Mr. Tian.
Nice to meet you.
Our boss asked me to tell you
he likes your gift very much.
He asked me to thank you on his behalf.
and let me propose a toast to you.
It's just a small gift.
As long as you like it.
Okay.
Mr. Tian, I’ll drink first.
Have a seat. Enjoy.
This man
a normal businessman.
Are you hiding here?
Where did you go?
I told you not to leave my sight.
What are you looking at?
It's strange to fly on the boat.
Where did he go?
I...
Are they going to rebel today?
Eagle.
You're so naughty.
Wait.
Don't run so fast.
He's really not an ordinary businessman.
He sneaked into the backyard.
in the backyard?
Eagle, slow down.
Don't follow me.
Then who else can I follow?
Eagle.
Eagle, why did you run so fast?
Sister Eagle.
Eagle.
Stop hiding. Come out.
I'll be the son-in-law of Qinglong Fortress.
After we get married,
give birth to a golden tooth for me.
I'll make you a golden tooth.
Our whole family has golden teeth.
How big is your golden tooth?
Where did you come from? Get lost!
Hey.
Chief of Qinglong Fortress invited me here.
Your breast hair is still wet.
Can Shangguan Bao invite you
Yes, he invited me to extract my teeth.
I think you're scolding me.
Get lost if you know your place.
Get lost!
Stop!
Eagle.
Be good. Be good.
You little bastard, you're inhumane!
Are you going to cut my root?
Kid, I'll kill you.
My father said
you can't shoot a man.
Nice gun.
It's for shooting ghosts.
Am I a ghost to you?
Come on.
Do you dare to shoot?
Shoot me. Do you dare?
I dare not.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Sit down.
It's about the family.
Keep eating.
You little brat.
How dare you shoot me?
I'll hit you.
Take revenge on me.
If you dare to bully Miss Leng again,
I'll kill you now.
I'll kill you first.
Stop!
I shot him. I shot him.
It has nothing to do with you.
I'll take care of everything.
Banliang has thousands of people.
If they all rebel,
can you take the responsibility?
Cut the crap.
Darn it.
Fly on the plane. Are you watching?
Actor table.
Lee Seung-yup.
and the actors.
Zhang Fan Cheng from Hongda Tian State Peak.
Yue, Wang, Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai Mei Liangdong.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo Gong Jian Feng, Sun Haochun from Li Kai Wu Village.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin. Wang Yukun.
Huhe Wu Jianyu Zhang Guangyan Sun Yuanwen Chang
Chen Yao's jungle competition.
Qin HaoSen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Liangliang, Lin Nan, Liu...
Du Geng Geng.
Li Jinyang, Zhang Jianing, Liu Rong Qi.
Staff table.
Director team.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
The clothing team.
Han Yuchao.
Wang Jin-sung.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Props team.
Ye Youth.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian Qiao Chunsheng Yang Tao Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong Xi.
Zhang Chenggui, Su Mingxin, Liu Hongxing, Di Yuping Xu Guanglle.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li Zhang Changchang.
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Chou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping
Yang Shuli Chen Yongsheng Liu Junfeng Liu Fumin
Yang Soori
Cut. Cut.
Wu Xiaobo.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Ma Junnan.
Dubber.
Zhou Xiangning.
Zhang Ruobing.
Music Producer
Cheng, Spear.
Theme song, Hero.
Cheng.
Tang Tiantian.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple, Village Cave Scene.
[Seobu Village Committee of Lingbao City]
The village committee of Shanzhou District,
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Legal consultant Zhu Yongpeng.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
There are three gates in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong County Commission.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park]
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
[Henan Movie Development Co., Ltd.]
[Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.]
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Gansu Lanyi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
[Henan 3 Daodong Watery Culture Development Co., Ltd.]
Zhang Bing will be rewarded first.