National Radio. And Telvison Administration
It's about 1944.
when the devil came to our three-track temple,
The people have nowhere to settle down.
Take the mountain as a king and be a swordsman.
The Eight Army sent Cai Yun.
His mission is to fight together.
Have you completed the task?
The story should start all over again.
Please let me tell you the origin.
Brother.
Master.
Isn't it too grand
Isn't it too grand?
It's not.
Sir, please tell me.
Five years ago,
you went out of Black Tiger Mountain once.
and never stepped out of the fortress.
I recited the strings in the study all day.
Those who don't know
I thought you were a Grand Secretary.
Patriarchs of each mountain came to visit you.
You always asked me
to hide in the backyard and refuse to see guests.
Now,
a children's song is popular in Yuxi region.
It's called
Three axes.
There are swordsmen on the tunnel.
Qinglong Fortress is famous.
A leopard in the Fortress.
Shangguan Bao, the head of the stick.
He's good at flying in the clouds.
Brother.
It's time for you to show up.
Yes.
Thanks for your concern.
I have to show up.
Yes.
The invitation for our birthday banquet
is like a thunder
in Shaanxi.
A storm is coming.
We'll wait and see.
Captain Li, how have you been?
Yes.
I know.
Your master’s 60th birthday is in two days.
You just sent invitations
to every mountain.
How do you know?
Thanks for your concern, Captain Li.
There are many things to do in the fortress.
If there's nothing else,
we’ll leave first.
Wait a minute.
Just in time.
please send me a message.
Tell them the security team will join us this year.
to celebrate their birthday.
You are an official and we are bandits.
Are you here to celebrate your birthday
Do you bring a gun or a gift?
You're funny.
Do you think I'm suitable to carry a gun
or a gift?
It depends on what you like.
Right?
Let him go.
Let's go.
Young man.
What's the matter?
Sir, do you sell this monkey?
No, I don't.
If you don't sell it, how can Sun monkey go to the Peach Association?
Let's eat puppets rice.
How can you sell your own stuff?
Everyone knows this rule.
You are Comrade Wu Jingyuan.
Why are you so young?
Comrade Wu Jingyuan, actually I...
It's not safe here. Let's talk on the way.
This way.
Mr. Wu, you...
Listen to me.
If something happens,
you're my son.
called Wu Zhen.
This is the general situation.
Kong has no news at all.
One thing is for sure,
a traitor betrayed Kong.
When he broke up with me,
Give me this.
They say the bandits in Shanzhou are rampant.
We've been in Shanzhou for so long.
We haven't seen a killing bandit.
That's right.
I guess
he was scared by our army.
They all ran away.
Bandits are bandits.
It's just a bad pass.
Give me the gun.
Cover with fire.
Yes.
What's going on?
Boss, there's a fight at the back.
Why don't we take a look?
What are you looking at?
Hurry up. Let's go.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
Listen to me. Don't rush!
There's a sniper!
Bastard!
Japanese.
Go back and wait for me.
What a fool.
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Where did he come from? Interesting.
Stay here.
Major, they're too strong.
Let's go!
Brother.
How did you know they were Japanese?
I was resting on the road.
He didn't see me.
I heard them speak Japanese.
Bro.
You look familiar.
Have we met somewhere before?
What's your name?
Wu Zhen.
Thank you for saving my life.
You two.
What's your name?
You saw that
they are not swordsmen.
This is our territory.
When did you see
our people will be masked when they go down the mountain?
That's right.
You two are swordsmen of the Three Avengers.
Our Brigade Commander is asking you.
Are you deaf?
Everyone, listen to me.
We are all Chinese.
Just one sentence.
We don’t need to beat our own people.
Mr. Wu is right.
No need.
Captain Joo.
Don't hold your gun against our savior.
Mr. Wu, you're quite skilled.
Are you interested in joining our army?
You must have a place to use martial arts.
Do you know where this is?
This is the place of swordsmen in Moyun Ridge.
There are 100,000 swordsmen.
Your army is nothing.
It's just a security group
who bullies the people.
Brother.
Come with me.
Go with you?
Who are you?
Shangguan Bao,
It's my father.
Nice to meet you.
Why do you want to be a national army?
Just bully the people.
The rest are useless.
Why don't you go up the mountain and be my bodyguard?
Live happily and freely.
What do you think?
Really?
We'll know when we go up the mountain.
Young Lady Zhen Zhu, stop it.
I'm not.
My father’s birthday is in two days.
We need someone in the village.
Let’s go.
Fly faster.
You want to be a national army?
Wu,
See you again.
How useless do you think the security group is?
That's why these swordsmen are so arrogant.
Bastard!
Lieutenant, we still have a chance.
The superior finally deciphered the password.
I know Choi Moon-Kui.
He came to Shanzhou to form a defense line.
to stop my royal army from going west.
I wanted to kill him here,
and disrupt the deployment of the Chinese army.
I didn't expect
I underestimated him.
and wasted a great opportunity.
It seems that
is not an easy place.
The Republican Party and Communist Party are all here.
I didn't expect that.
But I think
they came here for only one purpose.
is to win over the swordsmen.
The last two riding men
should be the real swordsmen.
Major, our target is the airport.
Idiot!
The airport is over there.
Once the Chinese are built,
we'll occupy it.
As for the swordsman of the Three-Daodari,
Whether it's the Republican Party or the Communist Party,
Yucy will become a hard bone.
That's my biggest problem now.
If we don't solve this,
our army
can only be trapped in Luoyang City and can't go west.
In this way,
when will the empire be completed?
Right, Major.
According to Agent No. 1's latest news,
the 60th birthday of Shangguan Bao,
It's almost time.
Good.
Let's take this opportunity to meet him.
Secretary Peng.
Wu.
Here.
The security team is here again.
Yes.
The people who can escape have already escaped.
What? It's not working again?
I did.
But I just got it.
The code hasn't been matched yet.
The devil and the National Party Army are on fire.
They're separated.
I can't find it.
I haven't given you the task yet.
Our priority now
is to get in touch with him.
I just received an order from my superior.
I have to leave now.
to the border of Jinchaji.
Besides,
I can't come back in a short time.
You and the special forces
depends on you and the special agents.
Secretary Peng.
I'll go to the lost place tomorrow.
The villagers all know that
as a teacher,
I play shadow puppets on the street.
to make a living.
It's very convenient.
It won't arouse suspicion.
Wu.
I know you're a cautious person,
I have to remind you.
Yes.
The battle of 100,000 swordsmen
not only has Kong's efforts,
but also
it's also about the anti-Japanese battle of Yuxi.
Don't take it lightly.
Secretary Peng.
The organization gave me such an important task.
I won’t let you down.
Don't worry.
When you return to the Three Axes,
I believe the three axes
all the banners against Japan.
Okay.
For what you said,
I have to propose a toast to you.
No.
It should be like this.
To win against Japan,
let’s toast in advance.
What do you think?
Fine.
I’ll drink tea instead of wine.
Let’s toast to victory.
Come on.
Here.
What ticket?
Two gold tickets and one flower tickets.
Where are they from?
To work.
How far is the road?
My son-in-law.
Miss Leng.
I'll protect the person behind.
Follow me and serve him well.
Yes.
Stop!
I don't want to come.
Your lady invited me.
What are you doing?
Brother, the rules in the Fortress.
No weapons are allowed when strangers enter.
That's all I'm wearing. Are you happy now?
Let's put them in the wooden prison first.
No.
Please.
Miss Leng.
Miss Leng!
Father.
Uncle.
Father, the invitation has been sent.
Eagle, you're finally back.
We're going to shoot today.
We were worried about you.
You mean that thing?
We did it.
It's so lively.
On my way back,
I saw a ghost.
He pretended to be our swordsman
chasing after two armies.
Can I leave them alone?
You can't, right?
Ghost.
The Japanese?
and met the security group.
called Li Gang.
Father, he said
he would come to visit you in two days.
No.
What are you talking about?
The post is over.
From tomorrow on,
study on the mountain.
Father,
I told you.
From tomorrow on,
I'll check your homework.
Okay.
Well...
Dad.
I'm leaving.
Rest early.
Brigade Commander.
I didn't expect this pit to be so interesting.
You see, the trees don't see the village.
We can't find the house.
Smell it, but no one is here.
Interesting.
How dare you, demon! Take this!
Okay.
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
We'll shoot if you keep running.
Okay.
Stop.
Why are you shouting?
Let me ask you.
Did you see two people go over there?
No, no, no.
No.
Old man, have you seen two people?
Boss, I'm just a puppeter.
I only look at the thing in my hand, but not people.
Kiddo, do you see it?
I saw it.
Come on.
Where did it go?
They went that way.
Over there.
Yes.
Go after him!
Let's go.
Come on.
One more time.
Chief.
Political Commission.
Chief, I failed to stop him.
Cai is so strong.
What is it?
Chief, the Political Commission.
I'm going to the front line.
The brats are in Luoyang, Henan.
If we keep hiding here, we'll lose our home.
What are you yelling about?
Who said we are hiding here?
How dare you!
Cai, let me ask you.
Are you from Shaanxi?
I'm from Shaanxi.
Do you know kung fu?
Three or five demons can't get close.
Wei,
I want to go to Shaanxi personally.
First, I want to find out the truth myself.
Second,
if Kong really sacrificed,
I'll go see Shangguan Bao.
Since Shangguan Bao can dominate the Three Avengers,
it means he's not easy to deal with.
If you go there rashly,
if Shangguan Bao refuses to acknowledge you,
the bandit will be ruthless.
Wei, listen to me.
Time is running out.
We must meet Shangguan Bao at the appointed time.
Otherwise, he will think
the Communist Party goes back on his word.
We finally took a step.
he's going to take it back.
Don't worry.
We have our people there.
I’ll play it by ear.
I'll take Cai with me.
He is from Shaanxi and knows kung fu.
He can protect me.
Don't worry.
Say something.
Chief, the Political Commission.
I just want to go to the battlefield
and fight with the brats face to face.
You're so dumb.
If you send me to Shaanxi,
I'll send you to the front line when you're back.
I'll let you fight with the devil.
Really?
I'll complete the mission.
Go.
Bao, go!
Political Commission.
Political Commission, you're hurt.
By the bridge, persimmon tree.
Do you remember the contact code?
His name is
Wu Jingyuan.
I remember it all.
Political Commission, stop it.
Let's go.
Zheng.
I can't take it anymore.
Go.
I'll cover you.
Political Commission, I can't leave.
I failed to protect you. It's all my fault.
Let's go together.
Zheng.
My mission in Shanzhou
is to turn the 100,000 swordsmen
into a powerful anti-Japanese force.
to stop the devil from going west.
This mission concerns the safety
and Yuxi's safety.
must be completed.
You must go to Shanzhou to find Wu Jingyuan
and complete this mission with him.
Understand?
One person can't defeat a demon.
We have to unite all the unity
to defeat them.
Let's go.
Go.
I'm not leaving.
Go. This is an order.
If you don't leave, I'll die right now.
Political Commission.
Let's go.
Go!
Mr. Zhao died.
What should I do if I were him?
Since I'm here,
I think I can meet Master Shangguan Bao.
and Shangguan Bao.
How should I explain my identity?
and finish
the mission that Kong and Zhao didn't finish?
Come here.
What?
Wu Zhen.
If the trial goes well tomorrow,
you'll be my bodyguard.
Let me show you the rules first.
Rules?
There are rules.
Nonsense.
Qinglong Fortress has rules.
Listen carefully.
First,
you have to listen to me.
Do you hear me?
Second,
if I want to go out to play,
you have to prepare the water
and dried food.
The knife should be grinded like a mirror.
The gun needs to be loaded with bullets.
The water should be full.
Noodles.
It's mixed.
It has to be mixed.
Are you choosing a bodyguard
or a maid?
Third,
Don't interrupt when I'm talking.
That's right.
Okay.
And then,
when I lie to my father,
you have to help me.
I know which is a lie.
You'll know then.
No, no.
I told you not to interrupt.
Okay, go on.
How many?
I...
Who is she?
She...
You talk a lot.
I need to know who I serve.
I think so.
She is the legal executive of Qinglong Fortress,
of Qinglong Fortress, He Xiaoni.
He Xiaoni.
He Xiaopian.
Are you sure it's the father and daughter?
What do you mean?
Besides good martial arts,
you’re quite eloquent.
Madam.
This is basically the situation along the way.
Li said he was coming.
Yes.
What is he up to?
He wanted to use your birthday
to discuss the current situation.
Keli just came.
what should come will come.
The world is dangerous.
We can't fall behind.
Yes.
Brother is right.
We should plan ahead
and plan ahead.
Where is the person that Eagle brought?
In the wooden prison.
Fifth,
We are all men here.
Many people like to peep at us.
You have to beat them up if you see them.
What if you can't?
You have to fight even if you can't.
Otherwise, what kind of bodyguard are you?
Don't worry.
If you die,
I will avenge you.
It's not too late.
Sixth,
If we did something wrong,
you have to take the blame.
Yes.
If you get punished, you have to take it.
Stop yawning. Do you hear me?
Got it
Go on.
Catch.
Eighth.
Right, eighth.
If someone asks us who looks better,
what do you say?
I can only choose between you two.
Not you.
Remember.
You have to tell anyone.
My sister is the prettiest.
I'm the second one.
Got it.
I have another question.
If someone asks you who is the best swordsman in Qinglong Fortress,
what would you say?
I know.
You're the first and she's the second.
No, she won't.
I'm second.
If you're second, who dares to be the first?
My father.
Yes, Madam.
Madam.
Did he remove all his weapons?
They're all here.
Show me.
Madam, this way.
Eagle.
Sir. Father.
Uncle.
Take them back to their room.
Miss Leng.
Are you Shangguan Bao?
Bastard!
How dare you talk to Madam?
What’s your name?
Wu Zhen.
Do you want to be a swordsman?
I can follow you.
What did you say?
I mean
I’ll follow your order.
What if I want you to die?
It depends on your fate tomorrow.
Shangguan Bao
is not a simple leader of swordsmen.
I can only stay here
to find out what happened.
Why are there so many Japanese in Shanzhou?
Brigade Commander, what are you thinking?
I'm thinking
why the Japanese arrived in Shaanxi so soon.
How did you know
those people were not swordsmen yesterday?
but Japanese.
At this time,
It can't be the Communist Party.
The swordsmen wouldn't have covered their faces.
And their weapons are very delicate.
Only the Japanese.
I remember.
Looks like the Japanese really came here.
Search! Search!
Search one by one.
Which part are you from?
Which part are you in?
Which part?
Which part? Are you blind?
Drop the gun. Drop the gun.
Okay, okay.
What are you doing?
Sir, we're here to collect money.
What money?
Sir, there are too many bandits here.
They took money from bandits.
Why did those bandits
still act recklessly?
This...
Because there are too many bandits,
we can't defeat them.
Where is your captain?
The captain went to buy a birthday gift.
Who's celebrating his birthday?
It's Shangguan Bao's birthday. It's his 60th birthday.
Our captain
Shangguan Bao.
Yes.
Leader of Qinglong Camp, Shangguan Bao.
Get lost.
Yes.
Let's go.
You two go get ready.
Let's go up the mountain.
to pay our respects.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Come on. Come on.
Stand still.
Wu Zhen.
My daughter wants you to be her bodyguard.
You have to show her your skills.
Brother.
I used to be your bodyguard.
Since you're here,
you must defeat me.
Please.
Is he okay?
Our boss
is one of the best fast killers in the village.
Even the old man praised his cutting skills.
I don't think he can beat him.
What do you know? Go.
We'll see.
It doesn't look good.
I just think he's quite interesting.
so I brought him up the mountain.
Tell me.
It's boring
It's boring, isn't it?
Actor table.
Lee Seung-yup.
Choi Bo-wol.
Deng Bao Quan.
and actors.
Li Hongda Yu Guofeng Gong Fan Cheng Kaiyan.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhao Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin, Wang Yukun.
Ji, Chao, Zhao Zhigang, Kung, Ji Youyi.
Yang Tao, Chen Yao, and Rui Qian.
Qin Haosen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Liangliang, Lin Nan. Liu, Yu.
Xu Shidong, Liu Yongtao.
Du Geng Geng.
Li Yang Wang, Xu Gan Xin, Yan Long, Zhao Chang Yi.
Staff table.
Hello. Hello.
Director team.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Cho Jeon-min.
The clothing team.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Zhang Zefeng.
The prop team.
Props team.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
Gunman Sun Hai
The recording team.
The venue team.
Zhao Gongli.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Kang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong Xi.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li, Zhang Changchang.
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Chou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping
Cut.
LilStar.
Drama photo, Wu Xiaobo.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
One Zhu Jiaxin.
Jun Nan.
Chen Mingjun.
Xie Hong.
Xu Xiaojia.
A dubber.
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
The base of HongMong Red Film in Shandong. [The national 4A-class scenic area]
[Shandong Blumund Red Filming Base] [The national 4A-class scenic area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple Sheung-Mun's Government.
The Jade Association of Shanzhou District
[Sanmen Mingu Pu Theatre]
The Civilian Committee of Lingbao City
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Shanzhou District.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Tianan Lake, Zhishan Lake City Wetland Park.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
Sanmen City Swan Lake Wetland Park.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Lan Yi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
Sandao Watery Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Let's go! Let's go!