A great fire destroyed the Qin family.
But fortunately,
there was a hidden hut outside the courtyard.
It was filled with my father
and grandfather's years of autopsy and case
files and notes.
Under the moonlight,
I moved them all back to my pharmacy.
When I was twelve,
the landlord took back the deed.
Luckily, Chunyi took me in,
so I had a place to settle down again.
Since then,
I read all kinds of case files every day,
hoping to find the murderer who killed my family one day.
You are actually still alive.
Why didn't you come to me?
I am sorry,
Uncle Su.
Because on that day,
a silenced murderer
said to another person next to him,
"Your Honor."
I knew then
that a high-ranking court official wiped out my family.
His minions and spies
must be all around.
Knowing the person but not their deeds,
their identities are hard to guess.
Even though we have met now,
I didn't dare to acknowledge you.
But fortunately,
since the truth of Su Xiang's case was revealed,
I am certain
that your friendship with my father is deep.
Didn't you also say
that my eyes and brows look a bit like his?
Great.
So Constable Qin has descendants.
The Qin family still has descendants.
But for this case,
I must get to the bottom of it
and bring the murderer to justice.
Only then can I console all those in my Qin family who died unjustly.
But now you are in prison,
how will you investigate?
I went to prison on purpose.
You actually could have proven your innocence.
But you realized you were being watched,
so you thought the prison was the safest place.
Exactly.
The wound on the victim's chest was about 1.3 inches deep.
Normally, the blood would have sprayed out.
But strangely,
the front of my clothes was completely clean,
without a single drop of blood.
Instead, my back was covered in mottled bloodstains.
This shows that at the time of the crime,
after the real killer ambushed and knocked me down,
when he pulled the knife from the victim's chest,
the gushing blood
splashed onto my back as I lay face down.
Then,
the real killer shoved the murder weapon into my hand.
But the flaws in the distribution of bloodstains on the clothes
are exactly the key to breaking the conspiracy.
If the death of Constable Qin
is because he found out the truth of the colored glaze pearl case,
then the mastermind behind the scenes
must be the Minister of Works, Yuan Feng.
If you want to know the inside story,
you can ask Lu Yunxian who was just released.
Although Lu Yunxian has been released,
he is actually less safe now than he was in prison.
If we want to investigate the case,
I'm afraid we don't have much time.
Vice Governor Li.
You are the only one who can help me now.
Just pretend I'm not here.
Father, I understand.
I'll go with you.
Jueming will face many dangers on this trip.
I will go with him,
so I can keep him safe.
After finding out the truth,
I will come back.
I heard nothing.
Mr. Lu,
Squire Lu was murdered.
He broke out of prison.
A wet-behind-the-ears kid
dares to play tricks on me, huh?
Very well.
Then I'll play along with him.
Get up.
It was inconvenient to make a move while he was in prison.
Now that he's out,
it's not up to him anymore.
Yun'er.
I never thought you would
give your life to save me.
Minister Lu,
what is the hidden truth behind the collapse of the Anlan Dam?
Too many people lost their lives because of it.
Please tell me everything.
When the Anlan Dam collapsed,
the Emperor was furious.
Yuan Feng, the Minister of Works, pretended to conduct a thorough investigation.
In the end, he brought in two scapegoats.
He stated directly
that Cui Yide, the Water Conservancy Director of the Ministry of Works,
colluded with the Anlan Dam designer, Ye Hongru,
to alter the dam's dimensions and materials,
and embezzled the funds.
Finally,
dozens of people led by the two of them
were beheaded in public.
But Yuan Feng
and Cui Qing, who was the supervisor at the time, remained safe and sound.
Later,
Ye Hongru's wife paid a private visit.
She insisted that her husband would never be involved in corruption.
To prove her husband's innocence,
she drowned herself in the river a few days later.
That old thief, Yuan Feng,
he is the real instigator.
All the sketches and materials for the dam
had to be confirmed by him.
Ye Hongru and Cui Yide
were just his scapegoats.
How is Lord Cui's relationship with Yuan Feng?
Cui Qing
is Cui Yide's younger brother.
He has no blood relation to Yuan Feng.
Cui Qing likely holds crucial evidence.
That's why Yuan Feng won't touch him.
Mr. Lu.
The chicken soup is poisoned.
You poisoned it.
No, I didn't.
Let him go.
He is nothing but a pawn.
Where is Lord Cui now?
He lives in his old residence in Lantian County,
80 li southeast of Chang'an.
Depart immediately,
and you'll arrive by noon.
Minister Lu.
They will definitely go to Lu Yunxian first.
If Lu Yunxian is not dead,
he will definitely go to Lord Cui to find clues.
Although Minister Cui is a coward and wouldn't dare to speak out,
as things stand now...
No.
We can't let them meet.
We must ensure the secret
has no chance of leaking.
Then I will immediately inform the yamen,
say they broke out of prison,
and issue a wanted poster.
No, no, no, no, no.
That is the Supreme Court's job.
What does it have to do with me, the Minister of Works?
But Minister Cui is different.
If he meets the fugitives, he will fight them.
They will mutually destroy each other
and all die.
We can use this opportunity to catch them all,
leaving no survivors.
You've made progress.
I am tired.
Who are you?
We are old friends of Elder Cui.
We came all the way from Luoyang
to see him.
Elder Cui is seriously ill.
He sees no one without an invitation.
Please go back.
I wonder if the sword in my hand
can serve as an invitation.
How did I teach you?
You must focus when playing chess.
Lord Cui.
We are here for the matter of the Anlan Dam.
The theft of the Glazed Orb is full of suspicions.
His Majesty ordered Dali Temple to reinvestigate the case.
I don't understand what you are saying.
If you are not here to play chess,
please see the guests out.
Who exactly are you?
I am the daughter of Li Ze,
the Junior Governor of Henan, Li Jinglan.
They are... So it's the daughter of Junior Governor Li.
It's said some important criminals escaped from the Luoyang prison,
taking the Junior Governor as a hostage.
I wonder if Miss Li is a hostage
or an accomplice.
Cui Qing.
Now Lu Yun, Cao Shi, Ye Hongru,
and your own brother Cui Yide are all dead.
Moreover, Lu Yunxian was also brutally framed.
The Glazed Pearl has been recovered,
and the Emperor is thoroughly investigating the matter.
Do you think Yuanfeng will really leave you alive?
A few escaped convicts.
I told you to leave earlier, but you didn't.
Now it's too late to leave.
None of these people are pushovers.
It seems he won't talk.
Then we'll carve a bloody path,
and pry his mouth open with our swords.
Mother.
Madam.
Son.
Go.
Today,
none of you are leaving.
Son.
Madam.
Yuanfeng,
you untrustworthy man.
How could such a sinister person
keep his word to you?
I told you,
he won't leave anyone alive.
What Yuanfeng wants
is behind that plaque.
What is this?
Back then, Yuanfeng
ordered my older brother to secretly alter the dam's dimensions.
As the supervisor,
Then proceed with the modified construction.
Most of the embezzled money
was taken by Yuanfeng.
My brother and I secretly divided the rest.
After the collapse of the Anlan Dam,
Yuanfeng summoned us privately.
He reached an agreement with Cui Yide.
My older brother would take all the blame
to save my life.
Falsely claiming it was the designer Ye Hongru.
and tampered with the dam data.
To prevent Yuan Feng from cheating,
my older brother Cui Yide secretly kept a copy of the tampered original design draft.
It has Yuan Feng's handwriting on it.
Yuan Feng didn't know where this draft was,
so he didn't dare to touch me.
Poor Ye Hongru was loyal
and devoted himself to the construction of the dam,
but he ended up a wronged ghost.
They never knew where the draft was hidden.
They never expected
that it was actually behind the plaque in the main hall.
Minister Lu has always had doubts about the collapse of the dam,
so he secretly investigated the matter while transporting the disaster relief funds.
Yuan Feng was afraid he would be exposed sooner or later,
so he came to me.
He secretly told me the transportation route of the glazed orb.
That day, Ye Xiao ambushed on the route and robbed the orb,
creating the illusion that the disaster relief orb disappeared.
In this way,
Yuan Feng could impeach Lu Yunxian in the court,
saying he was incompetent
and stole what was entrusted to his care.
After Yexiao got the orb,
he went to Niutou Mountain to find Cao Shi, the Deputy Magistrate of Henan.
Cao Shi was someone I bribed.
He killed Yexiao to silence him.
A boy climbing the mountain accidentally saw this.
The boy ran all the way down the mountain,
but was abducted by human traffickers.
That saved me a lot of trouble.
But Cao Shi knew too much.
So Yuanfeng had me bribe his brother Cao Fang,
to take advantage of the coffin opening in the ancient tomb
to kill Cao Shi with venomous insects.
You gave the Gu worm
to Cao Fang.
Unexpectedly, Constable Qin, who was investigating,
refused to let the case go.
After he secretly met Madam Cao,
I kept following him in secret.
Qin Rui went to Niutou Mountain
and dug up Yexiao's body and the orb.
He discovered my secret.
He had to die.
You killed my father.
You killed my whole family.
Your family
was killed by Yuanfeng himself.
Jueming.
There's a secret passage behind that cabinet.
You need to leave now.
There's no time, Jueming.
No.
This must be the tunnel Cui Qing prepared for fleeing to Chang'an.
Hurry.
Su Lang.
Hurry up.
Go to Chang'an quickly.
Su Lang, what are you doing? Su Lang!
Protect Sister Jinglan.
If I stay, no one will be able to leave.
Go.
Su Lang, what are you doing? Su Lang!
Su Lang, open the door.
Su Lang, open the door!
Su Lang,
don't do this. Open the door!
Take the evidence to Chang'an.
Go!
Su Lang.
I'll wait for your return.
You must come back.
Come, let's pray together, okay?
Okay.
I'm back.
Son.
Ah.
Giddy-up.
Yuan Feng, the Minister of Works, took bribes and bent the law,
colluded with others using his position,
and disregarded human lives.
He is sentenced to beheading.
All his embezzled wealth shall be confiscated to the state treasury.
I heard you wanted to see me.
Who are you?
Why do you keep coming after me?
Who am I?
I am the one who will tear you to pieces,
personally throw you in jail,
and watch you die.
The tens of thousands of people from Dongshui Town who suffered from the dam collapse
all died because of you.
You killed my father, my mother,
as well as my sister and grandfather.
People like you deserve to die.
You are an orphan from Dongshui Town.
I will never forget the look in my mother's eyes when she died,
along with my sister and grandfather.
It was you
who destroyed my home.
who took everything from me.
I am the ant you spoke of.
Do you remember now?
Five people in total.
Two children and two adults, all accounted for.
Once this fire burns,
there will be no evidence left.
A bunch of ants
trying to shake an elephant.
How ridiculous.
How laughable.
My name is Qin Nian.
I am a descendant of the Qin family,
the son of Qin Rui.
Impossible.
Remember?
Look at you now.
You spent decades scheming,
only to become a prisoner.
People like you
will be cursed for generations.
You lied to me.
You lied to me. You lied to me!
I will watch you die.
Impossible.
Ants.
They are all ants.
I will watch you die.
Under the imperial edict, Buliangren Jue Ming,
in the investigation of the Glazed Pearl case,
has finally retrieved the national treasure.
With outstanding merits,
he is hereby appointed Minister of Dali Temple.
May he uphold justice
and enforce the law. Execute as ordered.
The Emperor ordered you to take office at Dali Temple immediately.
That is a high position many people dream of.
Why are you delaying your departure?
I still have one thing left unfinished.
What is it?
I only survived by using Jue Ming's identity.
But I still don't know
why his mother, Shen Zhiling, died.
I remember my grandfather saying
she was stabbed several times,
and every cut was fatal.
The crime scene was a pharmacy,
but there weren't many medicinal herbs in the house.
So my grandfather suspected she had another identity.
The only clue to this case
is the murder weapon.
That sword with the blue dragon and roaring tiger pattern.
For the name Jueming,
I will solve this case.
I'll go with you.