Liu Qing was originally named Xiang Qing.
Her father, Xiang Yue,
was once a timber business partner of Liu Jinzhao.
The two of them often went deep into the mountains to find timber.
Once, they found good wood in a catalpa forest.
However, they encountered a python on the way back.
Xiang Yue
unfortunately lost his life.
His daughter, Xiang Qing, was fostered in a temple.
After Liu Jinzhao logged and sold the catalpa forest,
he made a fortune.
The first thing he did after getting rich
was to go to the temple to bring Xiang Qing back
and adopt her as his daughter.
Fire!
Fire! Father, why are you in such a hurry?
What fire?
The courtyard where Jueming lives
caught fire.
Then let's go check it out. Go.
When I just arrived at the courtyard,
I found it was on fire.
Fortunately, the fire was not big.
The fire was put out, and the house was saved.
Only this desk was burned down.
Did you see clearly
who did it?
There are no other clues at present,
but I've arranged for others to investigate nearby.
Constable Su, the arson suspect has been found.
Where is he?
Found by Prefect Chen.
The person has been escorted to the government office,
waiting for the court session to be questioned.
Return to the government office.
Hold court!
Silence.
Who is kneeling before the court?
What crime have you committed?
Confess everything truthfully.
Your Honor,
my name is Guo Cheng.
I make a living transporting goods on the Cao River.
Business has been slow these past few days.
I saw an empty house nearby,
and I had evil thoughts.
When I tried to steal some valuables,
I accidentally knocked over a candlestick.
I was so terrified.
I didn't dare to stay,
and ran away.
I didn't manage to steal a thing.
According to Tang law,
attempted theft without obtaining property
is punished with 50 lashes.
You accidentally knocked over the candlestick,
started a fire,
and burned the table.
Although unintentional,
you must also bear the responsibility.
According to the laws of the Tang Dynasty,
if the damage caused by the fire is minimal,
the punishment is 40 days in prison.
Chen You.
Come, take the suspect Guo Cheng away.
First, give him 50 lashes,
then lock him up in the cell,
and keep him there for 40 days.
Court dismissed.
Silence.
I sent someone to investigate that Guo Cheng.
He is indeed a transport merchant on the Cao River.
Normally, government goods
are transported by him.
He definitely skims off a lot.
Someone of his status,
how could he possibly commit theft?
And I didn't light a candle when I left the house.
There's no need to light a candle to burgle my house during the day.
This Magistrate Chen, he must be hiding something.
I'll have my father investigate Chen You thoroughly.
We don't have enough evidence now.
Going there so rashly
will easily alert the enemy.
Su Lang,
do you have any other clues?
I also found out
that Father Liu did leave a will.
According to custom,
he invited relatives and prominent people
in the neighborhood to be witnesses,
and also a minor official from the government.
Father Liu only has
Liu Shiqin and Liu Qing.
They split the inheritance 70/30.
Liu Shiqin gets 70%,
and Liu Qing gets 30%.
Could it be
that Liu Qing was dissatisfied with the inheritance distribution,
and colluded with Chen You
to kill Liu Shiqin while she was severely injured?
These are all speculations.
We still have no way to find out
the relationship between Sun Wenhuai and Liu Shiqin.
If the table hadn't been burned,
there might still be some hope.
Back then,
when we caught Sun Wenhuai and put him in prison,
he once faked a stomachache and escaped.
He really did run away.
When we caught him again,
Get in.
I never intended to escape.
You caught me on my way back.
Do you think I'd believe you?
Still trying to make excuses.
I've written down exactly what happened.
Once he sees it,
he will definitely figure something out for me.
I didn't understand what he meant back then.
But thinking back on it now,
his prison break that time
was just to deliver the suicide note to you.
The antique shop where you sold the desk,
what was its name?
Ruixiang Antique Shop
is still open today.
He did come here back then.
It was probably early afternoon.
He ran over wearing a prison uniform.
So I remember it very well.
Shopkeeper! Shopkeeper!
A few days ago,
did a boy surnamed Sun
sell all his furniture here?
Was there a brown desk?
Where is it now?
Every now and then,
he would repeatedly open the secret compartment to check.
After a long while,
his eyes were filled with disappointment.
He still asked me,
saying if any new letters appeared in the secret compartment,
I should give them to his younger brother.
How could new letters possibly appear in this secret compartment?
He might have been
provoked by something at the time,
and wasn't in his right mind.
Is it possible that
Sun Wenhuai put the blood letter in the secret compartment,
so it appeared in your desk?
But Chen You burned the desk,
so the blood letter was gone.
If so,
is the suicide note Sun Wenhuai put in the secret compartment back then still there?
Yes.
I took it out after he left.
I thought he would come back.
What are you looking at?
Can you read it?
Is this your brother's handwriting?
Yes.
It's my brother's handwriting.
I first met Liu Shiqin at the Lotus Pond Poetry Gathering.
She has exceptional zither skills
and a sweet smile.
That day, everyone drew the first line of a couplet.
Snow covers the green mountains,
cold shadows and lonely peaks are hard to paint.
The green water ripples.
Fine ripples and shallow waves easily form a poem.
The first line of the couplet I drew
happens to be by Liu Shiqin.
I thought hard to come up with the second line,
but felt it wasn't profound enough,
so I put the couplet in the drawer.
I wanted to use the couplet to ask Liu Shiqin for advice,
but I didn't know how to bring it up.
She misunderstood me,
and called a constable to scold me.
I expressed my affection for Liu Shiqin,
but was insulted by the officer.
I wanted to clear up the misunderstanding,
so I went to find Liu Shiqin again.
I saw her arguing with the owner at the eatery.
I wanted to step forward and reason for her.
But Liu Shiqin turned and ran when she saw me.
I hurriedly chased after her.
The eatery has two floors.
She accidentally fell down while going down the stairs.
I did not touch Liu Shiqin at all.
Constable Su Yu'an recklessly concluded
that I pushed her downstairs, causing her injuries.
Su Yu'an made this false conclusion,
determining that I am directly responsible for Liu Shiqin's injuries.
According to Tang law, the case entered the recovery period.
Unexpectedly, during the recovery period,
Liu Shiqin unfortunately died.
I was then considered a murderer.
I am completely innocent.
Su Yu'an is the chief culprit who framed me.
I implore the court to see the truth.
Liu Shiqin and I
have known each other since childhood.
You could say
I watched her grow up.
When I learned
that Liu Shiqin was injured,
I concluded that
Sun Wenhuai approached her just to bully her
and did it.
Back then,
I was young and hot-blooded,
so I insisted that
Sun Wenhuai pushed Liu Shiqin down the stairs.
I originally just wanted to punish Sun Wenhuai a little
so he wouldn't harass Liu Shiqin anymore.
But I never expected
that Liu Shiqin
would pass away within
the period of liability.
What's done is done.
Blaming yourself is useless now.
If the truth can be revealed,
it will surely comfort Sun Wenhuai's soul in heaven.
The letter mentioned that
when Sun Wenhuai found Liu Shiqin,
he saw her arguing with the shopkeeper.
Mr. Su.
We need to understand
why they were arguing.
This shop
is still there today.
Let's go take a look.
Come on, boss.
Tell us what happened that day.
She actually
argued with me that day.
Then she fell down the stairs.
I was actually gloating a bit at the time.
I didn't expect her to die from the fall.
Why did you argue with her?
Our shop has always delivered food to her family.
That day, she suddenly came to confront me.
Boss, why was my father's food changed?
What food?
Look here.
Your ledger clearly states
that my father's food was changed to white rice and white flour.
He can't eat that.
He can only eat coarse grains.
Look,
you guys must have notified us to change it.
When did I notify you?
No, you...
We wouldn't change it without your notification.
I have things to do. I'll go first.
I remembered it wrong at the time.
I said she was the one who changed it.
Then we started arguing.
Who wanted to change it?
It was her sister, Liu Qing.
Liu Qing... She is indeed a suspect.
Mr. Su,
where is the master's grave?
I'll take you to find it.
Let's go.
Slow down.
Master Wang,
it is truly fate that we met.
I am here now to find out the truth of your death.
So I have to bring you out now.
Please don't blame me.
But don't worry.
When everything is cleared up,
I will put you back.
I have my reasons.
Please don't blame me. Dad, go take a look.
You scared me to death.
I thought Master Wang was here.
Why are you so timid?
What do you mean?
Are you trying to invite Master Wang out
and put your dad in?
How could I bear to do that?
Let's go.
The bones are still intact.
Nothing inside has been touched, right?
Okay, let's ask Miss Li to take another look.
Miss Li.
Coroner Li.
It's your turn.
Go ahead.
We don't understand it anyway.
Is there something wrong with this corpse?
For those who die of a stroke,
the cause of death is usually cerebral congestion or phlegm blocking the collaterals.
Their bones wouldn't have such black discoloration.
For those who are poisoned,
once the poison enters the body,
it circulates
along with Qi and blood.
The throat is a vital passage for eating and breathing.
Poison easily accumulates there,
causing the bones to show abnormal colors.
Therefore, we can infer
that the advisor didn't die of the rumored illness,
but was poisoned.
Poisoned?
Yeah.
I knew there was something wrong with this advisor.
Died of poisoning.
That explains everything.
Back then, they used Sun Wenhuai as a scapegoat
and then silenced the advisor.
Now, Guo Cheng in prison should be the new scapegoat.
Chen You is very likely to target him.
The young lady is embroidering a sachet in her room.
Time to eat.
Oh, time to eat.
I'm starving to death.
There are chicken legs.
Let me go.
You are not fated to die.
Thank God.
Madam, they are looking for you.
You may leave.
Liu Qing.
Liu Jinzhao suffered from diabetes.
Did you know that?
I did.
Dr. Wang from Baicao Clinic said
that in the late stages of Liu Jinzhao's illness,
he was completely blind and had lost his sense of taste.
He couldn't even tell the sugar content of his daily food.
The food shop owner said
that you took the coarse grains Liu Shiqin had been ordering.
Replaced with fine, sweetened white rice and flour.
For a patient with diabetes, eating this would rapidly worsen their condition.
Did you know that?
I didn't.
I imagine back then,
you probably said the same thing.
We've both heard the doctor's orders.
For a patient with diabetes,
eating sweetened white rice and flour
will rapidly worsen their condition.
There is no way you didn't know this.
And you were specifically in charge of father's diet.
Only you could have tampered with it.
Father made a will.
You got a small share,
so you treated him like this.
Since you know everything,
if you die,
wouldn't I get an even bigger share?
Don't mention your father to me.
He is the enemy of our Xiang family.
Since you found out,
you can't live either.
What are you waiting for?
If she doesn't die, we'll be in trouble.
Hold her down.
Quick, grab her wound.
What's that sound?
Yes. It was a mouse.
Where is Shiqin?
She's already asleep.
Buy some rat poison.
Don't let the mice
keep us awake all day long.
As long as the mice are gone,
everything will be fine.
You and Chen You killed Liu Shiqin,
colluded with the advisor,
and tampered with Liu Shiqin's autopsy report written by Qin Boyan.
To eliminate future trouble,
you poisoned the advisor.
I opened the coffin and examined his body.
There are indeed signs of poisoning.
It is not hard to figure out
if the advisor shared a meal with you before he died.
What else do you have to say?
My father, Xiang Yue,
went to the deep mountains with Liu Jinzhao to find timber.
On the way back, they encountered a python,
and my father unfortunately died.
After Liu Jinzhao adopted me,
one night when I woke up,
I heard him talking in his sleep.
Brother Xiang,
I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
Don't blame me.
I didn't mean to push you into the snake pit.
I was too scared.
Please don't blame me.
The wealth earned by the Liu family
should have belonged to my Xiang family.
It should have
belonged to my father.
Why do they get to live so well?
Why?
Get in.
What are you doing?
Lord Chen, you have quite a lot of nice things.
Come, tell him
why we came to find Lord Chen today.
It was the magistrate who ordered me to strangle Guo Cheng
and fake his suicide to escape punishment.
Chen You,
you liar!
You told me that
if I confessed, I'd get all government transport contracts for the next three years,
but now you want to silence me by killing me!
You are making false accusations!
What proof do you two have?
Come! Take them all away!
Where is everyone? Guards!
Lord Li.
Lord Li, listen to my explanation.
There is a misunderstanding here.
Liu Qing,
bring him in.
Chen You.
Magistrate Chen.
What else do you have to say now?
Guards,
take them all away.
Move.
Congratulations, Mr. Li,
on solving another major case.
It's all thanks to you.
To think of using a desk
to communicate from beyond the grave,
only you could do that.
Elder Su.
What do you mean?
Do you really think I'd believe
that the dead Sun Wenhuai was writing to me?
How did you know it was me?