Daughter,
Heaven is sending you home.
sending you home.
Daughter.
Dad is sending you home.
Master Lu,
where are you going?
Our master has ordered
that you can't go anywhere.
Here.
Daughter,
Dad is sending you home.
Daughter.
Master Lu,
where are you heading?
My beloved daughter passed away from illness.
My younger sister is still missing.
I need to take her back to our hometown before the seventh day of her passing
so she can rest in peace.
Lord Guan has ordered.
The Lu family is suspected of being involved in the disappearance of the Guan family's daughter.
Anyone entering or leaving the Lu residence must be inspected.
Please open the coffin,
so we can inspect it.
This...
How dare you!
The officers are here.
Is it your place to inspect?
The magistrate's office has been investigating this case.
Initial findings suggest
that my younger sister
has been murdered.
But we are still tracking down the suspect.
So we came to inform you.
Thank you, thank you.
Please find the real culprit quickly
to bring justice to the dead.
Since the Guan family cannot do it,
please inspect it, officers.
No problem.
It is our duty to serve the people.
Then,
Jueming, go take a look.
Excuse me, coming through.
Troupe Leader Lu.
Coming.
Coming, coming.
Butler. Troupe Leader Lu.
What can I do for you?
Troupe Leader Lu,
there is good news.
What good news?
The little girl you took in is the granddaughter of the Guan family.
Master Guan specially sent me to take her home.
For this, we're giving you a cart of jewels
to thank you for raising her all these years.
From now on, you won't have to sleep in the open
and perform everywhere.
No, Butler, it's like this.
This money is enough to last you a lifetime.
We can't accept this.
Master.
From now on, this is your home.
After all, she is just a woman.
If it weren't for the death of my little grandson
and the family's decline,
I wouldn't have sought out outsiders.
Master.
She was abandoned because the birthmark on her face
would affect the Guan family's fortune.
Should we find a master to resolve it for her now?
Of course.
Go do it now.
Also,
arrange blind dates
to find someone to marry into the Guan family as soon as possible.
They need to have a chubby boy
to carry on the family line.
Yes.
Little sister, the Guan family sent someone to pick you up again.
They are right at the door.
I won't go.
Didn't you say at the time
that when you found me, you asked around and no one said they lost a child?
Master Guan seems to love me,
but he actually locks me in a cage like a bird,
makes me learn this and that,
won't let me see my brother and sister,
and won't let me do magic tricks.
Yes.
Oh, blame me for being slow-witted.
When they asked about your background,
I sensed something.
It seems the Guan family won't let this go easily.
When we found our little sister,
she was just a baby,
placed neatly in a corner.
With the Guan family's power in Luoyang,
finding a lost child shouldn't be hard.
Is it hard?
Exactly, they are definitely up to no good.
Father,
just say
that my little sister wants to stay with me because I'm seriously ill.
And she will return in a few days.
We really can't bear to let our little sister return to the Guan family.
So we will stall the Guan family first,
pack our bags,
and prepare to go far away.
Here you are.
Shh.
There are people outside.
We can't leave.
Then what should we do?
What should we do?
We can't really send Xiaomei back, can we?
No. Let's rush out.
No. The courtyard is full of the Guans.
I have an idea.
After I die,
cut off my limbs to make a decoy.
During the performance,
Xiaomei will enter the wooden box,
and quickly replace it with the severed limbs,
letting all the audience witness this accident,
so they believe Xiaomei was kidnapped by robbers,
and Xiaomei can escape in the chaos.
Your plan will absolutely not work.
How can I let you die without an intact body?
I'm not leaving either.
Xiaomei, be a good girl.
Leave here with Father and Brother.
No.
I want you to live.
I want you to be with me.
You are lying.
You lied to me.
You didn't keep your word.
Didn't we agree to go to Chang'an together?
Pray at the temple together,
then get married together,
and have children together?
We still have so many things to do. You lied to me.
Xiaomei.
Because of this,
you have to live a better life.
Get married for me.
Have children for me.
Perform on stage for me.
Xiaomei.
Promise me.
Experience the world for me,
okay? - No.
We are going together.
We promised each other.
According to the plan,
cut off my limbs
to make a decoy
and leave the Guan Manor.
No.
Xiaomei,
listen to me.
When the Guan family finds out you have no limbs,
Master Guan will definitely not pursue you anymore,
and he won't care about the troupe anymore.
Xiaomei.
You are naturally naughty
and like freedom.
How can you stand a cage like the Guan Manor?
Not just for me,
but also for yourself.
I can't promise you this.
We must be together. - I don't have much time left.
Promise me this request,
okay?
Live well, okay?
Okay, I promise you, alright?
I promise you.
Don't cry.
Don't leave me.
It has been confirmed
that they are Lu Yue's remains.
Daughter!
My poor daughter!
Master Lu.
My condolences.
Master Lu,
if the young lady's remains are found,
and the Guan family refuses to take them,
and you have not returned,
where should she be buried?
Under a pine tree at the foot of Dongpo Mountain.
Find a small plot to bury her.
In front of the grave,
just place a plum blossom branch.
Your previous deduction was indeed correct.
When we found the last riddle
and you told me
the severed limbs were taken from the victims,
my earlier speculation was confirmed.
What does that last riddle mean?
Formless and shadowless, wandering everywhere,
it sways willow branches in a gentle dance.
It ripples the lake with a thousand waves,
and wafts the scent of flowers over the small pavilion.
The answer is the wind.
The wind is free.
How could it bear to be restrained?
Little sister, look! The stars.
Making a wish upon the stars is the most effective.
I hope before I leave,
I can watch you perform one more time.
Do you still remember our promise?
We said we'd never part,
and always stay with the Lu Troupe.
I remember.
I said back then,
'Silly girl,
in one year we'll have our coming-of-age ceremony.
In the future,
you'll get married
and have children.
How can you follow behind us for the rest of your life?'
And I said,
'I want to have my coming-of-age ceremony with you, Sister,
get married together,
and have children together.
Then I can always follow behind you.'
You are such a sweet talker.
Do you remember where you said you wanted to go back then?
I remember.
I said
I wanted to see the snow mountains of the Mohe tribe.
I heard it's shrouded in snow and mist,
with hanging ice waterfalls,
and snow all year round.
They say there's a silver crater lake at the top.
I also wanted to go beyond the Great Wall,
to experience the flying sand and endless rolling dunes.
Or go to the picturesque
Jiangnan water towns with their misty willows and painted bridges.
In short,
for me,
what I long for
is the vast world, the mountains, rivers, lakes, and seas.
This smoke is too heavy,
it stings my eyes.
We made a pinky promise.
Do you remember?
You said we'd always be together,
and you'd take me wherever you went.
But little sister,
I might not be able to go.
You will go.
You must promise me
to live well,
and visit those places for me.
You can go.
We'll go together.
I hope
that in the future, you can be like the wind,
blooming freely
anywhere
in the world.
Sister, I will learn the magic tricks you taught me well.
We'll perform together,
see the world together,
and bloom freely like the wind together,
okay?
Please don't leave me, okay?
Little sister.
You must remember me.
But please don't cry anymore.
Whenever you think of me from now on,
you must smile.
Sister.
In front of the plum blossoms at the foot of Dongpo Mountain.
This should be the place.
Let's go.
It seems Yueyue can finally rest in peace this time.
So we rushed over just to let Boss Lu out of the city.
But what about us?
How are we going to report back?
And what about your father?
What should I tell him?
The Guan family has too much power in Luoyang.
We can't let them know.
So,
This secret stays between the three of us.
You can't tell anyone else.
As for my father,
I'll figure something out.
I won't put you in a difficult position.
Our Coroner Li is now both kind and smart.
And the ability to solve cases has also improved.
Sometimes,
not all cases must be solved.
The three of us came to Yanzhi Alley in the North Market
and found this last poetry riddle.
After saying goodbye to Troupe Leader Lu,
we followed the clues
all the way to the outskirts.
At this moment,
the thief was riding away on a horse.
We then drew our swords and left.
How many thieves were there in total?
Thir... thirty people.
Thirty people.
Thirty people?
Of course, thirty people.
The Guan family is such a big prize,
they were targeted by the thieves long ago.
So,
we tracked these thieves to the cliff.
Mainly Su Lang.
Su Lang
took the frontline
and fought ten at once.
Swish, swish, swish, swish!
He kicked them off the cliff one by one.
Where is the body?
There is a lake at the bottom of the cliff.
It sank to the bottom.
I mean our sister's remains.
Our sister...
She has already
been chopped into many pieces.
There is basically nothing left.
I was thinking
they probably dug a hole in the graveyard
and buried her.
That would be safe.
Yes, yes.
Brother Guan.
Look, even though the suspect has been caught,
the little granddaughter's remains haven't been fully found.
Look at this.
It's just one side of the story.
There is no factual evidence at all.
How can you expect me to believe it?
You three,
take some men to the graveyard immediately.
Even if you have to dig three feet deep,
you must find my little sister's remains for me.
Yes, yes.
Thank you for upholding justice for me, Deputy Governor.
Brother Guan.
Please don't thank me.
It is my duty
to protect the peace of this region
and restore justice to the people.
I will take my leave now.
Take care, Brother Guan.
Commissioner Li, where are you going?
No need to ask.
Send someone to search at once.
Hurry up.
What should we do?
Take people to find her immediately.
Where should we look?
Let's go.
Then I don't need to go, right?
Searching like this won't yield any results.
Have you thought about how to wrap this up?
This graveyard is so big.
Maybe she was eaten by wild beasts.
Just say that when you get back.
I think,
you should just say
that Xiaomei fell into the lake with the bandit's bones.
Wouldn't that be great?
What if he asks you to fish them out?
You'd be standing at the bow in the cold wind,
directing everyone.
In that case, the graveyard is better.
But my father said,
that there are many wronged souls buried in the eastern suburbs' woods.
It's often haunted.
When the Anlan Embankment collapsed back then,
it caused a flood and drowned many people.
Many of the deceased
were residents of Luoyang City.
In order to return to their roots,
they brought the bones back to Luoyang.
I heard that at night,
you can hear people crying.
Stop talking.
He's scared.
Then let's go back.
Go back?
Look around.
With so many constables,
do you think they're here to search the mountain?
That's just an act.
They're all here to keep an eye on me.
Believe it or not,
my father will interrogate them one by one tomorrow morning.
If you're so afraid of your father,
why are you a coroner?
Being a coroner is my freedom.
Do I look afraid of him?
Are you okay?
Did you get hurt anywhere?
Get up.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Really?
That's good.
What could happen to me?
Who is so inconsiderate
as to leave a hoe here?
Why is there a compass here?
Constable Su, there are traces of grave robbers here.
Constable Su, this side has also been dug up.
And there's one over there.
The soil is bright in color.
It probably hasn't been exposed to the wind, sun, and rain for long.
This group must have just left.
Look, in this tomb,
they dug up all the burial objects.
And those untouched tombs
show that
they didn't have enough time to rob them.
In my opinion,
they will come back.
Then let's lay an ambush right here
and wait.
We've been waiting for so long. Why is there no result?
Why don't we go back?
I think I know a place.
The Ghost Market.
Let's go ask.
Maybe we'll get something.
Follow me closely.
Don't get lost.
The Ghost Market is a mixed bag,
gathering all sorts of street folks.
It operates day and night,
doing business as usual.
New items.
If you want to ask about anyone,
or find lost items on the market,
you can try here.
Look here.
This treasure gourd placed upside down
means the shop has good stuff for sale.
If it's placed upright,
it means there's nothing good in the shop.
Or the situation is relatively critical,
and not suitable for trading.
That's amazing.
Let's go.
No one's here.
Do you want to find some items,
or buy some treasures?
Jueming,
why are you here?
Let me show you something.
What is it?
Take a good look at this for me.
Whose is this?
I don't know about this.
This has nothing to do with me.
No, stop messing around. Look closely.
Take a good look.
I am a constable of the yamen,
handling a case on orders.
How dare you conceal what you know?
Looking at your clothes,
I knew you were an officer.
But here,
it's the ghost market.
The ghost market has its own rules.
Don't talk about things you shouldn't.
Here,
you can't arrest me.
If I speak,
tomorrow,
I'll be thrown into the river.
- Then I'll take you back to the yamen and see if you confess.
- No, no, no, no.
Su Lang.
Indeed,
we must follow the rules of the ghost market.
- Right?
- Right, right, right, right.
If you don't want to speak,
you don't have to.
I definitely won't force you.
If you want to speak,
It definitely has its benefits.
This is really a good thing,
but I'm still in a bit of a dilemma.
How about now? Still in a dilemma?
Not at all, not at all.
I remember now.
I remember everything.
People who come here
never reveal their names.
All I know
is that these two are grave robbers.
One is a man,
not very tall,
around his thirties,
and he brought a thirteen or fourteen-year-old child.
This child looks a bit foolish.
His mind
is quite unusual.
It's you.
What good stuff did you find this time?
Got any more goodies?
This time is different.
I almost died in there trying to get this bead.
Xiaobao,
check if it's still alive.
It's still alive.
Then it's safe.
Get ready to go down.
To the honorable tomb owner,
I am but a humble commoner.
I have no other choice today,
so I ask to borrow some of your treasures.
If fate permits in the future,
I will definitely return them in full.
Xiaobao, tug the rope once you find the treasure.
Okay.
Take it easy.
Step firmly.
Keep going down.
You'll be fine.
Where is the southeast corner?
I don't know.
Then I'll just put one in all four corners.
I'm so smart.
It's empty.
There's a bead.
Master said
that beads are definitely valuable.
This bead
is worthless.
The tomb you raided is empty.
This means
someone has definitely been there.
How could they leave a precious bead for you?
This is called a scent bead.
It's carried around for its fragrance.
It was most likely
dropped by your fellow raiders.
We've known each other for so long.
You're not lying to me, are you?
How could I lie to you?
Look at what I do.
Are there any other big tombs nearby?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
It's yours.
This thing is completely worthless.
The bead is gone. Can we still eat meat?
I'm hungry.
Xiaobao, Master will take you to get some meat.
Let's go. Okay.
Fool.
It's this bead.
This is called Hexiang bead.
It's worthless.
It's used to enhance the fragrance.
These two men,
just fled here.
If you want to catch them,
they are short of money,
so they will definitely strike again.
Yesterday, this grave robber...
Thank you. Here.
Oh, you still have the nerve to eat and drink.
I heard the dismemberment case of the Sun family's daughter
hasn't been solved yet.
Without me here,
can't you solve a case?
If I, Su Yu'an, were here,
within two hours,
I would definitely solve this case.
I used to think
we could analyze the case together.
Everyone pitch in your ideas, okay? Thanks.
We can still solve this case.
But now I realize. Eat this, this.
I'm the absolute core here.
If I weren't here, you guys couldn't solve the case at all. Eat this.
How about this? You guys brief me on the case,
and I'll sort it out for you.
What's going on with this case anyway?
What exactly is happening with this case?
Why so fierce?
I'm just a lowly coroner.
Let Constable Su explain it.
Your dad is asking you. Jueming, you speak.
You speak.
I'll say it then.
We were indeed investigating the Guan family's case,
but that clue
led us to the graveyard in the eastern suburbs.
As soon as we went to check,
wow, we found traces of tomb raiders.
We staked out there all night,
but found nothing.
We plan to go back and stake out again after dinner.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Did you go down into the tomb?
Yeah, yeah.
Come here. What is it?
What is this?
This piece of jade
is natural.
There are no carvings on it,
so, playing on the homophone, it's called a 'Peace Pendant'.
Wear it, and you'll be safe when going down to the tombs.
It looks nice.
Right?
The pendant looks alright,
but it doesn't seem to be worth much.
Why are you so tactless?
It doesn't even look as valuable as the treasure we found that day.
Look how beautiful this bead is.
Wait a minute.
This bead
must be the one given to me by Mrs. Qin.
Which Mrs. Qin?
Constable Qin's wife.
Su Yuerong gave it to me.
Su Yuerong?
Then why would this bead be in the tomb?
Right.
How could it be? Back then,
we had to enter a tomb to solve a case.
So Constable Qin gave me this plain tablet,
and Mrs. Qin gave me this incense bead.
Enter a tomb?
What case was he solving?
The case of Junior Governor Cao's death.