These three bodies,
judging from the lividity and degree of decomposition,
have been buried for less than two weeks.
These bodies
were dug up in the back mountain by Constable Su and me.
Behind them hides an unknown secret.
Because of this,
four murders were triggered in one day.
I think it is very necessary for me to tell you
the real reason behind these murders.
Sixteen years ago,
Deputy Governor Cao was killed by his younger brother Cao Fang.
The newlywed Mrs. Cao gave birth to a son the following year,
named Cao Wen.
Mrs. Cao used all the property she received
to buy this house
and pinned all her hopes on her young son,
hoping that at sixteen he could emulate the talent of Cao Zijian,
composing a poem within seven steps,
becoming famous far and wide,
or have the intelligence of Cao Chong.
Weighing an elephant in childhood,
he showed his brilliance,
and became famous overnight.
He was expected to restore the family's honor
and live up to expectations.
Under such pressure,
Cao Wen did not write a good article.
But Lady Cao had already announced
that her son had written an essay
and it would be published soon.
So Lady Cao ordered her steward...
Recruited four poor scholars.
But these scholars from humble backgrounds left their hometowns
and came here
just to advance their studies
and earn some money to support their families.
The steward used the promise of high pay
to trick these scholars into ghostwriting for Cao Wen.
Scholars are honest by nature.
They never expected that coming here
would leave them with no way out.
Their way home was cut off.
One of the scholars wanted to go home.
The steward found out, killed him, and buried him in the back mountain.
Another scholar happened to see this,
so he wrote this book, 'The Scheme of the False Pregnancy'.
The manuscript was later handed over to Master Yuan.
To avoid further trouble,
at Master Yuan's suggestion,
Madam Cao killed all the scholars.
Writing a book is like a pregnant woman giving birth.
I said long ago
that he couldn't write such an article.
To complete a book,
they didn't hesitate to murder others
and steal their benefits.
Absolutely shameless.
Scholar Jiang, who is close to Madam Cao,
and Compiler Dong, who is in charge of revising this book.
Do you know about the bloody case behind this?
Actually,
I didn't have much interaction with Madam Cao.
She asked me to put in a good word for Cao Wen's work.
But as for other things,
I know absolutely nothing about them.
What about you?
I... I'm just a compiler.
The texts Madam Cao handed over
were all discussed and copied by Workshop Master Yuan.
I was only responsible for having the workers bind them.
As for what's behind this,
how would I know?
Such evil deeds
are truly intolerable by heaven.
Envoy Jueming,
since things have come to this,
I just want to know the outcome.
Cao Wen,
answer me honestly now.
How many scholars did you hire to write your books
in your residence?
Four.
But there are only three bodies here.
I believe there is another body
which the suspect has dug up.
Just like what is written in this book.
The murderer in the book takes Consort Zhao's child away.
I believe the real suspect
will also dig up his closest relative's bones.
Don't move!
Behave yourself!
Let me go!
I will tell you the truth.
Fine.
Killing them
and leaving you as a puppet
to let the world see
the hypocritical and vicious true face of the Cao family
is just as satisfying.
Are you confessing?
I didn't plan to live.
These beasts
deserve to die.
Who... who on earth are you?
I am Zhang Chiwen's biological brother.
My real name
is Zhang Renjiu.
Before my brother left,
he said he would concentrate on writing here.
Unexpectedly, once he entered this villa,
there was no news from him at all.
I was heartbroken at home.
After inquiring around,
I found out that
the other scholars who came to the villa with my brother,
their families had also come to this villa looking for them.
But this villa's manager
was very unreasonable.
He forcibly drove them away
and kept insisting that
these scholars had never been here.
At that time,
I learned that
Cao Wen published a new book,
'The Fake Pregnancy Plot'.
I went to great lengths
to finally purchase this book.
When I read it carefully,
I felt the writing style
was very similar to my brother's.
I couldn't help but wonder
if this book was written by him.
To find out the truth,
I sneaked into the villa
and got a job as a servant.
After entering the villa,
I searched everywhere
and finally dug up several corpses in the back mountain.
You lied to me again.
Didn't you say
you'd be back soon?
Brother.
I was heartbroken
and quietly moved
my brother's remains into my room to hide them.
Then I thought carefully.
Many things are related to this 'Fake Pregnancy Scheme'.
Isn't what's written in that book
an allusion to this tragedy?
Consort Zhao, who miscarried in the book,
corresponds to Cao Wen.
The Consort's mother corresponds to Madam Cao.
And
Imperial Physician Sun, who informed the Emperor,
doesn't he correspond to Workshop Master Yuan, who pushed the book?
And Xiao Shunzi, who was busy running around,
doesn't he correspond to the villa's manager?
In that case,
I secretly forged a dagger exactly like the Six-Star one
to confuse the order of my killings.
How did you know about me and Madam?
The book says it all.
Imperial Physician Sun had an affair with Consort Xian's mother.
What do you mean?
Did you really see the killer?
Who is it?
It's me.
If things go smoothly this time,
after I kill the last person,
I will definitely reveal the truth to everyone.
Even if I fail,
I will make it known to everyone,
so the truth won't be buried underground forever.
In that case,
why did you kill Gu Yitong?
He is a distant relative of the Cao family.
Look at how he flatters them.
It doesn't hurt to kill one more.
I was also forced by my mother.
I can't write anything.
I can't write anything at all.
She insisted on making me the pride of the Cao family.
What could I do?
You say your brother is pitiful.
Am I not pitiful?
I am nothing but a walking corpse.
Since I was young,
no one has ever truly cared about me.
They only cared if I had fame,
and if I could bring glory to the Cao family.
No one ever considered my feelings.
But I know I am good for nothing.
She insisted on me having this fame.
At this point,
I can't pretend anymore.
Jueming.
The boat has reached the ferry.
Let's go.
Sit down. Have another drink with me.
Let's go. We're in a hurry.
This fine wine of Yayuanju is a rare treat.
If you don't drink it now,
you'll rarely get a chance again.
We can come again.
What?
Here.
This is really good.
Sister.
This was found in Liu Renjiu's room.
I believe that in this world,
no one wants to kill voluntarily
unless they have no other choice.
Just like me.
Aren't my hands
covered in blood now?
I believe he had no other choice either.
Just like last night,
I am willing to bear all this for him.
According to the order in the book,
the last person Liu Renjiu intended to kill was not Gu Yitong,
but Cao Wen.
He would kill Cao Wen using the same method,
and then place this fourth volume.
Su Lang.
You committed a copycat murder.
After disposing of the body, you came to us.
You didn't expect that we had already caught the suspect.
What reason would I have to kill someone?
It really wasn't me.
Jueming, Miss,
we found another body.
So you panicked.
Yes.
According to your plan,
you could frame Liu Renjiu for Gu Yitong's death
without any problems.
But where it went wrong is,
the timeline doesn't match.
He lives in the west wing,
and I live in the utility room.
Besides, how could I kill him in such a short time
and then return to the pond by the utility room to throw away the dagger?
If you hadn't finished dealing with it.
You should have a book
missing the fourth volume on you.
I wanted to take it with me when I left.
Why did you do this?
He is not human.
I remember you are here to search for the suspect's tools.
This has nothing to do with you, right?
Who drew this?
I drew it.
Why? Do you like it too?
I am Honglian's adoptive father.
Honglian is a child I took in.
I raised her all these years.
How could I let a poor constable like you have her so easily?
How much money do you want to let Honglian go?
Ten guan?
A hundred guan?
A thousand guan?
I will give her to anyone I need to curry favor with.
So you came to the villa this time
just to push Honglian to Cao Wen.
Exactly.
One night is all it takes.
I'll give you money.
I can marry Honglian.
Silly boy.
Who would sell the goose that lays golden eggs?
Honglian is my golden goose.
If you want to sleep with her, it's simple.
Just pay.
Since you all know,
why didn't you expose me last night?
This character 'xue' must be written straight and true.
There must be rules.
Come, take a look.
Look at what I wrote.
Do you see?
Wow, so beautiful.
Alright, let me see what you wrote.
Not bad.
This stroke, it can't stick out here.
Writing is like being a person.
You must be proper.
Be straight and true.
Be reasonable and organized.
My eldest son is back from the villa.
How was it?
Did you benefit a lot this time?
Wow.
You brought so much good food.
Freshly bought sesame cakes. Try them.
Pickles.
Sesame cakes with pickles.
It's my favorite.
All right,
put down your brushes, you two.
Let me see how you did.
Let's see yours.
You did quite well.
You followed my instructions. It's standard,
straight,
and aligned.
Not bad.
You can eat now.
Let's see yours.
It's a bit messy.
Not very standard.
Correct it next time.
Got it.
Let's eat first.
Here.
Why aren't Jueming and the eldest lady here?
There was a murder in the villa.
They went to the government office to deal with it.
Another murder?
Who died?
Madam Cao.
And
their butler.
And Master Yuan of the Moxiang Bookstore.
It's so hard for people to stay alive nowadays.
Why do they have to commit murder?
What's wrong?
Why aren't you eating?
I wrote several characters wrong today.
I want to punish myself.
In a person's life,
they always make some mistakes, big or small.
As long as you can correct them, it's fine.
Okay?
Come on.
Go and correct them.
Eat today.
No need to punish yourself.
Mm.
Chief Constable Su.
You'll be busy from now on.
Go buy some clothes for Mother.
I see her clothes are worn out.
And you too.
You always wear this one.
Alright.
We have food and clothes.
We don't need your money.
You need money now.
Keep it for yourself.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good.
There's still so much left.
Why did you stop eating?
I'll go to the government office.
Brat.
Since you all know,
why didn't you expose me last night?
We wanted to give you a chance.
I'll go surrender myself.
But I want to see my father one more time.
You can write more words when you're full, right?
Yes. Yeah.
I was wrong.
It's okay.
Wait for me.
I will figure something out.
Su Lang.
Just go.
We are over.
Your portrait has been seen by so many people,
and your father...
Do you despise me?
We can't go back.
Just leave.
You said you would protect me.
Was everything you said a lie?
Just treat it as a lie.
Go.
Leave!
Someone told me
that a person's palm prints represent their destiny.
Do you believe in fate then?
I'll believe it if my fate is perfect.
If it's bad,
why should I believe it?
But the family I was born into decided my fate.
Just like a shadow.
I can't shake it off.
Then I'll hide with you.
Hide from the sunlight,
and let's hide our shadows together.
I am a murderer now.
There's no going back.
Do you remember that day
we were on the swings together?
I said I would always protect you.
This time, I broke my promise.
Honglian,
I want to introduce you to my dad and my friends.
Tell them we are together.
Honglian.
I hope you can always be this happy.
I will always protect you too.
Maybe in the next life.
I will protect you in the next life.
As for my father,
my mother told me everything after I grew up.
She told me
that my father was killed by her own brother, Cao Fang.
After Cao Fang died,
the constable in charge of the case came to see her.
He really used a Gu insect.
That's right.
This is what we found in Cao Fang's room,
the vessel containing the dead Gu insect.
I married here from Yunnan.
This kind of Gu insect only grows in Yunnan,
and if it leaves its natural habitat,
it won't live for long.
But Cao Fang had never been to Nanzhao,
nor did he have any friends from Nanzhao.
So, Madam, you mean...
someone else was directing Cao Fang.
Madam,
did Vice Governor Cao go anywhere recently?
Did he make any friends?
One day, he went out on foot alone for a long time.
When he came back, his shoes were covered in mud.
When I asked, I found out he went mountain climbing.
I reckon
the only mountain nearby that can be a day trip
is Niutou Mountain.
When did this happen?
About three months ago.
He usually takes a sedan chair for long trips.
He wouldn't go alone,
so it made a deep impression on me.
I found it very strange,
but I didn't dare to ask.
Why would a person
go to Niutou Mountain alone?
My mother said.
After my father's funeral,
we moved out of Shaoyin Mansion.
Since then, that constable never came again.
Why are you asking me this all of a sudden?
The constable who questioned your mother has gone missing.
I want to know where he went.
Lord Li,
I truly have no way out.
That is why I boldly came to beg you for help.
I beg Your Excellency to save my son's life.
I have worked diligently for the Yamen for half my life,
never daring to slack off,
and solved countless cases.
But I never expected that today,
a case would fall upon me.
My son had a moment of folly
and was blinded,
committing the grave crime of murder.
But this child grew up by my side.
He only wanted to follow in my footsteps
and contribute to the Yamen and the court.
He is not bad by nature,
nor is he a heinous villain.
I beg Your Excellency to show mercy.
Mr. Su,
please get up.
Get up.
Mr. Su, take your time to speak.
Lord Li.
I am not an ignorant person.
I also know how strict the law is.
But I only hope you, Lord Li,
can spare Su Lang's life.
Just let him live.
This is the petition we wrote for Su Lang.
He has helped us solve many major cases.
The difficulty of those cases
is still vivid in our minds.
We only hope you can present this document
to the new magistrate,
so he may consider his past merits
and show leniency.
Mr. Su.
Su Lang has committed a felony of murder.
According to the laws of the Tang Dynasty,
this crime is punishable by death.
I also know you are extremely anxious right now.
As for whether his past contributions to the yamen
can lead to a reduced sentence,
this matter
depends on the new magistrate's consideration.
Although I am the Deputy Mayor of Henan
and in charge of local affairs,
if I rashly influence the direction of the case,
it would be inappropriate
and contrary to the law.
All right, I can only truthfully convey the facts of this case
and Su Lang's past merits
to Magistrate Zhao.
The subsequent ruling
will be entirely up to him to decide according to the law.
What the final result will be
is hard to predict.
You still need to mentally prepare yourself
and await the verdict.
Master, Lu Yun, Vice Director of the Ministry of Rites, asks to see you.
Vice Director Lu was also invited to the villa yesterday.
He is familiar with the details of the case.
Invite him in immediately.
Deputy Governor Li.
I am Lu Yun, Vice Director of the Ministry of Rites.
I take the liberty to come here today
to discuss an important matter.
Vice Director Lu, please have a seat.
Please.
Vice Director Lu, you've gone to such great lengths.
What is this about?
Yesterday, I gathered with you all at the villa,
and we experienced a murder case together.
Your crime-solving methods are truly amazing.
Now Su Lang has violated the law
and is imprisoned.
And you are looking for a way out.
I happen to have a cold case here
that remains unsolved.
If you can solve this case...
It can certainly win a sentence reduction for Su Lang.
I will truthfully report to the Ministry of Justice,
so they can reduce Su Lang's sentence at their discretion.
Or I can report to Dali Temple,
and wait for their fair and strict investigation.
What case are you referring to, Vice Director Lu?
You might as well speak plainly.
The national treasure,
the theft case of the Glazed Pearl.
Mr. Lu.
I'll send someone to get Jueming right away
to listen to your analysis of the case.
We'll take this case.