Come on, Dad.
Slow down.
This magic trick
was originally created by our family.
I also rigged
this floor.
After Xiaomei enters the wooden box and closes the door,
she can use the mechanism on the floor
to enter the secret passage under the platform.
Once she safely goes down into the passage,
she places the prepared cat on the floor
and closes the mechanism.
This way, a person can turn into any object.
When this wooden box
has made a full rotation,
Xiaomei
uses the same method to lift herself back up.
This way, the cat turns back into Xiaomei.
So, where does the other end
of this secret passage lead?
Behind the curtain.
After Xiaomei entered the secret passage,
she was ambushed by the suspect.
Because the audience around was too noisy,
we didn't hear Xiaomei's cries for help.
Xiaomei fainted from blood loss or shock.
The suspect then took Xiaomei onto a carriage and fled.
Based on the note next to the severed limb,
it's likely Xiaomei was kidnapped by bandits.
But why would the bandit cut off her arm on the spot?
She probably resisted.
And being pressed for time,
the person harmed her.
Such a villain,
I will definitely bring him to justice.
Troupe Leader Lu, everyone.
We have conducted some investigations.
We will certainly get to the bottom of this.
I beg you, officers.
Please, you must save my daughter.
Even if we have to spend all our savings,
we will save her.
I beg you.
Please get up.
But right now, the kidnappers
haven't left any valid clues for a trade.
We can only wait for now.
I beg you.
Troupe Leader Lu.
Where do you usually live?
Our acrobatics troupe
lives right here in this big courtyard.
If the kidnappers come now
and see all of us constables here,
they definitely won't dare to approach.
Have them all change into plain clothes later,
then stake out near the Lu family courtyard.
We will wait for them to come to us.
Okay, I'll arrange it right away.
Rise and shine. Who is it?
Jueming.
Here you are.
Here,
put it here.
These are dishes from Weimanju.
I specially had them delivered.
Try some.
This is too much. I can't finish it by myself.
How about we share some with Master Lu?
And for the brothers outside.
These are all prepared for them.
Please help take them over.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's nothing.
You haven't slept all night.
Skip the noodles.
Have a bowl of beef.
Hold out your hand.
Close your eyes.
Did you also learn magic tricks at the Lu Troupe?
Guess
what it is.
A family heirloom.
A bone.
I can't guess.
Isn't this what I saw yesterday?
I saw you liked it yesterday,
so I bought it.
Do you like it?
I like it.
It's very thoughtful of you.
I'm glad you like it.
This is
other than what my father gave me,
the best gift I've ever received.
Why?
Mr. Lu,
no matter how I persuade him, he won't eat.
Make some room for me.
You know, no matter how anxious he is,
he shouldn't skip meals entirely, right?
Why aren't you eating?
I'm watching you eat.
Looking at you makes me full.
Tell me,
the Lu Family Troupe is so popular,
and their performances have always gone smoothly.
They usually perform every few days.
Why did he suddenly announce the final show yesterday?
Then let me tell you.
Because besides Xiaomei, Troupe Leader Lu
also had an eldest daughter
named Lu Yue.
But she had a terminal illness.
To treat her illness, Troupe Leader Lu
spent all his savings.
But unfortunately,
Yueyue
still passed away.
Troupe Leader Lu was deeply devastated
and wanted to return to the countryside to recover.
But at this crucial moment,
something also happened to Xiaomei.
That's strange.
Kidnappers usually target children of wealthy merchants and high officials
to demand a high ransom.
But Master Lu doesn't look like a rich man at all.
Why would they kidnap Xiaomei?
If it's not for money,
it must be a personal grudge.
A grudge?
What kind of grudge?
How should I know?
Then go find out.
Right.
Go check. Go check.
Take this for them to eat. Go check.
What did you just say?
I said,
if they're not after money,
then they have other motives.
No, I mean,
you just
said this is the favorite gift you've ever received.
Why is that?
Because...
There's news.
I...
What are you two talking about?
Nothing.
What is it? What news?
We need to go to the Guan family immediately.
Which Guan family?
Guan Shan, the richest man in Luoyang.
His youngest grandson's funeral is today.
But his servants found in his coffin
that his young grandson was holding a left arm with both hands,
and there was a bamboo strip in his hand.
Inside the coffin is the body of an eight-year-old boy.
A woman's severed left arm was placed on his chest.
There were also bamboo slips with writings on them.
Okay.
Jueming.
Auspicious beasts of the ancient dynasty show their majesty.
Auspicious birds of this year dance in splendid colors.
Who was the first to find
the remains inside the coffin?
It was me.
These past few days,
I have been keeping vigil for the Eldest Young Master.
I was so tired last night
that I fell asleep without realizing it.
When I woke up this morning,
I didn't notice it at first.
I wanted to burn incense,
but I found the coffin lid was not closed properly.
I took a look inside
and saw this severed limb placed on his chest.
So you didn't notice
who moved the coffin
and put the severed limbs in.
Who?
Who moved my grandson's coffin?
Master Guan.
I didn't
see it.
You useless thing!
I'll kick you to death!
Stop hitting him!
Even if he is your servant,
you can't hit him.
Besides, he's not the one who moved your grandson's coffin.
Who are you?
She is Li...
Let me do it.
I am
the coroner of the magistrate's office.
I heard that in your grandson's coffin,
severed limbs were placed,
so I came with Constable Su to investigate.
How do you know he didn't do it?
Look at him.
This servant
has lifeless eyes,
is as timid as a mouse,
and weak.
If he tampered with the coffin
and put limbs in it,
he would have run away long ago.
Would he still be here waiting for you?
You are quite eloquent, Miss.
Then tell me, who did it?
A group of bandits.
Last night, they went to the Lu Troupe and kidnapped the youngest Lu sister.
A severed right arm was left at the scene,
along with a note.
I suspect it's the same group.
You are saying
that the youngest sister of the Lu Troupe was kidnapped?
Master Guan.
Master, are you alright?
Master.
No, why did mentioning my younger sister
make him like this?
Little sister
is the master's biological granddaughter.
Master.
Are you alright?
It seems the poem on this bamboo strip
has another meaning.
Think carefully.
Have you seen this handwriting before?
I haven't.
No.
You don't know this, but
although Master Guan is destined for wealth,
But there were many misfortunes in his family,
and his children passed away early one after another.
His little grandson was the apple of his eye,
but he suffered from a brain disease half a year ago
and has been bedridden all day.
That night, when I came back from getting medicine for the young master,
I saw the Lu Troupe performing on the way.
I happened to glance over
and saw the female illusionist on stage
had a birthmark on her face.
This was exactly the same as Master Guan's lost granddaughter.
I hurriedly asked for details.
Boss Lu told me
that he indeed found Xiaomei.
I asked,
and the time and place she was found
matched perfectly with the little granddaughter.
I then hurried back to tell Master Guan this news.
After several confirmations,
we finally made sure
that Xiaomei of the Lu family is my Master Guan's biological granddaughter.
Coincidentally, the young master passed away,
leaving the Guan family without an heir.
Master Guan just wanted to bring Xiaomei back home.
To repay the Lu Troupe for raising her,
Master Guan offered three chests of jewelry.
The exchange would happen after the young master's funeral.
Unexpectedly,
before he could bring Xiaomei home,
this incident occurred.
No wonder they kidnapped Xiaomei.
You must have leaked the news.
They weren't targeting the Lu Troupe at all.
Officer, this...
I'm not an officer.
I'm a coroner.
Officer Su,
he is the officer.
Officer.
With just this severed hand,
how can you be sure it's Xiaomei?
When Xiaomei was performing on stage yesterday,
we were all there
and witnessed how she was kidnapped.
Judging from the bloodstains at the scene and the condition of the severed hand,
it is exactly Xiaomei's right hand.
The two severed arms,
and the attached bamboo strips,
have the same handwriting.
They were done by the same person.
Then hurry up and find her!
Did the bandits mention money?
My Master Guan is the richest man in the city.
He can afford it.
As long as the young lady's life is spared,
don't let them hurt her!
The key to the problem is that
the bandits haven't sent any messages.
It looks like
we have news now.
Give it to me.
The location where they want to trade
It's already hidden in the poem.
The last two lines on this first bamboo slip
say that
if we want to ransom our little sister,
we need a chest of jewels.
As for the previous line,
it seems to say she is in grave danger,
but it's actually a riddle.
I understand.
'Heaven and earth are separated,
Yin and Yang are parted.'
This refers to a location.
The location is
a mourning hall.
But there are so many mourning halls.
How do we know which one it is?
Right.
This is too complicated.
If we can't find it
or guess it,
don't these kidnappers want the money?
For them to do this,
there must be a reason.
We might as well play their riddle game
and see where they will show up.
'Auspicious beasts show their majesty.'
A lion.
Speaking of lions,
Fengqi Restaurant on Changle Street opens today.
It's a restaurant funded by Master Guan.
There will be a lion dance at the Si hour.
Fengqi Restaurant.
When did this restaurant appear on Changle Street?
It used to be Wangyue Restaurant.
Boss Zhang couldn't keep it running.
and sold it to Master Guan.
So it was renamed Fengqi.
Wangyue Restaurant opposite Yichun Brothel has changed its name and owner.
Exactly.
The lion dance at the opening ceremony
matches the riddle perfectly.
Let's set off immediately.
Then pick a few smart constables,
bring a box of jewelry, and go to Changle Street.
Okay.
Brother Su.
Please arrange some men
to secretly protect
the Guan residence and Troupe Leader Lu's compound.
Okay.
I'm worried this bandit is cunning,
and this riddle is actually a trap to lure us away.
Okay.
You be careful too.
Jumping so high!
Good!
Fengqi Restaurant is really something else.
Yes.
Good!
There are too many people here.
Be careful.
Okay.
Good!
Here's another one.
Another one.
This one is not from Fengqi Restaurant.
Sister Chunyi.
Are you and Miss Li here to watch the lion dance?
We still have a case.
The child from the theatrical troupe.
Kick his lower body.
I'll reward a string of cash for every one knocked down.
Did you call this yellow lion?
Haven't you heard?
During a grand opening lion dance,
if the lion's head falls to the ground,
it means business will not go well this year.
The business will definitely shut down.
Sister Chunyi.
Boss, why are you doing this?
Do you hold a grudge against the Guan family?
As you know,
this shop belongs to the Guan family.
Although Guan Shan is the richest man,
I wish he would drop dead sooner.
Sister Chunyi,
how come I didn't know you had a grudge against the Guan family?
Actually, very few people know about this.
Actually,
the name Yichun of this Yichun Brothel
doesn't refer to me,
but Zhou Yichun.
She originally married Guan Shan's eldest son.
But because the baby girl she gave birth to had a birthmark on her face,
Guan Shan considered it an ominous sign,
and ordered his servants overnight
to abandon the baby girl.
The next day, unable to find her child, Zhou Yichun
searched like a madwoman.
Who knew that Guan Shan, this despicable man,
would force his eldest son to divorce his wife?
Although the eldest son was devoted,
he didn't dare to disobey his father's order,
and secretly gave Zhou Yichun a sum of money.
Having seen through men, she
took the money, left the Guan family,
and opened this Yichun Brothel.
When I first came to Luoyang, I met her.
Because of our similar names, we became sisters.
Who knew she had depression in her heart.
In less than half a year,
she passed away.
She left this Yichun Brothel to me.
Now Guan Shan wants to open a business at my doorstep.
Isn't he the most superstitious?
I'll let his lion head fall to the ground,
so he can't get a good omen.
Beat it down.
Attack!
Good.
Whose yellow lion is this?
Keep fighting.
Nonsense. This is absolute nonsense.
Hey there, why are you causing trouble?
I just love causing trouble.
Is it any of your business?
There's also a red lion.
Keep fighting.
Good.
Fight.
We guessed the wrong place.
Where to find such pristine beauty.
Brother Guan.
Vice Governor Li.
Here, Brother Guan.
This is the money box found at the Yamen gate at the hour of Si.
Take a look.
First they sent the hands to my residence,
and then the legs to the Yamen.
These bandits
are going too far.
They completely ignore the law.
Yes.
The thieves are outrageous.
They actually openly provoke the Yamen.
I will definitely dispatch more men
to search the whole city,
arrest the criminals as soon as possible,
rescue your granddaughter,
and get justice for you, Brother Guan.
Without her hands,
and missing a leg,
she is no longer whole.
What's the point of bringing her back?
What's the point?
Is she just a tool to you?
She is your own granddaughter.
Even if she is disabled,
she is still your own granddaughter.
No wonder when she was born a girl with a facial birthmark,
you abandoned her.
What did you say,
Jinglan?
Brother Guan,
my daughter is poorly disciplined.
Please forgive her.
Am I wrong?
If the Guan family's grandson hadn't died of illness
and left no heir,
he wouldn't care about his granddaughter's safety at all.
Get out!
I... Get out, all of you.
No, Father. I...
Get out.
Su Lang.
I promote you to Chief Constable.
Within two hours,
find the Guan family's granddaughter,
dead or alive.
Don't be angry.
Your father usually dotes on you so much.
He is your father, after all.
You argued with him in front of Elder Guan.
And it was at the government office.
He was put on the spot.
Calm down.
You heard him just now.
He said it himself. He doesn't care about his granddaughter's life
just because she is physically disabled.
In his eyes,
his granddaughter is just a replacement that could be abandoned before
and called back now.
If I were Xiaomei,
I would want to stay with Troupe Leader Lu too.
My dear lady,
you've vented your anger,
but I'm doomed.
The Deputy Magistrate gave me two hours to solve the case.
Where am I supposed to solve the case?
Take out your riddle and see.
What location is it?
Thousands of beauties add color,
where to seek the powdered jade?
Is it talking about rouge?
If it were really that simple,
we wouldn't have made mistakes again and again.
Then why was the previous answer
not the lion in front of Fengqi Pavilion?
Look,
there are also stone lions at the government office,
which makes sense too.
One riddle can have multiple answers.
Which one is the correct answer?
To get the correct answer,
we need to see someone.
Troupe Leader Lu.
Let's go without delay.
Su Lang.
I know.
If Xiaomei was just a troupe member,
she wouldn't have been kidnapped.
It's exactly because someone learned she was a member of the Guan family
that she encountered the bandits.
The people in this troupe know about the secret passages
and could immediately find out Xiaomei's true identity.
They fit all the criteria for a suspect.
The people in the troupe have no motive.
Think about it.
They could have just taken a healthy Xiaomei to the Guan family for ransom.
Why go to all this extra trouble?
Troupe Leader Lu.
I'm coming.
Did you find Xiaomei?
No.
Mr. Lu,
we came here today to find out about Xiaomei.
You said
you were the one who found Xiaomei back then?
No, no.
My youngest son found her.
Brother, brother.
When we first found the child,
she was less than a year old.
Just a baby like this.
Right here on her right cheek,
she had a red birthmark.
Everyone asked around,
"Whose lost child is this?"
After three or four days, there was no news at all.
So everyone guessed
this must be an abandoned baby.
Our theater troupe travels everywhere to perform.
Leave her behind?
How could we bear to do that?
Then everyone thought about it,
and decided to raise her in the troupe.
Because she was the youngest,
everyone called her Xiaomei.
Xiaomei grew up with her older brothers and sister.
Although life was poor,
there was a lot of joy.
She was loved by her two older brothers
and had the company of her older sister, Yueyue.
The two sisters were inseparable.
They were like family to each other.
Unexpectedly,
Yueyue fell seriously ill.
The doctor said it was terminal.
Yueyue wanted to pass her unique magic tricks
on to her little sister.
Her little sister adamantly refused to learn at first.
She sought medical help everywhere,
hoping to cure Yueyue.
But Yueyue's condition only worsened.
Knowing her days were numbered, Yueyue
began to teach her little sister her skills.
Magic is an illusion,
which is sleight of hand.
As long as your hands are fast,
you can make the audience cheer for you.
But I'm clumsy.
I can't learn my sister's tricks.
It doesn't matter.
You're so smart.
You will definitely learn it.
Little sister, look at the stars.
Making a wish upon a star is the most effective.
I hope before I leave,
I can watch Xiaomei perform one last time.
To fulfill Yueyue's wish,
Xiaomei studied hard
and finally learned how to do magic tricks.
In the audience,
the one applauding the loudest
was Yueyue, watching the show.
Troupe Leader Lu,
where did you find her back then?
It should be Yanzhi Alley in the North Market.
Yanzhi Alley.
The answer is not rouge,
but Yanzhi Alley.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Sir.
Have you seen a box this big with a copper clasp? Have you seen it?
No.
Sir, have you seen
a box this big with a copper clasp? What are you doing?
Go, go, go, go.
Okay, thank you.
Sorry.
Jinglan.
Sulang.
There is a box here.
Formless and invisible, it wanders around,
caressing willow branches to dance gently.
It ruffles the lake into a thousand waves,
and sends floral fragrance past the pavilion.
Another riddle.
If we keep guessing,
our sister will only have her head left.
Strange.
Could our sister have already been killed?
What makes you say that?
A dead person's muscles lack elasticity and the ability to contract,
making the wound relatively flat,
just like this one.
As for a living person,
if their limbs are chopped off,
the muscles will contract,
leaving uneven wound edges.
And the blood color would be bright.
As for this one,
there is only a little blood loss.
When the severed limb was first found,
was it also like this?
No.
What if the limb was chopped off right after death?
Would it match a severed limb chopped off from a living person?
It's hard to tell.
I see.
Jinglan.
You cleared up my last doubt.
Sulang.
I'll take you to the real killer.