What's this?
Coroner Li,
any findings?
The victim's eyes are missing,
and the eye sockets are a bloody mess.
They were likely gouged out with a sharp weapon.
The method was extremely cruel.
The fingernails were forcibly removed.
The body is covered with knife wounds
of varying lengths and widths.
They likely weren't inflicted all at once.
The dagger was thrust straight into the heart.
Judging from the depth,
this should be the fatal wound.
Also,
this dagger matches the one in Madam Cao's chest.
Go quickly and check if the murder weapon is still in Madam Cao's chest.
Hurry up. Okay.
Hurry. Let's go. Okay.
The dagger is missing!
Go report it!
Let's go. Okay.
It's gone. It's gone.
The dagger in Mrs. Cao's chest is gone.
This dagger belonged to my late father.
Six jewels are inlaid on its blade.
It is named Liuxing.
It is the only one of its kind in the world.
Just now, I asked you two
to carry Mrs. Cao's body into the room.
Was the dagger still there at that time?
Yes, it was.
Which means...
Master Yuan was murdered after we settled Mrs. Cao's body.
Compiler Dong.
Look at how Master Yuan died.
Doesn't it look like...
The deaths of Master Yuan and Mrs. Cao
are exactly the same as what Young Master Cao wrote in his book.
At first, I thought it was a coincidence.
But now...
This...
This was deliberately done by the suspect!
In that case,
you are the murderer.
I am not.
Although his death matches the one in my book,
it really has nothing to do with me.
This is really bizarre.
Don't be afraid.
It really wasn't me. Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid.
Beside Mrs. Cao's body is the first volume.
Beside Master Yuan is the second volume.
It seems the murderer
wants to guide us to finish reading "The Scheme of Fake Pregnancy".
Push.
Push hard.
Push, push.
The head is out.
Hold on. The baby is coming.
The baby is here.
The baby is born.
It's a boy.
Thank goodness.
After two girls in a row,
I was getting worried.
Look how much he looks like you.
You may all leave.
Yes.
Look at our baby.
I want to see the baby.
Alright, take a look.
Oh, wow!
So chubby and fair!
Here.
Look, the baby.
My baby.
Come look at your baby.
The baby.
Let me see.
Show me.
Eunuch, Consort Zhao gave birth to a baby boy.
It's a baby boy.
I will go report to the Emperor right now.
The other pregnant women in Consort Zhao's residence were all silenced
and buried in the back mountain.
From then on,
the palace claimed these pregnant women had never been here.
Perhaps due to the heavy negative energy,
these dead babies turned into vengeful spirits.
Various supernatural events began to happen in the whole residence.
Why is there still crying?
That shouldn't be.
Right.
Why is this chair moving?
Go take a look.
Right after that,
a murder occurred in the palace.
The first was Consort Zhao's mother.
The second was Imperial Physician Sun.
And their state of death
was exactly the same as the two murders at the villa.
It seems the suspect has read this book thoroughly,
knows its contents inside out,
and is copying its murder methods.
How many copies of this book were printed?
Who has read it?
That would be a lot.
For the first trial printing and publication,
there were no less than 100 reviewers.
This gathering
was also meant as an opportunity
to collect words of praise from you gentlemen
for future book promotions.
If the suspect is copying the book's methods,
who is the real killer?
And what is the ending?
The ending is that everyone is killed by a ghost one by one.
The killer is among them
but hasn't been found.
Why wasn't the real killer caught?
I originally wanted to leave a hook for the sequel.
I haven't decided who the killer is yet.
I just thought
people might like reading it this way.
Isn't this kid harming others and himself?
Still writing a sequel?
What you should worry about most is
who will be the killer's next target.
No matter what the suspect's motive is,
or why they are copying the book,
these are not our concerns.
We should leave this place right now.
Right.
I shouldn't have come. Let's go, hurry up.
Stop! Leave immediately!
No one can leave.
Why?
The suspect is hiding among us right now.
If everyone just leaves,
he will take the chance to escape.
We absolutely cannot do that.
You mean we should be trapped here? But soon,
we'll be sitting ducks. We're going to die here.
We will find out the truth.
We can't just wait here. Won't we all die here?
We are from the government.
It's getting late.
Why don't you all head back to the government office with me.
We'll investigate one by one,
and question everyone,
until we find the real culprit.
This works.
It's feasible.
Young Master.
Slow down.
This way, this way.
Where is the boat?
Why is it gone?
How could the boats be gone? They were right here during the day.
Yeah.
Is there any other way back?
This is the only waterway from the villa to the outside.
Without boats, there is no other way out.
The ropes. Someone cut them on purpose.
The suspect let the boats loose on purpose.
It seems they want to trap us here.
The killing hasn't stopped.
It must have been carefully planned.
The killer must know the villa like the back of their hand.
Right?
I want to go back.
Are there really no other boats?
Calm down, young master.
Where is the boat, young master?
Every day at Mao hour, a boat comes to deliver fresh vegetables.
At other times,
we rely on the four boats docked at the pier to ferry people.
What time is it now?
What time is it now, young master?
It should be Xu hour.
Since we can't leave,
the safest thing to do is to return to the villa.
Everyone gather in the hall.
No one should go anywhere alone.
That way, the killer won't have a chance to strike again.
We are...
missing someone.
Someone is missing!
Where is the steward?
Where did the steward go?
I haven't seen him for a while.
Yeah, where did he go?
It seems the servant who came with me is also gone.
Why didn't he stay with you?
Why didn't you mention your servant earlier?
Wasn't he with you?
Seeing him so panicked,
there must be something suspicious.
- Why didn't you mention your servant earlier?
- I didn't know either!
Stop arguing.
Enough!
Listen to me.
Our top priority now
is to find the killer and the two missing people.
And I suspect the killer is among us.
Waiting here until Mao hour is not an option.
It's so dark outside.
The suspect might strike again.
Right now, the only safe way
is for us to stick together,
go back the way we came,
and find the two missing people first.
You lead the way.
Young master, stay close to me.
Stay close to me.
Stay close. Go, go, go.
Hurry up.
Walk faster.
Come, this way.
Keep up.
Manager Zhang, hurry up.
Come, keep up.
Achi.
Manager.
Manager Zhang. Manager Zhang.
Manager Zhang.
Chi.
Wake up.
Are you okay?
Come help him up.
Careful.
Another one dead.
Nobody move.
The killer is so brutal.
Go check on that person.
The victim's head was severed.
The neck incision is clean.
It should be caused by being quickly cut off with a sharp weapon.
The dagger in the chest is exactly the same as the previous one.
According to the wound and surrounding signs,
he must have been stabbed directly in the chest with a dagger,
injuring his vital organs and causing his death,
before having his head cut off.
According to the residual temperature of the hand,
the time of death was not long ago.
Why did you faint here?
Did you see anything?
I also heard a noise here when I was going down the mountain,
so I rushed over.
But as soon as I came,
I was knocked out.
Who knocked you out?
I didn't see clearly.
A Chi, think carefully.
Why did so many people die tonight?
And who killed the steward?
Everyone was in a hurry to go down the mountain and escape for their lives.
Who would notice him?
This is to kill us all.
No.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
Even without a boat, I'll swim back.
No one can leave.
If you leave now,
the next one to die
might be you.
Right, you can't leave.
In case you are the murderer,
wouldn't you escape just like that?
What do you mean?
I've been walking with you all the way.
We haven't left each other for a step.
How could I kill someone?
Right? You all saw me.
Sir.
Just now when we were walking together,
I saw you slip back into your room alone.
What were you doing?
Say something.
Tell us.
I went to get my luggage.
Get your luggage? Luggage?
You are empty-handed.
You are clearly lying.
Yeah, where is your luggage?
Madam Jiang gave this to me.
Nonsense.
You're just a scholar. Why would she give you so many gold bars?
Could they be from Master Yuan?
That's right. You killed Master Yuan.
And you took his gold bars.
It was you!
I didn't kill Master Yuan.
It was you.
He put these gold bars in the room himself.
I saw Master Yuan with my own eyes,
sneaking the gold bars under his pillow.
When I was going down the mountain,
I remembered the gold bars were still in the room,
so I went back to the room and took them.
But as for where Master Yuan got them,
I have no idea.
If what you say is true,
those gold bars
must have been given to him by his mother to buy books.
My mother gave him two gold bars.
When the new book went on sale,
she wanted him to secretly buy it in batches
to create the illusion that my book is a best-seller,
thus attracting everyone's attention.
Speaking of suspicion,
I think you're a suspect too.
Owner Yuan originally wanted to promote your new work, right?
But Mr. Cao's new book was finished first,
so yours was put on hold.
I think you held a grudge against the Cao family
and decided to kill him, didn't you?
I held a grudge?
If I really held a grudge,
the first person I would kill is Cao Wen.
It has nothing to do with Owner Yuan and Manager Zhang.
And Scholar Jiang,
you're having an affair with Mrs. Cao.
No matter how dissatisfied I am,
I'd still have to show you some respect.
Nonsense!
Wait.
When I came to the villa today,
I immediately asked a servant to take me to Mrs. Cao.
I wanted to present the gifts I brought to her.
Madam,
here are some selected gifts for you.
It's enough that you came.
There's no need for gifts.
I accidentally noticed
a cabinet door by her bed wasn't closed properly.
There was a piece of a sleeve in that gap.
I didn't pay much attention to it then.
But thinking about it now...
Scholar Jiang,
Your sleeve and the one caught in the door
look quite similar.
Could the person in the wardrobe be you?
I haven't been to the east wing today.
Scholar Jiang,
I escorted you there this afternoon.
So you do have an affair with Madam.
I have no involvement with Madam Cao.
I was just discussing Cao Wen's work with her.
What does this have to do with the case?
Most murders are committed by acquaintances.
Either for money,
or for love and revenge.
All kinds of personal entanglements
could hide trouble.
Our investigation is like unspooling silk.
We need to clarify everyone's relationship with the deceased.
That makes sense. It does.
In the current situation,
with so many people talking,
it's hard to avoid confusion.
To seek the truth,
everyone, please return to your rooms for now.
Stay separated,
and don't collude.
That makes sense.
Chief Su,
you must personally search
every item in everyone's room
to find clues
and catch the real culprit.
Just as you expected,
the dagger on Master Yuan's body is gone.
The suspect first killed Madam Cao with a dagger,
then pulled it out to kill Master Yuan,
and finally pulled it out again to kill the manager.
Even if committing the murders,
why use the same dagger?
Could this dagger have some special meaning?
The first body was found in the backyard,
with the first volume of "The Plot of False Pregnancy" next to it.
The second body was found in the granary,
with the second volume of "The Plot of False Pregnancy" next to it.
The third body was found in the inner hall,
with the third volume of "The Plot of False Pregnancy" next to it.
Based on this,
one would naturally think the order of death is Madam Cao,
Master Yuan, and the manager.
But what if there is more than one identical dagger?
At Madam Cao's crime scene,
we didn't see Master Yuan,
which means Master Yuan died before Madam Cao.
The suspect only needed to prepare two identical daggers
to create confusion about the victims' times of death.
He first helped Master Yuan to the granary
and then killed him.
He left the murder weapon
and placed the second volume of the book on the table.
Right after, he went to the backyard.
Then he killed Madam Cao.
He stabbed her with another identical dagger
and left the first volume of the book.
Next,
he found a way to let someone discover Madam Cao's body first.
While transporting Madam Cao's body,
he took the dagger away.
When we found Master Yuan's body
and caused a commotion,
the killer took advantage of everyone fleeing the manor.
At this time, he pulled the manager aside and said
he saw the real culprit.
The manager believed him
and thus became the third victim.
He took the dagger from Madam Cao's body
and stabbed it into the manager.
Then he took the dagger from Master Yuan's body.
Next, he quickly went down the mountain
and followed everyone back to the manor.
The person who could cut the boat rope in advance, hint Gu Yitong to go to the backyard,
take the dagger while transporting Madam Cao's body,
kill the manager,
and knock out the servant Achi before
rushing to the ferry,
could only be another servant in the residence.
Based on deduction,
"The Plot of False Pregnancy" has four volumes.
He still hides the dagger that killed Master Yuan,
preparing to strike again.
So, you arranged for everyone to return to their rooms first
and let Chief Su check the rooms one by one.
The current suspect
will definitely take the risk to throw this dagger away.
Liu Renjiu.
You are indeed the murderer.
It wasn't me. I was framed.
After I went back to my room,
I found a bloody dagger under my pillow.
This... this isn't mine.
Afraid I couldn't explain it,
I decided to throw it into the lake.
Do you think I'd believe you?
It really wasn't me.
The Cao family has treated me well.
Why would I have a reason to kill anyone?
It really wasn't me.
Brother Jueming, Miss.
What's wrong?
Another body has been found.
Stand up straight.
You killed him too.
Tell me, did you kill him?
It wasn't me.
He lives in the west wing.
I live in the utility room.
To go to his room, I'd definitely have to pass through the inner hall.
Besides, how could I kill him in such a short time
and then return to the pond by the utility room to throw away the dagger?
Su Lang.
How did you find the body?
I waited until everyone went back to their rooms,
then searched them from east to west.
I found nothing suspicious in the rooms I checked.
Boss Gu.
When I got to Boss Gu's room,
I knocked softly but got no answer.
So I pushed the door open
and found him dead inside.
Take good care of Jinglan.
Okay.
Miss Li,
you must stand up for me.
Even if you gave me ten times the courage,
I wouldn't dare kill so many people.
I swear it really wasn't me.
The dagger is indeed gone.
I went straight from the inner hall to the pond.
When I left, the butler had a dagger on him.
Under these circumstances,
even if Liu Renjiu had the chance to kill Boss Gu,
he wouldn't have had time to take the dagger from the butler.
Was my deduction really wrong?
Liu Renjiu isn't the real killer.
He was framed.
But if that's really the case,
I dismissed everyone
and asked them to return to their rooms.
This instead gave the killer an opportunity to strike again.
There are still two volumes of the book unread.
The answer might be in them.
Strange supernatural events kept happening in the palace.
And then a third victim appeared.
Xiao Shunzi.
Xiao Shunzi died tragically in the embroidery room, beheaded.
A dagger was also stuck in his chest.
Consort Zhao felt guilty.
She believed her servants' words,
and invited someone to catch ghosts.
A Taoist master came to the palace,
along with a shaman and a retainer.
The Taoist master performed rituals and gave everyone amulets for safety.
The shaman possessed the dead body
and spoke the deceased's grievances.
To determine who the murderer is.
But both methods seemed utterly absurd to the retainer.
He believed it must be a living person causing trouble.
After some searching,
the retainer found the pregnant woman's corpse buried in the back mountain,
thus discovering the truth about Consort Zhao having a child.
Consort Zhao's mother, Imperial Physician Sun, and Xiaoshunzi died one after another.
This indicated that the suspect was highly likely seeking revenge.
The retainer carefully checked all personnel movements in the residence,
and found that a batch of eunuchs was recently recruited.
The suspect was very likely among them.
The suspect's wife was the pregnant woman,
who was recruited into the palace for embroidery work.
and never returned home.
To find out the truth,
he entered the palace and became a eunuch.
Just as there was a new clue in the case,
a shrill scream echoed through the palace.
Consort Zhao is dead.
The retainer realized he was still a step too late.
The fake pregnancy bundle
was put back onto Consort Zhao's abdomen.
Judging from this,
the child taken by Consort Zhao was the suspect's flesh and blood.
After taking revenge on Consort Zhao,
he would definitely take the child away.
The retainer rushed to the royal nursery
and found the baby was still there.
However, as he turned around,
a sharp blade pierced his chest.
A story of a Virtuous Consort faking a pregnancy in the palace.
Why imitate this story to commit murder?