You've been watching me for a long time.
During the Ghost Festival,
when I was chasing you,
you already knew I was your daughter.
Actually,
I have always been secretly watching you.
Especially whenever you cracked a major case,
I felt happy,
truly happy from the bottom of my heart.
That is also why I haven't left Luoyang for so many years.
Li Ze is now in prison,
torturing his biological daughter in every possible way.
When the hour of Shen arrives,
he will personally send his daughter to her doom.
Then I will go tell him
that Moying is his real daughter.
Why are you so sinister and vicious?
I am just a law-abiding citizen.
How could I be sinister and vicious?
Inside Luoyang City,
all these major thefts were committed by me.
But I've robbed so much treasure,
and I've never squandered it.
Neither has Mo Ying.
I gave a lot of treasure and money
to the people in the city.
Because back then, your mother and I
also suffered from hunger and cold.
So I swore back then
that one day,
I would give this money to those poor people.
Am I that sinister and vicious?
But what about Li Ze?
He locked me in prison back then.
When your mother was giving birth,
there was no one at home to take care of her.
Died tragically at home.
He is so sinister and ruthless.
What about Moying?
Do you have absolutely no affection for her?
She is dead.
Aren't you even a little bit sad?
Moying
had been with me for so many years since childhood,
but never enjoyed a good life.
And her only wish
was to leave Luoyang City and see the outside world.
But as her father, I couldn't even fulfill such a small wish.
If there is a next life,
I will repay Moying for this father-daughter bond.
Moya.
Let's see if you will show up or not.
It might be a big deal if the execution is halted.
Deputy Governor, the time has come.
Execute!
Hold the execution!
Jinglan.
Did he make things difficult for you?
You're back.
I have something to tell you.
My child.
Moying is your biological daughter.
And I
am Moya's child.
Calm down.
I can let you into the execution ground.
But I have one condition.
I need you to face everyone
and tell the truth.
Really?
Yes.
Shaoyin.
Shaoyin Li,
wake up!
Shaoyin Li.
It's been years. How have you been?
Is what Li Jinglan said
true?
Look at our daughter. Does she look like me or you?
Please calm down, Shaoyin.
Please calm down, Shaoyin. Calm down.
Yinger.
Are you... are you okay?
So your plan
was to have Li Ze order my execution himself.
Using my life to complete your revenge.
You plotted every step
just for today, didn't you?
At the execution ground,
I was still worried.
I was afraid you would come to save me.
I was afraid
you'd fall into Li Ze's trap.
Looking back now,
I worried too much.
Now I just want to ask you one thing.
Did you ever treat me as your own daughter?
Yes, of course I did.
No, you didn't.
If you did, you wouldn't have done this.
Family affection
to me,
is nothing but a joke.
In your heart,
you never treated me as your own daughter.
Since childhood, I respected and loved you,
and saw you as my only family.
But you just treated me as a pawn,
a bait.
It's not like that. I love you.
Who knows my heart?
How could you be
so hypocritical?
If you
wanted to see me die in front of Li Ze,
then I will grant your wish.
Child!
No!
All unlawful acts were committed by Moya,
and have nothing to do with Moying.
Moya pleads guilty.
Jinglan.
I've made the bed for you.
You just got caught in the rain,
so I also made some brown sugar water.
Thank you.
You just got caught in the rain.
Drink it before it gets cold.
Thank you.
It's raining so heavily outside.
If you don't go home,
your father must be worried.
If you're not going back,
you can sleep here.
I'll sleep over there with the two kids.
Thank you for taking me in.
But I'm just the daughter of a thief.
Whether the blood in my veins is good
or evil,
I don't even know myself.
Our friendship
is not because your father is Li Ze.
But because you are Li Jinglan.
Even if your biological father is Mo Ya,
it doesn't matter.
It won't affect our friendship at all.
Look.
You have so many virtues.
Smart,
kind, and brave.
All these traits make up the real you.
Think about me.
When Sister Chunyi died,
I was so sad,
but I didn't tell anyone.
But you?
You understood me,
empathized with me,
stayed by my side,
and even arranged her funeral.
I was very happy.
And the little girl from the Lu Troupe.
She yearned for freedom,
and you helped me close that case
as unsolved.
And you?
You were so loud, rushing to the front
to keep her safe.
Remember Chen You?
The one who always smiled at you.
He took such good care of you before.
But later?
We found out together that he was a hypocrite.
Extremely greedy,
and treating human life like dirt.
I didn't expect
you to put aside personal feelings and handle the case impartially.
I think you must have
been very sad back then.
A person's sense of right and wrong
isn't determined by their background or bloodline.
It lies in your heart.
A heart that upholds justice.
A kind and honest heart.
Right?
But I'm still very scared.
I'm afraid to face them.
I'm afraid to see my father,
and I'm afraid to see him too.
If our identities hadn't been switched back then,
Mo Ying might not be the way she is now.
And me.
It's also very likely that he's already a wanted man by the yamen.
Whenever I think of every little thing I shared with my father...
When I was young, he taught me to ride a horse.
He knew I liked boyish things,
and bought them all for me. Also,
he indulged me in apprenticing to be a coroner.
Whenever I think of these scenes,
right before my eyes,
they scatter like fragments.
You know?
I'm really scared to see him.
I'm afraid that when I look at him,
he will look at me with strangeness
and alienation.
I'm afraid he'll feel that all these years were wasted.
Do I have no home now?
It's okay.
I'm here.
Do I have no home now?
You do.
You have me,
your father,
and Mr. Su.
You have so much.
Such a beautiful person,
why are you crying so hard?
Look,
you just said a lot of what's on your mind.
Shouldn't you tell your father
to let him know
that his tomboy is back?
I'll go with you.
Look, Jueming is holding Jinglan's hand.
I said long ago they would be together.
Exactly.
Master.
Take it away.
I can't eat.
Any news about Jinglan?
Everyone went out to look for her.
The young lady might be on her way back.
Miss.
Go on.
He is your father.
Don't be afraid.
I will wait for you right here.
Go ahead.
Shijun.
My girl.
When your mother passed away,
you were still very young.
When you learned to speak,
the first thing you called me
was 'Dad'.
You can't change that now.
You've always worried me since you were little.
You loved doing what boys do.
Other girls hold dolls all day,
play string instruments,
and do needlework.
But you prefer to tinker with dead things
like a tomboy.
Other girls would cry in fear when they see a mouse.
But your eyes light up,
you reach out to catch it,
and play tricks on people.
When I pretend to beat you,
you find a corner to hide in.
Poking her head out to scare me and make me mad.
Such a special daughter,
no one can compare to her.
No matter your background,
in my heart,
you are the most excellent daughter.
Daughter.
My daughter.
Moya.
For revenge,
you pushed everyone into the abyss.
Is it worth it
to do this?
Vice Governor Li,
who pushed me
into the abyss
back then?
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
It's my fault for my subjective assumptions
and stubborn prejudices back then,
which caused you to suffer an unjust injustice.
It made you end up like this.
So you also know you were wrong,
Vice Governor.
Back then,
when you judged the case at the yamen,
you had no solid evidence.
Just based on those old things about me,
you concluded that I was the thief
and locked me up in that prison.
You kept me in prison for a few days,
and my wife starved and froze at home for a few days.
In the end, when she was giving birth,
she died tragically at home.
Did you know that?
When I begged in prison,
who paid attention to me?
This is the pain of my life.
And
your saying,
the child of an official is always an official,
and the child of a thief is always a thief.
Is that so?
Your child could be a thief,
and my child could be an official.
Back then, I secretly swore
I must take this revenge.
My fault.
This is all my fault.
But if there's anything,
you can come at me.
You really shouldn't have
targeted the two children.
Jinglan, Moying.
They are innocent.
They are our own daughters.
Is this situation
really what you want?
Then what about my wife?
Wasn't she innocent?
Moying.
Moying is also your daughter.
Although Moying has no blood relation with me,
we have depended on each other for so many years.
I have long treated her as my own biological daughter.
As for Jinglan.
I hope in the future,
you can treat both of them well.
Moya.
I'm sorry to you.
I plan to resign from my official post
to make up for my mistakes.
Don't worry.
After Moying gets out of prison,
I will do everything in my power to take care of her
and protect her.
What about Li Jinglan?
She is outside.
About the Glazed Pearl,
I will only tell her.
Okay.
My lord.
How is it?
Jinglan.
He wants to see you.
About the Glazed Orb,
he only wants to tell you.
Take care, Lord Li.
I will wait for you outside.
Jinglan, hurry!
Go ahead.
As for the Glazed Orb,
it was indeed my doing.
Back then,
Yexiao somehow found out
the transport route and time of the orb.
We lay in ambush along the way.
After catching the three transport commissioners off guard and drugging them,
we found the orb in the brocade box.
As agreed,
he gave me a bag of silver
and left with the orb to meet the client.
I never heard from him again.
I figure that by then,
he had already been silenced.
And after that,
the matter was never mentioned again.
When he left,
which direction did he go?
Opposite the mountain road is Niutou Mountain.
He probably went
towards the west.
Niutou Mountain.
Cao Wen said Cao Shaoyin also went to Niutou Mountain back then.
Could he be the client Yexiao went to meet?
On the west side of Niutou Mountain,
there must be clues.
We've been digging for three days.
How long are we going to dig?
Stop complaining.
Shaoyin has given an order.
We must find clues even if we have to level the mountain.
Keep digging.
Jueming,
have a drink first.
Are you sure this is the right place?
Why can't we find it?
I'm sure. Let's keep looking.
Okay, keep digging.
I'll dig over there.
Keep trying hard.
Okay, tell me if you find any clues.
Found it.
Found a clue.
Look around quickly and see if there are any orbs.
Hurry up.
- Dig all around here.
- Okay.
See if there are any orbs. Hurry.
Dig here.
Here.
Bring it here.
Yes, Su Lang is saved.
The orb is found.
There is also a skeleton.
A skeleton.
Dig and see.
Hurry.
What is this?
Let me see.
Bring the light.
This looks like Constable Qin's sachet.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
Constable Qin used to carry it every day.
I've seen it many times.
But why would Constable Qin's sachet
be here?
Slow down, Jueming.
Father's remains have been found.