In the winter of the tenth year of Kaiyuan,
the Anlan Dam in Dongshui Town, Yangzhou collapsed.
The flood drowned the people,
and countless commoners lost their lives.
To pacify the disaster, His Majesty
not only donated money for relief,
but also gave the state-protecting glazed orb, which symbolizes peace and harmony,
to Kaiyuan Temple in Yangzhou.
This orb was transported from Chang'an to Yangzhou,
but vanished without a trace in Luoyang.
Minister of Revenue Lu Yunxian
was dismissed along with other officials
and imprisoned.
Minister Lu is my uncle.
He treated me very well when I was young.
If the orb can be found,
I will definitely be able to save my uncle from prison.
Who escorted the precious pearl along the way?
It was relayed by transport commissioners from each post station, appointed by Minister Lu.
There were seven post stations in total.
Each station had three transport commissioners.
The precious pearl was placed in a chest
and handed over sequentially through the post stations.
It departed from Chang'an,
heading to Luoyang and Bianzhou Pavilion.
But the envoy's transport cart never arrived,
so they knew something went wrong.
The government has been tracking the whereabouts of the pearl.
However, the pearl never appeared again.
It became a cold case.
We recently caught a transport commissioner.
Here is the confession.
Here, take a look first.
Okay.
Stop.
Did you steal the pearl?
Even if you gave me a hundred times the courage,
I wouldn't dare steal what I was guarding.
The three of us received the goods at the Luoyang post station,
and immediately headed to the Bianzhou post station.
Who knew that while passing Niutou Mountain,
we suddenly heard cries for help.
It turned out to be two traveling merchants attacked by bandits.
and robbed them of all their valuable gold and silver jewelry.
At that time, we were too soft-hearted,
so we dismounted to check their carriage.
They took advantage of our unpreparedness
and threw knockout powder at us.
By the time I woke up,
the treasure we were transporting was already gone.
Wake up.
We three brothers all knew
that losing the transported goods would surely cost us our heads.
We simply made up our minds
and fled for our lives.
We changed our names
and lived in seclusion.
Where are they?
We swore an oath
to never contact each other again.
Could it be
a trap they set on purpose?
There were plenty of opportunities along the way.
Why collude with outsiders?
What did that merchant look like?
Any distinguishing features?
He had a scar on his face.
I know him.
His name is Moya,
and he has a daughter named Moying.
They make a living by stealing.
The local yamen has wanted them for a long time,
but hasn't caught them yet.
On the Ghost Festival,
Su Lang and I found their whereabouts
and chased them all the way.
I saw his face.
There is a long scar on the left side.
That was the day you bumped me out of the coffin.
Come, let me take a look.
I know this person too.
You know him too?
I personally convicted him.
He wasn't called Moya back then,
but Zhang Shuijing.
How come I didn't know?
I've never heard you mention it.
You were still in your mother's womb at that time.
Chen You was the magistrate,
and I was the recording officer.
I was in charge of trying his case.
Deputy Magistrate Li,
what crime did he commit back then?
Theft.
Back then, a butcher shop was burglarized.
The owner of this butcher shop,
after finding his money vanished,
was burning with anxiety.
He immediately grabbed all the customers in the shop
and dragged them to the government office.
After some investigation,
I noticed this Moya.
His father
was a flying thief I personally arrested.
As the saying goes, like father, like son.
In my heart, I was certain
that he most likely stole the money.
During the interrogation, he flatly denied it.
I found the stolen money on him
and threw him in jail.
I thought
it would make him turn over a new leaf.
Who knew
he wouldn't give up
and went back to his old ways.
In the end,
he actually dared to steal the Glazed Pearl.
Looking back now,
when he claimed in court that he was framed...
It's just an excuse.
What's more heartbreaking is that
after his daughter was born,
she also joined him in committing theft.
Now this father and daughter are guilty of many crimes.
The government has no choice but to offer a huge reward for their capture.
As they say, a thief's child can hardly change their thieving nature.
Unfortunately, the judgment made back then has come true.
Is the glazed pearl still in their hands?
We will only know that after we catch him.
When he committed the theft last time, whose house was robbed?
Feng Residence on the East Street.
This might be our breakthrough.
Mr. Su, go to the Feng Residence on the East Street.
Bring Shopkeeper Feng to the government office.
Let's ask him how he was targeted by Moya.
Okay, I'm familiar with this family.
I'll go right away. Okay.
My lord.
My lord, I'll take my leave.
Be careful on the way.
Thank you for your hard work.
I am Feng Nan.
I usually do some silk business.
The money saved at home
is hard-earned money from doing business.
You see, it was all stolen by him.
I...
If you want your money back,
answer my questions.
What did you just ask me?
Okay.
Think carefully.
Why are you hesitating?
Just say whatever comes to mind.
Well...
This...
How about this, if you don't want your money back...
We'll just take the ledger
and go home. Let's go.
Let's go.
The thief has already scouted the place anyway.
He'll come looking for you in a few months.
Let's go.
Again?
What else?
To him, you're a long-term silver vault now.
Whenever he needs money,
he will come to you.
He'll keep
coming to you.
Okay, let's go.
Case closed. Time to go home.
Pack up.
We won't write this part. It's useless. Let's go first.
Pack all this up. Pack it up.
Pack it up. Wait.
I'll talk.
That was when he set his eyes on you in the jewelry store.
This one is pretty.
This one is pretty too.
Do you think I look good wearing this?
Yes.
Then I want all of these.
Thank you, boss. Let me give you a kiss.
See if there is anything else you want.
Look over here.
Are you sure it was in the jade shop and not somewhere else?
Definitely.
Because during the robbery,
that woman also said it.
Said what?
I didn't see anything.
Do you know how I targeted you?
He took a beautiful young woman
to the jade shop and bought several bracelets.
What?
Look at you.
Working yourself to the bone to guard the little money the family has.
But what about him?
He spent all the family's money
on that mistress outside.
Do you think it's worth it being his wife?
You went out with that woman again.
At a time like this,
why are you bringing this up?
You won't tell them?
Then I will.
All his money is hidden down the well in the courtyard.
Just pull the well rope,
and the money box comes up.
What do you mean by this?
I live frugally at home,
while you spend lavishly on a mistress.
Then no one gets to spend it.
Looks like they've been staking out the jade shop for a long time.
In that case,
I have an idea.
Young master,
you're so handsome. - Young master. - Yes.
Jinglan. Constable Su,
will this work?
This is his great idea,
luring the snake out of its hole.
My lady,
you could have done it,
but your face was seen by Black Crow.
So I had to hire three temporary ones.
Young master, you truly have heavenly looks.
My lady, I paid to hire those three.
You have to reimburse me for this.
You have the nerve to ask me for money?
Young master, you're just too handsome.
Yes.
Don't look, don't look.
I'm just looking.
Wow, so pretty.
Young Master, buy this for me.
Okay, I want this one.
Go pick.
Shopkeeper.
It's so beautiful.
This one is pretty.
This one is pretty too.
Everything the three of them pick today,
I'll pay for it.
Okay, boss.
So luxurious.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Buy some more.
So you finally came back.
Business has been too busy lately.
Rest early. I'm tired.
Will he take the bait?
He definitely will.
If my father finds out about this...
Then I'd be the one going to jail.
Don't speak.
Young Master Liu,
it's time to get up.
It's an ambush. Let's split up.
Surround them! Catch the thieves!
If you don't want her to die now, step back!
Don't come any closer!
Where is Mo Ya hiding?
I don't know.
But I know
your daughter
is suffering the same torture as me.
The pampered young lady,
I don't know if she can bear it.
How dare you be so arrogant, you villain!
Just come at me with whatever you've got!
Let's see if your daughter dies first,
or if I break first.
Speak up,
or today will be your last day.
Speak!
Mr. Su.
Deputy Magistrate Li has ordered,
no one is allowed in right now.
He's lost his mind.
Jueming!
Deputy Magistrate Li.
You can't do this!
What's going on?
Jinglan is in Mo Ya's hands.
If we hurt Mo Ying now,
Jinglan will definitely be in greater danger.
We can't hurt her.
Yes.
How dare he!
If he dares to touch a single hair on Jinglan's head,
I'll tear him to pieces!
I told you to find Mo Ya's hiding place.
Any results?
We have sealed off the entire Luoyang City.
He can't escape.
Besides,
we have all the constables searching for him.
We absolutely cannot provoke Mo Ya,
or Jinglan will be in more danger.
Yes, Lord Li.
Search!
How long is it going to take?
Lord Li.
Jinglan is my daughter.
She is my only daughter.
Yes, Lord Li.
If Jinglan gets hurt in any way,
you,
and you,
will not have a good end.
Deputy Magistrate Li.
Lord Li.
I have already given the order.
This woman has committed numerous crimes,
including multiple severe thefts.
Her crimes are unpardonable.
What's more rampant,
is that she dared to kidnap the daughter of a court official.
The evidence is conclusive.
Today at Shen hour,
she will be beheaded.
Deputy Magistrate Li, you...
Mo Ya.
Let's see if you come to save her,
or not.
Boss, give me one.
Here you go.
Crispy and savory sesame cakes!
Have one.
Coming.
Crispy and savory sesame cakes!
Have a sesame cake.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Have one too.
Look at this. Quite the nerve.
Here you go.
This master thief is finally caught.
Yes.
I heard
it was a father-daughter duo.
But the mastermind hasn't been caught yet.
That's only a matter of time.
Right?
How long have these two been at large?
Shi Zhan Li Ru Chi Geng Duo.
Shi Zhan Li Xiang Chi Geng Duo.
You have to trust the authorities.
Now that the young one is caught,
the older one definitely won't get away.
I don't think so.
Yeah, not necessarily.
With your little skills,
you can't escape.
Are you hungry?
I just bought some hot roast chicken and steamed buns.
Come eat some.
I might not be able to beat you,
but you stole the Liuli Orb.
You can't escape.
I didn't plan to escape anyway.
The city gates have long been sealed.
There's still one who hasn't returned yet.
You want to take me hostage
as a bargaining chip.
Li Ze issued a notice today.
Moying will be beheaded in public at the Shen hour.
There are still two shichen left.
It seems
you have no intention of saving her at all.
Don't you care if she lives or dies?
I raised her myself.
We've been together day and night for years.
How could I not care?
But she's your daughter.
No matter what,
I must leave today.
You are my daughter.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I am not talking nonsense.
Every word I say is true.
is my daughter.
That year, your mother was several months pregnant.
Every day after working at the grain shop,
I hurried home to take care of her.
Although life was poor,
thinking of the child in her womb
filled my heart with warmth and anticipation.
That day, I wanted to buy some meat to nourish your mother,
so I went to the butcher shop.
But as soon as I arrived,
before I could even buy the meat,
the butcher said some silver was missing
and claimed there was a thief in the shop.
We argued with him endlessly.
Just then, a constable came by.
We followed him to the magistrate's office
to seek justice.
Fellow villagers,
money was stolen from the butcher shop today,
causing a dispute
that was brought to court.
Unfortunately, the magistrate had to go out
on official business,
so he cannot try this case in person for now.
I am Li Ze, the Registrar.
By the grace of the magistrate,
I will temporarily take charge of this case.
If you have anything to say,
please speak freely
to help us investigate this case thoroughly.
Court is in session.
Justice.
Sir, I put the money on the counter today.
But when I turned around to get the meat,
all the money was gone.
Only they were present at the time.
The thief must be among them.
This has nothing to do with me.
Nothing to do with me.
Aren't you falsely accusing us?
How could it be with so many people around?
I think I've seen you before.
Is your father's name Zhang Ting?
Yes.
What a coincidence.
Fellow townsfolk.
You may not know this.
This man's father
is a notorious thief.
His father stole for years.
He was finally brought to justice by me.
You were still young then.
You visited him in prison.
We've met before.
My Lord, that was over ten years ago.
It has nothing to do with the butcher shop incident today.
Have these people been searched?
Not yet, My Lord.
Search him.
Wait.
You have no evidence. Why search me?
My Lord, it was my father who broke the law back then.
He has already been punished.
I am a law-abiding citizen.
You can't just call me a thief based on his nonsense.
The villagers are watching. Zhang and Mrs. Li, they all know me.
My Lord, give me justice.
All right.
If you didn't steal it,
why are you afraid of being searched?
Search.
If you don't believe me, search me.
This is my family's money, My Lord.
My Lord, I found
a hundred copper coins on him.
How much did you lose?
A hundred coins.
It matches.
My Lord, I am wrongly accused. I am innocent!
My wife is pregnant.
I wanted to buy some food for her at the butcher shop.
This is all the money I've saved.
Look, my wife sewed this purse for me.
It still has a faint scent of jasmine.
You can smell it.
What a coincidence.
Your father is a thief.
You are also a thief.
Dragons beget dragons, phoenixes beget phoenixes.
A thief's child will always be a thief.
That's how he convicted me
and threw me in jail.
But I didn't steal a single penny.
So I have a clear conscience.
Because I had a hope in my heart,
which was my beloved wife
and my soon-to-be-born child.
No matter how great the injustice and suffering,
I was not afraid.
I could endure it all.
Three months later,
I was released.
You're back.
How is my wife?
Your wife
had a difficult labor.
She waited for you all night yesterday,
but you never came.
I'm sorry.
It's a girl.
Look how cute she is.
When I was released from prison,
I happened to learn that Li Ze just had a baby girl.
Because of his prejudice that dragons beget dragons and phoenixes beget phoenixes,
he falsely imprisoned me,
destroying my family.
Since that is the case,
I will let him experience the consequences of his false words.
I stole his daughter
and sent my own daughter to his mansion.
I want to see
if his fallacy that a thief's child is always a thief
holds true.
Nonsense.
Below your left chest,
there is a red birthmark.
Besides your parents
and the maid who serves you,
I'm afraid no one else
knows about this birthmark.
Who would have thought
that the daughter of the great thief Mo Ya
would become the daughter of the Deputy Governor?
And became a coroner,
and solved major cases one after another.
Thinking about it this way,
aren't Li Ze's arrogant words from back then
especially ridiculous and absurd now?
You've been observing me for a long time.
During the Ghost Festival,
when I was chasing you,
you already knew I was your daughter.