Good news.
Jueming, Coroner Li.
What is it?
Su Lang is saved.
The Liuli Orb has been recovered.
And Lord Lu's wrongful conviction has been cleared.
Now Lord Lu
and Deputy Magistrate Li are both pleading for Su Lang.
Su Lang is now spared from the death penalty.
Although his sentence hasn't been finalized yet,
his life is finally saved.
This is perhaps the best possible outcome.
Mr. Su, you can rest assured now.
I came today
to thank you all on behalf of my uncle.
If it weren't for all of you,
things would hardly have turned around for my uncle.
Thank you all.
It was our duty.
We helped each other this time.
His Majesty already knows the Liuli Orb case is complicated.
Dali Temple has been ordered to intervene
to find out the truth
and get to the bottom of this as soon as possible.
Coroner Li, do you have the autopsy results?
Based on the length of the leg bones and spine,
we can deduce this person was about 6 feet tall.
Moreover, the bones are thick
and the chest is broad,
indicating a burly build.
According to the records,
Constable Qin suffered a dislocation.
Plus, there was a sachet beside him.
Thus, we can deduce
that these are the remains of Qin Rui.
Can you find out where his fatal wound is?
There are traces of a heavy blow to the back of the head.
It is still obvious after so many years,
so it should be the fatal wound.
Also,
the ribs on the chest are broken.
They should have been broken by someone after his death.
Broken after death?
I was really foolish.
Why didn't I find this out back then?
That means out of the five charred bodies in the fire at the Qin family,
one of them was not Constable Qin,
but someone else.
In this way,
this fire was not a natural one.
It might have been deliberately set by someone.
There is another body here.
Looking at these remains,
the fingertips are quite unusual.
Normal people have fingers of distinct lengths
and different shapes.
But for this skeleton, the index and middle fingers are of equal length.
Its fingertip bones have been worn flat.
This is not normal.
I heard that great thieves in the martial arts world, in order to make their stealing techniques faster,
would practice a special technique.
Over time,
their index and middle fingers, because of this technique,
will become of equal length and worn flat.
Therefore, it can be inferred that
this skeleton is highly likely that of a great thief.
So after all that,
it's just to make picking pockets easier.
These thieves.
But that makes sense.
This body should be Mo Ya's boss in the underworld,
Ye Xiao.
He's here.
Mr. Lu.
Based on the current situation,
the Glazed Orb was stolen.
After Ye Xiao was killed,
the killer didn't take the orb.
It is clear that the person behind this
was not after the Glazed Orb,
but your uncle.
Right.
If Mr. Lu falls,
who benefits the most?
My uncle has been a man of high moral character all his life,
kind to others,
and highly respected.
If we talk about making the deepest enemies
and sudden disturbances,
it must be the collapse of the Anlan Dam.
When the disaster struck, wails were heard everywhere.
My uncle was burdened with the heavy responsibility of dispatching disaster relief funds.
He went to the scene in person and spoke out in public.
This dam was only built a year ago,
and it collapsed.
It was definitely not a natural disaster.
There must be human negligence and corruption.
As soon as this was said,
it caused a great sensation.
Since then, it has left many roots of trouble.
Yes.
When that disaster happened,
you were still young,
but I remember it vividly.
Many people died at that time.
This construction work was under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Works.
My uncle suspected that Yuan Feng, the Minister of Works, lined his own pockets
and sought personal gain by cutting corners.
Yuan Feng.
My uncle once said he would thoroughly investigate this man.
You can't say that carelessly.
The Minister of Works is in charge of major national projects' design and construction.
If someone were to tamper with it,
it's not entirely impossible.
Thinking about it now,
the theft of the glazed orb
seems like a carefully planned conspiracy.
My uncle was inexplicably drawn into it,
and became deeply entangled.
With his imprisonment,
the Anlanti case seemed to be frozen instantly.
All parties fell silent by tacit agreement,
and the path to a thorough investigation was immediately blocked.
Yuan Feng
is a third-rank official in the court.
His power there is not to be underestimated.
If he really committed this crime,
investigating this case
will be extremely difficult.
I still have one question.
I remember Mo Ya once said
that Ye Xiao took the Liuli Orb to meet the client.
Then,
Constable Qin's remains are buried with Ye Xiao's.
Could it be that Constable Qin is Yuan Feng's minion?
Constable Qin was upright all his life.
He would never steal what was entrusted to him.
Elder Su, I was just guessing.
Back then, Constable Qin might have
just found clues about the stolen Glazed Pearl,
which led to him being silenced
and his whole family being murdered.
Mr. Su, you and Constable Qin solved countless cases.
I want to re-examine all the files of the cases you solved.
Lord Minister, I've found out.
Jueming is just an ordinary Buliangren.
He has helped the yamen solve several major cases.
He is quite capable.
No matter how beautiful a flower is,
if it grows where it shouldn'...
We must uproot it.
I know what to do.
Children kidnapped and missing at Niutou Mountain.
If you want the truth, go to the Qin residence in the north of the city.
Mr. Lu.
Magistrate Zhao!
Magistrate Zhao, wait!
Wait, wait!
Please.
I have read the files.
Miss Li,
why are you in such a panic?
Magistrate Zhao.
Jueming is definitely not the murderer of Squire Lu.
There must be a hidden truth behind this.
He must have been framed by someone.
Just now,
the government office received a report
of a murder at the Qin residence in the north of the city.
When the constables arrived,
they found the victim's body on the spot.
And at the scene,
only Jueming was sitting next to the victim,
holding a bloody dagger.
After verification, the dagger in Jueming's hand
was indeed the murder weapon.
The shape of the blade perfectly matched the wound.
If you say he's not the suspect,
then who is?
Who reported the case?
If there was time to report it,
why didn't Jueming, as a suspect,
flee immediately?
Why would he wait at the scene for the constables to arrive?
I will naturally consider what you said.
But before Jueming's suspicion is cleared,
I cannot let him go for now.
Magistrate Zhao.
Miss Li.
I was transferred here as the county magistrate.
Upon arrival, I heard about your deeds.
You have solved many strange cases.
You even found the long-lost glazed orb of the Imperial Court.
But look closely at the people around you.
Su Yu'an was dismissed for perjury.
Su Lang was imprisoned for murder.
Only Jueming is left, and he is suspected of tonight's murder.
Your colleagues are right beside you day and night.
Dare you guarantee
that you have seen right through them?
Jueming.
Why are you wearing these clothes?
What crime did you commit?
That's not right.
My father came to me this morning
and said you found the court's lost glazed orb together,
making a great contribution.
Squire Lu wrote to the court
to ask the Ministry of Justice to resentence me.
Squire Lu...
He is dead.
When did this happen?
Who killed him?
They suspect it was me.
The victim and the evidence are both here.
You also have the victim's blood on you.
I think you are the murderer.
Take him away.
Move.
In that case,
did you see who knocked you out?
I was the only one at the crime scene.
Looking at it this way, I am indeed the prime suspect.
Oh, right.
You hurried to the Qin Residence in the north of the city after receiving a note.
Then we just need to find the note.
Since I fell into a trap,
it was carefully planned by them.
They must have taken the note when I was knocked out.
I think
they've already taken the dart from my house.
What do we do now?
What I'm most worried about now
is the two kids, Yichun and Nianxia.
I hope when the killer went to my house to get the dart,
they didn't hurt them.
Jueming.
I've already informed my father, Jueming.
Father, Alang,
you've suffered.
Are Yichun and Nianxia okay?
Don't worry.
I've already brought them to the manor.
They won't be in danger.
Thank you.
Even though right now,
I don't have evidence to prove your innocence,
they can't prove you're the killer either.
I will try my best.
Think hard again. Think carefully.
Did you miss any details?
Jinglan, Mr. Su.
The dart outside my door
and the files on my desk, are they still there?
The dart is gone.
The files on the desk are gone too.
The children were sleeping too soundly.
They said they didn't hear a thing.
His Lordship is here.
Lord Li.
You are all here.
Open the door.
Yes, sir.
Su Lang.
Jueming,
don't panic.
Even though I'm not familiar with the new magistrate,
he is still my subordinate.
If I order him to investigate this case thoroughly,
he won't dare to convict you without proof.
Yes, Jueming.
You must have dug into the higher-ups.
So they set a trap for you.
This exactly proves my theory.
I was looking in the right direction.
Mr. Su,
there was a case back then
called the Niutou Mountain child abduction and missing case.
Do you still remember the details?
I remember.
A woman came to report
that her child was abducted to Linhe Village
and being raised by someone else.
We went to investigate,
but when we found out, we realized
it wasn't what she said.
Her child was indeed kidnapped,
but by the time we found him,
the child had suffocated in a sack.
The woman couldn't take the shock
and developed hysteria.
Whenever she saw a child around her son's age,
she would claim him as her own,
causing a lot of trouble.
But later,
we still caught the human trafficker
who abducted her son.
All these years,
every time I sold a child,
no matter what they were used for,
I just took the money.
As for the child you mentioned,
running into him was just a coincidence.
What kind of coincidence?
That day, I was driving my carriage past Niutou Mountain.
Uncle! Uncle!
What's wrong?
Over there! Over there!
We got a free one.
There were four children in my carriage.
Only he was suffocated to death.
I didn't mean to kill him.
Come and identify.
Where did the child get off,
and where did you pick him up?
Look closely.
Here.
Are you sure?
How did you die?
I was murdered.
Murdered?
Did it hurt?
It hurt a lot. Feel this.
Stabbed so deep.
How old are you?
Seven.
Although you are highly suspicious,
you are not the real killer.
Because you are still young,
and don't have enough strength
to stab this deep.
Besides, the murder weapon has a lingering floral scent,
which means the murderer can only be...
Can only be...
You don't clean up when you get up every day.
The zither is gathering dust.
You want to grow flowers but are too lazy to water them.
Tell me, should I kill you?
Mother.
I know I was wrong.
Grandpa, you can investigate cases even blindfolded!
Of course I can.
The details of the corpse
and the smells on the body are all keys to solving the case.
Well said, Mr. Qin.
Hearing this was truly enlightening
and suddenly opened my mind.
Isn't that right?
Alright, stop flattering.
The porridge is ready.
Come over and help.
What's good to eat?
Here.
It smells really good.
Mrs. Qin, you put lotus seeds in it?
Yes. Lotus seeds can nourish the heart and calm the mind,
benefit the kidneys, and have a soft texture.
They also make the sweetness of the red beans richer.
Mrs. Qin, after I finish eating,
I want to take some home
for our little Su Lang to try, okay?
How old is he?
Come on.
He is one year younger than Xiaonian.
By the way,
when you two go out these days,
you must stick with your mother.
The child kidnappers have been very rampant lately.
You must be careful, hear me?
Yes, let me tell you.
The missing children are about your age.
Just because they were playful and naughty,
they came down the mountain by themselves,
and met a bad guy driving a carriage,
who took them all away.
Second Uncle always lies.
I don't believe it.
Exactly.
Me, lying?
Look here.
I even brought the map.
This is the proof, see?
They went missing right here.
Why did you bring this out?
Our Su Lang is even more naughty than them.
I have to show him the hard evidence to teach him a lesson.
Bad guys want to kidnap you two. Are you afraid?
I'm not afraid.
Not afraid? Do you know if you get lost,
how sad your parents would be?
Has Vice Magistrate Cao been anywhere recently?
For a round trip in a single day,
Niutou Mountain is the only place nearby.
Why would anyone go to Niutou Mountain alone?
I have something to do. I'm heading out.
Didn't you just get back?
Come back soon.
Constable Qin,
today was supposed to be a day off.
I already told my family I'd spend time with them.
So I won't go with you.
Come back early, Constable Qin.
Sister-in-law, let's eat.
Be careful.
Mr. Su.
How is the map marked?
There are no special marks.
It's just that this kid
came down from the west side of Niutou Mountain.
The west side of Niutou Mountain.
Isn't that where the glazed orb and bones were found?
You mean
when this child came down the mountain,
he witnessed a murder.
But before he could say it,
he was... Cao Wen told me
after Cao Shi died,
Constable Qin met Madam Cao.
Constable Qin always felt there were suspicious points about Cao Shi's death.
Madam Cao then told him
that Cao Shi did go to Niutou Mountain alone.
Later,
when Constable Qin looked at those map markings again,
he thought of that child from back then
who might have witnessed a murder.
To verify his speculation without any evidence, Constable Qin
came to the west side of Niutou Mountain alone.
He found a patch of freshly turned soil.
He started digging from there
and eventually found Yexiao and the Liuli Pearl.
Having learned the truth, he was immediately ambushed.
His bones were then buried together with the pearl.
So this is how Constable Qin was murdered.
I remember when I was little, you even used a map to teach me,
telling me not to run around.
That day was the Beginning of Spring.
But after the fire at the Qin residence earlier,
the charred corpse belonged to Constable Qin.
No.
It's the murderer's.
How do you know it so well?
Because I am Qin Rui's son,
Qin Nian.
This is terrifying.
Yeah.
During the festival,
such a murder case happened.
Where is Constable Qin?
I don't know.
I guess they'll be here soon.
Stabbed dozens of times.
Every strike hit a vital spot.
The victim was a pharmacy lady.
Why would the suspect be so ruthless?
Who is she to you?
My mother.
Did you see the suspect?
Is there anyone else at home?
You must be hungry. Eat something first.
What's your name?
Jueming.
My mother was a medicine merchant. I was named after cassia seeds,
which means to improve vision.
She gave you this name so you'd be clear-sighted
and insightful.
How old are you?
Seven.
Same as me.
What month were you born?
May.
I was born in November.
Child, from now on,
treat this as your home.
Wan'er is 10. She'll be your older sister.
Niannian is 7. He'll be your younger brother.
Okay?
My mother used to travel a lot.
She always forbade me from leaving the house.
Whenever I missed her, I would look at this portrait.
Now, I will never see her again.
It's okay. From now on,
this is your home.
Tell us whenever you are unhappy.
We will carefully glue your mother's portrait back together.
You can look at it whenever you miss her.
Give the painting to me.
Mother, I'm going out for a bit.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Slow down.
It's mended.
This is the best I can do.
That will be three coins.
Thank you.
Just like that.
That day, after the painting was mended,
I ran all the way back.
But when I returned home,
I saw a scene I will never forget.
Your Honor, the five members of the Qin family,
two adults and two children, are all accounted for.
Once this fire burns,
no one will dare to investigate further.
With you, the numbers add up.
No one knew
that the child who died back then
wasn't Qin Nian.
After that,
I took on Jueming's identity
and survived.