At first, when I told fortunes for people,
business was very bad.
No one believed what I said.
Later, I pretended to be blind and set up a fortune-telling stall.
Business was surprisingly good.
Everyone believed what a blind man said.
They figured, since you're already blind,
you wouldn't lie to me.
Some generous customers
would sometimes give me an extra copper coin or two.
People are really strange,
aren't they?
I make more money with my eyes closed than open.
You kill so cleanly.
The man fell into the water before he could even react.
Even the coroner couldn't find out anything.
You are truly a master.
This is all I have.
Enough.
I'll come back next month.
Didn't you say this was all you wanted?
I mean,
I want this much every month from now on.
Every month.
What else? Did you think I was easy to get rid of?
I'm not blind.
Wait.
I'll give you next month's too.
Don't come back next month.
All right.
Why must I alone drink the bitter wine of this world?
There is one more copy.
Bring it here.
Here.
This is too much.
It's been too long.
It's a bit blurry.
Found it.
Patient Xia Chunyi,
twenty years old,
a native of Luoyang.
She once gave birth to a mentally disabled child
and worries about the health of her future offspring.
She had a child?
I never heard her mention it.
Xia Cai,
male, nearly three years old, from Luoyang.
Mentally deficient
and appears foolish.
Xia Cai.
Ah Cai.
Do you like it, Ah Cai?
This is called a Longevity Pendant.
Your name is engraved on it.
Did the couple ever keep a dog?
Yes, they did have one.
At that time, Xia Zhiming used to complain about buying goat milk for it every day.
He said he'd rather use the money to gamble and win it back.
Where did you take Ah Cai?
Stop pulling me. I sold him.
Sold him?
Where did you sell him?
The ghost market.
Ah Cai!
Miss, have you seen a child this tall named Ah Cai?
I haven't seen him.
Ah Cai!
Sir, have you seen a child?
Sir, have you seen a child about this tall?
Go away!
Acai.
Why did you treat him like this?
He is your own flesh and blood.
He's three years old and still can't speak.
He's a fool.
I lose so much face outside.
When neighbors ask why I buy goat milk,
I can only say I have a dog.
How dare you hit me?
Not only do I dare to hit you,
but I will also report to the authorities.
Let me go. Why report this to the authorities?
Since you like kids so much,
let's have another one, okay?
Let me go.
Let go.
Doesn't murder require a motive?
Losing a dog isn't a reason to kill your husband.
What exactly is the relationship between this fool and Pan Lang?
I asked around.
Pan Lang really did find this fool in the ghost market.
Acai.
The fool is Chunyi's child.
Hey!
Wait for me!
Dad, why is he...
Do you know Master's favorite place to go?
The house full of beautiful ladies.
You always wait at the door.
Master is going to Yichun Pavilion.
Master isn't going to spend money this time.
He is going to ask the proprietress for money.
She gives him whatever food he asks for.
Come inside and have fun.
Come on, it's been a long time.
Come, have a seat, sir.
Pan is my master.
I know the secret of your husband's death.
I saw you kill someone.
If you don't pay me, I'll report to the authorities.
I'll give it.
I'll give it to you.
Acai.
I'm sorry.
This longevity pendant isn't silver.
But he will never snatch it away again.
Really.
Turn around.
I just want you to be healthy,
live a long life,
and stay by my side forever.
Acai.
I will never leave you again.
Wait for me.
Step aside.
Coroner Li.
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
What's going on? What happened?
There are three bodies inside.
Jueming.
Sister, that little fool...
He is the landlady's own flesh and blood.
Please leave us.
I want to be alone with her for a while.
I want to see her.
You're a grown man bullying a child.
Aren't you ashamed?
Why don't you stay here and do odd jobs?
I can't pay you much,
but I can provide food and lodging.
Are you willing?
I'm willing. I'm willing.
Thank you, boss.
Don't call me boss. Call me Sister Chunyi.
Sister Chunyi.
Chunyi.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'm an adult too.
I can help you.
I can.
You are my only family.
I also think of the time
when you saved me,
when you took me to see the stars with you,
when you gave me mustard porridge.
You're so cruel.
Only after I left Yichun Brothel did I realize
that life is about constantly losing
and constantly gaining.
Sister Chunyi, these are all my books.
I didn't expect you to have so many books at such a young age.
Thank you for taking me in, Sister Chunyi,
so I have a place to keep my books.
If I had a child learning from you,
they would surely learn a lot.
Do you have any children, Sister Chunyi?
I just love children.
Whenever I see homeless children, I want to give them a home.
This will be your home from now on.
Sister Chunyi went on a long trip.
Before she left, she specifically told me to take good care of you
and take you to your new home.
Where are we going?
Yeah, where are we going?
From now on, here,
I'll cook for you every day.
What do you like to eat?
Meat. What about you?
Vegetables.
Alright, we have everything.
Look, this is your new home.
- Is this okay, Dad?
- Yes.
Look over there.
That's the bed your sister made for you.
This is the new furniture Uncle Su bought for you.
Come sit.
So pretty.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Catch the thief!
Officer,
are you looking for a gift for your sweetheart?
You can take a look.
I brought all these back from the Western Regions.
They have a unique charm when worn.
Here we also have bracelets and jade.
Officer, you have great taste.
This bracelet is a rare treasure.
Let me help you try it on.
Look.
The craftsmanship of this bracelet is exquisite.
Its luster is soft,
like moonlight.
It's the most suitable gift for a beauty.
If you give it to your sweetheart,
it's guaranteed to make her smile.
I'll take it. Wrap it up.
Okay.
Tanghulu! Fresh tanghulu!
Take care, Officer.
This must be expensive.
As long as you like it.
I can't keep it here.
If my dad finds out...
We can just hide it.
Like this.
There you go.
Honglian,
I want to introduce you to my dad and friends,
and tell them we're together.
Honglian.
I hope you can always be this happy.
I will always protect you.
Hold on tight.
Careful!
If she can't make this dish well,
I'm really going to starve to death.
How many days have I been eating mustard green congee?
If I keep eating it, my face will turn green.
It's already the fifth day.
We've been eating it for five days.
My lady, I believe in you.
You can definitely do it.
Yeah.
Can you two stop arguing?
I want to focus on making this.
I believe I can make
mustard green congee just like the boss lady's.
I think we need to find a way to help her.
My lady, I think it's time to add the mushrooms.
Yes, it's about time to add the ingredients.
First, add some shiitake mushrooms.
The aroma comes right out once you sprinkle them in.
Then add some salt.
Oh no.
I added sugar.
It's fine.
If there's too much sugar, just add some salt
to neutralize it.
Add salt for too much sugar, add sugar for too much salt.
Taste it.
See if it's salty enough.
How is it?
Seems pretty good.
Not bad.
I don't believe it.
I remember Chunyi said this mustard green porridge is delicious.
Thick but not greasy, with distinct grains.
The time and rhythm of stirring are very important.
Keep stirring.
Just keep stirring.
Stir it,
stir it up, stir it up.
Try it.
This is the exact flavor.
It's exactly the same as Sister Chunyi's.
It's a success.
Thanks to you.
Yeah, my handful of sugar
and that handful of salt.
I take credit for it.
Yeah.
Finally, success.
Let's take the mustard green porridge to Jueming.
Okay.
Let's go.
He hasn't gone to the government office or left the house for so many days.
We need to find a way to cheer him up.
You're right.
But Sulang told me
that the proprietress
was his last relative.
Now, it's hard for him to accept it at the moment.
We must let him know
that he is not alone.
Yes.
He still has us.
Oh, kid.
You are writing so seriously.
Uncle An, Sister Jinglan.
Look what delicious food I brought for you.
Mr. Su.
Why are you here?
We brought some mustard green porridge.
Smells so good.
Who made it?
The eldest miss made it.
And your favorite,
shredded pork with green peppers.
Your favorite meat.
And scrambled eggs with yellow chives.
Also your favorite.
I want to eat this.
And some fresh green vegetables.
Your favorite.
It smells so good.
I made a lot of mustard green congee.
The folks at Yichun Brothel have already had some.
Sit down. Okay, don't worry.
Sit down, sister.
Thank you.
Eat.
Thank you. Why the long face?
Come on, eat.
Now that Yichun Brothel is managed by Mingzhu,
they still have a place to stay.
Rest assured.
The young lady practiced making this congee for days.
She finally got it right.
Does it taste the same as before?
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Don't be too sad.
If the boss lady is watching from heaven,
she surely wouldn't want you to be so depressed.
If she knew you blame yourself every day,
it would break her heart.
I am not blaming myself.
Such delicious food.
Right?
We all hope you can pull yourself together
and live a good life.
Eat up. Don't you usually smile a lot?
Eat up, eat up.
Okay, let's eat.
Let me get you another bowl of porridge.
By the way, you've already solved five cases for us.
According to the agreement,
this house is yours.
Thank you.
It will be okay.
Let's eat.
Dig in.
It's rare for her ladyship to cook.
Everyone.
I want to introduce someone to you.
She is very special to me.
Her name is Gu Honglian.
She is the one my heart desires.
Really?
You brat, when did this happen?
How come I didn't know?
I'm telling you now, aren't I? It's not too late.
Hello, uncle. Good, good.
Hello there.
This girl is so pretty and delicate.
So wonderful.
How did this boy trick you into being with him?
Su Lang has never tricked me.
He is a man of his word.
What a great day today is.
The Matchmaker has tied so many red strings
to this little courtyard.
So wonderful.
I have no problem with it.
But you need to find time
to take her back for your mother to meet.
My mother will definitely like her.
Right?
Honglian brought you gifts.
Look.
She made these herself.
Wow.
And us.
This is
Uncle.
This is Sulang.
And this is me.
These are Nianxia and Yichun.
This is Sister Jinglan.
And this one?
It's so beautiful.
How about this?
We'll stick these paper cutouts in our courtyard,
so they can keep you company every day. Okay?
Your crossing paths
is all due to fate.
There's one thing I must tell you.
From today on, your investigation squad
must unite,
work closely together,
and maintain the order of Luoyang City.
Okay, Father.
And don't forget what I always say.
Safety comes first.
Solving cases can wait.
Right, that phrase again.