How did you know it was me?
First is the smell.
Remember when we first found Sun Wuwei,
the smell of sesame cakes at his stall?
When we investigated Zhao Xuanli's case together,
the sesame cakes you brought us
had the same smell.
You've known Liu Shiqin since childhood.
When Liu Shiqin was pestered by Sun Wenhuai,
how could you not know his name?
This is the most common wooden box principle in street magic.
There are two layers inside.
The contents are different every time it's opened.
The antique desk you gave me,
its secret compartment
had been tampered with by you long ago.
That day,
using the topic of the strange tales
I found at the ghost market,
you pretended to rummage through the desk.
Taking this opportunity,
you let us find the couplet in the secret compartment.
You deliberately guided us to discuss the couplet,
but you had no idea how we would match the second line.
So,
Su Lang would get to it first.
At that time, I noticed a detail.
Su Lang's handwriting
matched the writing on the couplet.
Then,
under the pretext of Li Jinglan thinking of a better second line,
you opened the hidden compartment again.
I believe
you must have had another piece of rice paper on you at that time.
The couplet was already written on it,
along with the imitation of Sun Wenhuai's handwriting.
What was used here
is the principle of the hidden compartment in the wooden box.
As for the handwriting on the reply letter
that slowly appeared,
that used the silver salt development method.
Using salt water or liquid made from special substances
to write on the paper.
Once it dries,
the writing disappears.
But when baked over a candle,
the writing appears.
This letter,
I believe, was written by Sun Wenhuai himself.
Look closely at the last sentence.
"Su Yu'an
is the culprit who framed me.
I hope the court will investigate clearly."
If it were written to me,
why would he use the word 'court'?
I knew it.
I couldn't hide it from you in the end.
Indeed.
Back then, there was a blood letter
that Sun Wenhuai entrusted someone
to give to the young Sun Wuwei.
Fresh out of the pot.
Here's one for you, and I'll take one to taste.
Are there any hot ones?
The early bird catches the worm.
Get me a hot one.
I want the kind that burns my mouth.
You corrupt official!
You corrupt official! I'll kill you!
Don't do anything rash.
Please don't do anything rash.
Who are you?
I committed perjury back then,
insisting that Sun Wenhuai intentionally harmed Liu Shiqin,
which led to his wrongful imprisonment.
He gave his suicide note to his brother in prison.
However, by the time I saw that note,
Sun Wuwei had already returned from exile.
Do you still remember Sun Wenhuai?
Sun Wenhuai.
If this blood-written letter falls into the hands of the authorities,
I will certainly be dismissed and investigated.
Now,
I know the whole truth.
But I can't decide what to do.
I pleaded with Sun Wuwei to hide the truth for now,
promising to clear Sun Wenhuai's name.
I thought of a way.
Using the principles of street magic,
I made a special wooden table.
While you were moving,
I had Sun Wuwei and Su Lang carve an aged character "Wu,"
putting on a show of sending a message from the afterlife.
Seeing the two of you solve bizarre cases time and again,
I wanted to use your help
to clear Sun Wenhuai's name.
You led us to start from the case files
and find Liu Shiqin's autopsy report.
After following the clues to open the coffin,
the truth of the advisor's death surfaced.
All suspicions unexpectedly point to Chen You, an official.
Court is adjourned.
When the investigation hit a dead end,
you proposed
to look into the people involved
in order to find more clues.
This inspired me.
Seeing there was no hope of reversing the case,
I colluded with the owner of the Antique Shop.
Using Chen You's burning of the desk,
I fabricated the story that Sun Wenhuai escaped to send a letter to Jue Ming,
leading you to the Antique Shop to get the suicide note.
Now that I've said it all,
I feel so much lighter.
It was Jueming's words that reminded me.
If you are solving a case,
and right from the start,
you have a hypothetical suspect,
then all the clues you investigate
will revolve around this idea.
Even the clearest evidence
will be ignored.
You will create a miscarriage of justice.
Lord Li.
Criminal Su Yu'an
has been waiting for you for a long time.
Su Yu'an.
As an official of the Tang Dynasty,
you committed perjury back then.
According to Tang law,
based on the provisions regarding perjury and witness statements,
if false testimony leads to a wrongful conviction,
the punishment shall be reduced by two degrees from the original sentence.
Sun Wenhuai was sentenced to death.
A death sentence reduced by two degrees
means exile for 3,000 miles,
plus three years of hard labor.
My lord.
My father made a mistake in a moment of confusion.
I am willing to make amends for his crime.
Please be lenient, my lord.
Su Lang,
get up.
Father! Father, don't go. Don't go.
It's not like this.
Who is he?
He watched me grow up.
He stayed in the yamen his whole life.
He solved countless cases, big and small.
He has made countless contributions.
Why did this one case
wipe out all his achievements?
But what about the laws of the Tang Dynasty?
Vice Governor Li.
Constable Su turned himself in.
According to Tang Dynasty law,
those who surrender before their crimes are discovered
can be exempted from punishment.
Yes.
Very well.
Get up.
Constable Su.
I,
according to Tang Dynasty law,
will exempt you from all punishments.
But,
this uniform,
you can never wear it again.
I, the culprit Su Yu'an.
Thank you, My Lord.
Get up, Lang'er.
Su Lang.
You've grown up.
I actually wanted to take a break a long time ago.
I can't be a constable anymore.
But my son is still a constable.
You must enforce the law impartially.
Don't bring shame to me.
You always say I'm a glutton,
chewing non-stop every day.
Actually, you know what?
Over the years,
as soon as my mouth stops,
it seems the truth will blurt out.
I am relieved now.
Without me in the future,
maybe
Miss Li, you have to be careful.
No one will help you lie anymore.
From now on,
you must become a good coroner.
Otherwise, you'll have to get married.
Jueming.
Yes.
This place,
I'll leave it to you.
Yes.
This hot pot restaurant is very famous.
Here, try it.
This shop is deep inside Hengmen.
When we came, there were few people around,
but it's crowded at the door.
Did your father bring you here?
You are amazing, Brother Jueming.
The first time my father brought me here
was the day I officially became a constable.
At that time, we said
we would join hands to protect the peace of Luoyang.
Before,
I was always against you.
I'm sorry.
I still remember at first,
seeing you came from the red-light district,
I thought you were just a pretty boy.
Later, I saw you solve cases like a god
and crack bizarre mysteries.
To be honest,
I was quite jealous.
Is this why you treated me to hot pot?
Yesterday,
thanks to your righteous words, Brother Jueming,
begging the Deputy Magistrate for leniency,
my father was spared from punishment.
Your father
is fair and just,
and abides by the law.
He just had a moment of negligence
and made a mistake.
I just did my duty.
Your kindness from yesterday,
I, Su Lang, will keep in my heart.
How will you remember it?
Boss,
bring another plate of meat.
Coming right up.
And a pot of wine.
Eat more.
After eating,
let's head back to the yamen.
There are still many cases.
Since your father left,
all the cases have fallen on me.
You go back first.
I still have some things to do.
These two have started committing crimes again recently.
They don't look like good people. So this is Moya.
Look at the scar on his face.
I heard they are a notorious couple of thieves.
Have you seen this person?
No, I haven't.
Boss, a steamer of buns and a pot of wine.
Okay.
Here are the buns.
Sir, your buns.
Things are so tense right now.
I think
we can't stay in Luoyang anymore.
Here is the wine you ordered. Enjoy.
Okay, thanks.
That female coroner saw your face clearly.
You shouldn't have saved her.
This is a great taboo in our line of work.
If it were me, I would have taken her away.
That way, we wouldn't be exposed.
We were only after the money,
and we never hurt anyone.
But Dad,
she saw your true face.
Why didn't you kill her?
With just the few of them,
do you think they can handle me?
Do you think I'm that easy to catch?
I'm still worried.
The government office is watching us closely now.
How about we leave Luoyang?
In all my life,
I've never been anywhere else.
Besides, we've stolen everything worth stealing in Luoyang.
Why can't we move somewhere else,
buy a big house,
and live a good life?
Do you really want to leave Luoyang that badly?
I just want to live with you, Dad,
and live an ordinary life.
Besides,
the things we've stolen over the years
are enough to last us for several lifetimes.
Are you not planning to retire?
Eat the buns first. They're getting cold.
Please have some tea.
Look at my daughter.
Thank you for being lenient with Constable Su this time.
My daughter,
He was at fault first.
His punishment can be spared,
but his official position
really cannot be kept.
However,
I never expected
you to solve so many cases all at once.
We still have a bet.
Do you mean
you want to admit defeat early?
How is that possible?
The deadline hasn't arrived yet.
Although you're doing very well now,
I will stick it out until the very end.
Alright then.
When I win,
don't regret it.
Come, my daughter.
Sit down first.
Sit down and let me say a few words.
Daughter.
I'm really worried you won't get married.
Think about it.
Which gentleman
would dare to hold hands that touch corpses every day?
Daughter,
listen to me.
Let's quit.
Dad, you dare to touch my hands, don't you?
I... I am your father.
No, Dad. Those gentlemen you introduced,
I don't like them.
I don't want to marry them.
Who do you want to marry then?
You can't stay unmarried for your whole life.
I have my own plans.
I'll go get you some more tea.
Sweetie.
Honglian.
Honglian,
are you there?
Why are you here today?
I didn't put flowers outside.
My father is at home today.
There's a performance by the Lu Troupe later.
It's their final show.
If we don't watch it now, we'll miss it forever.
If my father finds out...
I...
It's fine. We'll just come back early.
It'll be fine. Let's go.
According to the informant,
the fire at the Qin family's house that day
which killed the grandfather, father, mother, second son, and eldest daughter,
was unfortunately
an accident.
Coming.
Bring more! Put out the fire!
Hurry, bring more!
Water is here!
Bring more water!
Hurry, fetch more water!
Coming!
The fire is big here!
Water is here!
Come and help!
Impossible.
This wasn't an accident at all.
This is impossible.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
I saw you were all busy,
so I came to check some old files.
What did you say wasn't an accident?
Look.
The fire at the Qin residence killed five people at once.
When the fire just started,
didn't they have a chance to escape?
That makes sense.
But this is just a theory.
You have no evidence.
Why are you so interested in the Qin family fire case?
I heard Catcher Su talk about Catcher Qin's deeds back then,
so I got curious.
Shouldn't you
go back with your father?
Because I promised Zhen'er
to accompany her to watch the Lu Troupe's performance.
I heard this is their last time.
They won't perform anymore after this.
Come with me.
I still have a lot of case files here.
Let's go. I...
Shopkeeper, pack these up and send them to the Guan residence.
Did Master Guan get married again?
This is for the Guan family's little granddaughter.
Master Guan has a granddaughter?
Don't ask too many questions.
Pack this up too.
Thank you.
The Guan family
is quite rich.
Wow, how scary.
Aren't you scared?
Hold this for her.
Let's go look around over there.
Look here.
Look at this.
Do you like anything?
You have good taste, Miss.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's starting.
The performance by the Lu Troupe
is about to begin!
I'll take this first.
Catch it. Alright.
Everyone, don't miss out as you walk by!
Excuse me.
Thanks.
Here.
Thank you all for your support.
Next, my older brother
will perform the fire pot show for you.
Great!
This is the final performance.
This is the Lu Troupe's specialty.
Wow, I love watching this.
The Lu Troupe is good at this.
Look.
Coming here today was the right choice.
Bravo!
Encore!
How dare you!
Tricking an innocent girl
into coming out to have fun with you.
Dad, I wanted to come out and watch it myself.
You're actually doing that money-losing business.
And you,
what do you think you are?
A petty constable.
Stay away from my daughter.
Get lost!
No.
I'll go.
Let me tell you, with your meager wages,
trying to trick my Honglian,
no way!
Go back.
Encore!
Encore! Look how high the flames are.
Great!
Mind your status.
Her dad is shortsighted.
You are so young,
with a bright future ahead.
You can definitely win her back.
Make him regret it.
Listen to me.
Jinglan is over there.
Great!
What's wrong?
Encore!
Come on, another one!
Was the previous show exciting?
Exciting!
Then, the excitement continues.
Next, our little sister
will bring you the next performance.
Please welcome her.
Good.
Ladies and gentlemen,
did you see the fire dragon dancing in the sky just now?
This is a very auspicious sign.
Today, I can grant a wish for someone in the audience.
If anyone has a wish in their heart,
please raise your hand.
Me!
Pick me!
Little girl,
what is your wish?
My mother passed away.
I want to see her again.
That's easy.
Watch closely.
Our departed loved ones become everything in this world.
Your mother has turned into this flower.
Put it by your pillow,
and you can see your mother every morning.
Thank you.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
today is the Lu Troupe's
finale performance.
We are performing here,
thanks to your
great support.
Next is the grand finale.
Please don't blink.
Watch this.
Everyone, watch closely.
Next, I will show you a magic trick.
Please look.
This is now an
empty box.
Sister.
How is this done?
Please look.
Wow.
That's amazing.
Change her back!
Don't panic, everyone.
Now my little sister has turned into a cat.
What's next?
I will turn her back.
The living person illusion!
Watch closely, everyone.
Look.
Little sister!
Father!
So cruel!
A murder has occurred.
Evacuate the crowd.