A mere ant
trying to shake an elephant.
Ridiculous.
I will definitely find you.
Daughter, I...
Daughter,
I have been invited to a literary gathering at Yayuan Villa.
The master of the villa happens to be the youngest son of the former Deputy Magistrate Cao Shi,
Cao Wen.
At this gathering,
this 'Miscellaneous Records'
has been discussed by current scholars.
Some say it has opened up a new literary style,
while others condemn it as intolerably vulgar.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Look, I am tied up with official duties
and cannot go.
You should go on my behalf.
Take the opportunity to meet this Cao Wen.
Since you are a good match,
maybe it could lead to a wonderful marriage.
Your daughter
already has someone in her heart.
Daughter, are you talking about that Buliangren?
Let me tell you,
you are the daughter of the Deputy Magistrate.
Everything must be a good match in social status.
What do his parents do?
As the saying goes, like father, like son.
What if he... Okay, okay, Father.
Autopsies are my job,
and you want to interfere.
You also want to get involved in my marriage.
In this huge city of Luoyang,
there are so many things waiting for you to handle.
Please spare me.
In this huge city of Luoyang,
in my heart,
you are my greatest treasure.
Okay, I am your treasure.
I am your little treasure.
I am your big treasure.
Master.
Young Master Xu, son of Deputy Magistrate Xu of Chang'an, is here.
He says he came specifically to see our young lady.
Look, I'm getting old and forgetful.
How could I forget about Young Master Xu?
His father is the current Deputy Magistrate of Jingzhao.
Now that's what I call a good match.
Quick, invite him to the main hall.
Yes, Master.
I'll accept this invitation.
No time to lose, let's go now.
Daughter!
I'm off, Father!
You're making me work for nothing again!
Oh, you!
This invitation is for Commissioner Li.
It doesn't mention me.
My father has official duties,
so he wants us to go in his stead.
I was thinking you haven't been out for days,
so we might as well go together to relax.
It's fine.
I won't go this time.
I still have to sweep Sister Chunyi's grave.
If you go, be careful on the way.
We agreed. Why are you so slow to react?
Oops, I didn't react in time.
I didn't react in time either.
Why haven't you two left yet?
This villa is on the mountain and you have to cross the river.
If you are late, there will be no boat at the ferry.
Kids,
look what delicious food I brought.
Come here.
I'm telling you,
only scholars and literati are going this time.
The host of this poetry gathering is Cao Wen.
He is the son of the former Vice Governor Cao.
He is just 16 years old this year,
but he is already an excellent writer.
By the way, brat.
Talk less when you get there.
Don't make a fool of yourself
and become a laughingstock.
I have good literary talent too, Dad.
Mr. Su.
Yes.
Is this Cao Wen the son of the former Henan Vice Governor Cao Shi?
Exactly.
When Head Constable Qin solved the case of Vice Governor Cao,
he was still in his mother's womb.
I can't believe he is already 16.
And he's become a great scholar.
You should go to the elegant gathering early this time.
Once you get there,
you'll definitely experience their poetic sentiment and grace.
Talking more with these scholars and poets,
regarding your future literary attainments,
will definitely be of great benefit.
Could that fire back then
be connected to Vice Magistrate Cao's case?
Since Cao Wen is so talented,
I actually want to go and see.
Really? There you go again.
We have no time to lose.
Let's set off immediately.
You two must listen to Mr. Su.
I'll give you some candy when I get back.
Okay, got it.
Good kids. Hurry up, let's go.
Remember to practice your handwriting!
Alright, you may go.
Leave things here to me.
Mr. Su, we'll leave it to you.
Okay. Eat up.
I'm coming.
Be careful.
Come, Sister.
I am Li Jinglan, daughter of Vice Governor Li Ze.
This is our invitation.
These two are my close friends.
So it's Miss Li Jinglan, daughter of Vice Governor Li.
I will arrange someone to guide you right away.
Thank you.
I am Liu Renjiu.
I will guide you three distinguished guests to the villa to eat and rest.
The villa is located at the top of the mountain.
This is the only mountain road from the ferry crossing to the villa.
Please walk slowly, you three.
Thank you for your trouble.
After you.
Please.
This way.
I never tire of gazing at the green hills.
The flowing water holds endless charm.
The ancient temple bell echoes from afar.
The moon reflects coldly in the deep pool.
Oh.
The emerald ridges have boundless rhythm.
The clear breeze blows without end.
Birds chirp loudly in the secluded forest.
A waterfall flows fragrantly in the deep valley.
Mr. Lu,
what do you think?
The one in the green shirt on the left is Lu Yun, Vice Director of the Ministry of Rites.
His uncle was once the Minister of Revenue.
Mr. Lu is skilled at literary criticism.
He holds a position of the secondary sixth rank.
The one in the gray gown is Dong Tu, a compiler at Moxiang Bookstore.
Mr. Cao's book is printed by this bookstore.
This way.
The north wing is for the ladies.
The West and South wings are on the other side,
where the gentlemen can rest.
I shall show you two the way.
It's so far away.
Are there any other arrangements for today?
If you don't want to rest,
my lady has specifically ordered
that you can go to the main hall
to express yourselves,
drink wine, compose poems,
talk about everything,
and enjoy the fun together.
A grand banquet will be ready at noon.
Tomorrow morning, we will see you off.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Then let me rest for a moment.
I'll see you in the main hall.
Okay.
Please. Let's go.
You two, come with me.
Go ahead.
This way.
What a fragrant sweet wine.
You are indeed an expert, sir.
This wine is a carefully brewed rice wine.
It has the sweet aroma of fermented grain,
which slowly diffuses in the breeze.
Here you are, you two.
Thank you.
The temperature and time of this wine are just right.
The scenery outside the window remains the same.
No wonder people say
Yayuanju is a paradise.
Thank you for your praise, sir.
I thank you on behalf of the owner.
Please, this way.
Little constable,
you want to trick my Honglian?
No way.
Who lives in the East Wing?
Mrs. Cao and Young Master Cao live there.
Come, brother.
Please.
Madam, the guests have arrived.
Mrs. Cao, I am Li Jinglan.
My father, Li Ze, has official business,
so he sent me to visit.
I want to appreciate the great works at this gathering
to improve myself.
I've heard Miss Li rarely visits here
and has a generous and righteous nature.
It is my honor
that you could come today.
May I ask who the two behind you are?
These are my friends,
Constable Su and Envoy Jueming.
Since they are your friends,
please take the seats of honor, all three of you.
Our banquet is about to begin.
Thank you.
Please.
Honored guests,
thank you for coming to the manor.
I invited you all here today
because my son has published a new collection of writings.
For my son's book to be published,
I truly must thank Yuan Zheng, the owner of Moxiang Bookstore.
Mr. Yuan's Moxiang Bookstore printed the collection for my son,
and deserves much credit.
You flatter me, Madam.
How could I claim the credit?
It's truly because your son is exceptionally talented,
writing as if guided by the gods.
Compiler Dong Tu and I...
I just put in a little effort
and did some organizing
so this masterpiece could be published.
It was my duty.
Not worth mentioning.
Jueming.
You said you met him before.
When was that?
He was the one who took Honglian away during the Lu Troupe's performance.
I remember now.
Honglian's father.
Why is he here?
He's not very educated.
My son's new book has been published.
I wonder if you have read it.
He is still young.
I hope you can give him some advice.
I think the novel style of this book
is amazing.
It's a big breakthrough.
In the vast sea of literature,
he has opened a path that no one has ever walked before.
Brother Caowen is truly a genius.
I don't think so.
This book is terrible.
It has no structure.
The content is absurd
and harbors malicious intent.
It is alarming
and truly not a good book.
Please. Absurd.
A book's merit lies not in its form, but its substance.
If the story is interesting and the words are meaningful,
it is a good book.
Calling it terrifying or unorganized
is merely a narrow-minded view.
Scholar Jiang makes sense.
Very reasonable.
Scholar Jiang, please sit.
This is Jiang Shan, a scholar of Jixian Academy,
a subordinate fifth-rank official.
If any refined scholar wishes to write a book,
they all must seek his help.
I poured my heart and soul into this book.
I am fortunate that you elders have taken the time to come today.
I sincerely hope to exchange ideas with you all,
and listen to your brilliant views.
It is truly my life's honor.
Mr. Cao.
I am just speaking my mind.
Please forgive me.
It doesn't matter.
Since it is a discussion,
I would like to seek some advice from Mr. Cao.
Everything written in this book is about palace secrets.
It is hard to fathom without personal experience.
You are still young.
How could you have such a writing style?
I...
It's just that...
I told him the fantasies and anecdotes I heard.
He mixed them together with a bit of his talent,
and wrote this collection.
So it was the Madam's guidance
that led to such a masterpiece.
Extraordinary. Truly extraordinary.
Just treat it as a pastime after a meal.
Everyone, please enjoy the food and drinks.
Come.
I offer a toast to everyone.
Let's drink this cup together.
Come, let's drink this cup together.
There's really no such thing as a free lunch in this world.
Who would have thought that after the meal,
Mrs. Cao would make each of us write a postscript
about how exquisite this book is?
This book is so thick.
If we don't finish writing, we won't be able to go back tomorrow.
If you want to write a postscript,
you don't necessarily have to read the book.
Why?
Mrs. Cao
just hopes everyone will put in a good word
to make her son's book sell better.
This way, her son's reputation will grow bigger and bigger.
As to whether you've read the book,
she doesn't care at all.
You just need to say a few nice words,
and she'll be fully satisfied.
I see.
Then I can get some sleep tonight.
Don't copy everything from me.
Think for yourself.
I'm just using it for reference. Honestly.
Someone is dead!
Help!
Someone come quickly. There's a dead body.
Someone is dead.
It wasn't me.
Someone is dead. It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
You can see the body now.
Mhm.
Lock down the entire villa immediately.
No one is allowed to leave.
Lock down all exits of the villa immediately. Okay.
Hurry up.
'The Plot of False Pregnancy' Chapter One.
During the Tianbao era of the Tang Dynasty, Daming Palace stood in Chang'an.
I told you to accompany Consort Xian for a walk.
Look at what you did.
You actually let her fall.
What use are you to me? What use?
Madam.
Get out!
Madam,
we couldn't save the baby.
This is royal blood.
How could you not save it?
How could it not be saved?
It's too late.
Stop.
This child is of utmost importance.
Don't act recklessly.
Report it truthfully to the Emperor.
Do you still remember the joy we shared in bed?
If you can work with me to keep this a secret,
when my daughter relies on the royal child,
bringing honor upon herself
and prosperity to our family,
our secret affection
will surely bring you endless wealth and glory in the future.
But if you betray me,
once our shameful affair in the palace
is exposed,
these palace walls
will be our burial place.
Dr. Sun told the Emperor
that Consort Xian's pulse is normal
and it's highly likely a boy.
The Emperor was so pleased
that he went to see Consort Xian.
Consort Xian hid a pillow under her dress
and faked her pregnancy, deceiving the Emperor.
This act of deceiving the emperor became increasingly severe.
Consort Zhao's mother came up with a plan.
She asked Eunuch Chen to find four pregnant women,
under the pretext of embroidering at home,
and kept them confined all day.
Are you also here to embroider?
Yes, the pay is good.
And they don't mind our inconvenience in moving around.
You just need to sit and embroider.
There's no need to walk around.
If you embroider the Phoenix Singing pattern,
and it gets selected,
you will be rewarded with another five strings of coins.
Really?
Ever since these pregnant women entered the palace,
they have never been able to leave.
They can only write letters to their families to let them know they are safe.
Please make sure to tell my husband
to take good care of himself.
Thank you for your trouble.
Please make sure this gets into my husband's hands.
Push hard!
It's coming out soon.
Hurry, push hard.
Why hasn't she come out yet?
The baby is born!
Great! Let's go see her.
Did she give birth?
We all want to come see her.
Today is a great day.
She just gave birth.
She is not feeling well.
Alright then.
We'll come back later. Let's go.
She is going home soon.
After all, she just gave birth. It's inappropriate for her to do these chores.
Did she finish her work?
No.
But my master is kind.
He still gave her three strings of coins
for good luck.
Did she have a boy or a girl?
A girl.
A girl. A girl is great.
I also want to have a baby girl. Yes.
How did you deal with those people?
I have already buried them.
Keep a close eye on these people.
You must have a son.
As for the rest,
I will handle it all.
Why is this book here?
Mother.
Young Master. Young Master.
Young Master.
Don't ruin the scene. Calm down.
What are you going to do?
Autopsy.
Mother.
Mr. Cao.
Lord Li's daughter is a coroner.
She likes to study corpses all day.
Let her examine it.
The nail pierced through the palm.
There is obvious bruising and laceration around the wound.
But this is not a fatal injury.
It only causes the victim immense pain.
The cuts on her face are uneven,
likely caused by a broad-bladed sharp weapon,
and made after death.
The strangulation mark on her neck is purplish-black
with obvious surface peeling and bruising.
Judging from its width and depth,
the fatal wound should be caused by a thick hemp rope.
After death, a dagger was plunged into her chest.
Time of death is within half an hour.
Half an hour?
We were all drinking just now.
We didn't leave.
The suspect strangled Madam Cao to death here first.
then dragged all the way to the wall.
After that, the killer pinned Madam Cao against the wall with their body
and nailed her into the wall.
Given the height and strength required,
the suspect is a male.
Who... who could be so cruel,
murdering my mother and torturing her like this?
You were the first to find Madam Cao's body.
Don't you stay in the west wing?
Why were you in the backyard?
You were the first to find her dead!
He still has my mother's blood on his hands!
My mother refused to fund you,
so you killed her in a fit of anger!
You are the murderer!
Calm down.
The authorities will find out the truth.
You can't say that.
We are relatives after all.
You're wronging me by saying that.
What relative?
This man is a distant relative from her maiden family.
The relationship is so distant, it's almost nonexistent.
He visited my mother before the banquet
to ask for a job,
even offering his young daughter to be my concubine.
What?
Listen to me.
I was indeed here to give Madam a gift.
Somebody!
Although he is obnoxious,
he shouldn't be the suspect.
That still doesn't prove he's not the killer.
For now,
he is still the prime suspect.
Jiang, you can't just say things like that.
Mr. Jiang.
I can prove he's not the killer.
Let's hear it.
From the bloody footprints on the ground, we can see that
when the witness came to the backyard and approached Madam Cao,
his foot had already stepped on the blood.
When he saw the body clearly,
he fell to the ground in shock,
leaving this footprint with the toe pointing outward.
But this is completely different from the footprint of the killer
who approached quietly and escaped safely after the crime.
By comparing the shapes of the footprints,
it can be confirmed that they are not from the same person.
This person's footprint matches this one perfectly.
He is the first witness who left such a unique footprint,
not the careful and orderly killer.
Young Master, did you hear that?
I was wronged! I am not the killer!
I am not the killer!
If it wasn't you, who else could it be?
Wait.
Where is Master Yuan?
No.
Just now at the banquet,
he got drunk.
Brother Yuan, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Brother Yuan is truly a passionate man.
Let me sober up,
then I'll drink to my heart's content with Brother Jiang.
Okay.
Be careful.
Be careful. Then I'll go inside first.
I'll go inside first.
Alright, Brother Yuan, be careful.
When I returned to my room,
Master Yuan was gone.
I thought
he was chatting about poetry with you, Scholar Jiang.
Yeah, then where did he go?
That I don't know.
See? I told you.
Everyone, listen to me.
Constable Su,
search every inch of this mansion carefully
to find Master Yuan's whereabouts.
Alright.
Coroner Li,
take some men and carry Madam Cao's body back to the guest room.
Settle her properly.
Alright.
Everyone else, come back to the inner hall with me.
You all must prove your innocence.
Answer truthfully:
what did each of you do after returning to your rooms,
and who can vouch for you?
I was in the inner hall keeping the guests company from beginning to end.
During that time, my mother suddenly said she had to leave. I drank too much and was drunk.
I stayed until the last guest left. Scholar Jiang and I both stayed in single rooms.
Before going to sleep, I saw the candlelight flickering in the room opposite, and then with the steward's help,
he was writing furiously. I just returned to my guest room.
So I went over the commentary I needed to write
for the anthology. I then pointed to the backyard.
I was in the same room with Constable Su.
After returning to our room,
we were both writing reviews.
Suddenly, we heard a scream outside.
So we went out to check.
We hadn't been anywhere else before that.
Brother Jueming.
We found Master Yuan's body in the Zangge Room.
What's wrong now?