Old Chen, you've got sharp eyes.
Bi Huaqiang.
Don't move.
Uncle Min, didn't we
have an agreement?
I wasn't finished talking, you know.
We can't damage the relics.
If there really are Jueda ruins below,
one swing of your ice pick...
Forget about how loud it'd be,
or if it'd trigger an avalanche.
It's on you if ice smashes the relics.
Then what do you suggest?
This is an ice-melting agent.
Ginger juice.
This stuff
can melt through any thickness of ice.
Don't rush, just wait a moment.
That should be about right.
It's open.
Xiao Qi.
You stay up here.
Okay.
Old Lu.
You take care of An Xiang.
Fatty.
Don't worry, I've got Officer He.
Get lost.
Come down with me.
Look.
So many stone statues here.
But these statues
all seem to face the same direction.
Fatty.
There's actually something here.
Looks like a pagoda.
Beautiful.
What is it?
Let me see.
There are paintings inside.
Come over and take a look.
In these paintings,
the pagoda has nine tiers.
Not three.
Three inner and three outer layers, right?
Add them up, doesn't that make nine?
I get it now.
What?
If that pagoda
symbolizes the Nine-Tiered Pagoda,
then the direction these statues face
should be where the Nine-Tiered Pagoda is.
Which way is it?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
What happened?
There seems to be something below.
Where?
It looks like a snake.
A snake?
Auntie He, Auntie He!
Auntie He!
This is the legendary
fire that can burn souls
to ashes,
the Boundless Karmic Flame.
Auntie He!
Ling La, Auntie He!
Ling La!
What's wrong with you?
If you keep shouting like this,
and it triggers an avalanche,
we'll all be buried with her.
Shut up!
I say we really can't go any further.
Forget about the avalanche.
A life is at stake.
We have to head back now.
Take her back for emergency care.
That's right.
Mission aborted. We're heading back.
Wait.
Let's go, let's go.
Godfather.
Godfather!
Bi Huaqiang, move aside.
What about Godfather?
It's okay, it's okay.
We're home now.
I'm right here.
The pain will stop soon.
Now it won't hurt anymore.
You won't suffer anymore.
Wait...
Are you out of your mind?
She's your wife!
How could you do this to her?
You... you... you...
You actually killed her!
Brother Chen.
Ling La...
There was no way to save her anyway.
If I hadn't done this,
everything we've worked for
would have been for nothing.
If she'd kept screaming like that,
all of us would've died here.
What I did
was for everyone's sake.
Ling La...
died pursuing the faith of civilization.
Her death was worth it.
I think this bastard's lost it.
He's a damn murderer!
The terrain here is dangerous.
Let's talk once we reach safety.
Brother Chen.
Miss He is right.
The mission cannot be canceled.
Who would've thought, beneath this ice,
there'd be such a vicious trap.
Under the ice must be a sealed chamber.
It holds a large amount of secret potion.
Years of being completely sealed off
let the potion fuse with the trapped air,
forming a special kind of gas.
The moment the ice breaks open,
it ignites and burns.
So what happened?
They went and buried He Ling La.
That old guy's quite the actor.
The way he cried,
you'd think he wasn't the one who killed her.
That's a human life, you know!
Let me tell you,
these people are bad news.
If we keep going with them,
who knows what'll happen.
We can't travel with them anymore.
What do you guys think?
It's more than just not going with them.
This is a matter of right and wrong.
He killed someone.
We've got to report it to the police.
Yes, yes, yes.
Call the police! Call the police!
Here's what we do, let...
Let Brother Xiao Qi keep an eye on them.
We four will go report it in the county.
No way.
We can't leave Xiao Qi here alone.
They probably aren't fast asleep yet.
Let's wait a bit.
At 4 AM, we'll quietly make our move.
We grab Xiao Qi and then go report it.
Good, good, good.
Commander Chen, what do you think?
I'll go with the Chief of Staff.
All right.
I'll go find Xiao Qi now.
Okay.
Old Lu, Officer He.
You two pack up the gear.
So it'll be easy when we leave.
I... I'll catch some sleep. Wake me then.
Fatty.
Four o'clock.
You loser!
Brother Lu, it's you.
Still up, huh?
Let me tell you something.
This world is a messy place.
A lot of people are ruthless.
You're still naive.
You've got a bright future ahead.
You need to stay on the right path.
Hold on, Brother Lu.
The right...
If you've got something to say, just say it.
Go ahead, spit it out.
All right, I'll be blunt then.
That godfather of yours...
he's a nasty piece of work.
I'm telling you,
you'd better watch yourself.
What my godfather did to Auntie He,
he had no choice.
No choice, my foot.
Just look at that face of his.
Looks like a vicious demon.
Full of wicked schemes.
If he dared to kill that He woman,
he'd kill you the next day.
Look,
let me lay it out straight for you.
Anyway, we're...
making a run for it.
Tomorrow morning at four.
That's when we bolt.
If you wanna come with us,
be waiting right here at four.
If you don't wanna come,
then forget it.
Four o'clock.
Four.
Got it?
Let's go.
Move.
Commander Chen, please pick up the pace.
Go, go, go.
Hey, hey, don't push me!
So early?
Up this early, are you?
Brother Chen,
fully armed in the dead of night,
where do you think you're going?
Xiao Qi, what's this about?
I do what I'm paid for.
What's this little act you're putting on?
Honestly,
you and I should be in the same boat,
sharing life and death.
Yet things have come to this.
All this gear here,
I paid for every bit of it.
You wanna leave? Fine.
Put down all my gear.
Then I won't stop you.
You old fart.
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
Taking all our equipment away,
isn't that driving us to a dead end?
You're the ones who pushed me to this.
You...
All right, all right, enough.
Fine.
I'll take you all along.
Brother Chen,
you and I are tied to the same rope.
You can't get away,
and neither can I.