How did it go today?
I sold a poem here for ten taels of silver.
Let's go drink at Yihongyuan tonight.
Brother, your literary talent is truly extraordinary!
Let's go. We won't stop until we're drunk!
Let's go.
Thank you.
What a waste of a trip.
Not a single decent poem.
Just a bunch of freeloaders.
I wasted the name Top Scholar Pavilion on this place.
Your Maj...
Master.
Great poetry is rare to come by.
Let's come back another day.
I'm not coming back. Let's go.
Who are you?
Why are you blocking our way?
Don't be nervous.
I'm not a bad guy.
Are you two looking to buy poetry?
Looking at you,
you seem like a down-and-out scholar.
What,
got poems to sell?
I'm skilled in all forms of poetry.
Just tell me what you'd like.
If you're not satisfied,
no charge.
Young as you are,
you sure talk big.
Like I said,
no charge if you're not happy.
Why not buy one first to try?
Buy more only if you like it.
When it comes to business,
I'm all about being fair and square.
Fair to everyone, young and old.
Try it?
Poetry isn't exactly food.
How can you taste that stuff?
You don't exactly look like a refined scholar.
One look and I can tell, you're a swindler.
Let's go, Master.
Let's head home.
Who says I'm a swindler?
I'm telling you,
I'll soon shake the literary world.
My poems will be worth a fortune.
If you don't buy now,
you'll regret it later.
Shake the literary world?
You're killing m...
You crack me up.
Looking all sissy like that,
do you even know poetry?
Who are you talking about?
Who are you calling sissy?
Who's a sissy?
I'm plenty manly!
Whoa.
He's not really a eunuch, is he?
Traveling around with a eunuch...
Then his master
must be royalty?
Give it back.
If you don't believe me,
go ahead and test me.
Alright, alright.
Interesting.
I've got nothing to do today anyway.
Let's give your poems a taste.
Please.
How about a white goose
as the topic?
Goose, goose, goose,
bending its neck, singing to the sky.
White feathers float on green water,
red feet stir the clear waves.
Rooster, rooster, rooster,
crowing at the sun.
Red crest atop his head,
yellow feet thin and long.
"Emperor thin and long"?
You're quite good at drawing parallels.
You, you...
That poem you just recited,
though lacking deep meaning,
wins by being catchy.
And it suits the scene perfectly.
Great for teaching children.
This Master truly knows quality.
Unlike some others.
Alright.
I'll buy this poem.
How much?
Finally, my first sale!
One tael isn't too much, right?
A hundred taels? Why not just rob me?
It's worth it.
A hundred taels it is.
This uncle truly has
a keen eye for gems
and taste finer than a jade lute
That line's quite good too
Add fifty more
With 150 taels in hand,
I can solve Xiao Mei's pressing matter.
This lad does have some real talent.
Let me test him further.
Come, young friend,
let's sit down and chat.
Alright.
Uncle,
winter's almost here,
and look at me,
still wearing thin clothes.
To be honest with you,
my whole family
is all dead and gone.
Only me and my little maid are left,
the two of us depending on each other.
We
haven't had a proper meal
in several days now.
Eat whatever you want, don't hold back.
Don't mind if I do, Uncle.
Yes, yes, don't be shy.
Eat, eat.
Eat.
Eat, eat, eat.
Slow, slow down.
Slow down.
Don't choke.
Yes, sir.
Young friend,
seeing you compose poems on the spot,
your talent must be extraordinary.
May I ask your name
and where you live?
My name is
Lan Xing.
Looks like I can't return to Lan Xing.
Let this be a tribute to my old home.
Lan Xing.
Is there a Lan family in the capital?
This lad probably isn't telling the truth.
And what is your name, Uncle?
Where do you reside?
I am
Tian Xuan.
"Heaven is dark, Earth is yellow"—
You claim two of those characters.
What a fine name.
Anyone with such a name
must be a person of high status.
If I can connect with him,
from now on
I'll never worry about earning silver again.
Didn't you say you're a master of all poetry?
Come on, give me a few more.
Don't be in such a hurry.
You haven't paid for the last one yet.
We'll talk about the rest after.
Here, here.
Uncle, you're truly my savior.
My admiration for you, Uncle,
is like a mighty river,
flowing without end.
Alright, alright.
So what other poems do you have to sell me?
Oh, I've got plenty.
Whatever kind of poem you want, Uncle,
I've got it.
Li Bai, Du Fu, Wang Anshi.
A hundred taels a poem, a real bargain.
Cows are flying in the sky,
and you're down here blowing the hot air.
When it comes to bragging on the ground,
I must admit defeat.
Bring it on.
True gold fears no fire.
Recently, our nation suffered losses at the frontier.
The enemy state even sent
the nanmu wood used to build their capital's pavilions
all the way to our capital.
As a subtle taunt:
one day, they'll trample over Da Xuan.
Many of our generals are filled with resentment.
Lan Xing,
let's take the frontier as the theme.
How about composing a poem?
Stumped now, aren't you?
Slap in the face, huh?
Which eye saw me getting slapped?
Just spit out a poem then.
You look like you're not even of age yet,
unaware of the battlefield's perils.
This topic is genuinely a bit difficult.
No harm in giving it some thought.
Got it.
A barbarian flask hangs at his arm,
his steed a fine purple stallion.
West of Suiye City,
the autumn moon hangs round.
By imperial decree, swift as stars,
the precious sword is bestowed.
Leaving His Majesty for one night,
to conquer Loulan.