Wasn't I on a mission at the border?
What is this?
I've transmigrated.
The original host, Ning Chen.
At twelve, his mother died,
and he was left on the streets.
His birth father, Ning Ziming,
concerned about his own reputation,
brought this illegitimate son back to Ning Manor.
For these eight years,
Ning Chen was humiliated at every turn.
Young Master.
He lived in constant fear.
Xiao Mei.
Only the fourth-rank maid Xiao Mei,
who served him from the start,
stayed close by his side,
never abandoning him.
I've transmigrated and become
Ning Chen, illegitimate son of Da Xuan's Minister of Rites.
Second Young Master, Third Young Master.
The Fourth Young Master just woke up.
Whatever the matter is,
perhaps it can wait until tomorrow.
Get lost.
Ning Manor only has three young masters.
Where did this fourth one come from?
Have you forgotten who your master is?
Third Brother.
Throw him out!
You can't!
Get up.
Move.
Let go of me!
Fourth Young Master!
If you want to drive me out,
bring Ning Ziming here.
Who do you think you are?
You're not worthy of seeing Father.
After all these years,
has he ever cared about you?
Nobody move!
Ning Chen, what are you doing?
This bastard!
Just try touching my Second Brother.
You asked for it.
So I will.
I...
You shut your mouth!
Young Master, you must not!
Why the hell not?
Today I'm taking their lives.
Since my life is worthless anyway,
dragging him down with me
makes it worth it.
Could this serious illness
have completely changed his temperament?
Fourth Brother.
Whatever it is, let's talk it out.
Don't do anything rash.
Let's talk calmly.
All of you, get the hell out!
You bastard!
Since when do you give orders in Ning Manor?
I...
Hurry, go!
Go, go, go!
You just wait.
Hurry up!
Move, move, move!
Quick, quick, quick!
Xiao Mei.
Go get a rope.
Tie him up.
To hell with you!
You miserable cur! Young Master!
You just wait!
Young Master.
This body is far too weak.
That outburst just now in the heat of the moment
drained every bit of my strength.
What do I do now?
Since things have come to this,
I might as well blow it wide open.
Mother!
What happened now? Help me, Mother!
Ning Chen.
That bastard Ning Chen has gone mad!
He is trying to kill your son!
Mother!
Look here.
And here too.
Xing'er, does it hurt?
It hurts.
That bastard has some nerve.
Where is he?
He is in the woodshed.
Servants!
Follow me to the back courtyard.
My son, you have worked hard.
These past few days,
how did the Imperial Examination go?
With my own abilities
and Father's and Grandfather's arrangements,
Zhuangyuan aside,
Bangyan or Tanhua, for me,
would be a breeze.
Excellent, excellent.
You must be exhausted these past days.
I shall have someone stew an old hen
to nourish you properly.
Thank you, Father.
Hurry, go, go!
Running around in a panic. Father,
where are your manners? Eldest Brother,
Third Brother,
what has happened?
You are finally back!
That bastard Ning Chen has gone mad!
He not only injured me
but also tried to kill Second Brother!
Nonsense.
Ning Chen has always been timid.
He dares not even speak loudly in the manor.
How could he commit such violence?
Father, it is absolutely true.
He stabbed Second Brother in the neck!
Blood was all over the floor!
Third Son.
Could there be some misunderstanding?
Where is Ning Chen now?
The woodshed.
That rebellious son.
Come, follow me to see
what on earth he is trying to do.
How dare you!
What are you doing with that tung oil?
Madam.
I am the Matriarch of Ning Manor,
and also your mother.
Why do you not kneel?
Did you not hear Mother speak?
Kneel down at once!
Young Master.
Mother?
My mother died long ago.
No.
Mother, he is insulting you!
Silence!
Truly raised in some wretched backwater.
You understand nothing.
I am the daughter of the Left Chancellor,
the Matriarch of Ning Manor.
For you to call me Mother
would be a blessing from your ancestors.
But clearly your ancestors lacked virtue.
You...
Guards!
Break his legs for me!
Stop right there!
Come at me if you wish to die.
What is going on here?
You have some nerve!
Bastard!
What mischief are you stirring up now?
Father!
He was trying to kill your child!
Look at this!
Fourth Brother,
what do you think you are doing?
Father is here, yet still you dare be so rude?
Have you forgotten
all that I, your elder brother, have taught you?
What have you ever taught me?
And also,
how is it I do not recall
that I even have a father?
You rebellious son!
Do you even know what you are saying?
Two days ago, I was pushed into the lake by scoundrels.
And you, my so-called parents,
showed no concern at all.
Had I been treated sooner,
I would not have fallen so gravely ill.
Fourth son,
this matter of you falling into the lake,
how is it that we knew nothing of it?
Knew nothing?
Truly Mother's three precious darlings.
You cover for her like this
just to keep her from earning
a name for cruelty and malice.
Why has his temperament changed so suddenly?
Father.
Though he is my Fourth Brother,
he twists right and wrong,
framing you and Mother.
He must still be taught a lesson.
Very well, then.
A small punishment as a warning.
Thirty strokes of the cane.
So in your heart I'm only worth thirty strokes?
Why not just burn me to death?
Today I will return my life
to Minister Ning.
I doubt you have the nerve.
Too easy.
Father!
Burn him to death!
Burn him! Burn him!
Come on!
Damn.
You've got to be kidding.
I see now, you wretched boy.
You're acting this crazy
just to get my attention.
The more you do this,
the more I detest you.
Fine.
In that case,
today we sever our family ties.
From this day forward,
we are strangers on separate paths,
never to meet again.
You...
Ning Chen!
You wound me like this
and think you can just walk away?
If you have a problem, come at me!
I...
How crude.
As a Young Master of Ning Manor,
how could I stoop to your level?
However,
after living in Ning Manor all these years,
now that you wish to leave,
we must at least
give you a thorough inspection.
Second Brother is right.
What if this brat is hiding
some of our manor's valuables on him?
Hurry up.
Take off your clothes, piece by piece,
so we can inspect you properly.
Minister Ning,
what is your view on this?
The Master has said
all matters of the manor are mine to manage.
As Matriarch of Ning Manor, I tell you:
You may leave,
but only after stripping bare.
Mother is right.
Once this bastard leaves Ning Manor,
taking his life afterward
will be effortless.
Lord Ning,
it seems being a kept man
isn't so easy after all.
Then open your pathetic eyes and watch closely.
You...
Father!
You wretched...
wretched boy!
I came into Ning Manor alone,
and now I leave with nothing but myself.
But I ask all of you to remember this:
What happened today,
I will repay a hundredfold.