Why is Commander Chen turning off?
What's he up to?
No idea.
Where's he driving off to?
Fatty, Shu Tong.
Don't worry.
I'm meeting a friend.
Tell Uncle Min the plan stays the same.
We meet at Tiger's Mouth River in two days.
Fatty.
Drive carefully.
See you in two days.
Hey, Chen Youxi, hey!
Boss, we lost the rear car.
Fatty.
Why can't I see Brother Chen's car?
Well, well...
Uncle Min, it's nothing.
Just relax.
That Brother Chen is a real ladies' man.
He's got a sweetheart around here.
He took a detour to see her.
But the plan stays the same.
We meet at Tiger's Mouth River in two days.
Don't worry, sir.
Dawang!
Don't run! Stop!
Dawang, if you dare, don't run!
You hurt two of my brothers.
I'm not done with you today.
Go!
Don't run! Stop!
Brother.
You really think highly of me.
Bringing so many men after me.
Cut the crap.
Dawang, you can't escape.
You hurt two of my brothers.
I'm gonna kill you today.
Fine.
You can kill me.
But tell your brothers to fall back.
Don't let them die for nothing.
Brother.
If you're a real man,
let's settle this one-on-one.
What do you say?
Go, quick!
Calling for reinforcements?
Look out!
Come here.
Who are they?
Poachers.
I caught their boss a few days ago.
They're here for revenge.
Isn't that mine?
It's our love token.
Dawang!
You gonna hide in there like a coward?
If you don't come out,
I'll burn you alive!
We can't hold out.
Same as always: one, two, three.
One, two, three!
What the hell?
What "same as always"?
Cover me, cover me!
Why didn't you just say so?
Look out!
Again!
Fall back!
This one's tough.
You just wait.
I'll be back.
Fall back!
Old Chen.
Since we took that photo together,
we haven't had a drink, have we?
A man in uniform really does look sharp.
Out with it.
You came all this way to find me.
There must be something else.
Speak.
I need to go to Mengna Valley.
I've looked through a lot of records.
Mengna Valley has no historical records.
Only your local elders would know about it,
in the Epic of the Enemy-Subduing Lord,
that's where it's recorded.
I figured since you've been here for years,
you might know something
about Mengna Valley.
Legend says
demons are sealed inside Mengna Valley.
Throughout history, many high monks
sought to protect the dharma and slay demons,
to wipe out Mengna Valley,
to stop the evil god from returning.
But
not one of them succeeded.
You're not even afraid of poachers,
yet this nonsense has got you so spooked?
Old Chen,
that's a different matter entirely.
I can't say what might happen
on the way to Mengna Valley.
And I really can't say
if disturbing the ruins of Mengna Valley
might trigger a chain of disasters.
Besides,
Mengna Valley is taboo around here.
My advice is,
you really shouldn't go.
Don't try to talk me out of it.
This is my last archaeological survey.
I've made up my mind. I have to go.
Alright.
When I get back from Mengna Valley,
I'll have a proper drink with you.
Take care of yourself.
What took you so long?
Why haven't you left yet?
Going through hell for a brother,
that's the you I know.
What's in this big bag?
Booze.
Hey, Old Chen's back!
Old Chen's back!
Old Chen, over here, over here!
This way, this way!
Here, here, stop here!
Hey, Commander Chen,
why'd you leave without a word?
Wait...
Dawang?
Old Chen, this is...
Dawang.
An old army brother of mine and Fatty's.
Mr. Da,
it's an honor.
His surname isn't Da.
Look at his physique,
he's tough and straight-up. Over time,
all us brothers just started calling him that.
Get out of here. What brothers?
He's no brother of mine.
I knew Brother Chen would come back.
He went to get us some outside help.
You two have bad blood?
Of course.
Otherwise, would I act like that?
What do you mean?
Back in our army days,
this bastard stole my girl.
You think I could just be all chummy with him?
No way, no way.
Exactly.
The new guy's carrying a weapon.
We need to keep a close eye on him.
Got it.
Once we find the Silver Eye,
if anyone steps out of line,
take them out immediately.
We're almost at Juedabu Cheng.
This is the only way through.
We can't drive any further.
We'll have to continue on foot.
Everyone, watch your step.
The slope is pretty slippery.
One wrong move
and it could trigger a landslide.
Brother Lu, slow down!
Watch your step!
Everyone, be careful while climbing.
If the ground gives way under you
or you slip and fall,
use your trekking pole to anchor yourself
and slow down your descent.
Ms. He,
that ice axe of yours
is meant for snowy mountain falls.
In a place like this,
I don't think it'll work as well.
Lao Lian, are you okay?
Godfather!
Impressive!
Brother Chen and Ms. He, a perfect match.
You two work so well together.
That was eye-opening.
Godfather, you alright? I'm fine, fine.
Let's go.
Glad you're okay.
Made a fool of yourself, huh?
Here, take it.
Shu Tong.
Those two...
Be careful.
This is the place.
It's exactly like the photo
Counselor He showed us.