Tian Qing, don't touch it!
What's wrong?
Tian Qing!
Tian Qing! Tian Qing! Tian Qing!
Tian Qing! Tian Qing!
Buddy, how is he?
These bugs...
Living year-round in such extreme cold,
their genes have mutated.
They must've developed a neurotoxin
to cause something like this.
Godfather!
There's more and more of them!
Old Chen, what do we do?
It's all that old white-haired geezer's fault!
He just had to push the ice wolf and trigger the trap.
Fire!
Old Chen, this thing actually works!
These bugs are scared of fire!
Hurry!
Avalanche!
Hurry, push the lid open!
Come on!
Give me a hand, hurry!
Get down, quick!
Lu, hurry!
Move!
Hurry, hurry!
Get down!
Fatty, down!
Xiao Qi, you go first!
Move!
Brother Chen, hurry!
Pull!
Sure, we survived,
but what do we do now?
There's an avalanche outside.
The way back is blocked.
We'll suffocate in here!
This place is huge.
I refuse to believe we can't find an exit.
Let's get moving.
It's pretty dangerous here.
I agree.
We're about to find the gate of Mengna Valley.
Let's push through in one go!
Adviser He.
These Jueda people really love abyss culture.
Look at how they dug this place out.
So deep,
so cold, so gloomy.
Since the Bingpo Guardian Mountain
guards the gate of Mengna Valley,
then this place
must be the path to the Gate of Cataclysm.
Past the Gate of Cataclysm,
that should be Mengna Valley, right?
It should be.
It must be the capital of Mengna Valley,
called Chiyan Jizhou.
What "Chi"? What "Yan"?
I think
what we should really celebrate
is our spirit of adventure.
For that alone,
Commander Chen owes me a hot pot dinner.
Old Chen, Old Chen, Old Chen! Godfather!
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Chen Youxi!
Don't move! Do you want to die?
Godfather!
What's going on, Old Chen?
What happened?
Xiao Qi is dead.
Xiao Qi.
Looks like...
it's too late.
Listen to me.
I worked for Uncle Min
because he kidnapped my fourth uncle.
He'd already heard Lu tip off An Xiang,
so he had me wait there early
to intercept you.
Dawang got kidnapped?
When did this happen?
The moment you all split up,
he grabbed my fourth uncle.
He threatened me,
saying I had to bring him back safely.
Otherwise...
Otherwise... otherwise...
Hang in there.
Uncle Min...
his eyes...
are the greediest, foulest eyes I've ever seen.
You have to be careful.
Chen... Chen...
Brother Chen...
If that's the case,
then Xiao Qi here
had no choice either.
He's always treated Old Chen like a brother.
Commander Chen.
If you ask me,
we should leave these people here
and let them fend for themselves.
I dare you to try.
Have you all lost your minds?
Is this a mutiny?
Xiao Qi said,
if anything happened to him,
I should listen to you.
I'm a businessman.
Minimizing risk in what I do
can't be wrong, can it?
Holding Dawang
was just to give myself extra insurance.
What's wrong with that?
We agreed to go all the way to Mengna Valley
and find the Lingxiao Pearl, right?
I put up the money, you put in the work.
Fair and square,
isn't it?
Right, right, he paid for it.
The hell it's fair.
Insane.
Fair?
Outside the tent,
when he had a knife, a weapon,
threatening us,
did he say it was fair then?
Right.
So what do you want to do?
We didn't kill Xiao Qi.
You didn't kill Xiao Qi,
but you threatened him
into betraying his friends.
So?
So our contract
doesn't include hurting friends.
From this moment on,
it ends here.
We part ways.
Let's go.
There's only one path in and out.
Talk about going separate ways,
but it's not that easy.
In a little while,
he'll come crawling back to us.
If he dares come,
I won't go easy on him.
Come on, Fatty.
This place is dangerous.
They don't even have weapons to defend themselves.
And there's a young woman with them.
What if, you know...
something happens?
You're just worried about An Xiang.
Then have her come with you.
See if she will.
The way you're talking,
I really don't like it.
You don't like it?
Then deal with it.
If you hadn't tipped An Xiang off,
and let that old fool overhear,
we'd have split up long ago.
Was that really necessary?
Xiao Qi held it in the whole time,
and only told the truth before dying.
Why don't you think about that?
That's all in the past.
Stop bringing it up.
I'm sick of it too.
Just drop it.
Shut your mouth.
I'm sick of hearing you talk.
One bite from a tiny bug can kill you.
Going any further,
we have no way back.
So stop saying things like
you're afraid of being a burden.
Brother Lu!
Wait up!
She's caught up.
Sister Shutong, Brother Chen,
please forgive my godfather.
Everything he's done,
it's all to find Mengna Valley quickly,
and unlock the secret of the Lingxiao Pearl.
Because he really doesn't have much time left.
What? What do you mean?
How is he running out of time?
Brother Chen should know.
The scar on my godfather's back,
it's already spread to his neck,
and all over his arms.
He doesn't have the strength anymore
to do anything else to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm begging you.
I apologize on my godfather's behalf.
Let me tell you,
it's only because we're deep in the wilderness.
If we were out in the world,
no question about it,
he'd be hauled straight to the police station.
He'd have to face legal punishment.
Please forgive my godfather.
All right, all right.
If no one has any objections,
then it's settled.
Go back and get your dad.
Come along with us.
Hurry, go get him.
Really?
Thank you, thank you, Brother Lu.
She got what she wanted.
Aren't you going to check on your father-in-law?
I'm going to scout the path.
So... so petty.
Unbelievable.
Come on, hurry up.
I wanted to tell you,
but so much happened along the way,
I didn't get the chance.
Don't be angry.
I'm not angry.
I just want you to stay alive.
This is truly a wonder of the world.
What... what are all these paintings?
This must be a ceremony of the Jueda people.
They opened the Gate of Cataclysm.
And used these paintings to record their great deeds.
So this is the Gate of Cataclysm.
Lu, I'll go scout ahead.
Keep an eye on him.
Don't let him cause trouble again.
Come on, take a break.
What are you studying?
Look at this painting.
It has four layers.
I have no idea what it means.
So I want to record it.
The first layer...
Why is this woman covering her face?
What does this snake on the second layer mean?
The third layer seems to have been deliberately damaged.
From the outline, it's circular.
Could it be the eyeball pattern?
It's possible.
Is the fourth one a statue or a person?
What do these four pictures mean?
This giant serpent...
I think it's a totem of the Jueda people.
As for this woman and the figure,
it must be a scene from one of their ceremonies.
And this eyeball pattern...
Based on our experiences in Yunling
and Nanyun before,
wherever there's an eyeball pattern,
there's a Lingxiao Pearl.
So I think
we're getting closer and closer to the truth.
How's it going, Old Chen?
Look, look.
Is there a path?
No, no, no path.
And no ice either.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's the one.
This place is lower than the glacier.
So the temperature is suitable.
What's more,
even though we're at the bottom of the abyss,
light still comes through.
So it's no surprise that plants can grow here.
I'm thinking,
could it be this wall?
Let's focus our efforts on this wall.
Maybe it's right behind the wall.
Fatty.
There's no ice over there.
None.
This ice wall extends to the ice beneath our feet.
There's probably an underground river below.
And these plants
mean the ice layer can't be that thick.
We chisel through the ice,
find the underground river below,
and swim under the ice wall along the river.