Chiaki, you like that girl, don't you?
- Like?
- I heard Anna is leaving the group,
so let's do our best, three of us!
I really want to join you, Director.
Ama.
I've always wanted to apologize to you.
Just once, let me talk to you.
Please contact me.
That movie audition was today, right?
I can only really become a character
if I've experienced something similar myself.
Experience it all with me.
Ama.
Go out with me.
But I can't ask that of you,
just so I can act.
It's not about acting.
Huh?
I don't want anyone else to have you.
I want you to be mine.
What?
Is it that surprising?
I mean, we're talking about you and me.
We live in two different worlds.
I like you.
You're kind, straightforward,
and you give it your all.
What do you think of me, Ama?
You're...
You're... a very important mentor to me.
That's it?
Don't hide.
Look at me.
Do you hate me?
So, do you like me?
If that's the case,
how about a trial run?
Until the audition,
just think of it as using me.
Using you?
I'd feel bad.
Don't.
I want to try...
to make you like me.
So...
please.
If you're really okay
with someone like me.
I'm so happy.
Excuse me, Mr. Chiaki?
What?
To be honest, this is my first time
going out with someone.
So, well...
Good.
I'm glad.
Wait.
This is what I think it is, right?
I have to close my eyes.
I'll call you "Ama" from now on.
You call me "Chiaki" too.
Chiaki.
Sorry, on second thoughts, I can't do this!
It's okay. I'll wait until you're ready.
Ama.
Watch your fingers.
Okay.
I've always been scared of falling in love.
Stop!
But...
if it's Mr. Chiaki...
Go out with me.
Here.
Huh?
Don't tell me.
You're serious about her?
You of all people?
I want to cherish her.
Here.
I don't want it.
Huh?
Good for you,
to be able to find someone like that.
I wonder if I'll ever fall in love again.
What happened?
Well...
I ran into a girl I used to like.
Oh.
I forced my number on her, but...
I don't think it's gonna happen.
You're usually more confident.
It's because...
I hurt her.
Senpai, if you're ever struggling,
please don't hesitate to lean on me.
Then...
comfort me.
Stop! Please, stop!
I'm sorry.
That was too much.
Back then,
I was going through a lot.
I wasn't myself.
I mean, that's no excuse, though.
I really regretted it.
What I did was awful.
It's not like you have to give up, right?
Huh?
Just tell her how you feel.
You're better than you were back then, right?
Chiaki!
Stop, you're annoying.
Don't say "annoying". It hurts.
It's an unknown number.
Hurry and answer it.
Yeah.
Hello?
Sorry for calling so late.
It's Minase.
Thank you.
I didn't expect to hear from you.
Kairi-senpai, I'm sorry about the other day.
Don't apologize.
It was all my fault.
Ever since I hurt you,
it's always been weighing on me.
About that,
I'm okay now.
So please, don't worry about it anymore,
Kairi-senpai.
I wanted to tell you that.
Thank you.
But I was so surprised
that you became an actress.
I'm surprised too.
That makes no sense.
I hope we can work on the same set someday.
Me too.
Well, see you.
See you.
Did it go well?
Good for you.
Oh, man.
I really like her.
I really like her!
I told you, you're so annoying.
- I like her!
- You're annoying.
I'm glad we talked things through.
I'll update Mr. Chiaki next time.
[Cast Waiting Room]
I'm scared of the fitness test.
Me too.
A backward jump is crazy.
[Room 205 today]
[Got it! I can't wait!]
Look at this.
- That person is back again.
- Annoying.
I wish Chiaki Hosho would just stop already.
Yeah. He's just a pretty face.
Chiaki Hosho.
How does he get these gigs?
What's this about Chiaki Hosho?
He's so hot!
Nah, you should stay away from him.
Huh?
Why?
He's a scumbag.
Right, Hibiki?
Yeah.
What? Now I'm super curious.
Tell me more.
[Ama Minase]
You've read the script, right?
Yes, of course.
This project has a fairly intense
love scene in the climax.
You're working as an idol too.
Aren't you worried about your public image?
No, I'm fine with it!
I want to work hard as an actress,
so I'll take on any role!
I'll do my best!
I like your enthusiasm.
[Mr. Chiaki]
Wanna come over today?
The audition's over, so I'll head over now.
Welcome.
Ama?
I'm too embarrassed
to invite you to my home now.
Don't say that.
Come in.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Thank you.
It was the final audition, right?
How did it go?
They asked me if I was prepared for it.
Prepared?
The project has a lot of love scenes.
Show me the script.
Sure.
My agency tried to stop me at first.
[A kiss of the nape, overflowing with desire]
But if I get a big role,
it'll open up a lot of opportunities.
I really enjoy acting.
[Kiss her exposed skin]
So I really want to seize this chance.
[Heavy breaths]
I want to give my all
to any role I get from now on.
[Kiss the neckline]
Mr. Chiaki?
I see.
I hope...
that you get the part.
Yeah.
Well, I'll be going.
Okay, good night.
- Hello?
- Director Tanuma, it's been a while.
How have you been?
Actually, there's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
I got the results
for Director Tanuma's audition.
Okay.
Sorry, but you didn't get it.
I see.
But making it to the final round
is a big deal.
Good luck at the next one.
Thank you.
I didn't get the part
in Director Tanuma's movie.
Instead of feeling down,
I have to focus on the work I have now.
Alright!
This is how I feel.
Huh?
You don't get it?
I do.
Your tone says it all.
Let me hear your tone too.
Hey, can I?
- Cut!
- Okay!
That's a wrap! Moving on.
Ms. Minase, your acting was great.
Really?
My heart just skipped a beat.
Oh, I'm glad to hear that.
Thanks for being in this, Hachimura.
Oh, thank you too.
Thank you.
Mr. Chiaki, what's wrong?
I thought you might be feeling down.
That's why you came here?
- Thank...
- Come here.
W-Wait, Mr. Chiaki!
The audition's over.
Huh?
What do you think of me?
You still call me "Mr. Chiaki".
Tell me.
If you don't say it out loud,
I'll get anxious.
I...
That reaction...
Does that mean you like me?
Ama.
Look at me.
I like you,
Chiaki.
Oh, no...
I'm so happy, I might cry.
Promise you'll never stop liking me.
Huh?
I'd never stop liking you.
Never?
You'll always stay by my side?
I'll always be by your side.
Thank you.
It's a promise, okay?
You promised.
Director Tanuma,
there's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
I believe a girl named Ama Minase
is auditioning for your project.
I hear she's actually
not supposed to do love scenes.
Apparently, her agency is forcing her
to do it.
Ama.
I love you.
I love you, I really do.
Don't ever leave me.
Do you have a boyfriend, Ama?
I'm glad to see you.
You look well.
Do you know who her co-star is?
- It's Kairi.
- Stop!
Ama lied to me.