Stop it!
What are you doing?
My lord.
You're finally back.
Ning Chen defied his elders.
And dumped filth all over Gan'er.
Father, Mother is right.
You can't keep favoring Ning Chen.
Chen'er.
Is what they said all true?
Yes, it's true.
But before Lord Ning passes judgment,
shouldn't you find out why this happened?
Ning Gan and Ning Xing trashed my room.
They turned a fine room into a pigsty.
Was I wrong to fight back?
These two unfilial sons!
Why provoke Ning Chen for no reason?
If His Majesty learns of this,
the entire Ning household is doomed.
Kneel.
Hey, Ning Chen,
didn't you hear what Father said?
Get on your knees, now.
I meant you two fools, kneel down!
Father.
We didn't do anything wrong.
That's right, Father.
We truly meant well for Ning Chen.
We brought men to check his room for rats.
I...
You think I don't know?
It's because Ning Chen is now in favor.
So you scheme every way to trip him up.
Can you really not tolerate him?
Ning Ziming!
What on earth are you doing?
Ever since you brought him home,
you've grown harsher toward me and my sons.
Could it be
that you want to drive us away,
so this bastard can inherit our estate?
Shut your mouth!
Foolish woman, what do you know?
Every time I pushed back before,
Ning Ziming would always concede.
Why is he so stubborn this time?
You've got some nerve, Ning Ziming.
Have you forgotten how you rose to power?
Smashing his room is nothing.
Even if I burned it to the ground,
so what?
As long as I'm here,
no one will split this family's fortune.
Wait, you...
Chief Eunuch Quan arrives!
Chief Eunuch Quan, what brings you here?
This guy is the Chief Eunuch?
The head of all eunuchs in the realm.
Then doesn't that mean the old man is...
Hey, kid.
Surprised?
Caught off guard?
Not really that surprised.
Your edict for the Imperial Inspectorate.
I won't bother reading it aloud.
The Imperial Inspectorate?
His Majesty values Ning Chen so highly?
This...
When did this bastard
become this capable?
Chief Eunuch, you arrived at the perfect time.
So that means
I'm now an official of the court.
Though only a Silver Robe,
I'm a genuine court official nonetheless.
So if someone
ransacked a court official's residence,
according to our dynasty's law,
how should they be punished?
By Da Xuan Law,
those who trespass in private homes
and steal others' property
shall receive fifty strokes of the cane,
and be imprisoned for one year.
For severe cases,
they shall be branded as slaves
and exiled three thousand li.
You two young masters,
who gets 50 strokes and a year in prison,
and who gets branded and exiled 3,000 li?
Decide amongst yourselves.
I happen to have a good idea.
You're off to the Imperial Inspectorate,
why not take them along?
I've heard the Imperial Inspectorate's
Zhao Prison is utterly terrifying.
Ghosts of the wrongfully dead linger on.
Often, the wailing of ghosts
when the skies darken
can clearly be heard.
No.
I don't want to go.
Mother, not the Imperial Inspectorate!
Father, Father, save me!
I can't go.
So now you know fear?
What were you thinking causing trouble?
Mother.
I can't go.
The Palace Examination is coming up.
If I go, my official career is finished.
Don't worry.
With your mother here today,
let's see who dares lay a hand on you.
I really did underestimate you.
Sneaking into the Imperial Inspectorate.
Don't you forget,
Gan'er and Xing'er's grandfather
is the current Left Chancellor.
A petty little official like you
trying to throw your weight around?
You're nowhere near worthy.
What did you just say?
Imperial Inspectorate serves His Majesty.
How dare you?
Truly the Left Chancellor's daughter.
What audacity.
But the words you just spoke,
at the very least,
disregard authority and offend the crown.
At worst, that's treason.
Unforgivable.
Punishable by death of nine generations.
And saying this before the wise, valiant,
the brilliant Chief Eunuch Quan?
Chief, you heard every word, didn't you?
Every single word.
Chief Eunuch,
it's a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding. You see,
my wife was just protecting her sons,
and spoke without thinking.
Chen'er,
we're all family.
Why act this way?
Who's your family?
Don't try to claim kinship now.
I'm not part of your nine generations.
Father,
how can he say such treasonous things?
Gan'er.
Look at the mess you've made!
Apologize to Chen'er at once!
What's it gonna be?
Want to rot in prison, is that it?
Ning Ziming,
you shut your mouth too.
Defying imperial authority?
Forget about me,
even if your father-in-law came,
he couldn't bear the consequences.
And you.
Think I forgot about you?
Get on your knees.
Apologize to Ning Chen.
Now!
The Left Chancellor holds great power.
His proteges are everywhere.
Just make your point.
And quit while you're ahead.
Quit, quit, quit.
Ning Chen.
Look, you're all brothers.
Brothers fighting brothers...
will make us a laughingstock.
How about this?
Today, just bear with them.
And later,
I'll discipline these two properly.
Cat got your tongues?
Bas...
No.
Fourth brother.
Enough.
No need for apologies.
You pretend to apologize,
I pretend to forgive.
We're all quite busy.
No need to act out this brotherly love.
However, Lord Ning,
those two trashed my room.
Well...
Your room's furnishings were old anyway.
I've long wanted to replace them.
I've just been busy with official duties
and hadn't gotten around to it.
Don't worry.
I'll have everything replaced right away.
I soon start at the Imperial Inspectorate.
I finally landed a proper job.
Bribes up and down are unavoidable.
No problem.
I'll have a thousand taels of silver sent
to your room right away.
So readily?
Seems my vision wasn't grand enough.
I asked for too little.
My lord.
Old General Chen awaits Ning Chen outside.
How dare you!
Dare you utter the Fourth Master's name?
Listen well, all of you.
If anyone again disrespects their superior,
they'll all be severely punished.
Is that clear?
Yes.
Congratulations, Silver Robe Ning.
Just an empty title.
Many thanks, Chief Eunuch Quan.
I'll repay you handsomely later.
You scared me half to death.
I appreciate the thought.
I still have urgent matters to attend to.
I'll take my leave now.
I'll see the Chief Eunuch out.
And see what Old General Chen wants.
After you.
Farewell, Chief Eunuch Quan.
Get up, quickly.
You all saw that clearly, didn't you?
It's not that I'm favoring Ning Chen.
It's just that now,
Ning Chen has caught His Majesty's eye.
You all... this...
Stay clear of him from now on.
Honestly...
I never expected
that Ning Chen would have such fortune.
I'm puzzled.
How did he ever meet His Majesty?
Mother.
Now he's in the Imperial Inspectorate,
after how we treated him before,
will he... will he take revenge on us?
Yes, Mother.
What's there to panic about?
A bastard will always be a bastard.
He'll never amount to anything refined.
Besides, he's merely a Silver Robe.
You go wash up properly in a bit.
You two come with me to see Grandfather.
There's a step here.
Don't trip.
Here, buddy.
Play with this for a while.
Greetings, Old General Chen.
Greetings, Chief Eunuch Quan.
Chief Eunuch Quan came to read the edict.
This boosts Ning Chen's standing at home.
I am merely following orders.
His Majesty awaits my report.
I take my leave.
Farewell.
Old General bought a carriage?
What's the act today?
What nonsense are you spouting?
You little brat.
A few days ago, you helped me out.
So today,
I picked out a special gift for you.
Bring it over.
I had this horse brought from Persia
just for you.
It can run a thousand li a day.
This horse is called
Black Qilin.
Today, I'm giving it to you.
Wow.
A foreign steed.
What's a foreign steed?
It means a forei--
Anyway, it's a fine horse.
A fine horse.
Truly a fine horse.
You're being awfully courteous today.
Don't tell me
you're up to no good?
Nonsense!
I simply admire you, that's all.
Take this gift
and treasure it well.
A true man should ride against the wind,
die in battle, wrapped in horsehide.
Not like me,
stuck in this tiny little place.
Dying in battle, wrapped in horsehide,
that's the end you truly seek, right?
Not like the way things are now.
At your age,
spare me the brooding act.
Maybe one day I'll surprise you.
I'd be lucky if you didn't scare me.
Give this horse a name.
What does this beauty want to be called?
Xishi?
Zhaojun?
Guifei?
Diaochan?
Oh, you want to be called Diaochan?
Alright.
Then from now on, your name is Diaochan.
Diaochan. What a fine name.
She chose it herself.
As long as the child likes it.
Now, back to business.
I meant to put you in the War Ministry.
You have the makings of a general.
You should be shining on the battlefield.
As you're in the Imperial Inspectorate,
he must have his reasons.
Today,
allow me to offer you some advice.
Please speak, Old General.
First.
You have a free-spirited nature,
unwilling to be bound by worldly rules.
But toward the royal family,
you must maintain due respect.
Second.
Imperial Inspectorate serves His Majesty.
Keep your distance from other officials.
Never give them grounds for gossip.
Third.
Imperial Inspectorate oversees officials,
and major cases across the nation.
You must hold fast to your principles.
Never let power or wealth blind your eyes.
Thank you for your guidance, Old General.
I will surely stay true to myself
and never forget my original intent.
Just remember it. That's all.
Alright then.
You and I, you rascal, are bound by fate.
Visit my residence often from now on.
I won't serve you fake wine.
Then I'll only bring peanuts.
Even stingier than me.
Head back.
Take good care of the horse.
Don't let it grow thin on me.
I won't.
With me, it will get fatter than you.
Rather than being the royal hound,
I'd much prefer to head into battle.
After all, I was once a soldier.
The battlefield is my true stage.
When you and I join forces someday,
we'll surely shine brilliantly.
The fate of the world is yet undecided.
You and I are both dark horses.