Greetings, Imperial Father.
Why have you summoned your child?
Take a look.
Huai'an.
Greetings, Imperial Father.
Did you come to see Us for a reason?
No reason.
I just missed you, Imperial Father.
You came at just the right time.
We were thinking of you, too.
Then let me rub your shoulders.
Alright, come on.
When His Majesty's children see him,
they act like mice that have seen a cat.
Only Princess Huai'an is cheerful,
clever and lively,
unafraid of His Majesty,
and deeply favored by him.
Have you finished reading?
Imperial Father,
Your child has finished reading.
Speak, then.
The Tuoluo Kingdom is poised to strike,
intending to raid our southern border again.
Do you have a way to counter it?
Imperial Father,
We've suffered repeated defeats recently.
Nanxuan harbors ravenous ambition,
Droughts and floods have left us drained.
We are in no shape to fight.
We should negotiate with Tuoluo
and provide them with grain and supplies.
Have you any brains at all?
Nanxuan harbors ravenous ambition,
but is Tuoluo any kinder?
Supplying them means feeding a tiger.
You are the Crown Prince,
the model of the imperial family.
Even if all court officials seek peace,
you must not.
Once backbone is lost,
it can never be recovered.
Yes, yes.
Your child will heed your teachings.
You...
Imperial Father.
Sit down, quickly.
Please don't be angry.
Royal Brother was thinking of the court,
of the common people.
Once war breaks out,
winning leaves the people destitute,
losing brings shame upon the court,
and we lose cities and lands.
Huai'an,
you're still young, you don't understand.
Right, right, I don't understand.
Brother, please get up.
Imperial Father, don't be angry anymore.
General Chen has arrived.
General, you have trouble walking.
Dispense with such formalities.
Yes, dispense with it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Old General, coming to see Us so late,
what brings you here?
Your Majesty,
I have found a way to deal with Tuoluo.
Crown Prince,
take a look.
General Chen,
these methods of yours,
did you devise them yourself?
Your Highness,
do you not trust me?
Enough.
We know exactly what you are capable of.
Leading troops into battle, no question.
But strategies like these
aren't something you could come up with.
Speak, then.
Your Majesty is wise.
In the last two days,
I encountered a young prodigy.
After hearing me describe
the situation between us and Tuoluo,
he quickly devised these countermeasures.
The capital has such a gifted youth?
What's his name? Where does he live?
I dare not deceive Your Majesty.
He is the Minister of Rites,
Ning Ziming's fourth son,
Ning Chen.
As I recall, the Left Chancellor
has only three grandsons.
Your Highness may not know,
Ning Chen is Ning Ziming's bastard son,
only recently brought back home.
I never thought that boy had such talent.
Imperial Father,
do you happen to know Ning Chen?
Did you read the poem We sent you?
Wasn't it signed by Lan Xing?
Could Ning Chen be Lan Xing?
So it was Your Majesty at Zhuangyuan Tower
who bought this boy's poem.
Excellent.
Excellent indeed!
Your Majesty,
Ning Chen is well-versed in poetry,
and understands military strategy.
Such talent is truly rare.
With proper cultivation,
he will surely achieve greatness.
I never expected old General Chen
to praise this youth so highly.
We recall
you've never praised the Crown Prince so.
Well...
Your Majesty may not know,
the capital has grown idle these years.
The young men are all soft and feeble.
They should toughen up on the battlefield.
Your Highness,
I'm not referring to you.
Your Majesty,
a promising talent like Ning Chen
must not go to waste.
But based on just one poem
and a few strategies,
entrusting him with great responsibility
would be premature.
The boy is still young.
Let's test him a few more times.
I never imagined the capital
had such an extraordinary youth.
Imperial Father,
Your child is quite intrigued.
Could you arrange for me
to meet him in person?
The Crown Prince may be indecisive,
but in judging and employing men,
he takes after Us.
What's the use of meeting him?
Such great talent isn't easily won over.
Imperial Father,
you and the old General
have praised Ning Chen so highly,
I want to meet him too.
You want to meet him too?
Very well.
But Ning Chen doesn't know Our identity.
Old General,
We'll trouble you to arrange it.
This...
Your Majesty,
Ning Chen doesn't know my identity either.
You...
I went out drinking,
forgot to bring silver,
and was beaten by the tavern boys.
He passed by and saved me.
The amusing part is,
he had no money on him either.
He just took the beating in my place.
Which shows his kind heart.
What shall We do then?
If he learns of Our identity,
he'll inevitably try to curry favor.
Such a pure heart
shouldn't be tainted by power too soon.
Your Majesty,
I have an idea.
Given Ning Chen's current situation,
he urgently needs silver.
Since he can write poetry,
he'll surely return to Zhuangyuan Tower
to sell his poems.
We can wait for him there.
Very well.
Crown Prince,
tomorrow,
you shall come with Us to see him.
Thank you, Imperial Father.
I really want to see
what that little brat looks like.
We almost forgot about Huai'an.
You shall come with Us as well.
Long live Imperial Father!
Mother!
Why did Father bring that bastard again?
Then everything we did before
will all have been for nothing!
I didn't think it through before.
I didn't anticipate public criticism.
But the three of you, rest assured.
Even if he lives in the Ning residence,
a bastard will always be a bastard.
The Ning family estate
will belong to you three brothers.
No one can take it away.
Mother,
about this matter,
if General Chen takes it to His Majesty,
will it affect my imperial exams?
Don't worry.
Your father and grandfather
have already suppressed this matter.
However,
this General Chen,
how on earth did he get to know him?
Do you know?
We don't know, Mother.
When we got to Xiaomei's home,
that old wretch...
that old general
was already sitting inside.
If that bastard clings to General Chen,
what shall we do?
That's right.
Xiaomei...
Xing'er,
right now he only cares about Xiaomei.
Send someone to watch her house.
She might come in handy later.
I have to go by myself?
Your eldest brother will soon take office.
He can't afford any trouble.
Your third brother is injured.
If you won't go, I will.
I'll...
go.
Second son,
Xiaomei is just a frail woman.
If she proves useful against Ning Chen,
you will have done a great deed.
I...
perhaps your grandfather
will see you in a new light.
I'll go, I'll go!
Come, Huai'an, give me one.
Good, good, good.
It's been several days now.
Could it be that boy
hasn't recovered from his injuries?
Looks like we waited in vain today.
Let's go.
Your Majesty...
No, no, no, Master Bi.
He's here!