National Radio. and Telvison. Administration.
I want to see your father.
and be filial.
Be filial?
What's our relationship?
Who are you to be filial?
Don't be afraid of being laughed at.
What? You don't like it?
I just don't want to.
What else can you do to me?
Let's give it a try.
This is Moyun Ridge.
If you dare to go on your own,
100,000 swordsmen
are your enemies.
My mission in Shaanxi
is to turn the 100,000 swordsmen
into a powerful anti-Japanese force.
Stop the devil from going in.
One person can't defeat the devil.
We have to unite all the unity
to defeat them.
Wu Zhen, come here.
What happened?
Oh no, they are walking in the village.
They look like Japanese.
Why are you so sure?
Was it not done by other swordsmen?
The knife is right in the throat.
It must be done
professional military training.
I'm very familiar with swordsmen on the mountain.
They don't have such tricks.
As a swordsman,
You know a lot.
Why did the Japanese kill our people?
Miss.
We don't know what's going on ahead.
Come back with me.
I'm not going back.
If anything happens to you,
if anything happens to you?
I don’t need your explanation.
My brother died for no reason.
I don't even know who my enemy is.
I can't go back.
Stop arguing.
For your safety,
go back with him.
I won't go back until we find out the real murderer.
Go back if you want.
Two men
are afraid of trouble.
I'm not afraid of anything. I'm worried about you.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Where are we going?
Don't you know this is the county security group?
Can't you read?
Brother.
Please inform them.
Tell them Choi Moon-Kui is here.
Choi Moon-Kui!
I don't care.
Our captain is not seeing anyone right now.
Get lost!
What about now?
Please forgive me, sir.
Someone broke into the security group!
What's going on?
Move!
I didn't know Brigade Commander was here.
Sorry for not welcoming you.
Put down your guns.
Captain Li.
This is indeed your station.
Your soldiers are much better than people from Qinglong Fortress.
I have no idea.
Are you blind?
Tie him up and shoot him.
Forget it.
The security team is so difficult.
He didn't do it alone.
Brigade Commander, please have a seat.
Do you mind?
No.
How is the airport?
There are too many scoundrels here.
The ones with arms are strong.
either ran away
or become bandits.
No, no.
Be a swordsman.
The rest of them
are really...
I think there are
in your security group.
Yes
Yes.
Gather your security team.
Keep half of them stationed in the west city for 30 miles.
The rest of you fix the airport for me.
Yes.
What are they doing down there?
Fixing the airport.
Airport.
You know the plane, right?
Yes.
It's the steel buds flying in the sky.
It's very loud when it comes to the head.
Yes.
This is where the plane takes off and lands.
It's so big
What's the use of that iron?
Transport. Transport.
transporting things, transporting weapons,
and fight in the sky.
You mean
people fight on the ground?
Planes and planes fight in the sky.
You got it right.
This plane is quite useful.
You two know a lot.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Officer.
I have a sick mother at home.
Please let me go back.
Let me go.
Screw you!
Cut the crap.
Pay the bandits if you don't want to work.
I really have no money.
You don't pay for the money.
Officer.
I have a sick mother at home.
They can't live without me.
Get up. Do you hear me?
Do you hear me?
Who is it?
Do you want to die?
Come out!
Or I'll shoot.
Get down.
Keep quiet.
You...
Go take a look.
You, go over there.
Yes, it's you.
Hurry up.
What did you see?
Officer
Nothing.
Then what was that?
This might be a wild rabbit.
Come back quickly.
Okay.
All right. Let's go.
Hurry.
Go.
Keep up.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Get up.
I'm sorry about earlier.
But don't worry.
If you do as I say,
we'll be able to catch those four losers.
Luckily, he didn't say anything.
He's my father.
They walk slowly.
You and Tongshang
Go to them.
How?
Don't worry.
As long as I make a move,
they will look back at me.
But you must hurry up, you know?
Kill those useless people.
to kill those trash?
Don't shoot! Don't kill!
Why? What's the use of keeping it?
It's still useful for me.
Be good. Go.
Spare me.
Please don't kill me.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Go over there.
Get up.
Stay still!
Yes.
Turn around.
What have you been doing these days?
It's a long story.
Father.
Why are you here?
Well,
I'll send some consolation
to the airport.
These soldiers are not bad.
Let them go.
Squat.
I heard someone is locked in the airport.
It's mysterious.
I think he betrayed our organization.
I want to see him.
I'll go on your behalf.
No, no, no.
You offended the soldiers.
How can you go?
It's useless even if you go.
I know
of the organization.
Only I go.
In front of them,
in front of them.
I'll go with you.
You go. This...
By the way,
these two new friends
look good.
But that lady
looks very familiar to me.
Who is it?
Let me introduce to you.
Okay.
Miss.
Father, this is the head of Qinglong Fortress.
Shangguan Bao’s daughter, Shangguan Eagle.
It's Miss Shangguan.
Excuse me.
Alright.
What should I shout?
What should I call you?
If you think
Father.
I dare not.
What's going on?
It's only been two days.
That's too fast.
It's a long story.
Hurry up.
That's basically what happened these two days.
So
you are not Zhao Weiguo?
I didn't say I am.
I was in charge of
to protect the leadership.
This time, he was assigned
to protect Zhao’s safety.
But on the way here,
I met the Japanese.
Mr. Zhao
He died.
Come to think of it,
the independent Brigade Commander of Yuxi
was also chased by the Japanese.
Yes.
On the day I met you,
So,
the Japanese are really coming?
So
you've never done intelligence work?
Strictly speaking,
I've never been in contact with intelligence.
Oh my god.
The contact code
Mr. Zhao told me before he died.
That's why I followed them one by one that day.
Fine.
I know.
You're going back?
Yes.
If I can get rid of that traitor this time,
I'll go back to the base
to apply for other comrades.
Are you going back to Qinglong Camp?
What do you mean?
The main task of Zhao’s committee
is to fight the West Blade.
I just escaped from there.
Besides,
I don't know much about this job.
I know.
You don't know.
It'll be troublesome if I go back.
I must die in the hands of that lady.
Because of this,
Let's change to another team.
you're not suitable.
Let me ask you.
Have you ever married?
No.
It has nothing to do with
to do with me?
It's a deal.
I'll send a telegram to the base tonight
to the base tonight.
No.
Mr. Cai,
Please imagine
tens of thousands of swordsmen
If they want to fight against Japan,
what will it be?
It can change the power of the whole war zone.
Think about it.
My daughter-in-law.
My son and I
are going to the airport.
I have something to do.
What is it?
Well...
Yes, it's like this.
We have an enemy.
is a sworn enemy.
I've been looking for him for years.
Now I finally know
he's at the airport.
We're going to
to meet him.
About this...
Yes.
I'll go with you.
No, no, no.
No, no.
If you don't want her to know,
please don't tell her.
What?
I've never seen an airport. I'll go and have a look.
Fly on the plane.
Come here.
Keep an eye on them.
If anything happens,
we can take care of each other.
I'm going to avenge with my father-in-law.
Wu,
Why are you here
Why are you here?
Third Brother, I miss you.
Can't I visit you?
You miss me?
Didn’t we just meet two days ago?
Besides, Madam has ordered
no one is allowed to go down the mountain this month.
Have you forgotten?
Third Brother.
Don’t mention Leader.
You really hold a grudge against her.
Shouldn’t I?
If Madam hadn’t stopped you,
you would have died that day.
So what?
Third Brother.
I’ve worked for Patriarch for so many years.
for Madam these years.
No matter how much I owe you,
I've paid you back.
Catch.
There are no bullets in your gun.
If you dare to talk nonsense there,
my gun can't open your eyes.
Understand?
Yes.
Understood
What should we say there?
I know
I know I know
Put your hat on straight.
Let's go.
What are you waiting for? Lead the way.
Yes.
Third Brother.
In front of Shangguan Bao,
in front of Shangguan Bao.
I know
what you think.
Bullshit!
I think you lack one ear.
Don't you like it?
Third Brother, listen to me.
If you make any progress,
you'll be the boss of Moyun Ridge.
It’s great for me to help you.
Right?
Shangguan Bao and his family are nothing.
Am I right?
Third Brother.
Third Brother!
Are you really going to rebel?
Third Brother.
That's not what I meant.
Third Brother!
Third Brother, I know you dare not do it.
If you don't eat jelly, you have to make a move, right?
If you don't, I'll do it.
Stop right there!
Since you came in,
I knew you didn't hold it back.
Third Brother, I was wrong.
Third Brother, let’s go.
Come with me to see Leader.
I’m not going, Third Brother.
I was wrong, Yinqi.
Third Brother, I'm sorry.
Don't move!
Third Brother, I was wrong.
I was wrong
talking too much to you.
Who are you?
Third Brother.
Let me introduce.
This is the lieutenant of the Japanese army.
Mr. Tawahara Masahio.
You colluded with the Japanese.
It’s not my fault.
Shangguan Bao is merciless.
Then I'll be unfaithful to him.
Third Brother, stop being stubborn.
Mr. Zhen.
There's an old Chinese saying,
"A wise man submits to fate."
Now the Japanese army is as strong as bamboo.
will take over China soon.
Resistance is useless.
I advise you to
like a golden tooth.
you'll have a bright future.
Let me be like this bastard.
Yes.
Dream on.
Did you see that house?
Right here.
Yes.
Captain Li sent it here himself.
He also asked us to serve him with good wine and meat every day.
Who's in there?
I only remember his name is Zhou Zhongxiao.
I don't know anything else.
Don't tell anyone about this today.
Otherwise, even if we get caught,
they won't give you a hard time.
Understand?
Yes.
Send the horse over.
Okay.
Why hasn't the meal come yet?
Do you want to starve me to death?
Let me tell you.
I'm your leader, the cash cow.
He wants to get promoted and get rich.
because of me.
How capable are you?
Our captain gave you face.
To be honest,
the whole Yuxi
anyone from the Communist Party
he won't have me.
Wu.
Get him!
He's the Communist Party.
Wu.
I'm sorry.
I deserve to die.
Look.
I can't stand it anymore.
You want to die, but he won't let you die.
I had no choice.
Wu.
You know that
I have my mother at home.
How dare you mention your mother?
Come out with me.
What?
You're here. It's here. It's here. It's here.
Yes.
Who is that person inside?
Traitor.
What is a traitor?
Many of us
in this area.
A lot of people went missing overnight.
He betrayed Li Gang.
Then why did Li Gang kill the Communist Party?
Just like Li Gang gave you swordsmen a hard time.
We swordsmen don't bully the people.
Communist Party too?
We protect the people.
What is Communist Party?
It's hard to explain.
We can't stay here for long.
229.
I'll tell you
I'll tell you.
Wait.
Just tell me.
Is the Communist Party a hero?
Why do you ask?
My dad said
229.
The world can protect the people.
Those who dare to fight the Japanese are heroes.
Your father is right.
Where are the other comrades?
Tell me if you know.
The others were sent to Black Tiger Mountain by Li.
Nonsense.
Let me tell you.
I am Shangguan Ying from Qinglong Camp.
If you dare to talk nonsense again,
I'll cut off your tongue.
Qinglong Fortress.
Shangguan Bao, you...
You... You were really defeated.
Say whatever I ask you.
Tell me.
It's me.
I betrayed the organization.
After Li got the news,
he took me to catch him.
Who else?
Too many. Can you catch them all?
With you and Zhou Zhongxiao,
I can catch them all.
Take him away.
Zhou Zhongxiao, you traitor!
Stop.
Captain Li.
Third Master.
Let me borrow your way.
to arrest a criminal.
Don't you want to give me face?
Why did you tie him up like that?
The Third Master is really strict.
He said I had a lot to do.
Our boss
just issued a killing order.
You have no idea.
Those who bully the people, kill!
Kill the tyrant!
Most importantly,
those who stir up the Japanese
Kill them!
I've heard of your Eight Cutting Tiles.
It's all against the inside of you swordsmen.
So there are three more.
specifically for the outside.
To be honest,
it's for you.
Me?
It’s your boss’s Shangguan Bao.
dare not touch the people I caught.
Are you a commie?
This is a Communist Party.
It was easy to discuss.
But now I'm in charge of this.
Do you want to be a human or a jerk?
I don't care.
I will save
the Japanese.
What do you think?
Please do me a favor.
Look.
Did you let him go
or me?
I told you.
Uncle Sanxing wouldn't do that.
So our comrade is locked in Black Tiger Mountain?
Tell me.
Who else is alive?
My lady.
I'll tell you.
And...
Kong.
Kong is still alive.
Don't worry.
As long as he's in Black Tiger Mountain, he'll be fine.
Sir.
It's so hot. Why are we working?
Cut the crap. Hurry up.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Hurry, let's go.
Hurry.
Hurry!
Oh no. Fly on the boat.
Come on.
Wu, what are you doing?
Comrade Cai, listen to me.
Here is the thing.
I'm familiar with the terrain here.
I'm going to distract the security team.
The guards can't catch me.
Li Gang is a fool.
I want you to save Kong now.
If it's too late, I'm worried about Kong.
Kong is the core of our work.
I’m afraid if something happens to him,
our relationship with Qinglong Camp will be completely over.
If we break up,
the work of Shanzhou underground party
has been in vain.
Also,
protect Shangguan Eagle.
She's Shangguan Bao's daughter.
Please be safe.
Got it?
Take them away now.
I'm here.
Wu, what are you talking about?
I don't agree.
Just hide here and don't move.
I'll be back soon.
Wu Zhen.
Be good.
Don't come out. Don't move.
Don't let one go. Charge!
Where's Father?
He's waiting at the back.
Go!
There are too many of them.
Let's go.
Okay.
You go first. I'll cover you.
Go after them!
Hurry up!
Let's go.
This way. Hurry.
After them!
Hurry!
They didn't catch up.
Did they withdraw?
Go! Go! Go! Go!
You go.
Hurry up.
Take him away.
I want you to save Kong now.
Kong is the core figure of our work.
If something happens to him,
our relationship with Qinglong Camp will be completely over.
Wu.
Your father...
What are you waiting for?
Go after him!
Young Lady Zhen Zhu.
You can't go.
That's your father.
Will it be okay if Li Gang has it?
My father deliberately wanted to distract the security team
to get us out of here.
If we go back now and get caught by Li Gang,
I'll let him down.
We must save him.
Shangguan Eagle.
Can you not be so impulsive every time?
You can't save my father even if you go back now.
I'll put all of you in trouble.
Where are you going?
Black Tiger Mountain.
Yes.
Get Uncle Sanxing to save him
Let's go.
Brigade Commander Cui, have some tea.
I just heard the news
I knew you were coming.
You should have told me earlier.
I could have sent someone to pick you up.
You don't have to make such a fuss.
I'm here for the military.
Brigade Commander Cui is a low profile.
I admire him.
Brigade Commander Cui.
How's your cooperation with Captain Li?
I just arrived.
As for the cooperation,
I don't think it's a problem.
That's good.
Brigade Commander Cui.
I heard
you went to Qinglong Hideout alone.
Master Shangguan Bao
didn't hurt Brigade Commander Cui,
but also gave him face.
Brigade Commander Cui, you're indeed a recruit in the army.
We can keep our city safe.
Mr. He,
In this aspect,
Mr. Choi doesn't agree with you.
Although these swordsmen have some evil aura,
but in terms of moral and moral,
he's better than some people.
I heard that
some military expenses
from the people.
Is that true?
Brigade Commander Cui, this...
I need to explain this to you.
The bandit is a bandit after all.
Of course.
The Shangguan Bao from Qinglong Fortress
is different.
I know.
he doesn't harass the people,
He knows the rules.
But there are so many leaders.
They are not in sync.
As you know,
the current situation is turbulent.
There will be some people who are not disciplined.
But when the country is in trouble,
I don't think they dare to cause trouble.
One day,
beat the Japanese away,
We have to deal with these people.
We have to deal with them.
Mr. He.
You have a long vision.
But I have to remind you.
Before the Japanese are taken away,
we'd better not fight each other.
Brigade Commander Cui is right.
I'm indeed a bit inconsiderate.
Report!
Brigade Commander.
Someone attacked the airport.
Lele Motel.
The 33rd National China
72 Brigade
I'm on the 30th Army.
When did that happen?
Just now.
Let's go.
Brigade Commander Cui, what happened?
The airport was attacked.
Goodbye.
Airport.
Who is it? Is it Japanese?
Guards!
Come out now!
What's wrong, Master?
Close all the doors.
No matter what happens,
no matter what happens.
Hurry up. Okay.
Master, what about the ladies?
Should we take them over?
Forget it.
Ride a horse and go to the airport.
If you see the Japanese,
come back by horse and report.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Zheng'er.
Why are you here
Why are you here?
Why do you have so much money?
Of course.
I don't have that much money.
can you live a good life?
You asked the people to pay,
but you hid so much.
Shut up!
Is this how you educate your father?
Zheng'er.
Your mother died early.
I brought you up with poop and urine.
It's not easy.
It's a chaotic time now.
How can you live a good life
How can you live a good life?
But...
the Japanese called.
No matter how rich you are,
you're still a country slave.
All right.
We'll see.
Don't listen to
to lecture you.
You're young.
There are many things you don't understand.
In such a troubled time,
your father had to go with him.
If I don't let you live a good life,
how can I live up to your dead mother?
Remember.
I'm not hungry when I'm full.
Only when you have money
to have dignity.
Actor table.
Lee Seung-yup.
Choi Bo-wol.
Deng Bao Quan.
and actors.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile, Wang Lusheng.
Li Shuo Yu Hongda Tian Guofeng Gong Fan Cheng Kaiyan.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhao Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin, Wang Yukun.
Ji, Chao, Zhao Zhigang, Kung, Ji Youyi.
Yang Tao, Chen Yao, and Rui Qian.
Qin Haosen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Liangliang, Lin Nan. Liu, Yu.
Xu Shidong, Liu Yongtao.
Chen Weigui Wang Ching Hua Wang Ching Yong Zhao Min-jie
Foreign King Xu Gan Xin Yan Long Zhao Changli
Staff table.
Director team.
Yun Lihua.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Cho Jeon-min.
The clothing team.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Props team.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
Gunman Sun Hai
The recording team.
The venue team.
Zhao Gongli.
Driver team.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Rong Xi.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu De Yu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Liu Hongxing.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li. Zhang Chang.
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Chou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping
Cut.
LilStar.
Drama photo, Wu Xiaobo.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
One Zhu Jiaxin.
Jun Nan.
Chen Mingjun.
Xie Hong.
A dubber.
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for your name.
Thank you.
The base of HongMong Red Film in Shandong. [The national 4A-class scenic area]
[Shandong Blumund Red Filming Base] [The national 4A-class scenic area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple Sheung-Mun's Government.
The Jade Association of Shanzhou District
[Sanmen Mingu Pu Theatre]
The Civilian Committee of Lingbao City
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Shanzhou District.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Tianan Lake, Zhishan Lake City Wetland Park.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
Sanmen City Swan Lake Wetland Park.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Lan Yi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
Sandao Watery Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
I'll reward Zhang Bing first.