If you wear shoes that do not fit,
you could easily fall.
Do you suspect he is lying,
Commissioner Di?
Confess everything now!
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 11=
In the end,
you still saw right through me.
I have studied
the classics my entire life.
I couldn't take it lying down.
I couldn't bear such humiliation.
(Mourning)
Pan'er,
if Zhuang hadn't told me
that you paid for my mother's medicine,
I would still be kept in the dark.
You only married him for my sake.
Pan'er,
no more regrets.
Make a choice for your own sake.
Let's leave this place.
Tonight.
We leave tonight.
The curfew begins at the Xu hour.
I will wait for you at Zhuang's.
I am already old and frail.
At my advanced age,
I only wanted to marry and have children
to carry on my lineage.
Yes.
I was indeed coveting Gu Pan'er's
youth and beauty.
But I was completely devoted to her,
and I never once wronged her.
I never expected
things to end so miserably.
The night she returned,
I killed her.
Then I hid her body
at the theater troupe,
framing Zhuang Luobai for it.
To cover up the truth,
I killed her mother.
And to eliminate
any remaining loose ends,
I killed that miserable gambler.
Buying and selling women
is already a grave offense.
Yet you doubled down
on your errors,
taking three human lives.
It is utterly
monstrous and unforgivable!
Yes.
I was wrong.
From the very beginning,
Prefect Gongsun,
take him away.
Guards!
What is it, Master?
We must have missed something.
(Gu Pan'er wanted)
(to give Zhuang Luobai)
(this green robe.)
It must be.
(Usually,)
(Zhuang Luobai only wears plain robes.)
Why would she give him a green robe?
(This green robe)
(was meant for Dong Ling.)
(We kept our eyes on Zhuang Luobai)
(and completely overlooked Dong Ling.)
Since you ask that,
did Hou Guangming kill her?
No.
It wasn't Zhuang Luobai
who wanted to kill Hou Guangming.
It's you.
Why wouldn't it be me?
(Hou's Residence)
(He wanted to draw us away)
(to help Dong Ling exact her revenge.)
(The one who truly
wanted to kill Hou Guangming)
(was Dong Ling.)
Sir!
We found a knife wound
on Hou Guangming's back.
Dong Ling is in danger!
Find her!
Split up and search!
Over here!
The knife wound on Hou Guangming
was from Dong Ling's attack.
But her injuries are more severe.
She can still be saved.
You're awake.
Commissioner Di...
Rest easy.
Hou Guangming has confessed.
Justice has been served for Gu Pan'er.
This is returned to its rightful owner.
♪Drifting snow falls♪
♪Fleeting dreams fly into the flame♪
♪This transient life is but a cage♪
♪Shattering the chains of fate♪
♪Seeing through the human heart♪
♪Life and death,
the grand illusion ends♪
♪Now scattered by heaven and earth♪
Commissioner Di.
I lied to you.
I didn't want Pan'er to be remembered
as a swindler after her death.
So I hid the fact that
we had planned to run away together.
That night,
I waited in Zhuang's room
until dawn.
I thought
she had changed her mind.
Little did I know,
she had already met a cruel end
at Hou Guangming's hands.
I wanted to follow Pan'er to the grave,
but I couldn't accept it.
Hou Guangming must be behind
the deaths of Pan'er and her family.
So I went to Zhuang.
I asked him to help me get revenge.
I am going to kill Hou Guangming.
Whether it's Hou Guangming
or us,
the authorities must be
watching our every move.
Killing him
will be no easy task.
Zhuang,
help me draw the authorities away.
You are a woman.
Do you have the strength
to kill Hou Guangming?
Pan'er cannot rest in peace.
How can I stand by and watch you
walk into the lion's den?
I must have revenge.
Even if it kills me,
I must have it.
Put this on.
You become a god.
The three of you cherished one another.
I am honored to have witnessed
such genuine devotion...
What do you think, Master Zhuang?
Don't I look
better than you?
Yes.
Master.
What on earth is wrong with you?
It's like that woman has bewitched you.
What is this nonsense?
(Zhuang was dragged
into this storm for nothing.)
(I am entirely to blame)
(for his involvement.)
As for
the rumors
about his affair with Gu Pan'er
have been publicly cleared.
Their reputations will be restored.
(One Month Later)
Master.
I was wrong.
Master!
Where are you?
(Marionette Umbrella Dance)
(Luobai,)
(you desired nothing more
than to become the Red-Faced Guardian.)
(Today, your wish is granted.)
♪Life is a dream♪
(Xuansi Drama Troupe)
♪A dream like chasing the wind♪
♪Yet I am lost within it,
refusing to wake♪
Wenbo truly is a master puppeteer.
Just look at this.
This puppet he made
really captures the essence
of Master Zhuang Luobai.
It is absolutely lifelike.
The resemblance is uncanny.
It looks just like a real person.
Wenbo deserves his reputation
as a master puppeteer!
Its build
looks exactly like Master Zhuang.
Indeed.
I couldn't agree more!
Master!
(Ming Yu.)
(For the God-Welcoming Dance,)
(you will be the lead dancer.)
(The future of this Nuo dance)
(is now entrusted to you.)
(Dance well.)
(Carry the will of the god)
(and guard this path of expelling evil
and upholding justice.)
(Remember,)
(do not fail yourself,)
(and do not)
(fail the Nuo opera.)
Master...
I was wrong, Master.
You taught me thousands of times,
yet I still make mistakes onstage.
It's because I am foolish.
Stop punishing yourself like this.
Master...
Take it off.
You will find your true self
and become who you are meant to be.
(But only by)
(shedding your worldly shackles)
(and forgetting yourself)
(can you perfectly bring her to life.)
(In my heart,)
(Master)
(is the Guardian itself.)
One day, you will surpass me.
I will be waiting.
Master...
Why did you kill my master?
You must be the disciple
Zhuang Luobai thought
of on his deathbed.
I must avenge my master.
I will kill you!
Stop!
He didn't kill your master.
The autopsy revealed
that your master died
of chronic exhaustion.
You should have killed me just now!
You should have killed me.
Why do you seek death so eagerly?
What was your connection
to Zhuang Luobai?
When I was ten years old,
Luobai and I fled a famine to Raozhou.
Completely alone,
we had only each other to rely on.
Later on...
(He studied the Nuo opera,)
(while I mastered puppetry.)
(Our crafts diverged drastically,)
(and we constantly argued
over form and spirit.)
I mocked his obsession,
and he chided my arrogance.
We parted ways in anger,
and for over ten years,
we never spoke
a single word to each other.
Until two months ago,
that fool suddenly came to see me.
He said
he came to say goodbye.
Only then
did I learn he was terminally ill
and that his days were numbered.
Why me?
For the very first time,
he invited me
to watch the Winter Festival.
He said I would see his apprentice
dancing with flowing sleeves.
Master...
To see how the woman in the script
emerges from her cocoon
like a butterfly.
It was all an idle wish.
On the day of the Winter Festival,
all I saw
was him alone in the snow,
taking his final breaths in this world.
Luobai.
Hold on.
Please, hold on!
I will go get a physician.
Wenbo,
you wanted your puppets
to dance just like me.
I have found a way.
My soul...
is about to fade.
I leave my mortal shell to you.
Put it to good use.
Promise me.
I will.
Wenbo,
look at that.
The Guardian has come for me.
(All mortal lives are caught in a web,)
(and who can truly be free of burdens?)
(Some are tangled by fame and fortune,)
(and others are bound
by the threads of love.)
(But if one can
break free from this cage)
(and escape worldly attachments,
even for a moment...)
(Even if the trap
is ultimately inescapable,)
(that brief moment of brilliant bloom)
(reveals a soul's truest self.)
(So it was for Zhuang Luobai,)
(for Dong Ling,)
(and for Pan'er.)
(And so it is for us all.)
♪Fleeting dreams fly into the flame♪
♪This transient life is but a cage♪
♪Shattering the chains of fate♪
♪Seeing through the human heart♪
♪Life and death,
the grand illusion ends♪
(Wangnian County, Raozhou)
(Changsha County, Tanzhou)
(Part Three: The Fox Demon)
Young Lady,
I am terribly parched.
Could I trouble you for a bowl of water?
Please, come inside and sit.
Thank you.
Little girl,
would you like some sweet fruit?
On the trees just over there,
there are so many sweet fruits growing.
They are delicious.
Let's get some,
- shall we?
- Sure.
Have some soup first.
What kind of soup is this?
It's your
black-hearted soup.
(Preview of Next Episode)
Master,
a report from the Bureau.
The fox demon has struck again.
What I desire
is your heart.
Won't you grant me my wish,
Young Master?
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪