National Radio. And Telvison Administration
Do all Chinese know this?
"Be a gentleman, be a gentleman."
Yes.
All Chinese who read Confucius
know it.
But...
there is
between us.
Speaking of which,
I have a question for Mr. Wu.
What do you think
what is the difference between the public?
The difference is obvious.
The Communist Party wants everyone to be the owner.
But your party
teach people to be slaves.
What do you mean?
Everyone in our party is equal.
What about the noblemen?
Our party has never taught anyone
to be a slave or a servant.
I want to correct you.
There is a difference
are different.
A slave is a state.
But a servant is a state of mind.
A servant
not only do you want to be a servant,
but also needs someone to be a servant.
To put it bluntly,
find fun from being a slave
and vent the grievances
to those
who are not as good as you.
Please think about it.
Is there such a person
Is there such a person?
Brigade Commander Cui.
Please read these two books
these two books.
There are Chinese
of Chinese people.
Brigade Commander.
He's stinky and hard.
What's the point of keeping him?
In my opinion,
it's better to kill him.
I don't need you to teach me.
From now on, you don't have to
about Mr. Wu.
Yes.
So cold.
We've been staring all night.
There's still no movement inside.
If it doesn't work,
I'll go in alone.
Wait for me here.
No.
Let's go together.
Didn't we agree that
no matter who's inside,
even if I'm caught,
for the sake of you and your father,
they won't kill me.
Then they won't kill me.
What if there are golden teeth inside?
It doesn't matter.
Let's go in together.
You just wait here to pick me up.
Guys,
Thank you. Come down for dinner.
Coming.
Thank you for your hard work.
The boss asked me to comfort you.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm really hungry.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Shoot me now!
Just stand here and wait for me.
Don't move.
I won't move when you tell me to.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Go!
Go after him!
Let's go.
I told you to hide up there. Don't come down.
None of your business.
I'll go.
Who should we help?
This is Uncle Sanxing's place.
Are you asking me?
I...
Let's wait and see.
Kong, go.
Go after them!
Hurry!
After them!
Old bastard, it's you again.
Kong.
Shangguan Eagle.
Kong, how are you?
Kong.
Guys, get him alive!
Eagle, you can't escape.
Let's go.
Go!
You are mine.
Hurry.
Uncle.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Hurry!
Kong.
What's wrong?
My lady.
Close the door!
Eagle.
Uncle Six.
Send Miss Leng back to Qinglong Camp.
Hurry up.
Golden tooth.
How dare you!
Hand me Brother Zhen San!
I'll kill him.
If you take another step,
I'll kill you too.
Master.
Let's go our separate ways.
I can't enjoy wealth as a swordsman.
I have to starve.
Why should I listen to Shangguan Bao?
How dare you call yourself a swordsman?
If you want wealth,
I won't stop you.
But you killed Zhenshan Liang today.
I won’t forgive you.
He Xiaopian.
Look how many guns I have.
Look over there.
If you can't defeat me today,
I'll give you face today.
I can let you go.
Don't force me.
Hand over the bodies of
of Zhenshan Liang and your brothers.
Just wait.
Here you are.
Take it.
Close the door.
Okay, hurry up.
Third Brother.
Golden tooth.
Liu.
Master.
The bodies are all here.
This is not the time to be impulsive.
Take them back first.
Let's go.
Third Brother, let’s go home.
Chae Yun from the Eighth Army.
He went down the mountain with Shangguan Eagle.
and experienced hardships.
You see true love in danger.
Wake up.
Don't talk. I'm not awake yet.
Let me sleep a little longer.
What happened?
It's okay. It hurts again.
I’m fine. I’ll go get Mr. He.
No need.
I feel much better.
I'm really fine. Much better.
I'm really fine.
Look at you.
Mr. He told you to rest.
Why can’t you sleep well?
Yes.
How did I come back?
Mr. He brought us back.
Where’s Leader?
My father
and everyone are at the graveyard.
Do you want some water?
I’ll get you some.
Goodbye, Mr. Kong.
Brother Shanliang,
I will avenge you.
your revenge.
I should have rushed in yesterday
and killed that bastard, Jintooth.
Liu.
With what happened yesterday,
we can't come back
no one can come back.
Besides,
Golden tooth has occupied Black Tiger Mountain.
and has so many weapons left.
We'll lose a lot if we attack rashly.
Boss, please give the order.
I'll take the lead
I will destroy Black Tiger Mountain.
Brother, I'll take the lead.
Even if I die,
even if I die.
Avenge Jin San!
Avenge Brother Zhen San!
Sir, give the order.
Yes, boss, say something.
Please give the order.
Now is not the time.
Without my order,
no one is allowed to attack Black Tiger Mountain.
Brother.
Don't talk about me.
What about your promise?
If I have enough guns,
if I have enough guns?
I told you.
the gun will arrive in three days.
But what about the money?
No one will work hard without the pay.
The money will be in place.
As long as you do your job well,
I promise you everything.
You've said this more than once.
Do you think I'm a fool?
Don’t think I dare not tie you up.
and send you back to Qinglong Camp.
Remember.
You killed Zhenshan Liang.
At that time,
I'll make a great contribution.
Tie me up.
Sure.
I’d like to see
how you can get into Qinglong Fortress.
Golden tooth, let me tell you.
There's no turning back.
At this point,
you want to turn back.
Even if I promise you,
the Chinese and the entire swordsman
won't agree.
In their eyes,
you are a traitor.
and their enemy.
Understand?
Don't worry.
I've met Li Gang.
I'll send you the gun and money later.
But for the time being,
you have to do something for me.
I'll do it for you.
If you kill Zhenshan Liang now,
and I have the Black Tiger Mountain.
Should I kill
all the swordsmen
to work for you.
Golden tooth.
Since you know
you are against the whole swordsman,
So, besides working with me,
besides working with me?
Are you threatening me?
I'm just reminding you.
The Japanese army has occupied Luoyang.
It's only a matter of time before we take down Yuxi.
What I'm doing now
is to clear all obstacles
to clear all obstacles.
Not to mention three levels,
the whole Shaanxi will be yours.
But no matter it's you or not,
it will be the royal army sooner or later.
Which is more important?
Think about it.
Mr. Tian.
What do you want me to do for you?
Cui Wenkui.
to pick a fight between him and Shangguan Bao.
Let me remind you again.
that Shangguan Bao
is inevitable.
If we make him enemies with Choi Moon-Kui,
Then he can kill someone with a borrowed knife.
Okay.
I'll do this for you.
Don't forget your promise this time.
Don't worry.
Eagle, why are you here?
I'm here to see you.
Father.
Don't be too sad about Uncle Zhen.
If you hurt yourself again,
You'd better go back and take care of Wu Zhen.
I'm fine.
He's awake.
Besides, I just
I just said a few words and you want me to leave?
Am I so annoying?
Who said that?
You're always a good daughter to me.
How is he?
Father, I'm your daughter.
Why are you
in three sentences?
Don't you know
if I'm hurt or not?
Are you hungry?
Okay, I'll ask Eagle
Are you tired? Are you hurt?
No, I'm not hurt.
Eagle.
Come here. I want to ask you something.
Father, go ahead.
I heard that
Wu Zhen
blocked so many people.
He's really brave.
Only courage left.
When someone called Kong,
just charge in.
If it weren't for me, I wouldn't have come back.
What did you say?
When he saw someone calling Kong,
he rushed out immediately.
What's wrong?
Dad, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Eagle.
Can you tell me
the details?
Kong, go.
Kong.
How are you, Kong?
Am I right, Father?
Without me,
I won't be able to come back.
Why did you call him that?
Dad, I’m hungry.
We haven’t eaten buns for a long time.
You’re just greedy.
It's good that you can still eat in troubled times.
You know what?
Wu Zhen
is quite smart.
Father.
Why don't you take a rest first?
Okay, go ahead.
Wu Zhen.
Kong.
Wu Zhen, Kong.
Isn't this Mr. He from Qinglong Fortress?
Mr. Tian.
Why do you have time to go down the mountain today?
I came down the mountain
if there are any food and groceries that I need to buy.
What a coincidence.
Mr. He.
In that case,
I want to treat Master He to a meal.
Mr. He, may I?
Thank you, Mr. Tian.
Why are you buying me dinner?
I can’t afford it.
Mr. He, don’t get me wrong.
Here’s the thing.
Since I met Master He last time,
since I met Master He last time.
I think I have a good eye for Master He.
So I’ve been looking for a chance
to meet Master He again.
We meet on the street today.
I feel that we are destined to meet.
I don’t mean anything else.
I just want to talk to Mr. He.
Thank you, Mr. Tian.
But I’ve had dinner.
Next time.
I won’t let you down next time.
Goodbye.
Let's go back to the fortress.
Major.
He's acting strange.
I'm worried
knows about us.
Not yet.
But I think this person is extraordinary.
Kirisha.
Find out who he really is.
Yes.
I’d like to see
of Qinglong Camp.
You're right.
My father said he was fine,
he felt worse than anyone else.
After Uncle Zhen left,
he was the most upset.
I went to the graveyard to visit Uncle Sanxing.
Look at him.
How can he just disappear?
Uncle Sanxing is the best to me.
I remember when I was young,
he always took me down the mountain
and bought me fried cakes.
and fried dough twists.
and brought me to have lamb soup.
He also told me
when he first went up the mountain,
When he knew my father was a bandit,
he insisted on going down the mountain.
It's not easy to get down the mountain.
People thought he was a bandit.
and beat him up.
In the end, my father
brought a lot of people to save him.
Then,
Uncle Sanxing became the Patriarch of Black Tiger Mountain.
Actually, I think my father
doesn't want to fight Heihu Mountain.
but he has no good ideas.
You have many ideas.
Can you help me?
Whether it’s true or not,
you're still the son-in-law of Qinglong Camp.
Right?
It's also your business.
Give me some ideas.
I'm talking to you.
Does it hurt again?
Wu Zhen.
Wu Zhen!
Have you seen Wu Zhen?
No.
He's healing himself.
Oh no.
He must go down the mountain to save his father.
I have to find him.
My lady.
has been sealed off.
No one can go down the mountain
no one can go down the mountain.
When did that happen?
Why didn't I know?
I thought escorting Mr. Zhao down the mountain
I would have accomplished my mission.
But I didn’t expect
Zhao and Kong
died in front of me one after another.
My mission failed.
But their mission can't be interrupted.
All swordsmen must be careful.
It's hard for me to do it on my own.
Now,
I can only go to Wu Jingyuan.
But where is Wu Jingyuan now?
Mr. He said he wanted to donate.
We're here to get something.
Our county magistrate is not home.
He's not at home. We can pick it up ourselves.
Adjutant Brigade.
Hello, Mr. He.
I’ll tell you where my dad’s money is.
But you have to promise me two conditions.
It depends on what it is.
First,
this money
you must use it to beat the devil.
Of course.
Second,
take me to Mr. Wu.
Mr. Wu?
Yes.
Mr. Wu Jingyuan, the teacher of the county academy.
Are you his student?
Okay.
I can promise you
these two conditions.
Follow me.
Brigade Commander Cui.
We have drought every year.
It's hot and running away.
That's all.
that we can count.
There's really no one here.
Really?
I heard that
you have food and money here.
Brigade Commander Cui.
I...
I admit it.
100 taels of gold.
100 taels of gold?
Mr. He, you're so straightforward.
You don't have to donate.
I've sent someone to pick it up from your house.
Brigade Commander.
Come in.
Say it.
Brigade Commander.
As you ordered,
Commander Li will lead the way.
We've arrived at Magistrate He's house.
Actually, he has already prepared
for us.
waiting for us to get it.
Really?
How much?
1,500 taels of gold.
12 boxes of silver.
and every concubine
and his concubines
There are so many of them.
Did you do as I said?
Yes, we have left
for Mr. He
to support our family.
I really admire
I really admire you.
Don't worry.
I will report this
to the First Warfare Command.
and make them remember your first merit.
I'll tell them.
you donated the money yourself.
It's better for me to take it.
Good donation.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Brigade Commander Cui.
Did Captain Li donate?
He's not as benevolent as you.
As far as I know,
he has a lot of money.
This is my order.
Take this money to help the refugees.
and the scattered army.
Those who want to join the army
Two silver dollars for reward. Train on the spot.
Those who don't want to be soldiers can eat and live.
Go fix the airport
And those old, young, and children.
Remember, make sure to arrange it well.
Just arrange it in the abandoned pit in the county.
and a kiln.
Go.
Yes.
Sit.
Thank you.
Sir, please come in.
Fang...
Why did you mention me?
Why do you mention me?
Brother, calm down.
If I don't mention you to him,
if I don't mention you.
Let me tell you.
A few days ago, he sent his men
almost all my assets.
Who should I complain to?
I'm so mad.
All these years,
for all these years.
That's not all.
I caught a commie a few days ago.
Oh Kyung-won?
Yes.
The teacher who plays shadow play
was also taken away by him.
We can't go on like this.
He's too arrogant.
We can't let him off so easily.
We have to think of a way.
We have to think of a good way.
Brother.
He has a commission letter.
Someone has a gun.
Back then,
your subordinates were all yours.
I have an idea.
Choi Moon-Kui.
Killing a Communist Party
can make Qinglong Fortress deal with Cui Wenkui.
Why don't I believe it?
Believe it or not doesn't matter.
As long as you follow my plan,
we'll get what we want.
Think about it.
What if the Communist Party
is the in-law of Shangguan Bao?
Exactly.
Wu Jingyuan is Wu Zhen's father.
Yes.
So
The problem now is
can you irritate Cui Wenkui
and let him fight Qinglong Fortress willingly?
Then...
I heard
Choi Moon-Kui placed the refugees
the refugees in the west.
and paid for food.
They don’t know about Qinglong Camp.
If we make them suffer,
Soldiers fight demons.
Two silver dollars each.
Is it true?
Yes.
Anyone who fights demons on the battlefield will be there.
What do you think, Mr. He?
I didn’t lie to you, right?
Take me to Mr. Wu then.
Okay.
Come with me.
Eagle, Wu Zhen must be a Communist Party.
Father.
From the day he went up the mountain,
I knew it.
How did you know?
I was not sure.
Before that,
the Communist Party came here before.
Eagle.
Have you seen this dagger before?
Isn't this his?
This is a token I gave to the Communist Party.
Eagle, come and sit.
When I first saw Wu Zhen open it,
I thought he was a new contact.
But I tested him twice.
He didn't know.
I also suspected
he was the murderer of the Communist Party.
Father, the Communist Party is...
That man
has left.
Eagle.
Can you tell me about Wu Zhen?
He's not Wu Zhen.
His name is Jennifer.
What? Really?
All recruits are assigned to the Corps of Engineers
Send them to the airport.
Tell them to repair the airport while training.
Yes.
Brigade Commander.
We have a lot of recruits now.
And our previous army
in our army.
I think
I'm not as good as an engineer.
I know.
Then why did you ask the recruits to fix the airport?
You two tell me
where is the only place
is?
The airport.
But there's one more thing I don't understand.
Go ahead.
Usually when we fight,
when we fight.
But this time you recruited all refugees.
We have soldiers,
but we're under a lot of pressure.
I've been thinking these days
why our soldiers
in war?
It's because when they fight,
when they were fighting.
The war hasn't started yet.
before the war.
How many major casualties
were hit by others
when we retreat.
But if they put their wife and children
behind them,
Then they'll get married.
They can only move forward.
They would rather die than retreat.
It does make sense.
I need to think about it.
Actually,
I learned it from the inmates.
You little...
What happened next?
We went to the airport together.
and met his father.
His name is Wu...
Oh what?
I don't remember.
I'm not his real father anyway.
After that,
we killed the traitor together.
In order to cover us,
he was caught by Li Gang.
Are you sure
is that man named Wu?
The Communist Party.
Before they killed their enemies,
the Communist Party.
Traitor.
Father, as you know,
I don't understand.
Anyway, I think...
Eagle.
Can you do something for me?
Go ahead.
Bring Cai back.
You want to see him?
with Mr. Kong?
Take Cai back to the fortress.
I’ll tell you
about this later.
Okay.
Dad, I’ll bring more men
to bring Cai to you.
No.
Don't tell anyone about this.
You mean
to go alone?
Now the fortress is in danger.
There are not many people we can trust.
You can’t go through the fortress.
Go back and pack up.
I'll wait for you in the backyard.
When the house is settled,
my wife and child will have money and food.
I'm relieved.
I'll join the army.
Do those Japanese!
Kill him! Kill him!
None of you can escape
from Qinglong Camp.
Stop!
Hello, Madam.
Miss.
Why did you bring me here?
You'll know soon.
Let's go down and have a look.
When
have such a place?
Eagle.
Look at these stones.
Is there any difference?
What's the difference?
Take it up and have a look.
Why is it so light?
It's full of gunpowder.
It can explode as long as it's plugged in a jar.
Why are we keeping so many bombs?
Actor watch.
Actor table.
Choi Bo-wol.
Li Qinghong.
and actors.
Li Hongda Yu Guofeng Gong Fan Cheng Kaiyan.
Yuewang Yang Zi Yi Tian Chenzhe Deng Kaimei Liang Dong
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhi Gang Kung.
Wang Jin, Liu Jiawen, Sun Jing, Wang Yukun.
Xu Fu and Wu Jianyu, Zhang Guangyan, Sun Yuanwen. Always.
Yang Tao, Chen Yao, Rui Qian in jungle competition.
Feng Yonghao, Wei Long, Deng Bao Quan, Wang Xiang.
Liu Hongguo, Yang Chenglin.
Jerome.D.
Chen Chen, Cui Weijie
Zou Lixiang, Xu Shidong, Liu Yongtao, Wang Mingqing
Zhao Jianhao, Li Xiaoyan.
Du Yiming, Chen Weigui, Wang Qingyong Jo Min-gul.
Staff table.
Director team.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Costume team.
Team B Costume Assistant Li Jinli Feng Xiaohui
The dressing team.
Art team.
Zheng Peng.
The prop team.
Set team.
Action team.
Joo Wol-ryeong.
Fireworks.
Fireworks Yao Jitao.
The firearm team.
Sun Hai.
The recording team.
Recorder, Li Zhen.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Rong Xijun.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Zhang Chenggui, Su Mingxin, Liu Hongxing, Di Yuping Xu Guanglle.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li Zhang Changchang.
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Chou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Wen Long, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jianping.
Xu Ying Quan, Yang Shuli, Chen Yongsheng, Liu Junfeng Liu Fu Min.
Cut.
[Photography of Wu Xiaobo]
behind the scenes, Shin Bae-jin.
[Shin Bae-jin]
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
dubber
Music production
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
The Steel Jade Association in Shanzhou District
The Jade Association of Shanzhou District.
[Sanmen Mingu Pu Theatre]
The Civilian Committee of Lingbao City
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
Jiangzhou City, Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Legal consultant Zhu Yongpeng.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong County Commission.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park.
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Commission
Henan Provincial Guangguang.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Provincial film and TV Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
[Qianzhou Cultural Development Co., Ltd.]
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
First reward Zhang Bing.
Reward Zhang Bing first.