This is Wang Xian!
What about Qi Feng?
There was never a Qi Feng.
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 6=
Du Ruo.
Do you intend to confess
to your crimes?
What do you mean, Commissioner Di?
The "water ghost" killings
were just a cover
for a personal vendetta.
You used Qi Feng's fake death
to murder Wang Xian,
Cai, and the others.
Must I lay out
every single detail for you?
Commissioner Di,
where is your proof?
You flinched
when you saw the charred corpse.
That's when I first suspected you.
When I said Laifu had confessed
and implicated Wang Xian,
you showed absolutely no interest
in where he was.
Lady Du,
didn't you care what happened to him?
With you on the case,
he'd surely be caught.
Because you knew he was already dead.
Dead men pose no threat.
You lied about Qi Feng's height
but forgot about his foot size.
You stayed silent
because the man lying there
isn't Qi Feng at all.
It's Wang Xian.
You didn't know his size,
so you didn't dare answer.
This is pure speculation.
I only wish it were.
You claimed
you saw Qi Feng screaming in the flames.
But Laifu testified
that the man on the bed
didn't move an inch,
even while burning alive.
That's because
you had heavily drugged him.
We found the apothecary.
He confirmed
the knockout powder in his stomach
matches the exact batch you bought.
Bring in the witness.
Make way!
Look closely now.
Is this the lady who bought
the knockout powder from your shop?
Yes, it's her.
It's this lady right here.
How ruthless...
I completely misjudged her.
Commissioner Di sees through everything.
I plead guilty.
I can't believe I ever trusted her.
What a cold-hearted woman.
How could she do this?
Six months ago,
after Wang Xian
admitted to killing Qi Feng,
I began practicing
Qi Feng's handwriting.
On that day,
(Ruo, meet at Buxianxian in two days)
I used a forged letter
(From Qi Feng)
to trick Wang Xian
into plotting Qi Feng's murder.
Impossible!
I knew how cowardly he was,
and that he wouldn't dare do it himself.
Once he hired his arsonists,
I played nice
and lured him to Buxianxian early.
I spiked his liquor
with a big dose of knockout powder,
and surrounded him with flints
to make absolutely sure he'd die.
Light it.
You do it.
You coward!
Don't you want to get paid?
Let's go.
Move!
Go!
But I never expected
that he would wake up.
Du Ruo...
How were you so certain
those two would set the fire?
I bribed the mystic Wang Xian hired
to plant a deep, unshakable belief
that Qi Feng was burned to death.
No...
He was burned to death.
He was burned to death!
Since water couldn't drown him,
I'll burn him alive!
Your Honor!
She deserves to die!
- Yes, exactly!
- Yeah!
She must be executed!
Silence!
Execute her!
There's a reason for everything.
You risked your life to do all this.
What drove you to it?
Wang Xian...
murdered Qi Feng,
and then he violated me.
And because I refused to marry him,
he repeatedly brutalized me.
Look at you.
You're not as beautiful
when you're hurt.
This fair skin
belongs to me.
But when I think
about Qi Feng touching you,
it sickens me.
Did I hurt you?
Ruo...
I'm sorry.
I...
I didn't mean to.
Ruo,
I couldn't help myself.
Ruo...
You're mine now.
Forget about him.
Start over with me.
We can start over.
Why won't you speak to me?
What a tragic story.
This fishing net...
I'm the water ghost.
She's the water ghost?
How is that even possible?
The Qi family shipwreck
was orchestrated by the Wang family.
I ordered men to sabotage the ship.
I'm the one who killed him!
Anyone who harmed my Qi Feng
deserves to die!
You two used to meet here in secret.
Now it belongs to us.
- So that's the truth...
- I see now.
They deserved to die.
The Wang family had it coming!
Commissioner Di, to protect my dignity,
you allowed me
to clear the Qi family's name
in front of everyone.
I am deeply grateful.
Ruo!
Commissioner Di!
It wasn't her!
It wasn't Ruo!
Father!
It wasn't her!
I'm so sorry.
I really am the water ghost.
I am the water ghost.
Father...
This is my final farewell.
First, I thank you for raising me.
I'll repay your kindness
in the next life.
Second, I wish you
a life free of worries.
Do not tire yourself
for my sake anymore.
Third...
I've been an unfilial daughter.
Despite everything,
I have no regrets.
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
Thanks to Commissioner Di.
Otherwise, the chaos here
would never have settled.
Now that the storm has passed,
Magistrate Cao,
you can finally get some sleep.
Indeed. Thanks to your brilliance,
I am
grateful to you, Commissioner Di.
Thank you so much.
If you truly wish to thank me,
just give me a small boat
and a capable boatman
to see us on our way.
That's easily done.
I'll see to it personally.
Right away.
(Memorial Tablet:
To My Late Son, Wang Xian)
Those officials
are only ever quick
when taking our money.
Xian...
I have
failed to keep you safe after all.
Scum like him deserved to die long ago!
Your daughter murdered my son!
I haven't settled that score with you,
and yet you dare come here!
Wang Xian was worse than a beast!
He violated my Ruo.
He deserved to die!
And what about you?
You destroyed the Qi family
and ruined Ruo's future!
You deserve to die, too!
Nonsense!
The Qi family died in a shipwreck!
What does that
have to do with my family?
Wang Dingrong,
did you really think
no one would ever know?
The very day the Qi family's ship sank,
I knew it was you.
Father,
everything is taken care of.
Now, it's your turn.
Your leg
must be broken.
Xian...
Can't we
just fake it?
Father,
brace yourself.
This is terrible!
My father broke his leg!
Somebody help!
Qi trusted you.
Without him,
would you even
have a place at the Salt Bureau?
And you repay him
by biting the hand that fed you!
You raised a beast
like Wang Xian!
Xian was my only son.
Whatever he wanted,
I would give him.
And Ruo was my only daughter!
I'll make you spend eternity
atoning for what you did to her!
Stop!
Let me go!
Wang Dingrong must
answer for his past crimes.
You cannot kill him.
Today,
I went to the provincial office.
I found no record from years ago
of the Ministry of War
requisitioning salt.
When the Qi family's ship sank,
why wasn't it recorded?
After the Wang family took over,
this official salt
was never dispatched again.
Let me ask you.
Was this shipment of salt
deliberately fabricated by you
just to harm the Qi family?
Wang Dingrong,
you and Wang Xian
conspired to commit murder.
You will be thrown into prison
to await your sentencing.
Take him away!
- Yes, sir!
Du Ruo has confessed to all the crimes.
The main culprit,
Wang Xian, is dead.
Why must you go to such extremes,
even sacrificing your own life?
Did you kill Wang Dingrong
to take the fall for her?
Do you want everyone
in Ruanjiang County to know
that the Bureau
arrested the wrong person?
Or...
are you the real water ghost?
Commissioner Di,
do you have any proof?
Of course I don't.
Du Ruo is the water ghost.
The evidence is solid.
Her methods are clear.
Guards!
Put up a notice
and inform the people
of Ruanjiang County.
Commissioner Di!
That is not the truth.
Not the truth!
What part of it isn't true?
Posing as the water ghost,
she used a hemp fishing net
to drag Sun Qi into the water
until he drowned.
As for Liu Shun and Jia Gui,
she waited until they were drunk,
trapped them in the net,
and sank them with heavy weights
until they drowned.
Commissioner Di,
Ruo is just a frail lady.
How could she drag large men like Sun Qi
into the water?
Then she must have had an accomplice.
I will get to the bottom of this.
Du Ruo
hated Wang Xian to the core
because of Qi Feng's death,
so she burned him alive,
and killed Cai to silence him.
To toy with an official
is an egregious crime.
It is unforgivable!
I'm the one who killed Wang Xian!
I killed him!
Wang Xian
destroyed the Qi family,
and violated my Ruo.
He deserved to die!
I had long been plotting
how to tear that beast
into a million pieces!
You're lying.
If you knew the Wang family
murdered the Qi family,
why would you
marry your daughter to Wang Xian?
Commissioner Di,
have you seen the scars
on Ruo's wrists?
I just wanted her to live.
After Qi Feng died,
Ruo suffered constant nightmares,
as if she had lost her soul.
She tried to kill herself.
During that time,
Wang Xian visited her frequently.
Let it go, Ruo.
He never left her side.
Until a year ago,
when Wang Xian came to propose.
To my surprise,
Ruo accepted with a smile.
Back then, I truly believed
she was willing.
I figured
the feud was only
between the Wang and Qi families.
As long as Wang Xian
truly cared for Ruo,
marrying into the Wang family
would give her a comfortable life.
It was only six months ago
that I found out
that this beast
was using my life to blackmail Ruo!
Remember?
Your face and neck cannot be bruised.
Not a scratch.
If your father comes to yell at me,
I'm afraid...
I won't be able to stop myself
from killing him too.
Ruo had no other choice!
Six months ago,
Du Ruo learned
that Wang Xian killed Qi Feng.
That was also
when you found out everything.
You planned these murders
for six whole months.
Yes.
I caught Ruo
practicing Qi Feng's handwriting.
I knew she wanted to avenge him.
I couldn't bear
to see Ruo's hands stained with blood!
So I became the water ghost
to do it for her.
I used Ruo's forged letter
to lure Wang Xian.
Impossible!
Are you saying
you killed all of them?
And Du Ruo
is taking the fall for you?
I really am the water ghost.
I am the water ghost!
I killed them all by myself.
When Ruo found out
I was the water ghost,
she wanted to protect me.
That's why she made up the story
about Qi Feng being the water ghost.
Father...
Qi Feng is the water ghost!
Killing Wang Xian for your daughter
is one thing.
But why murder
Sun Qi and the others?
Magistrate Cao,
if they hadn't murdered the Qi family
just for money,
none of this would have ever happened.
Whoever hurts my Ruo must die!
Then where is your proof?
In my study,
there is a River Transport Order
that I wrote to Wang Dingrong.
(River Transport Dispatch)
Is this the one?
Commissioner Di,
you knew all along.
Father...
Father?
Father!
Commissioner Di!
I did everything! I killed them!
My father is innocent!
Please let him go!
Ruo!
I've avenged the Qi family.
I also killed Wang Xian
to get justice for you.
It's been two years.
It's time to let go.
You need to start a new life.
That's not true, Commissioner Di!
It's not true!
I killed them!
Please let my father go!
Commissioner Di!
Ruo,
stop this!
Father!
Commissioner Di.
I'm not leaving, Commissioner Di!
Commissioner Di!
Father, I'm not leaving!
Father!
Commissioner Di!
I killed them!
Let my father go!
The peach blossoms
at Buxianxian this year
are exceptionally vibrant.
Yes.
Exceptionally vibrant.
(In this world,)
(the purest love)
(is a parent's love for their child.)
Commissioner Di,
forgive my ignorance,
but are we still arresting Du Ruo?
Why would we arrest her?
Because there are
no peach blossoms at Buxianxian.
They haven't bloomed yet.
Then why arrest her?
What do the blossoms
have to do with her?
Talk less, and read more.
Magistrate Cao.
Isn't the murderer
already in custody?
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
♪Breaking the chains
forged by the mist♪
I understand.
♪Praying she sees the sky once again♪
♪She plucks
the shimmering waves to adorn her brow♪
♪To attend this radiant display♪
Qi...
I'm all alone now.
Ruo!
(Yanbo Ferry)
♪As she wished♪
Wait for my return.
I will marry you!
Qi...
I'm here to marry you.
Am I beautiful?
You definitely are.
(The peach blossoms
at Buxianxian this year)
(are exceptionally vibrant.)
(Yes.)
(Exceptionally vibrant.)
(Ruanjiang County, Langzhou)
(Wangnian County, Raozhou)
(Part 2: Red-Faced Guardian)
♪Life is a dream,
a dream like chasing the wind♪
♪Yet I am lost within it,
refusing to wake♪
Help!
Someone's dead!
Troupe Master!
(Preview of Next Episode)
It's her.
Why is it her?
Divine punishment.
Must be divine punishment!
In the dead of winter,
she danced barefoot
endlessly
despite the frostbite on her feet.
It was as if her body wasn't her own.
It was as if
the Guardian
possessed Master's body.
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪