If the Imperial Inspectorate stops my work,
then His Majesty's favor would be wasted.
No, no.
I need to find another way.
Halt!
Stop right there!
We're from the Capital Prefecture.
Thank you, sir, for your help.
Chasing him down the street...
What crime did he commit?
Theft.
I...
I didn't steal anything.
I came to file a complaint.
I've been wrongly accused!
Shut your mouth!
One more word out of you,
and you'll be killed on sight.
Hold on.
The Imperial Inspectorate is on the case.
Lower your blade.
My lord,
this is a Capital Prefecture matter.
What?
A Capital Prefecture case—
the Imperial Inspectorate can't intervene?
You cried injustice.
What happened?
Can you take charge of this?
The Imperial Inspectorate oversees all,
granted by His Majesty himself,
with imperial authority.
So tell me, can I take charge?
My lord,
I'm a commoner from Zhenyuan County, Zhenzhou.
I accuse the magistrate, Ai Wenguang.
He fabricates charges and imprisons the innocent,
seizes property by force,
and treats lives as worthless, my lord!
The people of Zhenyuan County
have no way to survive!
I beg you, my lord, deliver us justice!
Silence!
How dare you!
Harming a commoner before the Imperial Inspectorate?
My lord,
perhaps you needn't trouble yourself with this.
Zhenyuan County belongs to Chongzhou Prefecture,
the Left Chancellor's fief.
The Left Chancellor?
The Imperial Inspectorate oversees all.
Who the hell is the Left Chancellor?
My lord,
I carry a petition signed by thousands.
Please, save the people of Zhenyuan County!
What are you standing there for?
Take him away, now.
My lord,
this is a Capital Prefecture case.
What you're doing breaks the rules.
Rules?
All of you, listen up.
The Imperial Inspectorate takes this case.
Anyone who dares resist
will stand trial at the Imperial Inspectorate.
My lord,
is this really necessary?
The Capital Prefecture is truly capable.
Right under the Emperor's nose,
a case like this—
you turned it into a theft charge.
Crawl back and tell your prefect:
when I find the time,
I'll be paying him a visit.
Thank you, my lord.
Eat slowly.
Don't choke.
Are you the only one from Zhenyuan County?
In answer to my lord,
there were over a dozen of us originally.
But we were hunted down all the way.
By the time we reached the capital,
only four or five remained.
The rest were seized by officials days ago.
Officials shielding each other,
all in collusion.
This isn't just about the Zhenyuan magistrate.
The whole bureaucracy is rotten to the core.
My lord,
do we still have any hope of surviving?
Rest assured.
With me here,
I will surely win you justice.
Thank you, my lord.
Please rise.
Seeing injustice, I must intervene.
Don't kneel before me again.
You and I are no different.
Young master,
you're really something.
The case is solved.
Exactly as you predicted.
Illicit affairs always lead to murder,
sordid feuds within noble households.
It's always the same pattern.
Young Master Ning,
let's just speak frankly here.
You're a young master from a noble house.
Coming to the Imperial Inspectorate
is just to gild your credentials.
But don't worry.
This time,
we'll state clearly in the records
that you assisted with the case.
That bit of trifling credit, though,
just leave it to us.
No wonder you've been cold to me.
You feared I'd steal the credit.
We're all brothers from now on.
On this case, I merely
provided a small clue or two.
How could I dare claim credit?
I'm not Feng Qizheng, after all.
Case solved, top credit goes to you.
When the reward comes through,
you take the lion's share.
Feng Qizheng? No way.
Hold on,
that man is selfish to the core,
never thinks of others...
Old Gao, what did you just say about me?
You called me selfish?
How dare you, Old Gao!
All right, all right, enough.
You two brothers, this time,
have toiled and worried day and night.
The top credit
rightfully belongs to you.
Oh, how could we possibly accept that?
Listen to Old Gao here.
As if we'd steal someone's credit.
We at the Imperial Inspectorate
always enforce the law impartially.
Credit goes where credit's due.
Lord Ning.
Ning Chen.
I underestimated you before.
Didn't expect you'd have real skill.
Feng Qizheng apologizes for his earlier attitude.
Brother Feng, you're too kind.
I have much to learn from you two.
How about this.
Once the reward money comes in,
I'll treat you brothers to food and drinks.
Now you're talking.
Brother.
Skip the meal.
True enough.
We've got to hit the Pleasure Quarter!
The girls there are truly stunning.
Listen, Old Gao.
Pleasure Quarter, Pleasure Quarter.
Is that all you ever think about?
Look at Ning Chen.
He's surely
a virgin, you know.
Still a virgin.
Aren't you going to lead him astray?
Just look at you.
This...
Brother.
Don't be nervous.
Brother Gao here is a man of passion.
Bold and straightforward.
When he says "Pleasure Quarter,"
he means investigating a case.
Investigating, yeah.
Come on, out with you.
What are you lot sneaking about for?
Nothing at all.
Ning Chen, come with me.
Wait, Ning Chen.
What did you do wrong?
Why is Golden Guard Pan's face
even uglier than when he smiles?
He looks ugly either way.
Ning Chen.
Old Pan's cold-faced but warm-hearted.
Tell you what, you go ahead.
We'll handle things here.
Right.
Alright.
Then this brother here,
I'll trust you to look after him well.
Don't worry.
My lords.
I didn't hear. I didn't hear.
Didn't hear a thing.
I really didn't hear anything.
Lord Pan.
Ning Chen.
Do you know your offense?
What did I do?
Grabbing a man from the Capital Prefecture.
Making enemies for no reason.
Getting Commander Geng impeached.
And reprimanded by His Majesty.
You did nothing wrong?
The Imperial Inspectorate's main duty is oversight.
Handling cases is only secondary.
Cases beyond the Capital Prefecture go to the Three Courts.
Cases beyond the Three Courts
are passed to the Imperial Inspectorate.
Golden Guard Pan.
Do you always rush to judgment
and scold subordinates without hearing them out?
How dare you!
You dare talk back to me?
Not only am I talking back,
I'm also questioning your competence.
Who gave you the nerve to question me?
Liang Jingru did.
Who is Liang Jingru?
The one who gave me courage.
Ning Chen.
I'll set aside this Liang Jingru for now.
But taking a man from the Capital Prefecture
violates the rules.
Send him back at once.
And if I refuse?
I'm not asking you.
I'm ordering you.
Cheeky brat.
He really is something different.
Chen.
Where are you storming off to?
What did Golden Guard Pan say?
Nothing at all.
By the way,
do you know where Commander Geng is?
I've been here so long
and still haven't met our chief.
Commander Geng?
The Imperial Inspectorate command post.
Got it.
Look after Li Si for me.
I'll treat you to the Pleasure Quarter.
We'll take good care of him.
Imperial Inspectorate Silver Guard Ning Chen greets Commander Geng.
What is it?
I have something here.
Please take a look, Commander.
A petition signed in blood.
Where did this come from?
Zhenyuan County folk came to file an imperial appeal,
but the Capital Prefecture's men
twisted it into a theft case.
I seized this from their hands.
Commander Geng.
The people of Zhenyuan County
would never have risked their lives
to come petition the Emperor
unless they were truly desperate.
Had I not come across this today,
the truth about Zhenyuan County
would never have come to light.
The Ministry of Justice and Capital Prefecture
can handle this.
Commander Geng.
I volunteer to go to Zhenyuan and uncover the truth.
Does Golden Guard Pan know?
He doesn't.
And he doesn't need to know.
Bypassing the chain of command: thirty lashes.
Wait till I return from this case,
and I'll take three hundred.
Did I say you could go?
Commander Geng.
What is this supposed to mean?
The Imperial Inspectorate answers to me.
Don't think His Majesty's favor
puts you above the law.