You little brats, finally here.
General Chen, forgive our delay.
Please pardon us, General.
I'll deal with you later.
Hurry, take this boy
back to the manor for proper treatment.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
Ning Ziming, as Minister of Rites,
a man of Confucian learning,
always preaching virtue and propriety.
Who would have thought
he'd raise three rotten brats like you.
You old...
General Chen,
today's incident is all a misunderstanding.
You are a man of great virtue and renown,
who rarely appears in the capital.
I hope you'll be magnanimous
and not hold it against my two brothers.
What?
Not calling me "old codger" anymore?
General Chen,
my brothers offended you first.
As the eldest son of Ning Manor,
I offer my apologies here and now.
I beg your forgiveness.
Big Brother, Second Brother,
what are you afraid of?
Who told him to hide his identity?
Besides,
our grandfather is the Left Chancellor,
also serving as Minister of Revenue.
The troops' provisions and pay
all depend on him, don't they?
Why should we fear him?
Third Brother,
am I wrong?
Our army has lost battle after battle lately.
These crude generals,
if they truly had any skill,
should go reclaim the lost lands!
Useless fools.
Strutting around in front of us youngsters,
what's the point of all that posturing?
How dare you!
Shut up, you fool!
I...
Are you saying
that our defeats in battle
are the soldiers' fault?
That's right!
Fine.
You ignorant brat,
who's never set foot on a battlefield,
yet you dare to spout such nonsense here!
Without our troops,
braving the snow and ice,
risking their lives in battle,
where would your wealth and glory come from?
Guards!
Sir!
Seize him!
Bring him to the palace at once.
Wait, Big Brother...
I'll ask Ning Ziming and the Left Chancellor face to face
who is truly to blame
for these military defeats!
General, please calm your anger.
Stop!
Father!
Please, save us!
General,
what has happened here?
You'd better
ask those fine sons of yours.
Speak up.
What happened?
Where's your fourth brother?
Father,
today's incident was purely an accident.
I thought our fourth brother was frail and weak,
worried he was going hungry and cold outside,
so I came to bring him back to the manor today.
But he held a grudge about leaving the manor,
and during the scuffle, he fell and got hurt.
I truly...
He's hurt?
Where is he?
I don't know.
You don't know?!
The General has sent Ning Chen back to the manor for treatment.
You two, hurry to the General's Mansion
and bring the Fourth Young Master back to recover.
Yes, Father.
Father,
we truly didn't know
General Chen Wu's true identity.
That's why
I offended him with my words.
Father,
today's incident
has nothing to do with me at all.
They can vouch for me.
What? Big Brother, you...
Shut your mouth!
Haven't you embarrassed us enough?
No, I...
General,
These worthless sons of mine
are young and ignorant.
Please forgive them.
Lord Ning.
Do you know what your fine sons
just said?
What's more,
they wanted to kill me.
What?
No, you...
Who said that?
Big Brother, Second Brother, you...
You wretched beast!
Father!
How dare you!
Do you have any idea
of the great service the General has rendered to our dynasty?
When he was killing enemies on the battlefield,
you weren't even born yet!
Enemy states offered a million taels of gold for his life
and still couldn't take it.
Who gave you the gall to speak like that?
Father, stop hitting me!
I was wrong!
Father!
Third Brother, don't blame me.
Noble house rivalries have always been this way.
General,
I have failed to raise my sons properly.
But please rest assured.
I'll take them home today
and discipline them severely.
Get out of here, now!
Halt!
You think you can leave just like that?
He's pushing his luck.
This old man,
does he really take me for a pushover?
Have they caused some other trouble?
Lord Ning,
your fine sons
said our recent military defeats
were all the troops' fault.
They also said
their grandfather, the Minister of Revenue,
is the one we brutes must all depend on.
Come.
Let's go to the palace now and ask His Majesty
just whose fault it really is.
Since when did the troops become the Left Chancellor's wards?
Has the Left Chancellor taken the court's funds and grain
as his own?
Does he not fear chilling the hearts of all our troops?
How could they cause such a huge disaster?
This won't do.
This must not be brought before His Majesty.
Otherwise,
all of Ning Manor will be doomed.
General, please calm your anger.
We've served together at court for years.
How today's matter came to this,
you and I both know well.
Let's speak openly.
What do you want?
Lord Ning, what do you mean by that?
You make it sound like I am extorting you.
It is just that winter is almost upon us,
yet the funds, grain, and padded coats
have yet to be secured.
Whenever I think of our troops
having to endure hunger and cold again,
my heart truly cannot bear it.
The court just cut military pay.
It seems this old man planned this all along.
I did not expect him to have such cunning.
Our soldiers risk their lives for the realm.
How can we let them go hungry and cold?
I will go back and petition His Majesty with the Left Chancellor at once
to make sure
the soldiers' food and clothing are taken care of.
On this matter,
do you have the authority to decide?
Rest assured, General.
I believe all the officials at court
deeply care about our soldiers.
Take your fine sons,
and get out of here.
Scram!
Let's go, let's go.
Thank you, General, for your magnanimity.
I shall take my leave.
Wait.
What is it now?
Lord Ning.
Your reputation...
I shall say no more.
I just want to tell you this:
Ning Chen is a fine young man.
If Ning Manor cannot accommodate him,
let me take him to the army.
This is all a misunderstanding.
Thank you, General, for the reminder.
I know how to handle my own affairs.
Farewell. Farewell.
General.
Are we just letting them go?
What more do you want?
The troops now have
their winter provisions and padded coats.
You really want to take this to His Majesty?
Let's quit while we're ahead.
By the way,
we have disturbed this household.
When the master returns,
give them some silver.
I have urgent business
and must enter the palace at once.
Yes, sir.
How is he, Doctor?
Lord Ning.
The Fourth Young Master's condition is grave.
Malnourished, weak, and frail.
His head was struck by a club.
In the future, he might even...
Spare me the details.
Treat him with the best medicine.
Rest assured, Lord Ning.
I will do my utmost.
Steward,
go with the doctor yourself to fetch the medicine.
And tell the kitchen
to stew an old hen for him.
Yes, Master.
One more thing.
Please keep today's matter confidential.
Rest assured, Lord Ning.
I understand.
I shall take my leave.
Chen'er.
You're awake.
Wasn't I at Xiaomei's place,
being harassed by Ning Xing and the others?
How did I end up here?
Chen'er.
Is there something you want to tell your father?
You...
No.
This boy has caught His Majesty's eye now.
I mustn't strike him.
Chen'er.
Why are you yanking your father's beard?
I wanted to make sure I wasn't dreaming.
Judging by your reaction,
this isn't a dream.
Of course it's not a dream.
I do care about you.
I've looked into this matter.
Your brothers
didn't mean to hurt you.
But don't worry,
I have already disciplined them.
Wow, this change in attitude.
Did Chang Ruyue mess up his head or something?
Lord Ning,
do you even hear yourself?
I'm your father!
Won't you even call me Father?
Don't.
Minister Ning,
a father like you,
is too high an honor for me.
It might cost me my life.
Just say it straight.
What is it you actually want?
Well...
Brothers fighting at home,
is a common occurrence.
I feel that,
family scandals shouldn't be aired in public.
Let's just drop this matter, shall we?
All right, Chen'er?
Lord Ning,
why don't you just call me Ning Chen?
It's easier on the ears.
I know
you don't like me.
But what a coincidence,
I don't like you either.
Insolent boy!
I am your father.
Speaking to me like this,
is completely unfilial!
There are no outsiders here.
There's no need for the phony act with me.
The reason you brought me back to Ning Manor,
we both know full well.
If you truly have any conscience,
let me leave Ning Manor.
You can't do any heavy labor.
You're no scholar, and no warrior.
If you leave Ning Manor,
you'll just starve to death on the streets.
That's no concern of yours, Lord Ning.
Even if I starve to death,
I won't sully
this auspicious ground of Ning Manor.
So,
please, Lord Ning, have mercy
and let me go.
Master.
You just woke up.
Your mind isn't clear yet.
Here's a bowl of medicine.
Drinking it will do you good.
I had this chicken soup specially prepared for you,
to help restore your strength.
Fourth Young Master, please drink the medicine.
There's poison in it, isn't there?
Fourth Young Master, you do love to jest.
The master truly does care
about you, Fourth Young Master.
While you were unconscious,
the master stayed by your bedside,
never leaving for a moment.
I have many official duties.
Get some rest early.
I will come see you tomorrow morning.
Oh, by the way,
Steward Liu will be guarding the door.
If you need anything,
just call him.
Such a swift change in attitude.
What on earth is he so wary of?