Old Lu.
What's the situation?
Based on the Mengna Valley book's records,
Chimi Jizhou was built inside a massive pit.
The Kunlun Mountains went through complex tectonic shifts,
with intense uplifts, folds, and fractures,
which formed the towering mountain range.
So I'm wondering,
could it be that, with the tectonic movements,
it's now buried deep underground?
I think it might be an imaginary space.
What on earth is that supposed to be?
All morning I've heard you talk about
this space and that space.
What does it actually mean?
If the space we're in is real space,
then an imaginary space might also exist.
A single point in real space
could, in imaginary space,
be an infinite 3D volume.
And an infinite 3D volume,
in imaginary space,
could be just a single point.
This...
This, this, this...
I don't get any of this.
What does it even mean?
This imaginary space thing,
I saw it before in Old Zhu's office,
in a science magazine.
It's like how a convex lens works, right?
It's called...
What was it called again?
Fourier transformer.
Right.
That, uh, transformer thing.
Why don't you explain it to everyone?
It's basically how a convex lens works.
Say there's a convex lens here.
The Chimi Jizhou we're seeing
is actually a virtual one,
an image formed by a convex lens.
If we find that convex lens,
we can pinpoint the real Chimi Jizhou.
Brother Chen, as far as the eye can see,
where on earth is there any convex lens?
It's getting late now.
We should turn in early.
We'll look for it first thing tomorrow.
Guess that's all we can do.
Then let's eat something first,
turn in early, and head out at dawn.
Let's go.
Anxiang.
This wind-eroded lake is full of water,
high in the middle, low on the sides.
It's exactly a convex lens.
A convex lens?
So, are you telling me
Chimi Jizhou is at the lake bottom?
Then go find me another convex lens!
Brother Chen,
the lake bottom is solid, right?
So how can a convex lens
form anything?
Project an image?
We just came up from the bottom yesterday.
Down there isn't solid ground.
It's a transparent glacier.
Brother Chen,
if we go down to the lake bottom,
just think about it,
what if we run into another fish swarm,
piranhas or something?
Going back down to find Chimi Jizhou,
wouldn't that be a dead end?
Who said we're going into the lake?
If Chimi Jizhou really is down there,
can you swim down and break the glacier?
Brother Chen,
do you already have a route?
Up the mountain.
No way,
climbing mountains again?
Let's go.
Such a beautiful lake,
why don't we just swim across?
Another stupid idea.
Swim if you want to.
Walking is much safer.
What could be in there? Look,
what could possibly be in it?
Take a look.
Look, look!
Look!
What...
What is that thing?
Calm on the surface,
but undercurrents surging beneath!
Quick, let's go, stay away from it!
Wait, aren't you going down there?
No, no, no.
Let's go swim at the reservoir instead.
Go, go, go!
Fatty,
what on earth was that thing?
How would I know?
Slow down!
Anxiang, take it easy.
Godfather.
What are you doing?
This place is so dangerous!
This cliff is bottomless!
If you had fallen just now,
you'd be smashed to pieces.
If you want to back out, it's not too late.
Did you pick this risky path on purpose,
to force me to give up?
I'm not as scheming as you.
Relax.
This is sedimentary rock. Very solid.
Hard to collapse, good for climbing.
But the key question now is,
how can you guarantee
where to dig and where to tunnel?
If we can't find the underground cave,
and we break through the lake bed,
won't we all be walking to our deaths?
So that's what you're worried about.
Have you ever dug a well?
No.
When digging a well,
the key is to find the aquiclude.
Clay, shale, igneous rock, metamorphic rock.
All easily form an aquiclude.
We just need to descend along this cliff.
Once we encounter such rocks,
and find the aquiclude,
we blast through from below,
and we'll definitely find Chimi Jizhou.
No.
We don't know what's down there.
Going down like this is too blind.
It's way too dangerous!
Tell you what.
We go down first to scout.
Fatty.
Officer He and I will go first.
You and Old Lu follow after.
Okay.
No, wait.
I suggest, Brother Chen,
that you go down alone.
We'll all wait up here.
Once you confirm it's safe down there,
then we'll follow you down.
That'd be safer and more reliable.
Be careful.
Got it.
Take it slow!
Stay safe, Brother Chen!
How did we end up running into
such a bunch of lousy people?
Why didn't he just fall and die earlier?
Here's what he's thinking.
He and Old Chen are both dying men.
If he pushes Old Chen too far,
Old Chen might take him down with him.
Bite your tongue!
You're the dying one!
Right, right.
Found the aquiclude!
I'm setting up the explosives!
Explosives?
Be careful!
Watch out!
Take cover!
Old Chen!
Chen Youxi!
Are you okay?
How is it?
I'm fine.
The blast made a hole.
I'm going to check it out.
All clear.
You can come down now.
Okay.
Miss He,
I really envy your father.
Don't tell me you wish
you had a daughter like me?
Miss He, to be honest,
as long as you're willing,
you can be my goddaughter anytime.
Just help me find Mengna Valley's secret,
and you'll be my hero.
You can inherit all of my assets.
We barely know each other.
How could I match Anxiang's devotion?
Of course you can't compare right now.
But bonds grow over time.
Besides,
compared to you, Anxiang's too young,
too inexperienced.
Lacks experience and is far too timid.
I'm warning you,
Anxiang trusts and is grateful to you.
You'd better drop that
use-and-discard routine of yours.
Otherwise,
you'll never find Mengna Valley's gates.
Fatty, stop swinging this rope, will you?
Stop swinging the rope!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
This is squeezing me to death!
Old Lu!
Fatty, what's going on?
I can't hold on anymore!
Old Lu!
Find a spot and brace yourself first.
I'll figure out a way to save you!
Old Lu, hang on!
Damn Fatty, catch it!
Okay, we're safe now.
Safe...
After you, Miss He.
Mr. Bi, thanks for lending a rope
at that critical moment.
A true buddy, a real pal.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
This might be the real Chimi Jizhou.
These densely packed caves,
like a honeycomb,
must be where the Mengna Valley people
once lived back then.
According to the Book of Mengna Valley,
the altar of Mengna Valley
lies at the very bottom of Chimi Jizhou.
It's an energy field of the serpent god.
So in Mengna Valley's social hierarchy,
the lower you go, the higher the rank.
These caves connect and descend in layers.
If we just keep heading down the caves,
we should be able to find the altar.
What's going on?
I'm guessing that explosive earlier
went off way bigger than expected.