National Radio. And Telvison Administration
When you're full, you're not hungry.
You have to be rich. You have to be confident.
Guys,
Black Tiger Mountain is now my territory.
The so-called feng shui takes turns
Now it's right in front of you.
As long as you follow me,
I'll make you enjoy your life.
is definitely better than
with Jinshan Liang.
Are you satisfied, Golden tooth?
Kill Jin San.
Master won’t let you go.
Jinya, who do you think you are?
I'm not convinced!
No! No!
No!
You...
There are still those who refuse to obey.
This is your end.
Which part?
The third place.
Impossible.
Brother Zhen San won't hide it from me after he changed his nest.
Let's go.
I thought the third son of this town would have some money.
He's even poorer than me.
Mr. Tian Yuan,
Working with you Japanese
You don't have only guns, do you?
The army won't treat you badly.
The gun will arrive in a month.
What about the money?
Don't worry.
We'll find the money soon. Okay.
Then you...
You can't even
you won't be able to make a few dog tails.
Where can I get the money?
Li Gang.
This is about stabbing a hornet's nest.
He's been fishing a lot these years.
He's fat.
I'm going to kill him.
What a fortune.
You can't kill him.
Why not?
It's like killing a chicken to get an egg.
Killing the chicken?
Look at this.
You won't understand.
I told you.
If you kill him,
if you kill him?
I see.
Mr. Tian Yuan is very talented.
Why did you kill a chicken to get eggs?
I didn't expect
the honest teacher
is actually an accomplice.
It's not too late
it's not too late.
You killed Zhou Zhongxiao.
If you have him,
he can only help the evil.
Tell me about it.
How many people are there in your party?
Too many.
I can't count.
Tell us the name and identity of the accomplice.
you won't have to suffer here.
If you want to continue teaching,
go back and teach.
If you want to play shadow puppets,
keep acting.
Why are you suffering here?
I want to eat wild meat.
Laughing and drinking the blood of Xiongnu
Let's start from the beginning.
Are you crazy?
Beat him to death!
Stop!
Commander Li.
Brigade Commander.
What are you doing?
We just caught an accomplice.
We're interrogating him.
He's an accomplice.
Communist?
I caught a traitor of the accomplice a few days ago.
but he ran over and killed me.
Captain Li.
You didn't even tell me you caught him, did you?
Yes.
I was too busy
I didn't have time to report to you.
This...
You just caught one person.
The airport is like the Japanese.
This old man
the teacher of our county school,
or a shadow puppet artist?
His surname is Wu.
Mr. Teaching.
A shadow puppet artist.
Okay.
How about this?
send him to my brigade.
I'll interrogate him myself.
No, Brigade Commander.
He's cunning.
For such a long time,
I didn't know he was an accomplice.
What if...
Captain Li.
Don't let such a trivial matter distract you.
Your main task now is to fix the airport.
You'll be beheaded.
Yes.
Mr. Wu.
Take care.
Brigade Commander, Mr. Wu is here.
Mr Wu.
Mr. Choi.
Please.
Mr. Wu, please.
Take care.
Mr. Wu, you must be hungry.
Please.
I didn't discipline my subordinates well.
Sorry for the trouble.
You just arrived.
It's not your fault.
Mr. Wu,
I have a question.
Could you tell me?
If Li Gang did it
the higher-ups,
I can tell you
he caught the right person.
I am the Communist Party.
You are a teacher.
Why did you join the Communist Party?
Do you really want to know?
I sincerely ask for your advice.
Brigade Commander Cui,
what is a country?
The country and the land.
Brigade Commander Cui actively fought against Japan
for the territory.
The aristocrats advocate three ethics.
Republic. Republic. Republic.
There is a word in every sentence.
When you can't fight for power, talk about democracy.
Talk about the territory when you want to protect your rights.
It seems you know a lot
about the National Party.
But you didn’t tell me
why you joined the Communist Party.
A good man has high ambitions and country comes first.
That's right.
But what is the root of a country?
It's the people.
The Communist Party
for the sake of 40,000 people.
I won't be a country slave.
They threw their heads and devoted their blood
They just want the people to live a good life.
This is the faith of the Communist Party.
I can be one of them.
I'm proud.
I know I don’t have much time.
But
I have no regrets.
Brother.
Recently, I've been taking a walk with a message.
shooting guns everywhere.
How about
send someone to look for it?
Has everyone been here recently?
No one else has been here except the Zhenshan Liang of Heihu Mountain.
Everyone else has been here.
Zhenshan Liang.
I'm also curious.
Among all leaders,
among all leaders.
Tell everyone who goes back today
We’ll go to the fortress every day.
and get the wrong clues.
OK.
Madam.
Master.
Liu, why are you here?
I've discussed with Third Brother of Heihu Mountain
to send a walk here every day.
We’ll switch bodies
once a day.
But he didn't come yesterday.
I know how he sprinkles dates.
But I went a few places
but I didn't see anyone.
Why didn't you go up the mountain and ask?
I was supposed to bring someone up the mountain.
But when I arrived at the end,
I saw a firecracker.
You even set off letters on Black Tiger Mountain?
Not only that,
there was a sound in the village.
I was confused and worried something might happen.
so I didn’t dare to go up the mountain.
So I came here to ask you
what to do.
Something really happened to Black Tiger Mountain.
Do you want to take someone to have a look?
Wait.
I'll go by myself.
Please don't, boss.
The situation is unknown.
You stay in the fortress.
I'll find out the truth for you.
Be careful.
Master, please.
Master, someone wants to see you.
I ate too much today.
I'm sleepy.
Send him away.
He said he just invited you to dinner.
You're not here for money, are you?
He even brought gifts.
It looks heavy.
Let him in.
Yes, Master.
Please, sir.
Please come in
The county magistrate is inside.
Hello, Mr. He.
Hello.
You're too polite today.
You bought me dinner.
Thank you.
Please sit down.
I feel ashamed.
I wanted to arrange a feast
to invite Magistrate He.
But I didn't want to take the liberty.
That's why it's simple.
I'm here to prepare some gifts.
for you.
Please accept it.
Sir.
You treat me to dinner and give me gifts today.
Why are you so polite?
It's my duty.
Sir.
I'm sure everyone wants something.
Tell me.
What can I do for you?
I’m flattered.
I have nothing to ask you.
I just want to talk to you
you are interested in.
Who are you?
Look who I am.
Sir.
You're handsome and elegant.
You must be a successful businessman.
Okay.
Businessmen are right.
Today,
I also want to talk business with you.
Sir.
You got the wrong person for business.
I'm just an ordinary parent.
I know nothing about business.
Besides,
I'm not interested in business.
Mr. He, business is simple.
It's just an exchange.
I use what I have
for what you have.
I may not be interested
what you have.
Besides,
I may not give you my things.
Back off.
Sir.
Are you Japanese?
You are really knowledgeable.
But I didn't say any conditions.
Why didn't you agree?
Tell me
what business is it?
If you work with me,
I guarantee your wealth
in the future.
Mr. He,
There's an old Chinese saying
"A wise man submits to fate."
Now the army of the Japanese Empire
has conquered half of China.
Even Fuyang
is in our hands.
Soon,
the whole Shaanxi will be plugged in the flag.
So, Mr. He,
the sooner you make a decision,
the better it is for you.
Do you have any other ideas?
Sir.
Then tell me
How are we going to work together?
Arrange a place for us to stay.
We'll talk about the cooperation later.
Sir, I don't think it's appropriate.
Think about it.
You live here in broad daylight.
Dad, I'm going out.
Zheng'er, don't wander around.
Go back to your room and study.
Mr. He is really handsome.
But the world is not peaceful now.
It's not safe to go out often.
If anything goes wrong...
Sir.
What's your name?
Masao Tahara.
Mr. Tanaka.
I'll arrange a place for you.
Stop!
Come here.
What did you bring?
Wait.
What's wrong?
Something is wrong.
This is mountain stuff.
Okay.
What is this?
These are mountain goods.
This is food.
Leave this here. Let's go.
No, no.
This is the youngest of our family. Get lost.
What are you doing?
Can you take a look first?
What's there to see?
I think Zhenshan Liang wants to quit.
Do you think he'll do that?
Get lost.
Yes, it's strange
Uncle Sanxing doesn't do anything to the people.
Even if something is missing,
they must go down the mountain to sell.
Wait here.
I'll take a look.
I'll go.
You can't even walk.
How can you go?
Give me your token.
What are you two doing?
Do you think I'm air?
You didn't even discuss with me.
You're the young lady.
We should go first.
You're always right.
Think about it.
If anything happens in the fortress,
Even if we were caught,
they won't threaten your father with us.
But what if you were caught?
what would your father and all swordsmen do?
Now everyone
knows you are the son-in-law of Qinglong Camp.
It's the same if you get caught.
It's not a big deal.
I'll go.
Stop fighting.
We don't have much time.
Give me the brand.
Don't worry.
If anything happens,
we will save you.
Take care.
Mr. Wu, how about this?
You should go back
and continue to be your teacher.
I won't give you a hard time.
In chaos,
There is no table in China.
Without students,
As a teacher, I'm naturally a decoration.
Then you can do your favorite shadow puppet play.
You're a soldier.
We are in the field of intelligence
our intelligence.
What do you mean?
From the moment I was found,
my life has ended.
Are you afraid
I use you to fish?
No.
Although we don't know much about each other,
I know
you and Li Gang are different.
There are two parties now.
seems to be working together.
So...
I know
you won't make things difficult for me.
I'm willing to treat you as my brother.
Brigade Commander Cui, if you don't mind,
I want to live here for a few days.
If I can wait until the day I exterminate the Japanese,
I would have no regrets.
What if I promise you
no one will harm you?
No, no, no.
I trust you.
And once something happens,
I don't want to suspect you.
Brigade Commander.
What should we do with him?
Let me think about it.
The mountain goods were good.
I'll cook it tonight.
Okay.
Stop!
Where are you coming from?
They will ask where you came from.
Just answer the King's Palace.
Golden Palace?
Whose beard?
If he asks you whose moustache,
just tell him
he knew you were from Qinglong Camp.
Supreme Lord Lao.
Let's go.
Good job, guys.
Oh, no! Secret Cannon!
Something really happened here.
Go back and find Madam.
and bring more men.
It'll be too late then.
Good harvest today.
Stop!
Sir.
There's someone outside.
asked me to give this to you.
He said he wanted to see you.
Do you know him?
No.
He said his surname is Tian.
Tian.
Bring him in.
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm Tian Zhengyuan.
We met at Qinglong Hideout a few days ago.
Qinglong Fortress?
It does look familiar.
A bandit.
Do I look like one?
Communist?
Nor.
Are you
are you working for Brigade Commander Cui?
Captain Li, stop guessing.
I’m nobody’s man.
I’m just an arms dealer.
arms business.
Why are you here?
A few days ago,
I saw the commander of security
is worthless to Choi Moon-Kui and the swordsman.
Don't you think it's pathetic?
What do you mean?
Calm down, Captain Li.
I’m here to help you.
Help me?
How?
You have people, I have guns and bullets.
I can give you both.
Take down Choi Moon-Kui!
Defeat Choi Moon-Kui
If I could bring Choi down,
I wouldn't have fixed the airport here.
So with Choi Moon-Kui,
there will never be a day for Captain Li to stand out.
Why don't we work together?
Why should I trust you?
Tell Captain Li the truth.
I had a grudge with Choi Moon-Kui.
If we work together,
we can not only get rid of Cui Wenkui,
the whole Shanzhou
will belong to Captain Li.
In the future,
in the future.
Stop!
What are you doing?
I told you not to come up.
Of course, you'll die here if I don't come up.
Do you know it's dangerous here?
Do you know if you die here,
I'll be a widow.
Being a widow is a lie.
Don't forget
we are engaged.
My father takes it seriously.
You can't die
you can't die.
Besides,
I saw them set off hidden firecrackers.
How can I not come up?
Secret cannon? What hidden cannon?
Red represents bright cannon.
Black represents dark cannon.
What's the difference?
Secret cannon is only bright.
It means enemies.
As long as a hidden cannon is seen,
within their control,
within their control.
A clear cannon is a courtesy.
Can't we just put the cannon here?
Are you stupid?
The head card just let off the hidden cannon.
How do we do it now?
Let's go first.
Why are you so smart all of a sudden?
I'm smart every day.
Learn from me.
No.
Something must have happened.
How did you know?
Uncle Zhen San is very meticulous.
Even my father always praises him.
But look,
There are light in the village.
There’s no one at the door.
This is definitely not Uncle Sanxing.
Let's wait
Let's wait and see.
You'd better hurry up.
We have to save your father after this.
The third in town are so stubborn.
Isn't it good to be with me?
Of course I need your meat.
I went up the mountain
for the head of town.
are two heads of the security group down the mountain.
You want me to convince you?
You don't deserve it.
Okay. You're a man.
I'll grant your wish.
Men, dig a bigger hole for me.
Bury it with those guys.
Wait.
Boss.
If you trust me,
give these bastards to me.
I only need one day.
to make them listen to you.
If you are capable,
you can't escape.
They are all masters.
They will follow you in the future.
Just wait and see.
Guards!
Take them all.
Lock them up!
Yes.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
You are wise.
What did you do before?
A doctor.
Selling some herbs in the county
He's a writer.
I need a counsellor now.
If you can
this job,
it's yours.
Thank you, boss.
Go.
Wait.
He's not your real father.
Then your real name isn't Wu Zhen anymore.
How did you become so smart?
Cut the crap.
What's your real name?
Is that important?
Of course.
We're engaged.
I don't even know your real name.
Do you think it makes sense?
Fine.
I can tell you.
But you can't tell others.
my name is Jennifer Cai.
Jennifer.
What kind of steamed buns are they?
I'm asking your real name.
Yes, my name is Jennifer Cai.
Are you lying to me again? Tell me the truth.
Believe it or not. I'm not lying.
Is it really called this name?
Why would anyone call it vegetable buns?
Let me ask you something.
Go ahead.
Are you afraid of dogs?
Is that meat bun?
You are so cunning.
The 18 swordsmen in Moyun Ridge
have different sources.
Since you told me your secret,
I'll tell you too.
You're loyal.
I heard from my father and Mr. He that
besides Qinglong Hideout,
we have 17 swordsmen.
There are six hills.
were found several decades ago.
in order to make a living,
to make a living.
Look, it's like the spring valley, the hawk tent mountain.
Bug Ridge and Baliang.
These four hills
have been passed down since then.
Basically, these people
are not under the control of Qinglong Camp.
and all the strongest.
who ranks second
and the Meng Shi rule of Tianchi Mountain.
But these two
are quite close to Qinglong Fortress.
I haven’t heard
they go out and do whatever they want.
There must be
in these six mountains.
At least 30,000 people.
Under my father's management,
Qinglong Hideout
Black Tiger Mountain, Qingfeng Hideout,
Eighteen plates of Song Iron Tower.
Mount Heishan, Mount Yanzi,
Water Ravine and Swallow Mountain.
These mountains have always been well-behaved.
But even if they are rich,
I'll ask my father in advance.
I've never hurt the people
never hurt the people.
Awesome.
Of course.
Otherwise, the swordsman in Moyun Ridge
would have such a reputation.
Take this box away.
Take all these books.
Okay.
Guys, we have delicious food.
Come in.
Let's eat inside.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
At least you won't die so soon with your golden tooth.
Time to eat.
Here.
Let's eat.
What are you thinking about?
When I went up the mountain,
the boss said
we are not bandits.
I know you are not bandits.
So don't rush to die.
You're going to die.
Who will deal with these bandits?
Wait for me.
Come out.
Come out!
Thank you for saving my life.
Don't thank me.
This is not a place to thank me.
Don't you have poison?
It doesn't matter
It doesn't matter.
What matters is
those who have been around him these days.
Who?
I can't identify him yet.
Get him.
and ask him.
He went down the mountain.
But I heard someone went up the mountain.
I don't know which way.
I heard they might be friends.
Although Jintooth is not popular,
but those with evil intentions
are willing to work for him.
The 18 swordsmen
are his men.
So I want to get you out.
Go back and tell Madam about the situation here.
Don’t let them
to die.
What about you?
You can't get out without me.
No.
You've saved our lives.
To be honest,
I've been in touch with the head of town.
He saved my life.
Who are you?
He's a Communist Party.
He was rescued
from Li Gang.
That day, I was...
When I was exposed,
the head of the town led the brothers
to save me.
He also promised me to join us
to fight the Japanese and save the country.
What a pity.
I have to find a way to get you out.
Mr. Wu.
I got these books
according to your instructions.
Brigade Commander Cui.
I'm very satisfied
in prison.
But these books
are not all mine.
But this is indeed the book I retrieved from your mansion.
These two books are for you.
Let's say
for dinner.
I can afford this.
Besides, I've learned the way of Confucius and Mencius since childhood.
But I would like to ask you
the essence of Confucius and Mencius.
Actor table.
Lee Seung-yup.
and the actors.
Li, Yu Hongda, Tian Guofeng, Gong, Fan, Cheng Kaiyan.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile Wang Lusheng.
Yue Wang Yang Ziyi Tian Chenzhe Deng Kai Mei Liangdong.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin, Wang Yukun.
Shou, Chen Yao, the Longevity Race.
Wu Jinxing, Feng Yonghao, Wei Long, Deng Bao Quan, Wang Xiang.
Liu Hongguo, Yang Chenglin, Liu Yinlong.
Li Jinyang, Zhang Jianing, Liu Rong Qi.
Li Zhendong, Chi, Rui, Zhang Ke'er, Yang Junjie.
Wang Qingyu, Feng Qimeng, Chen Weipeng, Zhi Ji. Wang Yan Qing.
Staff table.
Director team.
Lizi.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Cho Jeon-min.
Costume Team.
Costume team.
The dressing team.
Zhang Zefeng.
The atmosphere design, Lei.
The prop team.
Choi Guangchung
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Kang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Rong Xi.
Ge Wenlong, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jianping.
Yang Shuli, Chen Yongsheng, Liu Junfeng, Liu Fu Min
Cut.
[Shin Bae-jin]
[Late production]
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
dubber.
A dubber?
Music production.
Tang Tiantian.
Theme song, Hero.
Final production: Wang Chenyang.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
Golden Golden Golden Golden Golden Valley.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
[Jangok Association, Shanzhou District]
Shanzhou District, Temple, Village Scenic Area.
The Villager Committee of Lingbao City
Maple Theatre, Mumei City.
The village committee of the old store in Shanzhou District.
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
The People's Government of Sanmen City
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
There are three branches in total.
The People's Government
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong County Commission.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
The People's Government of YongChi County.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park]
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
Jiangjiang Dongyang Mai Jiang Culture Co., Ltd.
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
[Qijin Cultural Development Co., Ltd.]
Qijin (Quan Zhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Zhang Bing will be rewarded first.