National Radio. And Telvison Administration
Why is it so light?
It's full of gunpowder.
It can explode as long as it's plugged in a jar.
Why are we keeping so many bombs?
You'll know soon.
Follow me.
Eagle, be careful.
Slowly.
Dad, why did you build this path so narrow?
Can't you expand it?
This is also an idea from the Communist Party.
If the villains find this secret tunnel,
there's only one person left.
It'll be easier to guard like this.
What if they expand this?
If one of the pillars is destroyed,
this place will collapse.
Eagle, watch out.
Slow down.
What if someone attacks us?
what if we are defenseless?
Only the door
can only be opened from outside.
Come out from the inside.
The password must be right
until the code is right.
Is this the idea of the Communist Party?
I see.
The bombs at the door
If we lose this place,
we can blow up the entrance.
You're right.
This is the biggest difference
between the Communist Party and the National Party.
They have no money or guns.
But because of this,
their moves are simple and practical.
That's what your father admires the most.
But Father,
why are you telling me this
at this time?
There were three people who knew about this place.
I, Jinshanliang,
and the Communist Party surnamed Kong.
Now both of them are gone.
I'm just afraid.
What if? There's no what if.
Eagle, remember.
I'm in a hurry to give you something or make a promise.
have ulterior motives.
That's all
for now.
Go and find Jennifer.
I have something to tell you.
Let’s go.
Boss! Boss!
Please help us!
Boss!
Help us! Help us!
Boss.
Guys, get up first.
Don’t worry.
As long as Qinglong Fortress can do it,
I will help you.
Madam.
We just came here.
I heard a team is recruiting soldiers.
But who knew the Brigade Commander had no say in it.
and locked us up.
and drove our women and children
our women and children.
I don’t know if they’re dead or alive.
Boss,
We finally escaped.
Boss.
Boss, please help us!
Guards! Tie him up!
Boss.
Did Golden tooth send you here?
I am famous here.
but not yet.
You can recognize me
you can recognize me at a glance.
And your hands.
I don't care
or a sailor,
will not only leave calluses
in the second part of the index finger.
Tell me.
Did Golden tooth send you here?
Give the letter to the communication soldier.
Tell him to give it to the First Warfare Command Center.
Yes.
Brigade Commander Cui.
Brigade Commander Cui, bad news!
The refugees from the east of the village came to complain to me.
Refugees?
They said a group of swordsmen
took away
but also abducted a bunch of young men.
Swordsman!
Where are they?
They're all with me.
Go take a look.
Find Jennifer Cai for me.
Be careful.
Don't panic.
Father, I've remembered what you said.
Go.
Did they really say they are from Qinglong Camp?
Yes, sir.
They also said
no swordsmen will be killed.
My man refused.
They kidnapped me.
How many people did they take?
They came with us.
As long as they are capable,
as long as they are capable.
The money and food you gave
and grain left.
How can we live
How will we live in the future?
Sir, please help us!
Sister-in-law, come here.
Don't worry.
Brigade Commander Cui will help you.
These bandits are so despicable.
They are outrageous!
Why does he Huo the poor people?
Sir.
Here, Mr. Wu.
Mr. Wu.
Brigade Commander asked me to ask about your injury.
Tell the Brigade Commander to focus on work.
I'm fine here.
Don't think about it.
By the way, this is the best white medicine.
Take care of it yourself.
What do you think?
I'll keep my word.
Did you hit Mr. Wu?
Of course not.
Mr. Wu is so knowledgeable.
How could we
a knowledgeable person?
By the way,
when you see Mr. Wu,
ask him what he wants to eat now.
What do you want to drink?
What do you want to do?
What kind of person do you want to meet?
you can send a message to him, right?
Stop!
Who let you in?
He's Mr. Wu's student.
I asked him to come here.
Hello, sir.
Okay, let's go. Please.
Stop!
Who asked you to deliver food?
Mr. Wu.
What are you waiting for? Call the military doctor.
Yes.
Get him!
Why are you here?
I couldn't find you, so I went to your house.
I saw the radio.
Give this
to
A man called
Wu Zhen.
Remember.
I got it.
From now on,
I can't teach you anymore.
Mr. Wu
Mr. Wu.
Mr. Oh.
Looks like Wu is still alive.
But his life is in danger.
Where will he be locked up by Choi Moon-Kui?
I have to find him as soon as possible.
You guys go over there.
Yes. Yes.
Lieutenant Cui Wenkui.
What are they doing?
Wu, what do you mean?
Did you catch
Mr. Wu?
No.
We did catch someone recently.
But I don't know
where Mr. Wu
is locked up?
Follow me.
Come.
Come here.
Mother.
Why is the porridge getting thinner?
We've seen him.
It's good to have something to eat.
Keep sending it there.
OK. The water is boiling.
Coming
Help me stir it. OK.
Master, when will Madam
attack Black Tiger Mountain?
I’ll ask him myself.
Don’t disturb Madam.
How dare you stop me?
Keep an eye on him.
If you move again, tie him up.
Master Liu, do you understand?
I'll go check the backyard.
Master.
You...
I've long heard that there's a gold mine in our three provinces.
I didn't expect it to be in Qinglong Fortress.
Great.
Master and you are so far-sighted.
and thoughtful.
I'm just a mediocre person.
The secret of the gold mine is very important.
I hope you can keep it a secret.
Don’t worry.
I will keep my mouth shut
and keep this secret in my stomach.
All right.
Go out and do your own business.
I'll leave the disaster relief to you.
Yes.
Master.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
What flag is it?
It's okay.
Heroine, we escaped here.
As soon as we moved in,
they rob and rob people.
May I know your name?
We will repay you for saving our lives.
You're welcome.
Qinglong Camp, Shangguan Eagle.
Qinglong Fortress! Run!
Master Soldier! Master Soldier!
There are bandits!
Bandit! Hurry!
Does Liu want to go down the mountain again?
I can handle Liu.
They don't understand.
Black Tiger Mountain is easy to fight.
But after this war,
Yu Xidao will no longer exist.
Are you worried about ghosts?
We both know Jinya's temper.
He's strong on the outside, but he can't solve problems.
How dare he
how would he dare to provoke Zhenshan Liang?
I know.
Since you have a golden tooth,
I have to worry
someone else is following him.
Yes.
Although he's not good at work,
he does have a few men
close to him.
So it's not that I don't want to fight Black Tiger Mountain,
but to get it in one shot.
What's wrong with you?
Do you have something to say?
That's right.
Say it.
That accountant.
The deficit is huge.
This year, every mountain
in the mountain this year.
The scenery of the drought was almost cut off.
The food at the fortress is purchased.
Now there are so many refugees here.
We can't handle them.
My wife just told me
the porridge in the soup kitchen is so thin that it can see a person.
Go. Take these.
and distribute them to every fortress.
What is this?
Just take a look and you'll know.
Where did you get this?
Thirty years of swordsman.
I have enough money.
Go to the emergency and buy more food
Change the porridge into dried rice
You're so thoughtful.
You're right.
Go.
Go comfort everyone first.
As for Jaws,
let him live a few more days.
As long as no one follows him,
we will fight this battle sooner or later.
Where is he?
He's probably dead.
What do you mean?
You're a commie.
Brigade Commander Cui may be kind to you.
But I'm different from him.
Are you a general or a commander?
It doesn't matter what I am.
What matters is I can't watch you
watch you fight the bandits here.
Cui Wenkui hesitated
and let you succeed.
Tie him up.
Wu Jingyuan died too.
At this moment, I'm helpless.
Sacrifice in blood
was not just on the battlefield.
I started to doubt myself for the first time.
I'm not afraid of killing enemies.
I'm just afraid that I can't finish it.
the mission left by the Commissioner Zhao
to let their blood go in vain.
Give me back my man!
You killed my man!
Give it back!
How can I live?
Give my man back!
Give my son back!
Give me back my son!
Give me back my man!
I have a family.
Shangguan Eagle!
Give my son back!
How are we going to live?
Kill the bandits! Kill the bandits!
Kill the bandits!
Master!
Kill them!
Kill these bandits! Kill them!
Kill the bandits!
Kill the bandits! Kill the bandits!
Silence!
Quiet!
Listen to me.
I'm your parents.
I will
whatever happens.
Don't worry.
What's the identity of the murderer?
She claimed to be Shangguan Ying from Qinglong Fortress.
The leader of Qinglong Fortress, Shangguan Bao.
Who are you?
Cut the crap. That's my father.
Fine.
You admit it so easily.
Let me ask you.
Did you send someone to rob?
Notraiders?
Admit it.
That's not true.
You're a man of honour.
In my jurisdiction,
Anyone who breaks the law must be punished.
It's not enough to calm the people's anger
That's right. The county magistrate is right.
Do you admit it?
Don't talk nonsense.
If you don't admit it, I'll torture you.
Fine, torture her.
Let's see who dares.
torture her.
Let's see who dares!
Stop!
Brigade Commander Cui.
Why are you startled?
Mr. He.
It's quite lively here.
Let me introduce.
This is Brigade Commander Cui
Brigade Commander Cui from Yuxi independent Brigade.
He will help you.
We will punish the bandits of Qinglong Camp severely.
Brigade Commander Cui, help us! Let me go!
Brigade Commander Cui, please help us! It's not true!
That's not true.
Mr. He, you're so sweet.
You lift me so high.
What if I lose face?
Brigade Commander Cui, this is all your doing.
According to the people,
of course you are very prestigious.
I believe you will be impartial.
Brigade Commander Cui! Punish the bandits!
Punish the bandits! Punish the bandits!
Listen to me.
Be quiet.
This man...
can't be killed yet.
As for why, think about it.
If we kill her,
what about those who were taken away?
That's right.
What do you think, Mr. He?
Brigade Commander Cui.
I didn't think about that.
Brigade Commander Cui is right.
We can't kill him now.
Why?
Kill her. Those men who were taken away.
What should we do?
Right?
That makes sense.
Brigade Commander Cui, what should we do next?
If you trust me,
give me three days.
In three days,
in three days.
But before we find out the truth,
I have to take him away.
Mr. He, is that okay?
Do as Commander Cui said.
Captain Zhu. Yes.
Take him away. Yes, sir.
Get lost!
Brigade Commander Cui, take care.
What happened?
Have a seat, Miss Shangguan.
Have a seat.
Sir.
Come in.
Get out.
Drop the gun.
Let her go.
Tell your men to behave.
How dare you!
Do you know what you're doing?
Of course I do.
I'll say it again. Let her go.
You guys go out first.
Close the door.
Without my order,
no one can come in.
Can't you hear me?
Brother, you saved my life.
I'll give you a chance.
You can leave.
She must stay.
If you let her go, I'll stay.
I'll take full responsibility.
What did you say?
Take the responsibility.
Can you bear the resentment of tens of thousands of refugees?
I can't.
But I can bear the responsibility of killing my father.
Kill my father?
Your father is dead.
What are you talking about?
There are many things you don't know.
This jade pendant
was given to me
when I saved you.
I don't need your help.
As long as you let her go,
I'll let you live a few more days.
Let's settle
Let's calculate it separately from now on.
Let her go.
But if she really leaves,
the refugees and swordsmen will die.
Have you thought it through?
I’ll stay.
as the young master of Qinglong Fortress.
This is enough.
Let's go together.
We'll die together.
We accidentally caught Shangguan Eagle today.
The more you tie it, the more you die.
Leave this woman to me.
Don't touch her.
Brother, take it easy.
When the world is ours,
Who can't you take?
Let me tell you.
She's a tough girl.
Don't let her make a big mistake.
Everyone,
We won the first battle.
You three contributed a lot.
Everyone will be rewarded in the future.
Mr. Tanaka.
What should we do next?
Golden tooth.
Mr. Tian.
Tonight, you pretend to be a member of Qinglong Fortress
to take revenge on the refugees.
Please do your best.
Wonderful.
In the guise of avenging Shangguan eagle,
the refugees
hate Qinglong Fortress even more.
Cui Wenkui will lose face.
The result will be the same if we fail.
Brother,
Let me tell you.
Choi Moon-Kui is not bad.
You might lose a lot.
I can't kill him.
Of course Choi Moon-Kui is good.
But he didn't know
someone will take revenge tonight.
But...
Captain Li knows that you're a good person.
Don't worry, Mr. Tian.
Everything is under control.
Brother,
You killed several refugees
you killed a few refugees
and take revenge.
Captain Li.
You're outside the city.
and then withdraw.
The reputation of Qinglong Camp will be ruined.
Our leader, Li, will be famous.
Kill many birds with one stone.
Please.
Did Madam really say that?
He said it’s not the right time.
I'm suffocating.
Now is not the time.
When will it be?
Wu Qiusheng. Leader.
Madam, I’m not impatient.
Sit. I...
Take these swords tokens
with these swords.
Order Song Tie Building, 18 plates, Heishan Temple,
Mount Yanzi, Mount Bang, Longtan Ravine,
The head of the Six Fortress.
to deploy 200 soldiers.
to attack Black Tiger Mountain tomorrow morning.
Yes, Madam.
Madam.
I thank you on behalf of Third Brother.
Go.
Take care.
Yes.
Fly on the boat.
You lead enough men
to block all roads of Heihu Mountain.
You are not allowed to go in or out.
Yes.
Brother.
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Wait.
Brother, I'm going to attack the mountain too.
You can go with Air.
Please give me an attack token.
Sister.
Don't worry.
I promise you'll catch the gold tooth.
I promise you.
let her go.
I don't need your kindness.
I'm not leaving.
If you don't leave, I'll die here now.
If you die, I’ll die too.
Tell Madam
he will come to save me.
Actually, I also want to see Patriarch.
I didn’t talk to you.
I promise nothing will happen.
Eagle, focus on the overall situation.
You should go back.
Trust me.
Have you discussed it?
Captain Joo.
Yes.
Send Miss Shangguan back to Qinglong Fortress.
Miss Shangguan, please.
Before I come back,
before I come back.
If he loses a hair,
I'll kill you.
Sit down.
Do you know
this jade pendant is very important to me?
You used it too easily.
People like you won't understand.
I really don't know
about your father.
There are many things you don't know.
Don't tell me you're a commie.
You're right.
Anyway, I came here today
is achieved.
You can arrest me now.
I think there might be some misunderstanding between us.
Actually, I brought Mr. Wu here
to protect him.
Protect?
You're the independent Brigade Commander of Yuxi.
Not only you,
When did your army
protect the Communist Party?
Yes.
You are better than Li Gang.
At least you didn't hurt the people yourself.
You seem to be thinking about
how to fight the Japanese and save the country.
But do you know
Your army has so many soldiers.
You have so many guns.
Why can't you beat the Japanese?
Because all you think about is the chairman.
You'll get promoted and get rich.
You can't die.
If you die, there's nothing left.
As a soldier, I'm afraid of death.
What war?
Aren't you Communist Party afraid of death?
Yes.
So we got rid of him right away.
People like Li Gang
bully the people openly,
You don't care?
I don't want to fight in front of the enemy.
I don't want to.
Well said.
That's not what your chairman said.
He didn’t do that either.
Many of us died
killed by your commander?
Don't tell me you don't know, Cui Wenkui.
You're more educated than me.
You know how many Communist Party
your father killed.
Bao,
I've been looking for you since your father died.
You want to see me?
To get rid of him.
What? Cai Boxuan is an accomplice?
Do you have solid evidence?
I'll arrest him now.
Wen Kui
Are you going to catch him again?
What is it?
I want to go with you.
I can't today.
Why?
Stop asking.
Study hard at home.
Is it because you want to catch Uncle Cai?
How did you know?
He has been in our family for so many years.
but he's a commie.
I'm going to catch him with you.
Good boy. Let's go.
Mr. Tanaka.
This time,
is really flawless.
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
He tied the button so tightly.
What could possibly go wrong?
The first time Cui Wenkui met Shangguan Bao,
they were very close.
They will know soon
someone is behind this.
Mr. Tanaka.
So, you're going to have dinner tonight? Yes, I'm going to have dinner tonight. I'm going to have dinner with you.
Tonight,
Li Gang and Big Jaws...
These two idiots.
have been in Shaanxi for so long.
Take it as a gift
to Shangguan Bao and Cui Wenkui.
You mean
Golden tooth is caught by Qinglong Fortress.
he must be dead.
And Li has just fallen into Cui Wenkui's hands.
It should be sent to the Military Law Department.
In this case,
they might give me away.
Do you think you're the only one
the royal army?
They have two roles.
One is...
to see if the royal army
is still working.
Besides,
we can also see who else can use it.
Mr. Tanaka.
Without Captain Li,
there will be no one for us at the airport.
Then let Choi Moon-Kui fix the airport.
When he fixed the airport,
The royal army is good.
It's so high.
Li Gang and Golden tooth are your enemies.
Mr. Tian Yuan, my ending...
Magistrate He.
The reason why the abandoned son is abandoned
because they have fulfilled
their mission
is useless.
If you don’t want to be abandoned,
it depends on your performance.
Today, you have to make a bright move.
Do you hear me? Let's go.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Be smart.
Fly on the boat.
Madam has ordered
Xu Jin of Black Tiger Mountain is not allowed to leave.
Retreat!
Hurry up.
Oh no.
Fly in the air.
Did you sleep too much?
Look at this place.
This is my place.
I only need a whistle.
my brothers will come out.
We don't know who will die.
Okay, try it.
Come here.
Actor table.
Choi Bo-wol.
Deng Bao Quan.
and actors.
Li Hongda Yu Guofeng Gong Fan Cheng Kaiyan.
Yuewang Yang Zi Yi Tian Chenzhe Deng Kaimei Liang Dong
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin, Wang Yukun.
Ji, Chao, Zhao Zhigang, Kung, Ji Youyi.
Yang Tao, Chen Yao, and Rui Qian.
Qin HaoSen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Liangliang, Lin Nan, Liu, Yu.
Liu Hongguo, Yang Chenglin, Liu,
Xu Dagu Chen Weijie Liu
Xu Shidong, Liu Yongtao.
Li Yang Wang, Xu Gang, Xin Yan Long, Zhao Chang Li.
Staff table.
Director team.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Cho Jeon-min.
The clothing team.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Execute art, Zeng So-wook.
Props team.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
Gunman Sun Hai
The recording team.
The venue team.
Zhao Gongli.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Kang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong Xi.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li, Zhang Changchang.
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Chou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping
Cut.
LilStar.
Drama photo, Wu Xiaobo.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
One Zhu Jiaxin.
Ma Jun Nan.
Xie Hong.
Xu Xiaojia.
A dubber.
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
The base of HongMong Red Film in Shandong. [The national 4A-class scenic area]
[Shandong Blumund Red Filming Base] [The national 4A-class scenic area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple Sheung-Mun's Government.
The Jade Association of Shanzhou District
[Sanmen Mingu Pu Theatre]
The Civilian Committee of Lingbao City
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Shanzhou District.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Tianan Lake, Zhishan Lake City Wetland Park.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
Sanmen City Swan Lake Wetland Park.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Lan Yi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
Sandao Watery Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
I'll reward Zhang Bing first.