We're done for!
You okay?
Lao Lian.
Lao Lian, where are the others?
How could you leave them up there alone?
And did you find the Silver Eye?
The Silver Eye got smashed to pieces.
What?
The Silver Eye is broken?
Did they do something to it?
Next time you talk behind someone's back,
check which way the wind's blowing.
Gossips are either crooks or thieves.
What did you say, you fat slob?
Why so worked up?
Are you the crook or the thief?
All right, all right.
Well, if it's broken, it's broken.
As long as everyone's safe.
The Silver Eye map was pieced together.
I still remember some of it.
Ms. He, are you saying
you can recreate it?
I'll give it a try.
That would be wonderful.
Ms. He, do you know how crucial
the Silver Eye is to this whole trip?
Acting like a lapdog.
Old Chen.
The fog should be rolling in by now.
Let's set up camp.
Okay.
If you're so good, you do it.
I'm just here to supervise you.
Hurry up. Look at the state of you.
Eat, eat.
Thanks.
Let me tell you,
just now,
I saw that statue down there.
It's incredible.
That's a real treasure.
Absolutely priceless.
That craftsmanship... forget the past,
even today,
no one could replicate it.
I checked the map carefully.
To get to Mengna Valley,
the Nine-Story Pagoda is the only way.
Does it say anywhere
um,
which way the city of Mengna Valley is?
The whole Mengna Valley
is in a place called Qingluan Sacred Hall.
The Nine-Story Pagoda is there too.
Right, right, right.
I remember now.
This scroll of mine mentions it.
Four snow peaks surround Mengna Valley.
The four snow mountains represent
one of the four guardian deities.
The four guardians are
gold, silver, crystal, and glaze.
Built from these four kinds of gems.
The whole range linked together
is called the Qingluan Sacred Hall.
In local legend,
the Kunlun Mountains,
Kunlun is known as the Land of Qingluan.
If
Kunlun's shape resembles a Qingluan,
then it matches that epic poem.
Per the poem, Qingluan Sacred Hall
should be in the Kunlun Range,
at Xiaduo Yuzhang Pass.
Xiaduo Yuzhang Mountain
has two statues, white and silver.
White is the snow mountain,
and the glacier must be the silver.
The general direction is settled.
The area is at Xiaduo Yuzhang Pass.
Plus we've got Dawang with us.
We'll definitely find it.
Great.
Let's go.
You mean A-Zhong
wants to go back and steal that statue?
He doesn't have that kind of eye.
But you and Old Lu
hyped that thing up in broad daylight
like it was the greatest treasure ever.
He's definitely tempted now.
What are those two up to?
Old Whitehair and Uncle Min's wife.
What are they saying?
Let me listen, let me listen.
Just do as I say.
Once this job is done,
whether he's dead or alive,
I'll go with you.
Sounds like these two are saying
once this job's done,
they're gonna dump old Uncle Min.
That's cold.
No wonder I said they're rotten.
What kind of people are these?
We've lost him! Hurry, faster!
When we catch A-Zhong later,
we've gotta scare him good.
Scare him however you want.
Get ahead of him.
How do we get ahead?
Hurry, take the shortcut.
Commander Chen, what's the plan?
No plan. Just charge in.
We can't let him get into that cave.
Right, let's go.
Tell me, where is Dawang?
Dawang?
You've got the wrong guy.
I'll give you one more chance.
Where is Dawang?
What do you want?
You think if you kill me,
you can find Mengna Valley on your own?
Kill you? I wouldn't dare.
But making you suffer a bit,
that's easy enough.
Boss.
Old Fei's been in there a while. Nothing.
Should we go take a look?
Let's go.
Move.
Right.
Stop!
Don't run! Kill him!
Grab him!
Get him!
They're all here for Dawang.
Keep quiet for now.
What is this?
No idea.
How come every single pillar
seems to be hiding something?
What is it?
How would I know?
A mask!
Help!
Don't shoot!
Run!
Hurry, faster!
Hurry!
This way!
Here, here, here!
Hurry!
Hurry, hurry!
Fatty!
Help, A-Zhong! Help me!
Move it!
Move!
I can't run.
Wait for me!
I can't.
I've got altitude sickness!
I can't run anymore.
I've been watching for a while.
They won't catch up anytime soon.
Let's take a break.
Rest a bit.
Run!
No, no, no!
Hurry!
Wait, there's no way through here!
This way, this way!
Go!
Fatty!
No, no, no!
What is this?
Go, go, go!
What do we do?
Jump from here!
Jump!
Jump, jump!
Down!
Our lifelong reputation, you and me,
isn't gonna end right here, is it?
I-I don't wanna die here.
Like you have a choice?
What... what do we do about it?
Grab a rock.
Hit it!
Rocks!
Shutong!
Officer He!
Hurry, hurry!
Are you okay?
Old Chen, you all right?
I'm fine.
Dawang!
Nobody move!
Old Fei, tonight
you've lost quite a few men too.
All just to kill me?
Is it worth it?
Yeah, is it worth it?
But it's worth it.
Don't move!
Know why I have to kill him?
He... Dawang,
the backbone of the anti-poachers.
I'll kill you!
Hey, Brother Chen,
didn't I show up right on time?
Uncle Min, you showing up here now
is just perfect.
I just wanna know,
what that monster actually looks like.
Like a giant monkey.
A giant monkey?
A monkey.
Right, a monkey, you see,
the people living in the Himalayas,
they believe in a kind
of giant beast called the snow ape.
The first to spot a snow ape's trail
was a 19th-century foreign officer.
While climbing a snow mountain
in the northeast Himalayas,
at an altitude over 5,000 meters,
he found a snow ape's footprint.
But these snow apes live in conditions
that are extremely harsh.
So nobody's ever seen them.
Only in recent years,
I heard someone at the mountain's base
discovered enormous footprints,
possibly left by these snow apes.
You three,
why did you go to the ruins?
We...
We followed A-Zhong over there.
Why would A-Zhong go to the ruins?
You think it's right to ask us that?
Go ask him yourself!
Did A-Zhong die up at the ruins?
Yeah.
How did he die?
Probably trampled to death.
Really?
Maybe you three had a fight up there
and he got silenced?
What kind of twisted mind do you have?
During the day,
we mentioned that in Rahu Hall's cave,
we found a statue.
He must've set his sights on that statue.
By the time we got there,
before we could stop him,
the poachers arrived.
They clashed with A-Zhong,
so they attracted the great ape.
This A-Zhong, honestly,
greedy for petty gains.
All right,
let's not bring this up
again.
I trust Brother Chen.
Boss, help me!
A-Zhong!
Didn't you say A-Zhong was trampled?
Isn't it good news he's still alive?
Boss, I almost didn't make it back.
This is karma.
He got greedy for money first,
that's why he ended up like this.
If we keep bringing him along,
it might slow down our journey.
Boss, don't listen to her!
They... they...
Boss.
I think Madam has a point.
A-Zhong is a burden.