Old Chen really called it right.
There's a whole other world behind that ice wall.
Finally out of that frozen wasteland.
Look at all this green, it's so refreshing.
A real paradise.
Brother Chen.
I think we're on the right path.
From where we swam up,
I think if we push forward along this path,
we'll definitely make it out of the mountains.
No.
There's dense vegetation all around.
Yet this path is unusually flat.
I think it's been worn down by wild animals.
Let's go that way.
We'll head over there.
Old Chen, look over there.
Isn't that the giant eyeball?
It really is!
Miss He.
Could that be the city of Mengna Valley?
It must be.
Past the Gate of Cataclysm,
we should be in Mengna Valley territory.
The long poem Dawang left me said
Mengna Valley's capital is called Chimo Jizhou,
shaped like a massive honeycomb.
Nine times out of ten, this is the place.
The Tower of Babel in ancient Babylon,
the megaliths of Brittany,
the 9,000-year-old
golden city of Dwarka in Indian waters.
In ancient civilizations,
there are countless structures that defy imagination.
There's no mistake.
There's absolutely no mistake!
Shaped like a honeycomb.
Chimo Jizhou.
It's truly magnificent!
Wait...
I...
No, no, Uncle Min.
Don't get yourself worked up.
You'll give yourself a heart attack.
Once that happens,
your life's pursuit will be ruined.
Brother Chen.
Chimo Jizhou is right here.
I think there's no time to waste.
Let's hurry inside.
Rest, let's rest a bit.
Just now under the ice tower,
weren't you the one begging to rest?
Fatty, you little punk!
My lifelong pursuit
is to find Mengna Valley,
and uncover the secret of the Lingxiao Pearl.
That is my lifelong pursuit.
Now that it's right before my eyes,
how can you expect me
not to be anxious?
Brother Chen, let's hurry inside.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
What's he rambling on about?
Bi Huaqiang.
Come here.
Every time we got close to the Lingxiao Pearl before,
your body had strange reactions.
But every time
when we thought we'd uncover the truth,
we'd lose it at the last moment.
So you're scared.
You're afraid that once we reach Mengna Valley
and find the Lingxiao Pearl,
it'll all still come to nothing.
The Lingxiao Pearl is tied to the lives
of both Uncle Min and me.
But whether we can break the curse,
we have no idea.
I've been thinking the whole way.
From the ancient western city to Yunling,
and from Yunling to Nanyun,
the scale of the ruins along the way,
the level of civilization,
and the dangers we've faced
have become increasingly unbelievable.
So,
you're thinking of backing out?
I'll definitely finish this trip to Mengna Valley.
No matter the outcome,
I plan to bring my archaeology career
to a close.
As long as I, Chen Youxi, still draw breath
and make it back alive,
I want to stay by your side always.
Quite spectacular.
Beautiful.
Good, it wasn't a wasted trip.
Hey, Uncle Min,
you usually grab your little stick
and zip around pretty fast.
Why'd you stop here?
You fat oaf,
asking the obvious.
What's the big deal?
It's six or seven meters at most,
and it's not deep.
Can't we just wade across?
Wade across?
Easier said than done.
We nearly died getting out of that lake.
And look at this water,
it's filthy and murky.
Who knows what monsters lurk inside.
We can't get in the river,
so let's find another way.
In a city this big,
there's got to be another route.
Use your head, would you?
Take a look.
This was dug around the city on purpose.
Do you know why?
Precisely to keep out the likes of you,
ignorant white-haired thieves.
So Mengna Valley already had
the concept of building a moat back then.
This channel is pretty wide.
You call this wide?
You've never seen the moat in Xiangyang.
Sister,
to you this is a river.
But to Fatty here,
it's just a ditch.
Right.
Let Fatty here show you how it's done.
Be careful.
This, this is nothing, really.
Honestly.
Take it easy!
What is it, Fatty?
Nothing.
Bah!
Geez, my blood pressure nearly shot through the roof.
Look at that.
Now what?
There's a whirlpool.
A whirlpool?
Are there icebergs in there?
Any sharks?
Crabs, ribbonfish, anything?
Old Chen, help me!
Fatty!
What a faker.
Fatty! Catch!
Here!
It's a trap.
Don't just stand there, go help him!
Looks like a mechanism.
You fat oaf, you're way too heavy.
Eating less would have helped.
Hurry up, pull harder!
Why are they fighting now?
Are you done yet?
What's wrong?
Brother Chen, you...
Don't you know what your man's doing?
My man?
Bi Huaqiang!
Bi Huaqiang, what are you doing?
What's going on here?
Did you think we're about to enter Mengna Valley
and don't need us anymore?
So you sent him to grab weapons and silence us?
Bi Huaqiang, what happened?
I honestly have no idea.
I'm just as shocked he did this.
If you don't believe me, ask An Xiang.
Ask my ass!
Old Chen...
Why did you do it?
Without a weapon in hand,
I don't feel safe.
Safe my ass!
Godfather.
Godfather!
You're good for nothing but ruining things!
Here's how we'll do it.
Bi Huaqiang stays here.
You and An Xiang come with us.
I think that's fair enough.
This white-haired punk,
we really can't bring him along.
He'll just cause more trouble later.
His temper's too rotten.
Uncle Min, An Xiang...
Look,
Youxi has done right by us.
But there's an undercurrent in the river.
We can't cross either.
Brother Chen...
Shut up!
Fatty,
keep an eye on Whitey.
Old Lu,
find some wood to build a bridge.
Got it.
There!
Just set it down.
I'll go in and check first.
Wait for my signal.
Okay.
Take it slow.
Brother Chen!
How... how's it looking over there?
Quit rushing me!
Hang on.
It's safe!
Nice!
A trap!
Brother Chen, are you kidding me?