What a fine poem!
Wonderful!
"Farewell, my lord; Loulan was won in a night."
I never imagined one so young
could possess such literary depth.
Once this poem spreads,
your name will surely shake the capital.
I have no desire to shake the capital.
All I want is a full belly.
But why?
Fame brings trouble, like fat to a pig.
If my name became renowned,
the Ning household would never tolerate me.
A mouthful of absurd words,
a handful
of bitter tears.
All in the world bear hardships,
but who can grasp
the taste within?
You...
Speak plainly!
Plain words, please.
Can you even understand?
It means I'm having a hard time.
The great recluse hides in the city,
the lesser recluse hides in the wilds.
Heaven and earth, vast and primordial,
each follows its own path.
Why trouble oneself needlessly?
Enough of that.
My young friend,
this poem of yours,
how much silver will you sell it for?
Since Uncle has treated me to a meal,
I'll be straightforward.
One hundred taels, as before.
Done.
Many thanks, Uncle Tianxuan.
This is exactly what I like about you.
Forthright.
The hour grows late today,
so I won't keep you any longer.
If you compose new verses in the future,
Find me at Top Scholar Pavilion anytime.
Rest assured, Uncle Tianxuan.
Until we meet again.
Farewell.
After you.
And you,
farewell.
Your Majes— Master.
If this poem is released,
your reputation
will surely rise to new heights.
You want me to pass it off as my own?
Though I'm fond of poetry,
I wouldn't stoop to claiming false fame.
This servant thought since we paid for it,
the poem's already ours, isn't it?
You really think they're worth 250 taels?
These poems are priceless.
The reason I gave him 250 taels
is because he's young and frail.
I feared carrying too much wealth
might bring disaster upon him.
You truly think of everything, Master.
Copy these poems out
and send them to officials in the capital.
Let them study and admire them properly.
This lad has such talent,
he can't be from an ordinary family.
Though his clothes are plain,
there must be more to him.
Shall this servant go investigate?
Yes, look into it.
This lad is a promising one.
Yes, sir.
Xiao Mei.
Chicken for dinner tonight!
Where is everyone?
You stop right there!
Hold on,
I only had one cup of your wine.
Come on, is it really that serious?
Stop!
You shrew!
I just took your money— I'll kill you!
—for wine! You old cripple!
Still running?
What's going on?
I...
Help! I'll beat you to death!
Help!
Don't run!
You stand right here!
See if I don't beat you to death!
If I don't run, you'd kill me!
I'm not stupid!
You!
Sister-in-law, sister-in-law!
What happened?
You've got the nerve to ask?
My dear sister kindly
took you two in,
but this old wretch
actually stole our money to buy wine!
Do you have any idea?
That money
was saved by our family scrimping on
food and clothes for Mei Shi's schooling!
You!
You damned old cripple!
Give me back my silver!
I want to go to school!
Give back my silver!
Give me back my silver!
What's going on?
Give back my money!
I want to go to school! Stop shouting!
What have I always taught you?
Where are your manners?
The money's been stolen!
Why bother with manners?
Money!
Sister.
Don't blame me for being harsh today.
Either they pay back the money today,
or we go to the authorities.
Sister-in-law, sister-in-law!
Don't get violent yet.
You see,
I happened to earn some money today.
Here.
One hundred taels.
Two hundred taels.
Y-You... where did you get so much money?
Don't ask about that, sister-in-law.
I don't even know yet
how many days I'll be imposing here.
Take this money for now.
Send the child to school first.
I knew it.
A young master from a noble family
couldn't possibly be short on silver.
Wonderful!
With silver, I can go to school!
Yes.
My dear.
It's getting late.
Go kill the chicken first.
Right.
A live chicken, nice and fresh.
We'll all eat together tonight.
Just one chicken,
how can it feed all of us?
Tell you what,
I'll prepare a few more dishes.
What are you two standing there for?
We're out of rice.
Hurry, take the child and buy some.
All right, all right.
You old swindler!
You started drinking first?
Top Scholar Pavilion's Top Scholar's Brew.
Fine wine!
Quite the discerning palate.
So you know it's good, young master.
Your silver notes,
they surely didn't come honestly.
I haven't settled the swindling with you,
and now you're turning on me?
Let me tell you,
this money
was earned by yours truly.
Pfft!
Quit boasting.
Do you even know
what two hundred taels of silver means?
Your father, Ning Ziming,
as Minister of Rites,
earns only 150 taels a year.
A modest two-courtyard home in the capital
costs about that much.
You're young and have no real skills,
can't shoulder a load or carry a thing.
And you... you...
I earned this myself!
Just confess honestly,
where did you steal it from?
Exactly, young master.
Y-You're from a distinguished family.
Though you're facing some hardships now,
still,
you mustn't resort to thievery!
Young master, you're still young.
If you go down the wrong path
and ruin your life, what then?
Fine, fine, fine.
You all look down on me, do you?
Then today I'll tell you
exactly how I
stole this money.
Shut up!
Earned it!
Reporting to Your Majesty.
Was the poem bought today transcribed?
This servant has already sent men
to deliver it to each official's home.
By the way,
the identity of the man who sold the poem
has been confirmed.
Minister of Rites Ning Ziming's bastard.
Ning Chen.
Your Majesty, shall we have him arrested?
This is deceiving the Emperor!
But he didn't know my identity.
What crime has he committed?
However, since he is Ning Ziming's son,
why does he dress so shabbily?
And he even claimed
that all his family members were dead.
Ning Chen was exiled since childhood.
Eight years ago,
Ning Ziming
brought him back home.
This fellow
isn't favored at home.
And Ning Ziming
rarely mentions this son in public.
I remember now.
A few years ago,
someone cited Minister Ning's abandonment
to impeach the Left Chancellor for laxity.
At that time, I was at war with Tuoluo,
overwhelmed with troubles,
and I forgot about this matter.
Well, well.
A dignified Minister of Rites,
yet behaving like this behind the scenes.
It's time to give him a warning.
This is also a good chance
for the other officials at court
to take heed of the lesson.
Convey my decree.
Summon Ning Ziming to the palace.
Yes, Your Majesty.
This is the poem His Majesty sent today
to be circulated among the officials.
Take a look.
What do you think?
A profound and lofty meaning,
every word a gem.
I feel ashamed by comparison.
If this man takes the imperial exam,
I'd have no chance at being top scholar.
No need to worry.
I've already had it investigated.
He hasn't entered the exam this year.
I never imagined our capital
would have such a brilliantly talented man
who cares nothing for empty fame.
You three should follow his example.
Study diligently.
We shall remember, Father.
My lord, you are the Minister of Rites,
and their grandfather is Left Chancellor.
Even if they aren't his equal,
with you paving the way for them,
they'll rise swiftly through the ranks.
Why bother taking him seriously?
Mother is right.
Envoy Quan has arrived!
Envoy Quan!
What a rare guest, rare indeed.
By His Majesty's decree,
Ning Ziming is to enter the palace now.
This subject obeys.
May I ask, Envoy,
why His Majesty has summoned me
today?
You'll find out when you arrive.
And is His Majesty pleased or displeased?
The Emperor's mind is like a deep abyss,
neither pleased nor angered.
My lord, you should set off quickly.
Don't keep His Majesty waiting.
That old fox.
Unbelievable.
My lord.
Could it be...
that you and Father bribed for Gan'er,
and His Majesty found out?
He's not the only official's son testing.
Plenty of others bribe officials too.
You all wait here at home.
I'll go change my robes.
We'll talk after I see His Majesty.
You three, don't just sit idle.
Go out and find that bastard.
Mother, why look for him?
Didn't we just drive him out?
And now we bring him back?
How did I bear such a foolish son?
No matter how lowly he is,
he's still your father's illegitimate son.
If something happens to your father,
you'd have to split the estate with him!
Right, right, right.
Mother's right.
As long as that brat lives,
he's a threat.
Before, inside the manor,
we had to consider Father.
But now,
this is the perfect chance to kill him.
Mother, don't worry.
I'll hire someone to finish him off.
Gan'er,
do not act yourself.
Though the written exam is over,
you must still enter officialdom
and take the palace exam.
Do not give others any pretext.
I understand, Mother.
Go on then.
I understand. Thank you, Mother.
And that's how the situation is.
Young master,
since when did you learn to write poetry?
You barely had schooling at Ning manor.
Perhaps when it comes to poetry,
I happen to be quite gifted.
Travels with a eunuch in tow...
Could it be Prince Fu?
Bah!
You little brat.
Do you know the perils of the battlefield?
This old man believes that this time,
you merely got lucky.
Who says I don't know the battlefield?
Then this old man shall test you.
Bring it on.