Father.
This is how things stand.
Why not give Ning Ziming a warning?
Tell him to stop shielding that bastard.
So you're saying
that Ning Ziming
fears His Majesty.
Grandfather.
Has he truly caught His Majesty's eye?
What has he done to deserve that?
Exactly, Grandfather.
That bastard Ning Chen,
we used to bully him plenty.
But now he's joined the Imperial Inspectorate.
Could it be
he's actually turning his fortunes around?
What if he comes back for revenge?
What are we going to do?
Xing'er has a point.
With his Silver Guard status in the Inspectorate,
and Ning Ziming shielding him,
he might claim a share of the Ning estate.
Exactly, Grandfather.
Grandfather, we can't let this happen!
What do we do about this?
What's the panic?
I am, after all, head of all the officials.
He's just a mere Silver Guard.
What trouble could he possibly stir up?
Guards.
Your orders, Lord Chancellor?
Go to the Imperial Inspectorate.
Have them keep a close watch on Ning Chen.
Find an opportunity
to eliminate him with full justification.
We must not give His Majesty
any reason to find fault.
Yes, my lord.
Big brother.
The Imperial Inspectorate is restricted ground.
No outsiders allowed.
Outsiders?
I'm a big shot reporting in by imperial decree.
You?
What?
You...
Golden Guard Pan has arrived!
Greetings, Golden Guard Pan.
So you're Ning Chen.
That would be me.
Follow me.
Park the carriage properly.
Ask your boss for the tip.
The Inspectorate has one Purple Guard
who oversees everything.
Eight Golden Guards head eight departments,
each in charge of
investigation and arrests,
weapons and equipment research,
medical care, logistics, and so on.
The eight departments have different roles,
each handling its own...
It only fires one bolt at a time?
That's so outdated.
I'll upgrade it to a Zhuge repeater later.
I'm talking to you.
I heard you.
From now on, you're with me,
handling investigation and arrests.
Hey, boss.
Call me Golden Guard Pan.
Greetings, Golden Guard Pan.
Get him a set of Silver Guard robes.
Change quickly.
Once you're changed,
meet me at the gate. I'll introduce you.
Got it.
That look on your face,
you don't think much of me?
How much do you weigh, buddy?
Two hundred.
Over two hundred. You're pretty strong.
Does your hand hurt?
Next time I'll get you a sandbag.
Impressive moves.
Stand up.
Put your hat on.
Brothers,
let me introduce a new recruit.
Go on, introduce yourself.
Greetings, brothers.
My name is Ning Chen.
I look forward to working with you.
Hold on.
The Inspectorate recruits at the start of the year, no?
Don't tell me
he's another one who pulled strings to get in.
Um, Ning...
Handsome Ning here
This Ning
is a Silver Guard personally appointed by His Majesty.
And what's more,
he's Minister Ning's son from House Ning.
Chief, I have to say,
a pampered young lord coming to our Inspectorate
is utterly useless.
He'll only mess things up for us.
Old Gao, that's enough out of you.
A pampered lord like him
could never endure the hardships here.
Besides, His Majesty
would never allow a minister's son
to stay long with us.
Just bear with it.
He'll be gone soon enough.
No, you've misunder--
Enough.
Bring out today's case files.
Right away.
Don't interrupt when grown-ups are talking, kid.
Step aside.
Chief.
The coroner has examined Squire Zhang's body.
Just as we suspected,
the killer is about five feet seven.
And the murder weapon
matches our deduction as well.
It was a dagger.
What's more, the wound
runs from below upward,
which means...
That tells us this killer
must be shorter than Squire Zhang.
And Squire Zhang took seven stab wounds,
but the wounds...
Got something to say?
Go on.
The wounds are all very shallow.
Which means this killer
can't have been very strong.
According to his concubine and his son,
this killer
leapt onto the rooftop with ease.
This killer...
These people rely too much on assumptions
but the corpse is the most honest witness.
A master needing seven stabs to kill?
Use your head.
Hold on, here's what we figured.
Maybe it was the killer's first time.
Or maybe it was accidental.
For instance,
he was stealing something
and got caught by accident,
so he resorted to murder.
Did you check the roof?
We did. The tiles are intact.
Not a single trace.
Boss, could it be the rain a few days ago
washed all the evidence away?
I have a question.
How old is the Squire Zhang you mentioned?
Want to know?
What do you think that thing's for?
Come look for yourself.
Boss, I think there's
another possibility here.
Put your hat on properly.
Squire Zhang took seven stab wounds,
and the wounds are all very shallow.
Which means this killer
can't have been very strong.
According to his concubine and his son,
this killer leapt onto the roof with ease.
Did you check the roof?
Tiles intact. Not a single trace.
The wounds vary in depth.
It's more like the victim struggled violently,
and the killer couldn't overpower him,
which left him exhausted.
A master who can scale walls
needing seven stabs to kill an old man?
Unless...
this master doesn't exist at all,
but two people, neither being very strong,
killing him together.
What does a rich boy know?
Actually, I know a thing or two.
I wandered the streets since childhood,
only brought back to the Ning estate at twelve.
So when it comes to the harshness of life,
you two haven't seen more than I have.
Young Master Ning,
allow me to enlighten you.
To get by in our line of work,
you need real skill.
Playing the pity card
won't help.
Is it possible
that this testimony isn't truthful?
The killer you speak of
simply doesn't exist at all.
Could it be...
Squire Zhang's son and concubine lied?
The lad shows promise.
See?
Don't embarrass yourself, Young Master Ning.
Zhang Mingjie is Squire Zhang's only son.
Once Squire Zhang dies,
the entire estate goes to him.
Why would he kill for what's already his?
But Squire Zhang was advanced in years,
while his concubine is only thirty,
in the prime of her hungry years.
And his son?
Twenty-five.
Just the age that can't resist temptation.
This...
Come on, get up.
Who do you think you are, sitting there?
Listen here.
As the only son of the Zhang family,
what woman could he not have?
Why fall for his stepmother?
Truly a pampered young master.
Mind full of filth and lust.
Hey, come on now.
Sleeping with one's stepmother
defies all morals and propriety.
Zhang Mingjie is at least a scholar,
a man of reason.
How could he stoop to such depravity?
Don't believe me?
Investigate.
See?
Quiet.
What he said
does have some merit.
Since we have no other leads,
let's bring them in for questioning.
You two, go.
Look at you...
Go.
Go, go, go.
Zhang Mingjie, confess at once!
My lord, it wasn't me!
My lord!
I truly know nothing!
Boss.
I told you this young master is useless.
He just loves spouting nonsense.
Now he's playing with toy blocks.
Well?
Boss,
we have no evidence, only guesses.
Those two were utterly heartbroken.
It wasn't right to press them further.
These two are the killers.
"These two are the killers," he says.
Listen, young master.
This is a matter of life and death.
Not an idle game of falcons and crickets.
Sir.
Take a look at these two confessions.
The answer lies within them.
When people are frightened,
or in extreme grief,
their speech usually becomes incoherent.
In other words, as we often say,
their words don't quite add up.
But these two confessions
are perfectly coherent.
As if cast from the same mold.
Sir,
I have a suggestion.
You should look into
Squire Zhang's concubine's personal maid.
An affair like this
can be hidden from others,
but never from a personal maid.
During such trysts,
someone has to keep watch.
And that person
is usually the one she trusts most.
So young,
yet so composed,
and so sharp-minded.
What a pity.
You two,
go bring her in.
Wait, boss...
Go on, hurry.
Him, him, me...
Him, me...
Come on, come on, let's go together.
Back and forth with you, always so chatty.
We're off.
Sir, what about me?
You?
You're off duty.
I'm off duty just like that?
But I haven't done anything yet.
They can handle it.
I know you're young and eager,
hungry to earn merit.
But you see,
your status is special, after all.
I can't have you taking on
the kind of jobs that risk your neck.
If anything happened to you,
the Inspectorate couldn't face House Ning.
So that's the real reason.
Others fight tooth and nail,
yet still have to share credit with me.
No wonder they resent me.
Golden Guard Pan.
I am simply Ning Chen.
I have nothing to do with House Ning.
Do as you please.