You saw the eye pattern on the silver eye
and nearly passed out
because you have an eye-shaped scar too
When did you find out?
I found out before we set out
My scar
is different from yours
I've had my scar
since I was born
For most of my life
I've been investigating this
I never expected
to find it's connected to the Lingxiao Pearl
You want to find the Lingxiao Pearl
to cure yourself
I gave up that naive notion
twenty years ago
Now
I just want to know what secret
the Lingxiao Pearl truly holds
Then my life won't have been in vain
Brother Chen
Out of everyone
I, Lian Ximin, trust only you
All I seek in this life
is to know what secret
lies hidden in the Lingxiao Pearl
Believe me
I'll never keep it for myself
Let's go
Go on
Take care of those wounds
Don't get hurt next time
You'll never change, will you?
Let's go, come on
Old Chen, Fatty
We'll drink when you're back!
Brother Lu, are you okay?
How could I be okay?
Need a spray?
Spray it, spray it
The altitude here is only 2,000-something
and you're reacting this badly
What'll you do when we go higher?
N-Nonsense
My head hurts
Want another spray then?
Ignore him. Let him pass out.
He hit someone! He hit someone!
Where are you hurt?
Where does it hurt? You okay?
Should we go to the hospital? It hurts so bad!
My leg hurts! My leg!
You can't leave, you can't go
You can't leave
What are you doing?
He hit someone!
Let go!
You can't go, you can't leave
You okay?
Get out of the way
The cops are here! Cops!
Stop fighting! Stop! Stop!
Stop fighting!
Xiao Qi.
Have something to eat.
Thanks.
Help yourself.
Have some snacks.
Thanks.
Commander Chen, so this is Xiao Qi?
Look at those pearly whites.
No mistake about it.
Brother Chen, this man here is Dawang.
He's the one taking us to Xiaduo Yuzhang.
I just heard you want to go to Xiaduo Yuzhang.
So, Brother Xiao Qi,
I'd like to ask you,
what exactly is Xiaduo Yuzhang?
Why does everyone we meet on the road
react like they've seen a ghost when they hear it?
Did the place do something to you guys?
There's nothing special about the place itself.
But in our ancient legends,
it symbolizes a sea of disaster.
It's a place of ill omen.
Brother Xiao Qi,
I still have to trouble you
to please guide us into the mountains.
I'm counting on you.
I'm exhausted.
What's all this ginger juice for?
You planning to brew ginger soup up there?
If you're afraid of the cold,
wouldn't a couple bottles of liquor be better?
Looks like you really did come prepared.
Hey, hauling a barrel of ginger juice,
how does that count as being prepared?
The glaciers up on the Kunlun Mountains
are ancient ice, millions of years old.
You can't imagine how solid they are.
Even swinging a pickaxe is useless.
Ordinary tools
basically can't cut through that ice.
Old Chen,
you had us gather ginger juice to melt the ice?
Brother Xiao Qi already said it.
The Nine-Tier Pagoda is beneath that ancient glacier.
We don't know how deep it goes.
Better safe than sorry.
Those are black-necked water birds.
What about them?
They're coming from the north.
Black-necked water birds normally
don't get startled easily.
Even if an avalanche hit the northern mountains,
you'd rarely see them fly off.
The mountain pass we're heading to,
it's to the north.
That's right.
From here to the Xiaduo Yuzhang pass,
it'll take at least four days.
We'd better set off as soon as possible.
Be careful!
What a deep gorge.
Elder Chen.
Brother Chen.
What are you thinking about?
Scared stiff?
This must be the Valley of Dry Bones.
I hadn't said a word,
and you already figured it out.
I originally thought the Valley of Dry Bones
was just an ordinary path
on the way to Xiaduo Yuzhang.
I didn't expect that this time,
we'd have to take it.
What do you mean?
Ancient sites of this kind
always come with two equally-sized
dragon-shaped burial trenches alongside.
You suspect this Valley of Dry Bones
could be one of the burial trenches
near the Nine-Tier Pagoda?
Yes, I'm guessing this is one of them.
Inside this Valley of Dry Bones, we'll surely find
more information about the Nine-Tier Pagoda.
An Xiang, take a look at this place.
What do you think?
See anything?
That's good then.
The old folks used to say
that for hundreds of years,
every year, huge numbers
of gazelles, bison, and wild horses would jump to their deaths.
The phenomenon of wild animals
committing suicide in herds
happens all over the world.
But I've never heard of
different species of animals
all killing themselves together.
This is what the elders say.
In ancient legends,
whenever there's a full moon,
the beasts would gaze up at the moon
and then leap down,
to appease the wrath of the heavens.
It's fine.
It's solid.
Look, look, he just walked right across!
Get back, get back!
You, come back, come back!
Get back here!
It's hollow underneath.
Hollow?
It really is hollow.
Not entirely.
Otherwise, how would these bones pile up?
These animal bones interlock like fangs,
hooking together easily.
That's what creates this illusion of solid ground.
These canines and carnassials are so developed,
and the upper molars have distinct cusps.
It couldn't be a tiger, could it?
Wild dogs?
They're wolves.
Wolves?
If that's the case,
then these fresh bones
are all leftovers from wolf hunts.
Let's go catch ourselves a wolf,
tie a rope around it,
put it in front, let it walk first,
then we follow in its footprints.
That way we won't fall through.
What do you mean?
Catch a wolf to lead the way? Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
Brother Chen, what should we actually do?
Wolves are clever and cunning.
They've hunted here for years,
so they must know this terrain
like the back of their hand.
With all their long-term trial and error,
where they step is the safest ground.
What we need to do now
is examine the shape of these bones,
to see if they've been gnawed on.
If they've been chewed,
then that's where the wolves stepped.
Got it.
You mean,
we follow the path the wolves took,
and we'll be safe?
Yes.
Come on.
Let me help you.
I don't need help.
I need to take a leak.
Go on then, fine, fine.
Hurry up!
Don't fall too far behind!
I'm exhausted.
An Xiang's a good kid.
Pretty down-to-earth.
Help!
Old Lu! Old Lu!
Old Lu!