You know,
all the way here,
we haven't seen any rain.
Just mountains and dirt slopes,
all pretty dry.
Why is this place so damp?
We always end up in godforsaken places.
With all this weird, spooky stuff,
how can you not imagine things?
Go ask her to check the map.
He Shutong,
Chiyan Jizhou is so vast.
Where do we go from here?
This is the map from the Rahu Hall.
I copied it from the mask.
I didn't know what place it showed before,
so I just kept it on me.
Now it seems
it must be Chiyan Jizhou.
Chiyan Jizhou is circular.
So what's at the center?
The Mengna Valley people loved ceremonies.
This center
must be where they
held grand rituals, the Altar Site.
The Altar Site.
Why is it getting more humid here?
Don't tell me more poison bugs are coming.
Relax, Old Lu.
It's just water vapor.
Everyone, stay close. Don't get separated.
What the heck?
Where's this smoke coming from?
Where is everyone?
Old Lu!
What's going on?
Smells like a smoke bomb.
Someone's definitely up to something.
It must be Bi Huaqiang.
He grabbed the smoke bombs in the chaos.
Uncle Min must know what's at the Altar Site,
so he wants to get there before us.
Everyone just learned from you
that this terrain is circular,
and the Altar Site is at the center.
He knows the route and wants to ditch us.
No time to waste. Let's move.
Fatty and Old Lu aren't here yet.
With their experience, if they lose us,
they'll definitely head to the center.
Besides,
Uncle Min is already heading there.
He just wants to take the Lingxiao Pearl.
If it really is at the Altar Site
and he takes it,
it'd be a massive blow to our search
for the Mengna Valley civilization.
We have to get there first.
Are you worried about losing artifacts,
or worried about me?
The Altar Site is just ahead.
The idol of the Mengna Valley people
is a winged serpent.
And these stone pillars,
what do they mean?
Shutong,
how do these statues tie to Mengna Valley?
What Mengna Valley worshipped
was a serpent with bat wings.
All prehistoric civilization legends
unanimously believe
that gods created everything.
But why would Mengna Valley
worship a serpent?
Slow, slow down.
Slow down!
A fake snake? Seriously?
Is this the meeting spot?
This place is huge.
Only this spot looks like the Altar Site.
Where else could it be?
What the... what?
Who tapped me?
What's the deal?
Hey, don't mess with me!
He Shutong.
You're picking up bad habits from Chen!
My heart can't take this!
I'm gonna collapse right here.
Sorry about that.
Where's that old fox Uncle Min?
Did he throw the smoke bomb?
Must've been him.
No idea where he's hiding now.
What took you two so long?
Don't even ask.
This place is seriously creepy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Guess what we found.
Old Lu, come up and look.
Why's there a pot of stewed beef here?
It's empty.
An optical illusion.
Just like that cave in Yunling,
where you saw that fake face.
No, no, no.
This is different from Yunling.
The one in the Yunling cave,
you could tell the builders
made it on purpose to scare people.
But this one...
Who'd scare people with fake beef stew?
What else did you find that's fake?
Everything else,
the stones are real,
the walls are real,
the thick fog is real,
the Altar Site is real too.
Old Lu, got any cans left?
Yeah, I do.
Have some, go ahead.
Toss me one.
I've got crackers too.
Is this one beef?
It's empty.
This one's empty too.
This whole city is fake!
So this entire huge area
is just one big shrine.
It's not Chiyan Jizhou at all.
This statue is tilted.
Someone's been here.
There must've been something here
that someone took.
What was taken?
My guess is,
it relates to Mengna Valley's history,
the Altar Site, or even the Lingxiao Pearl.
Seems we all underestimated Uncle Min.
This book isn't made of paper.
Looks like some kind of animal hide.
Can you read it?
These symbols
must be Mengna Valley hieroglyphs.
Does it mention the Lingxiao Pearl?
Godfather, this book is too thick.
It's full of these symbols.
We'll need He Shutong's help.
Godfather, honestly, just now,
you shouldn't have used that smoke bomb.
Without He Shutong,
we still can't crack
its secrets. What do you know?
They've got all the weapons and manpower.
The closer we get to the truth,
the more likely they'll ditch us.
This book is our only bargaining chip.
Let's move!
Hurry, this way!
Don't move.
Where are they?
Hey, brothers.
You know why I'm here?
We're short-handed inside.
I came to get you.
Brother Chen's inside.
He's found tons of stuff.
Come on, follow me.
We're really short-handed in there.
You need to find a vehicle here.
Let me explain.
An Xiang, keep up!
We don't have enough vehicles.
He's discovered so many things.
You get what I mean?
Nobody move!
What's going on here?
Attacking people in broad daylight?
You think out in the wilderness,
you can do whatever you want?
Brother Chen, you sure move fast.
Let me tell you all,
I've got something in my hands right now.
An Xiang.
It's that book she's holding.
To unlock the secret of Mengna Valley,
not only do I need it,
but you need it even more.
This isn't the real Chiyan Jizhou at all.
That place you just visited
isn't where the Mengna Valley people
held their grand ceremonies either.
This Chiyan Jizhou simply doesn't exist.
It's all an illusion.
Then where's the real Chiyan Jizhou?
That depends on what this book says.
Brother Chen,
take a look at the situation now.
The weapons are in my hands,
and the key to the Chiyan Jizhou mystery
is also in my hands.
So wouldn't you say
I'm in a position to negotiate now?
To keep things fair,
you can read this book,
but I have to be the one who keeps it.
What do you say, is that acceptable?
Deal.
Great, thank you.
Miss He.
Can you actually read this or not?
These should be pictographs.
The style resembles ancient rock art.
Is this book made of animal hide?
Quite possibly.
The Kunlun Mountains don't suit farming.
So logically speaking,
they must have lived by hunting.
So hide-made books were easy to carry.
That's possible too.
Judging from these characters,
they haven't faded in thousands of years.
Technically speaking,
they used materials like Dunhuang murals.
Master Lu,
I think the book's origin and materials
don't really matter anymore.
What matters is finding out
what it actually says.
This book tells the origin of Mengna Valley.
Long ago, people in the Kunlun Mountains
were attacked by a giant serpent.
One person used a mysterious pearl
to subdue the serpent.
He gained the serpent's power,
and inside the pit where the serpent grew,
he founded Mengna Valley,
becoming the king of Mengna Valley.
Under the king, the Mengna Valley people
held a grand ceremony every year,
similar to the Fengshan rites,
to pray to the serpent god for blessings.
This snake drawing is so exaggerated.
It's bigger than a dinosaur.
Ancient records of history
always contain exaggeration and flair.
Plus, in the era of cold weapons,
humans had limited fighting power.
Any wild beast
posed a serious threat
to their lives.
So drawing a giant snake isn't a surprise.
Then, at such blessing ceremonies,
this, this...
the leader of this region
is holding a pearl.
Could it be the Lingxiao Pearl?
Uncle Min, Uncle Min, Uncle Min.
These are pictographs.
It takes time to decipher.
Give He Shutong some time.
You have to let her think it through.
Fine, fine, you think then.
You've been thinking all morning.
It mentions here
that all Mengna Valley rulers were female.
What follows is likely
the ruling class of Mengna Valley
fabricating feudal superstitions
to intimidate and rule the commoners.
What kind of stories could
Mengna Valley's rulers make up?
The book says
after each queen of Mengna Valley dies,
a new queen will be born among the people,
chosen by the serpent god.
China's ancient emperors
followed hereditary succession.
What's going on with this Mengna Valley?
Who knows who the serpent god
will choose as the queen?
Every queen shares one trait:
they're born with heterochromatic eyes.