Careful, everyone.
Come on.
Slow down.
Here, give me a hand.
Easy now.
This looks like...
some kind of Ritual layout.
That's the Four Mindfulnesses,
the Four Right Efforts,
the Four Bases of Power.
The north one is the Pure Five Faculties.
Where temples, pagodas, and demons stand,
chaotic thoughts and anger arise.
So the Nine-Story Pagoda
should be at the center of the energy field,
which is the lotus position in the north.
Come.
This is Qilian juniper.
Below are square and round timbers,
plus a rammed-earth structure.
Be careful when you go down there.
Don't damage the load-bearing logs below.
Get your gear ready. We're going down.
Okay.
Go get the rope.
What is this thing carved here?
A bull? A wolf? What is it?
A bull-wolf?
A donkey, maybe.
In The Scroll of the Heroic Lord Baoji's Triumphs,
the silver demon, the White Wolf King,
this must be it.
How do you know?
The Scroll of the Heroic Lord Baoji's Triumphs,
Dawang told me everything before he left.
I remember the White Wolf King's name was
something like Bingpo Zhenyu Shan.
Wait, hold on.
You've got me all confused.
Is it a wolf or a mountain?
How can you not understand anything?
This thing here, it's a wolf.
It looks like a bull,
but it's not called a bull-wolf.
Its name is Bingpo Zhenyu Shan.
A bit long, just deal with it.
Wait, it's a perfectly good wolf.
Why's it named after a mountain?
I've heard of this Bingpo Zhenyu Shan.
In life, it was a giant white wolf,
ancestor of all vicious wolves in Kunlun.
Legend says after it died,
it became a massive ice crystal mountain,
hence the name Bingpo Zhenyu Shan.
They say it guards the base of the pagoda,
protecting the gateway to Mengna Valley.
The moment anyone approaches,
the demon wolf descends from the sky
and devours everyone.
This ice disc
must be an ornament called a Ling Gai.
Probably every floor has one.
Only by opening this Ling Gai
can we enter the next level.
Wait.
It's open.
Push!
Look.
Old Lu, come take a look.
Come on.
Slow down, easy now.
Come, come, watch your legs.
You're so clumsy.
Hurry, take a look at this.
Impressive, isn't it?
After going down so many floors,
we finally see a proper relic.
You know what?
Coming down floor by floor so smoothly,
it actually makes me uneasy.
You're a glutton for punishment.
You just have to trigger a trap,
then have a near-death experience,
for you to feel at ease, right?
Old Lu, you've got it wrong there.
Fatty, that's an archaeologist's instinct.
Give him a break,
I'm getting nervous too.
This Nine-Story Pagoda
should be where an evil god is buried.
How could there be no defenses at all?
Brother Chen,
how's the situation down there?
Is it safe or not?
This floor is different from the others.
Ghost Banners are hanging everywhere.
A statue is where the Ling Gai should be.
For safety's sake, just stay up there.
Alright.
Be careful down there then.
Tell you what,
I'll send Bi Huaqiang down to help you.
Let me have a sip of water.
An Xiang.
Sit.
Are you
hiding something from me?
I'm not hiding anything from you.
It's just that I've noticed
you've gotten along well with them lately,
especially with that guy named Lu.
Did they
plan to ditch us and leave on their own
without giving you a heads-up?
How could they possibly tell me?
No matter how well we get along,
we've only just met, after all.
If they really had told me,
I'd definitely have told you.
These past few days,
I've been feeling awful.
About what happened to Aunt He,
I hope you don't overthink it.
Godfather, I understand.
Look at these Ghost Banners.
They kind of resemble a Ritual layout.
The directions marked here
are different from normal.
Our north is their west,
the red Xiniu Hezhou.
Our east is their north,
the blue Beiju Luzhou.
All this east, south, west, and north...
you've got me totally turned around.
I just want to know,
where is this floor's mechanism exactly?
Where on earth is the Ling Gai?
I think,
the Ling Gai was centered on past floors.
This time, if you ask me,
the Ling Gai must be under this statue.
The Ling Gai's definitely under it.
Let's move it aside.
What are you "hmm-ing" about?
Everything I say is based on evidence.
I examined this statue carefully.
Look at this.
On the surface, it looks kind and gentle,
but in fact,
it's cradling a human head in its arms.
What is this thing?
It's pretty strange, right?
So let's study it.
Alright, we'll follow your lead.
Forget everything else,
let's move it aside first.
Give me a hand.
Come on.
You broke it!
What's going on?
Chen Youxi, up ahead!
Take cover, quick!
Hurry, hurry, take cover!
Quick!
Don't just stand there!
Old White-hair, push it aside!
Then we can just head down, right?
It won't budge! This thing...
This statue must have a mechanism.
It can't be pushed open.
Look!
The color of those beads has changed.
When we first came in,
the directional colors were opposite,
they were reversed.
I, I have an idea.
Maybe,
if we restore the colors of these beads
back to their original state,
perhaps,
perhaps the mechanism will shut off.
Old Lu makes a good point.
Anyway,
you'll be the one turning the beads.
Okay, okay, okay.
We'll cover you.
No, no, no!
I'm just the idea guy.
Should we go down and help them?
No need.
He can handle it.
Old Chen,
I noticed that
it only fires every three seconds.
Just like playing that Contra game.
There's a time gap in between.
Three seconds?
You're kidding me.
Three seconds won't cover a round trip.
Don't even try it!
If you mess up,
the arrows will shoot from behind,
and I'll be the first one skewered!
If I don't try,
the arrows will soon pierce the statue,
and shoot right through the front too.
Two, three.
One, two, three.
Lend me the Demon-Subduing Umbrella.
Old Chen, the statue is almost sliced up!
I can't hold on much longer!
It stopped!
Move aside, let me see.
What did I tell you?
I said it was right under here.
Am I right or what?
Huaqiang.
This is a cultural relic.
This time,
we should at least
keep one of them intact.
Why are you causing trouble?
You're such a coward.
Bro,
you can't just scare people like that.
My heart nearly jumped out of my chest.
So this is the Bingpo Zhenyu Shan?
I thought there'd really be a wolf-headed,
human-bodied mummy here.
Turns out it's just a statue.
Don't look down on this statue.
Making something like this isn't cheap.
What's it made of?
It's ice crystal from the Nine-Story Pagoda.
But...
what I don't get is...
Look here.
These layered, scale-like ripples,
what are they?
These...
Must be special sound waves sealed inside.
Once the ice crystal shatters,
it could trigger an avalanche.
Now I get it.
This is how it guards Mengna Valley's gate.
If an intruder breaks it,
they'll be buried here by an avalanche.
Forget about entering Mengna Valley.
I'm just wondering,
where exactly is the gate
to this Mengna Valley?
We just discussed this, and you still ask?
Use your head, would you?
It's obviously buried under the mountain.
The Jueda people were really cunning.
They buried the gate to Mengna Valley
right down here.
You can't move it,
or push it,
and breaking it causes an avalanche.
It's a brilliant dead end.
Won't budge.
Hey, Old White-hair,
this thing won't budge.
Isn't that obvious?
Then what do you suggest?
With so many of us here,
are we just going to stand and watch?
A little bug.
This little bug is pretty interesting.
In such a harsh environment,
it can still survive.
Mother Nature,
can create all kinds of miracles.
In this frozen environment,
to adapt,
it kept evolving,
into something like this.
Looks like a little ladybug.
Careful!
These bugs have lived here for years.
Maybe
they're also part of the trap.
When I was a kid, I heard
that in the Kunlun Mountains,
there is a kind of blue bug.
They come from hell,
and whoever touches them
will face utter disaster.
Stop spreading these feudal superstitions.
Hell? Utter disaster? Seriously?
Tian Qing, don't touch it!