I love seeing
how girls from a happy household look
when they make that look of despair.
The necklace is gone.
Are you accusing me of stealing it?
- You're mistaken.
- Did you get that girl?
Don't tell me you're actually struggling?
Shut up.
Just hand over the cash.
I wish I'd never given birth to you.
You useless thing!
He's a very important person to me!
Don't ever do anything like this
to Mr. Chiaki again.
Mr. Chiaki, are you okay?
Please.
Don't move.
Stay with me.
I'm sorry, Ama.
It's okay.
That's my mother.
Hard to believe, right?
After she got pregnant with me,
the guy who was my father left her.
It's all because of you
that my life is a mess!
That's why she treated me so harshly
since I was a kid.
Hey, isn't that abuse?
- Should we report her?
- You shouldn't.
The nearby adults all turned a blind eye.
So when a scout approached me at 14,
I jumped at the chance.
I thought I was finally free, but...
she started coming to me for money,
saying, "Repay me for raising you".
It's laughable, isn't it?
I'm stronger than her now.
But whenever I hear her voice, I can't move.
It's pathetic.
There's nothing pathetic about that.
It hurt, didn't it?
I'm sorry.
But...
I was really happy.
Until now,
no one around me
has ever bothered to save me.
No matter how poor we were,
my family was what kept me going.
But, Mr. Chiaki has always been alone.
It's okay.
If anything happens,
I promise I'll protect you.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're a kind person, Ama.
Mr. Hosho, you're up soon.
Mr. Hosho?
Yeah, sorry.
You're sleeping so peacefully,
I'll leave without waking you.
Hey, Chiaki, stay a little longer.
No.
I can't sleep around others.
She's so shameless.
I would've quit a long time ago.
Hey! You can hear me, right?
Don't you feel any guilt?
I haven't done anything to feel guilty about.
If you don't believe me,
you can call the police.
- What? We'll call them then...
- Rina.
I'm fine, don't worry.
- Jeez, Anna, you're just too nice.
- Yeah.
That's not true at all.
I'd never let it go.
[Thanks for the other day. Are you okay?
Did you make up with your members?]
I think they still don't believe me.
But I'll keep trying.
[Diamond heart necklace]
[Ama]
Oh, you're here.
By the way, I saw Kairi yesterday.
He was pouting
because you've been distant lately.
I bet.
I stopped doing that stuff.
Huh?
[Ama]
Oh, Ama?
Yeah.
There's something I want
to talk to you about,
so I was hoping to see you tomorrow.
Then I'll go pick you up.
See you tomorrow.
You're... on the phone with a girl.
You always say things like,
"Calls and texts are a pain".
"Is communication necessary anywhere
but in bed?"
And you'd block them immediately.
They're still a pain now.
But Ama is different.
I actually wonder what she's doing right now.
Why?
"Why"?
Since when?
When did this start?
It started...
when she got hit.
Huh?
For my sake.
By my mother.
What?
Tell me the details!
Okay.
What?
Chiaki, you like that girl, don't you?
Like?
Yeah.
I think this calls for a good drink!
Barkeep, give me your most expensive drink.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, not at all.
So, what did you want to talk about?
What's this about, calling me out like this?
Saotome, I wanted to talk to you properly.
I don't want to talk to a thief.
I really didn't steal your necklace.
Who's going to believe
anything you say now?
You don't have any proof that I stole it.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Yeah.
That necklace...
Isn't that the one you said you lost?
Why did you lie about that?
You're such an eyesore!
Why does the lowest-ranking member
of our group
get all the good breaks?
"Oh, I can't do anything."
But then you take all the good gigs.
People like you are the worst!
Saotome.
Why don't you tell
the other members about this?
Not that anyone would believe you.
After all, everyone hates you.
Disappear.
Disappear, disappear, disappear!
Get out of my sight!
I recorded all of that.
Huh?
I sent this to your manager.
Good.
It worked out.
Mr. Chiaki, thank you so much.
No problem.
If it weren't for you,
who knows what would've happened?
So, what did you want to talk about?
Actually, I saw something interesting.
I think this is
Anna Saotome's private account.
That's the necklace she said she lost.
Hey, Ama.
Do you trust me?
Who's going to believe anything you say now?
[Mr. Chiaki]
Excuse me.
Hello?
Step out for a moment.
Okay.
Keep talking.
As loud as you can.
Okay.
Well, about the upcoming filming,
there's something I wanted to ask you.
I never imagined Saotome
felt that way about me.
You're too pure.
Huh?
In this world,
the more popular you get,
the more people try to drag you down.
But it's okay.
I'll stay by your side.
Thank you.
Our shoot together is almost over, right?
Yeah.
Oh, right.
I actually have a new drama lined up.
Oh, that's great.
And I also got an offer
to audition for a movie,
so I think I'm going to try it.
I realized I really do like acting.
I want to keep
challenging myself from now on.
I'm so grateful to you
for making me realize...
I don't like that.
The thought of you being on set without me.
Huh?
Mr. Chiaki?
Don't talk to other actors.
Ignore them.
And don't exchange contact info with anyone.
Come straight home after filming ends.
Oh, right.
You should always have your manager get you.
No, it'd be better if I pick you up.
Mr. Chiaki?
What's wrong?
Sorry.
You're so cute, it worries me.
I'm not...
You're cuter than anyone, Ama.
Listen, okay?
No matter how close you get to him,
don't make any mistakes
with Mr. Hosho, alright?
Mr. Chiaki is kind.
That's the only reason he said those things.
I heard from Mr. Suzui.
Anna is seriously messed up.
But I always knew she had a dark side.
I heard Anna is leaving the group,
so let's do our best, three of us!
Let's do our best!
- I'm really sorry for everything.
- I'm really sorry.
[Thicket and the Flower Basket]
[Auditions]
I'm filming in the studio
next door right now.
Join one of my projects again.
I really want to, Director.
Glad to hear it.
Ama.
Ama?
Those auditioning, please come this way.
Thank you very much.
Ama!
I've...
I've always wanted to apologize to you, Ama.
Just once, let me talk to you.
Please contact me.
See you.
I knew Kairi had become an actor.
But...
Please don't.
I thought he was a distant presence,
someone I'd never have to deal with again.
[Mr. Chiaki]
Can you meet today?
Wow, this is a beautiful place.
I wanted to show you this view.
Thank you.
Ama, did something happen?
You can tell me.
Well...
I bumped into someone
I had a falling out with in high school.
A falling out?
That person tried to apologize,
but I ended up running away.
Are you still angry at that person?
No.
It's more than that.
I'd rather he just forget about it.
If you feel that way, why not tell him?
It's okay.
I believe in you.
Thank you.
I'll try to properly tell him.
Oh, right.
That movie audition was today, right?
Yeah, for Director Tanuma's new project.
He helped me out
when I made my debut too.
He's a good director.
Oh, I see.
I hope I get the part.
What's the movie about?
It's more of a mature romance, I think.
I'm a little worried about
getting into character.
I feel like I can only
really become a character
if I've experienced something similar myself.
Method acting, huh?
Method acting?
Acting by reliving your own emotions.
Maybe you've been doing that naturally.
I see.
Hey.
Yes?
Was it the same, the first time you acted?
I love you.
I've always loved you.
Yes, it was.
So that's why I was able to do it that time.
Who was it?
Huh?
Back then, who did you think of?
Someone I liked back in school.
I see.
But, I've never been
in a mature relationship.
What should I do?
Then have one with me.
Huh?
Experience it all
with me.
Ama.
Go out with me.
I don't want anyone else to have you.
To be honest, this is my first time
going out with someone.
I was so surprised
that you became an actress.
So I'll take on any role!
My heart just skipped a beat.
Ama, I love you.