Help!
Did you see it all
with your own eyes?
I saw it myself.
It's the truth.
If this happened last night,
why did you only report it
to the Bureau this morning?
I...
I was terrified!
Red-Faced Guardian's curse
is still going on,
so I had to hide until daybreak
before I dared to come out.
The body has multiple fractures.
Severe bleeding from both eyes.
Subcutaneous bruising.
We're doomed.
I've been cursed!
I...
I'm just as doomed!
None of us is going to escape this.
Zhuang...
Zhuang Luobai...
It was Zhuang Luobai!
He's the one who brought
the Red-Faced Guardian's curse!
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 8=
Master,
have you heard?
Gu Pan'er's mother also suffered
a curse from the Red-Faced Guardian.
The Red-Faced Guardian
protects the people.
Where would a curse come from?
But Gu Pan'er broke the rules.
Focus on your dancing.
Don't worry about anything else.
How can I not?
You care about her so much.
Ever since she married,
you've become a different person.
You constantly berate and beat me,
taking your anger out on me.
Isn't all of this
because of her?
Is that
how you see me?
Isn't it?
I've poured my heart
into this dancing,
yet it's never good enough for you.
You refuse to give me any recognition,
but the Troupe Master values me.
So he's replacing you with me
for the Winter Festival.
Master,
you've taken me in for ten years.
The very bricks
on these floors have witnessed
all the sweat and tears we've shed.
Gu Pan'er was always an outsider.
If she died, who cares?
It's good that it ended your obsession.
Look at you.
Ten years of heart and soul,
and I've raised someone so cold-blooded.
You're right to scold me, Master.
But this coldness is only for outsiders.
When it comes to Nuo opera,
I am completely dedicated.
A Nuo performer
uses a righteous heart
to drive away evil.
But yours is clouded by selfishness.
The divine path is closed to you.
Reflect on this yourself.
Get out.
I can't be your master anymore.
I, Zhuang Luobai, have failed you.
The hand that wields that iron rod
has quite the talent.
Listen more, learn more,
and talk less.
This brush is already fraying.
I happen to have a good one here.
You're just barely worthy of it.
Take it.
Di.
Di!
Gu Qi lied to us.
Oh?
Gu Pan'er wasn't without friends.
She had a close confidante
named Dong Ling.
This lady looks...
Hold on, Duan.
I just dipped the brush in ink.
Go on.
She's taller than the average woman.
- Taller than you?
- Thin...
Thin lips, phoenix eyes.
She rarely smiles,
but she seems like a kind soul.
Draw!
Raise the eyebrows a bit!
Make the cheekbones more prominent!
That looks just like their description.
Di.
Di!
(I've seen her before.)
(The Nuo opera is starting!)
(Look, it's starting!)
(Let's go to see Master Zhuang Luobai!)
Is this show still going on or what?
Who is this?
We came to see Zhuang Luobai!
We want to see Zhuang Luobai!
(Dong Ling...)
(Dong Ling)
Sirs, my mother has just passed.
It's a mess inside.
We should talk here.
Is that alright?
Do you know Gu Pan'er?
She was murdered
and left backstage at the theater.
When was the last time you saw her?
Three days ago.
She was with you the day she died.
Where did you go?
What did you do?
When did you part ways?
It was the day of my mother's funeral.
Pan'er...
Pan'er came to pay her respects.
She went home in the afternoon.
Was there anything wrong
with her that day?
No.
Do you know
who she was close to
before she died?
You want to ask about
her and Zhuang Luobai, right?
There was nothing between them.
Why are you so sure?
I've known Pan'er
since we were children.
We grew up together.
I know her character.
Besides,
she and Zhuang Luobai
had known each other a year ago.
If they really had an affair,
why would she have
married Hou Guangming?
Didn't she marry Hou Guangming
for his money?
She did it for me.
For my mother's medical bills.
That's why she agreed
to let her father sell her
to Hou Guangming.
Do you know Hou Guangming?
No.
But I asked around.
They say
he's an old scholar.
Kind,
well-read and cultured,
and he treats Pan'er well.
So their marriage
must have been a happy one?
She never talked about it.
Whenever I asked,
she'd say things were fine.
But I knew.
Married to a man she didn't love
wouldn't make her happy.
I could see it
in her eyes.
So, was Pan'er in love
with someone else?
Why are you asking?
Do you suspect Hou Guangming killed her?
I'm still investigating.
You went to the theater the other day.
Who were you meeting there?
No one.
Just watching the show.
Sir!
Hou Guangming is
at the Bureau to see you.
He's found evidence.
My apologies for the interruption.
Sir,
while I was going through
Pan'er's belongings,
I suddenly remembered this.
Are you suggesting
this belongs to Zhuang Luobai?
It certainly does.
Why are you so sure?
I didn't want to air our dirty laundry,
but to tell you the truth,
a few days ago,
we had a huge fight
over this robe.
You're going to see Zhuang Luobai again?
Pan'er,
if you love Nuo opera so much,
I'll hire a troupe to perform
at our manor
for three days and three nights.
How about that?
You?
You paid a fortune to buy me.
I've given you face in front of others,
but let's stop making
each other miserable here.
Pan'er...
I truly care about you.
Money is indeed a good thing,
but it only makes me greedier.
Look closely.
The man in my heart is not like this.
You can't leave!
Don't go!
Is this...
You sewed this for him yourself?
Give it back.
But you...
You've never even
sewn a single stitch for me.
Why are you crying?
It's all my fault.
Why did I have to argue with her?
Now that I think about it,
if she had just run off with someone,
that would have been fine.
Why did she have to die so brutally?
From what I've observed,
Zhuang Luobai
only wears red
when performing Nuo opera.
Normally,
he only wears simple, plain robes.
Then why would Gu Pan'er
gift him a blue robe?
Sir,
we're at the Bureau,
and I would never dare lie to you.
Relax.
It's not that I don't believe you.
Get up.
Please.
You must get justice
for Pan'er and her mother.
You suspect he's lying?
Yes.
If the victim
had an affair with Zhuang Luobai,
he would be the prime suspect.
But if what Dong Ling said is true,
that there was no affair,
then why would he
be so desperate to frame Zhuang Luobai?
Framing?
But the footprints at the scene
don't match his.
Why is there an extra body here?
(Preview of Next Episode)
Father,
Mother says it's time to come home
for dinner.
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪