MkvDrama.net
Shall I help you?
But on one condition.
You have to marry me.
[Thank you for staying up.
Warm it up before eating.]
Are you telling me
to break up with Takahito?
That's not an option.
If Takahito fails, it'll drag everyone down.
It's simple, isn't it?
Your marriage was a mistake to begin with.
It's okay.
Good morning. How are you feeling?
Good morning. I'm fine.
Did you stay late at the office again?
Yeah, just going over some estimates.
I was thinking of negotiating on the prices
to see if they'll fulfill the order.
I see.
Bye then. Careful with your health.
Um,
is there anything I can do about the project?
Don't worry.
For now, put your health first.
Thank you.
Okay.
If the project fails, then the company...
[Episode 7]
It's going to be really bad.
I mean, with all those ads and pre-orders...
We might go under.
Should I start looking for another job?
But we've already come this far.
What about the mortgage?
And the kids' exams...
If Takahito's partner were Rena,
she probably wouldn't
make everyone feel this uneasy.
Shiori.
What's going on with the project?
There's a rumor in sales
that it might be canceled.
Yeah.
If the project fails,
that golden boy
will definitely be removed.
What?
But when you think about it,
it was only a matter of time
before he failed.
I mean...
Since you're a jinx.
Now, it's that golden boy's turn
to be miserable.
Serves him right.
If it's a factory issue,
we'll look for a solution on our end too.
No, say what you will, but it's impossible.
Why?
Could it be...
you're rejecting us for another reason?
No, that's...
I knew it. There's another reason.
Anyway, please just let this go.
Oh, Shiori.
A visitor.
Huh?
What do you mean you can't fill our orders?
I'm truly sorry.
This is a token of my apology.
Um...
Please tell me the reason.
Last time, you were happy
that it was turning out well, weren't you?
Why so suddenly?
To be honest,
we got a large order.
Huh?
I was going to turn it down.
But they said if I refused,
they'd never do business with us again.
No way...
Ms. Hanai, I can't apologize enough.
Please raise your head.
By the way, where is the large order from?
Well...
Asakaze Bussan?
Yes. Factory Manager Nijihashi told me.
This might mean...
that Asakaze Bussan was involved
with the other two factories too.
Does this mean Rena was involved?
It's my fault, isn't it...
Shiori, calm down.
Nothing's set in stone yet.
I'll look into it.
But...
It's okay.
Just focus on your own work.
Okay.
Look who finally decided to call.
You took way too long
to figure out the cause, CEO.
Was this really your doing?
When you want to control people,
don't play nice.
That's the golden rule of business
we grew up with.
Don't get in my way...
any further.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
This marriage involves the future
of Asakaze and the Seko Group.
It's not just about us as individuals.
Think it over again.
Anyway, make up your mind soon.
I don't like to be kept waiting.
Oh...
And another thing.
Don't bother contacting other factories.
We'll sign contracts with them
before you can even lift a finger.
See you, bye.
So it was you, Father.
The one getting in my way.
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb.
Rena said she would sign contracts
with clients before I could.
The only one who could collude
with Rena and help Asakaze Bussan...
is you, Father.
What's your angle here?
When you raise bonsai,
you have to cut off the useless branches.
The tree will feel pain for a moment,
but it'll grow into a remarkable bonsai.
Takahito.
Don't get hung up on the unnecessary,
whether it's work or people.
It ruins the quality.
Are you saying...
that marrying Shiori is unnecessary?
That's right.
I won't let you have your way.
You're all talk.
Okay.
Understood.
If anything comes up...
Shiori, you look pale.
No, I'm fine.
We'll manage, so go home for today.
No, no, in this situation,
I have to work hard.
Hey. That body's not just yours anymore.
Sasaki. Mr. Takahashi.
Shiori's leaving, so can you finish her work?
Got it!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it!
I can help too.
Thank you.
Go on, Shiori.
Okay.
All of it...
is my fault.
I won't approve of you marrying her.
It's simple, isn't it?
Your marriage was a mistake to begin with.
If the project fails, then the company...
It's going to be really bad.
Should I start looking for another job?
What about the mortgage?
And the kids' exams...
It's because I fell in love with Takahito...
Shiori.
Shiori!
Huh?
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
No, you're not. You spaced out just now.
Sorry.
Wanna sleep over tonight?
No...
I still have things I have to do.
Will you be okay alone?
All right.
Thank you.
Shiori?
Yuna,
did Shiori come by?
What happened with Shiori?
So she was here...
She looked so troubled
and wouldn't say anything when I asked.
She's going to the office.
Huh?
She said she had things she had to do.
Thank you.
Hey!
Shiori...
You better treat her well, or else.
Shiori.
Have I always been blind to your feelings?
If only I stood by your side...
Shiori!
Shiori.
I'm sorry.
Shiori...
You were trying so hard to help me...
but I refused to let you in.
I just didn't want you to worry.
That's not it.
I...
think you have a talent
for making people happy.
I don't want you...
to waste that on someone like me.
Clothing with "comfort
that makes everyone love themselves."
You absolutely have to make it.
You have a duty
to protect everyone in this company.
So, Takahito...
please choose Rena as your wife.
If you do,
the project can restart right away.
The company and everyone will be saved.
But if you stay with me...
everyone will get dragged down.
No...
You're wrong.
That's not true.
Meeting you...
changed me.
The old me...
was always worried
about work achievements...
and acted cold to everyone.
But,
now...
I want to build a company that
enriches the lives of its employees.
Because I've realized...
that my employees have families...
who are important to them,
just like I do.
If...
I'm able to do good work right now,
it's because of...
you and the child inside you.
I...
can't live...
without you...
and this child anymore.
Thank you.
But...
it's different for me.
It's...
hard living with you, Takahito.
I can't keep up with...
the wealthy lifestyle
of people like you and Rena.
The custom-made clothes
and the expensive ring...
were too much for me.
Even at restaurants,
I'm always worried
about not embarrassing you.
I'm...
exhausted from being with you, Takahito.
Please forget about me.
As for our child...
I'll raise it on my own.
Is that...
how you really feel?
Yes.
Goodbye.
Wait.
I enjoyed...
our time together.
I thought this was for the best.
This marriage arrangement with you
is an incredible stroke of fortune.
Marry me.
The CEO is the only one
who can save this company.
I'll make this project a success,
no matter what.
Sir, we need to talk.
MkvDrama.net