Thank you.
For what?
Thanks for always being by my side.
I don't really have a way to repay you.
Repay?
Well, there is a way, if you want.
What is it?
Go back abroad with me.
Right now,
we don't even have a clue
where the next Lingxiao Pearl is.
You can't just keep wasting time like this.
What if I told you I have a lead?
Beautiful dreams,
like beautiful poems,
can't be forced, only encountered.
They appear when you least expect them.
And I think beautiful people are even more so.
Bai Lingling once mentioned
that the head of their organization
holds many leads on the Lingxiao Pearls.
He's been secretly investigating too.
So I believe
this Ghost Eye
is very likely the Lingxiao Pearl.
Jumping to conclusions from a few words
seems a bit hasty, don't you think?
It's fine.
I'll go see Curator Zhu when I get back
and see if he has any new findings.
I just feel that
the Kunlun Mountains are too treacherous.
I'm worried, given your health.
But it's okay.
I won't give up.
Having a lead is a good thing.
I'll go searching with you.
So, what do you do?
I'm an archaeologist.
In my spare time,
I help restore antiques for the state.
Things like ancient swords, ancient zithers,
that sort of stuff.
Nothing worth mentioning.
Wow, you're really impressive!
Oh, hardly impressive.
But impressive?
Yeah, that I am.
Just ask around in archaeology circles.
The name Lu Di, well, definitely...
How rude.
So what brings you here?
Don't even ask.
There's a big tomb out here.
A big tomb?
Big herd.
We're going over to discuss
raising cattle, sheep, you know,
livestock-related projects.
Yes, yes, exactly.
Cheers.
Come on, sit, sit.
What kind of liquor is this? So strong.
Erguotou.
Let's be clear, it's my treat today.
Why is that?
This trip,
I caused everyone a lot of trouble.
Well, aren't you polite.
When have you ever not caused trouble?
Right, right, right.
Then I won't hold back.
Don't.
Waiter!
Two more plates of fresh lamb.
Old Chen.
You and I have to drink to this.
Come on.
Your place got blown up like that,
you can't live there anymore, right?
I've got an idea for you, buddy.
Just go with the flow.
Tonight, you go with Advisor He
back to her hotel.
Get lost.
I'm going home with you tonight.
Don't count on me.
I've got a date tonight.
You've got a date?
This girl, a real babe.
Real tall.
Gorgeous.
Lao Lu.
I'll crash at your place.
Sure, sure.
Dad?
Dad.
My, my dad...
He's sick.
Yeah, not feeling well.
He said he'd stay with me for a couple of days.
Look at this... talk about bad timing, huh?
I know about that.
Find somewhere else.
I'm telling you, Old Chen,
this is fate.
Destined by heaven.
There are three of us.
Forget about us two.
You can only beg Advisor He
to take you in.
Advisor He, do me a favor.
This kid's pretty pitiful.
Why don't you take him in?
No problem.
My hotel room is a suite.
I'll leave a bed for you.
No, no, no.
Are you kidding me?
I'll just leave my luggage with you...
I just remembered something.
I need to hit the bathhouse for a scrub first.
Wash off this dusty stench.
Then I've got to go pick up that girl.
You two chat, I'm off, Advisor He.
Thanks for taking him in.
Don't you pay the bill.
I'll pay, I'll pay.
I'll, I'll get it.
Oh, right.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
The info on Ding Dawei's dagger
is vague, and the scope is too broad.
And it's in the Kunlun Mountains.
I don't want you taking that risk.
Right.
You're absolutely right.
I'm absolutely right.
But you just won't listen, will you?
I didn't say that.
So you'll listen?
Fine.
No problem.
Good boy.
Sir, we're here.
Why'd you drive here?
Isn't this your home?
You're telling me to go home?
Where else would you want to go?
Little Chen.
Old Zhu.
Did Advisor He ask you
to help clean this up?
Something like this,
only Miss He would think to do for you.
Kid,
you owe her more and more favors.
A few days after I got back from Jinghong,
I received a document from the Northwest.
The sender
was an old college classmate of mine,
now a professor at the Institute of Geology.
The letter basically said
that while doing geological surveys in the Northwest,
near Xiaduo Yuzhang Mountain,
they found a huge pit.
An eye pattern made of animal bones?
I believe so.
How was it formed?
He wasn't sure.
He just said
there were no signs of habitation in the area,
nor any traces of human life.
Hold on.
I mentioned to you on the phone before
that Ding Dawei, who went into the tomb with us,
and Bai Lingling were hired by the same person.
I've talked to him too.
I suspect
this is the clue to the next Lingxiao Pearl.
Combined with this photo of yours,
I'm even more sure my guess is right.
What are you going to do?
Go explore it.
Maybe.
What's going on?
You'd never hesitate before
when I told you about things like this.
That place is so mysterious.
How can we go without any preparation?
I need to check the relevant materials first.
Fair enough.
Tell you what,
let me know whatever you need.
Coming!
This door of mine
is going to get smashed by you sooner or later.
The sun's already high in the sky.
You're still not up?
I was reading all night last night.
Didn't sleep till dawn.
Reading?
What book got you so interested?
We're heading into their territory, right?
Know yourself and your enemy, win every battle.
My goodness.
I never knew you were such a diligent person.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means you're doing well.
You reap what you sow.
Good job.
I know that one.
By the way,
are you still going to
Fatty's speech?
I forgot.
I'll go change into my...
My...
suit.
Suit.
I'll go change into my suit.
Don't forget to eat breakfast!
Not coffee and sandwiches again, I hope.
This time it's soy milk and fried dough sticks.
Thank you so very much.
Thank you, Advisor He.
Hold on.
Tomorrow at eight, embassy visa interview.
Here are the interview questions and answers.
Memorize them.
I've always hated memorizing texts.
Isn't there another option?
You want a fake marriage with me?
Speech Draft
Archaeology is a discipline
that studies human history.
It's not only
the examination of ruins,
but also the organization of historical records,
com-
pilation.
Compilation.
The father of Chinese archaeology, Li Ji, once...
Li Ji Zeng, for Chi-
The father of Chinese archaeology is Li Ji.
I, I, I know.
I know there's no "Zeng."
I was just testing you all, right?
Just a joke.
The father of Chinese archaeology, Li Ji,
once
once, for China's archaeological community,
established a rule of the trade.
Gulaijin.
Satisfying all your cultural needs.
Master Lu,
with teeth like yours,
aren't you afraid these sugar-roasted chestnuts
will crack your gold tooth?
Stop looking outside.
You won't find me.
Who are you, anyway?
Buddy,
if you've got something to say, just say it.
All this sneaking around in the shadows—
what's the point?
By the way,
you missed Fatty's speech today.
What a real shame.
Who, who, who are you?
Cut the chitchat or I'm hanging up.
Listen carefully.
Li Ke has already been taken.
If you don't want him dead,
before five this afternoon,
come to No. 6 Courtyard, Ping'an Hutong.
Then I have a question.
I'd like to ask the two teachers.
Little sister.
Why do you look so familiar?
What "little sister"?
Uh, well, this young lady...
I mean, classmate.
What's your question?
Based on what you said earlier,
the two of you teachers
found this kind of eye totem
at two ancient sites in Yunling and Nanyun.
Previously, an archaeologist
also discovered the same totem
in an ancient city in the Western Regions.
Does this suggest that these two civilizations
share some kind of subtle connection?
Or, if we place this totem
within these three civilization systems,
what kind of significance would it have?
The eyeball, right?
The eye.
The eyeball, the eye, well, it's...
It's like this.
The eye is our
window to exploring the unknown world.
Its shape symbolizes observation.
Many civilizations on Earth
also have this kind of eye pattern.
As for whether it's
related to those three civilizations,
or whether more unexplored ancient sites
also contain the same totem,
that'll have to be left to our archaeologists
to continue researching.
Little Chen.
Students, please continue.
Okay, okay.
Students, let's thank Teacher Chen.
Just now,
I got a phone call.
The person on the other end
not only knew exactly what I was doing,
but also said Fatty had been kidnapped.
Fatty's giving a lecture right now.
Could it be a prank?
Prank or not, I don't care.
Anyway,
I... I won't step out of this courtyard.
Hey, student.
The Teacher Fatty who was just lecturing?
I just saw
him leave with a man in a suit.
A man in a suit?
Yes.
Thanks.
What now?
We've gone around in a huge circle.
Where on earth do we get in?
A Guangliang main gate,
a three-courtyard compound,
a textbook south-facing house with a southeast gate.
Who lives here?
Bro, at a time like this,
why are you pondering that?
It's ten minutes to five.
What do we do?
Here's the plan, Lao Lu.
I'll go in first.
If I'm not out in twenty minutes,
go to the nearest police station and report it.
Mr. Chen, I've been waiting for you.
Please.
What took you so long?
What's going on?
What do you mean, 'what's going on'?
Weren't you about to die?
Drinking yourself to death still counts.
Lao Lu is worried sick about you.
Okay, okay, stop, stop.
Let me introduce you.
Come on, come on.
Uncle Min.
A filthy rich Hong Kong businessman.
Let me tell you,
all of our foreign trade dealings,
Uncle Min set them all up.
All right, all right, Fatty.
Brother Chen.
I've been waiting forever to meet you.
Come, come.
Sit down, sit down, let's talk.
Here.
Brother Chen's been in seclusion lately,
not seeing outsiders.
So I really had no choice
but to resort to this.
I hope you can forgive me, Brother Chen.
Uncle Min.
Lian Ximin.
I've got things to do later.
What did you want to see me about?
Straight to the point, as expected.
Yes, yes, that's my buddy.
All right.
Then I'll get right to it.
No need to beat around the bush.
I invited you here, Brother Chen,
because I'd like you to join us
on a trip to the western mountains,
to search for the legendary Mengna Gu.