Let me put it this way, boy.
Northern Tuluo Kingdom cavalry are fierce.
Every autumn, they raid our borders.
They abduct our people,
plunder our wealth and provisions,
and burn down civilian homes.
Though our forces hold the line,
we can only repel them temporarily.
But the grasslands are too vast.
When our troops pursue,
they often lose their bearings,
and frequently fall into ambushes.
Even if they cut their losses in time,
the front lines stretch too far.
Provisions and water supplies
cannot be guaranteed.
So tell me, regarding this near-success,
how should it be handled?
This old fox is no simpleton.
He knows court affairs,
and understands border warfare.
I'd better test his depth.
You little brat.
Let me tell you something.
Writing poetry and the battlefield
are two completely different things.
On the battlefield,
there's no such thing as innate talent.
Even a martial arts master
on the battlefield
might still face the risk
of being killed by some nobody.
So, you little brat,
from now on,
don't go shooting your mouth off.
That's not fair.
My Young Master is still so young.
He hasn't studied military strategy,
nor has he been on a battlefield.
If he can't come up with a solution,
that's only natural.
If this brat went to battle,
he'd just wet his pants, I reckon.
Looking down on me, are you, old fox?
I'm afraid I'd scare you if I told you.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Come on, let's hear it.
It's simple.
Don't they just want people and supplies?
Have our soldiers disguise as civilians,
let them be captured,
then strike when they least expect it.
Catch them completely off guard.
Easier said than done.
How exactly would you strike?
Perhaps...
poison their provisions.
Ridiculous nonsense.
You little brat.
Do you think Tuluo Kingdom's generals
are just useless fools?
Seems this old man has some real skill.
A true sage hides among the common folk.
I was just joking earlier.
Now hear my real thoughts.
The grasslands are too vast.
We are unfamiliar with the terrain,
so we're indeed at a disadvantage.
Therefore,
rather than defending passively,
we should take the initiative.
Select hundreds of elites from our army,
infiltrate Tuluo Kingdom in disguise,
create chaos,
incite the people,
seize the mountains as warlords,
and rise against their court.
This is called
"breeding bandits to disturb a nation."
Then send envoys to neighboring states.
Have envoys from the neighboring states
arrange marriage alliances,
open trade routes, build connections,
to hold the Tuluo Kingdom in check.
If none of these methods work,
then we'll have to play dirty.
Take corpses of plague victims
along with some animal carcasses,
and dump them in Tuluo Kingdom's water
to spread plague within their borders.
Mass troops at the border, ready to strike
forcing Tuluo Kingdom on high alert.
A massed army consumes immense supplies.
With plague raging within,
and enemies lurking outside,
trouble from within and without,
Tuluo Kingdom can't take the pressure.
They'll surrender on their own.
Under such urgency,
this is all I could come up with.
Give me a bit more time,
or send me to the front lines,
and I can think of more strategies.
Are you sure
you've never studied the art of war?
I swear.
Young Master has barely read a few books.
Could it be that this kid
truly has extraordinary talent?
Damn right, I am extraordinarily gifted.
So what?
Don't try any stalling tactics with me.
Answer me this.
What's your relationship with Ning Ziming?
Your servant, Ning Ziming,
pays respects to Your Majesty.
Your humble servant...
Silence!
What is troubling Your Majesty?
Are you punishing me?
Could it be that recently
I have done something wrong?
My Minister Ning,
rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
My Minister Ning.
Are you all right?
I am fine, Your Majesty.
My Minister Ning,
I have heard
that My Minister's eldest son, Ning Gan,
took part in this year's imperial exam.
Could it be
that my bribery for Ning Gan's exam
has reached His Majesty's ears?
In reply to Your Majesty,
yes, indeed.
Ning Gan has come of age,
having studied for many years.
It is time he served the nation
and shared the court's burdens.
Good. Very good.
You raised him well, My Minister Ning.
Have you read the poem I sent you?
Of what Your Majesty bestowed,
your humble servant has surely read it.
And what did you think?
Magnificent, sweeping thousands of miles.
Whoever composed such a poem
must possess extraordinary talent,
well-versed in our dynasty and Nanxuan.
Then in your view, My Minister Ning,
how does this man compare to Ning Gan?
Which is the better of the two?
Ning Gan cannot hold a candle to him.
And what of your other sons, My Minister?
Reporting to Your Majesty,
my second son Ning Xing, third Ning Mao
are mediocre in literary talent.
They dare not be compared to him.
You scheming Ning Ziming.
Still trying to deceive me.
And what
of your fourth son?
Why does His Majesty ask about Ning Chen?
Did someone expose me abandoning my family?
His Majesty most despises
heartless and faithless men.
Your humble servant confesses his guilt.
I beg Your Majesty for mercy.
I beg Your Majesty for mercy!
Enough.
I summoned you here alone
not intending to punish you.
I simply feel
that the boy Ning Chen
is a fine young man.
You ought to show him more care.
As for me,
I can grant you one more chance.
But you must remember:
should you disappoint me again,
you shall ascend the Dragon Platform
and test if my royal blade is still sharp.
Your humble servant understands.
Your Majesty may rest assured.
When did His Majesty meet Ning Chen?
One more thing.
Ning Chen does not know my identity.
Therefore,
Of our talk as sovereign and minister,
I do not want anyone else to know.
This will not do.
I must hurry and find Ning Chen.
You may withdraw.
Your humble servant thanks Your Majesty.
Shipeng.
Summon the Crown Prince.
At once, Your Majesty.
Thank you for your trouble, Xiaomei.
Living quite comfortably, aren't you?
Wine and meat on the table.
When you left the manor,
did we not search you thoroughly?
Did you sneak out with manor valuables?
Bullshit.
I earned the money for this food myself.
It has nothing to do with Ning Manor.
What are you three doing here?
You're full of it.
We are Young Masters of the Ning Manor.
Do we need to report to you where we go?
This is Xiaomei's home.
You're not welcome here.
So you know it's someone else's home.
Then who are you to decide?
Exactly.
Ask this lowly maid yourself
if she dares to drive us away.
If the three Young Masters wish to come,
this servant naturally dares not object.
I only hope you can speak civilly.
Speak civilly, my ass.
Back at the Ning Manor,
this Bastard nearly killed me.
Now he wants to walk away and end it?
In your dreams.
What do you want?
To send you to see your mother, of course.
Get him!
Stop!
Big Brother.
I thought it was some martial arts master.
Turns out it's just an old cripple.
Do you know who I am?
Not just you three milk-mouthed brats,
even if your father Ning Ziming were here,
he wouldn't dare mock me.
You old geezer, quite the nerve you have.
Calling my father by his name.
Watch I don't kill you for it.
Why waste words on them?
Today, even if the King of Heaven came,
it wouldn't help.
Such big talk.
If you've got the guts, come try me.
You old fool.
Getting more worked up by the minute.
I... I...
Calm down.
He looks somewhat familiar to me.
Big Brother.
Anyone with that Bastard Ning Chen,
how important could they be?
Probably just this maid's neighbor.
Right, Second Brother is correct.
If a few words could scare us off,
word would spread,
and we three brothers would become
the laughingstock of other Young Masters.
Exactly.
Mother gave us instructions anyway.
You stand back.
Leave this to me and Second Brother.
Right, right, come on.
You came here for me.
Whatever it is, come at me.
It has nothing to do with anyone else.
Death is staring you in the face,
and you're still playing the hero.
Forgotten the wound on your neck already?
You...
I just let my guard down, that's all.
You damn dog.
Get him!
Look out!
Xiaomei!
Young Master!
Young Master, don't scare me!
Young Master, wake up!
All of you, get up!
Are you all useless?
Get him!
Get up, now!
Greetings, General Chen.
He's General Chen Wu.
You little brats, finally here.