Master Wang,
the Young Master seems
to have vanished without a trace.
We haven't found a single clue.
Useless fools!
What about Laifu?
The men we sent after him
have disappeared, too.
You...
Master Wang,
please rest assured.
I inquired at the Bureau.
They never caught him either.
They are posting notices on the streets.
Go find him!
Ten thousand in silver
for whoever finds him!
Ten thousand for catching Laifu?
For finding the Young Master!
The Young Master!
You senseless fool!
Get out!
Ten thousand...
Wang Dingrong really loves his son.
Hengshun Salt Bureau is now
in complete chaos.
Wang Dingrong has
even fallen ill because of it.
It seems he has gone missing, then.
(Missing or in hiding)
I've found the physician
who treated
Wang Dingrong's leg back then.
Wang Dingrong claimed
his leg was broken from a fall.
But when the physician examined it...
Master Wang's leg
wasn't broken from a fall.
Someone
broke his leg.
If he was beaten,
why claim it was a fall?
Could he be hiding something?
The sinking of the Qi family's ship
is looking more and more
like premeditated foul play.
With Wang Xian missing,
the letter written to Laifu...
Who exactly wrote it?
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 5=
This dirty old man sure is fast.
Ledgers and water transport dispatches
from the Wang family's
first and most recent six months
managing the salt bureau.
And these are from the Qi family's
last six months, and two years ago.
Lin, why don't you come over and help?
Let's look into this together.
Because he
can not read.
(Signatory: Wang Xian)
Since Wang Dingrong is in charge,
why are the signatories
on all the accounts
Wang Xian?
Wang Xian.
It really is him on all of them.
Why is there no record
of the Qi family's shipwreck?
Furthermore,
after the Wang family took over,
this batch of official salt
was never dispatched again.
It is a significant loss, after all.
I guess Wang Dingrong was unwilling
to take it on.
(Water Transport Dispatch.
Cargo: Liu Shun.)
(Come to Hengshun Salt Bureau
at night for the money.)
(Shun)
There is no need to investigate
the shipwreck case anymore.
Since
our goal is the same
as the water ghost's,
we just wait to uncover
the water ghost's true face,
and the truth will
naturally be revealed.
Master,
you seem to have missed something.
This water ghost, Qi Feng,
is already dead.
Carefully compare
these three "Shun" characters.
The "Shun" on the note Laifu received,
the "Shun" of Hengshun Salt Bureau,
and the "Shun"
in Liu Shun's death dispatch...
are exactly the same.
Moreover, the handwriting on the note
is not Wang Xian's.
It was written
by the water ghost to Laifu.
The water ghost
is not Qi Feng.
(What exactly have we overlooked?)
(Where exactly does the problem lie?)
(The thumb ring.)
(The note.)
(Since you knew
how to impersonate Wang Xian)
(to lure Laifu out,)
(you must be intimately
familiar with all of this.)
(You lured Laifu out)
(and allowed the Bureau
to capture him easily.)
(Your goal)
(was to have Laifu
testify against Wang Xian.)
It belongs to Wang Xian.
(You did it to prove that)
(Wang Xian murdered to silence them.)
(You must hate Wang Xian to the bone.)
(Who exactly are you?)
In order to give my daughter
a place to express her grief...
Such devotion
is rare and precious.
Commissioner Di,
my daughter's mind has not recovered.
She cannot withstand any shock.
Please...
Rest assured.
I understand.
Ruo.
Commissioner Di.
We have captured Laifu.
He fully confessed
to Wang Xian's crimes.
And he testified that Wang Xian
murdered Cai to silence him.
Hence,
we can finally give Lady Du
an explanation
regarding Qi Feng's death.
Lady Du,
aren't you concerned
about Wang Xian's whereabouts?
With you here,
Wang Xian will surely be caught.
Commissioner Di,
what about the sinking
of the Qi family's ship?
This case is already two years old.
Evidence is nowhere to be found.
Please forgive me, Lady Du.
The Wang family scuttled the ship.
Where did you learn this?
Half a year ago,
Wang Xian said so himself.
(Wedding)
Qi Feng,
even though
we were not formally married,
in my heart,
you are the only husband I'll ever have.
You have been gone for so long.
It is time for you to come back.
He's never coming back.
What are you doing here?
If I hadn't followed you...
I never would've known
about this nice little spot.
Qi Feng is dead.
He died in the river.
He's never coming back.
Shut up!
Listen up!
Qi Feng isn't coming back!
I had his ship scuttled.
I killed him.
Do you know why?
Because I love you,
Ruo.
But why do you only have eyes for him?
We were childhood friends too.
We grew up together too!
Why does he get to have you,
while I could only watch?
Let go of me!
Because he's
the Young Master of the salt bureau,
and I'm just a poor boy?
It doesn't matter.
For you, I can
take everything from him.
And destroy it all.
Despicable!
I'm going to report you!
I'll report you to the Bureau!
Ruo.
You're a smart girl.
Surely you realize
that I could take over
Hengshun so easily.
I'm not afraid of you reporting me.
One time,
you fell into my arms.
Ever since then,
you're all I dream about.
Let me go!
You two used to secretly meet here.
Now, it's ours.
I wanted to report it to the Bureau.
But I didn't have any evidence.
And I couldn't put my father in danger.
Commissioner Di,
my daughter needs to rest.
Please leave.
Did Wang Xian
also find out
that Qi Feng is the water ghost?
He didn't.
It's all my fault.
I was careless.
I accidentally exposed the letter.
It brought death upon Qi Feng.
I hate myself.
I just watched helplessly
as he burned in the fire.
Commissioner Di,
we've told you
everything we should
and shouldn't about the Wang family.
My daughter really
can't take any more shock.
Please.
What was Qi Feng's shoe size?
Why do you ask?
Nothing important.
Could you tell me?
Qi Feng is dead.
I couldn't tell you.
Before you started the fire,
did you look inside the room?
What state was the victim in?
He was
lying on the bed.
Did you see his face?
His back was to the window.
I didn't notice.
Before you killed someone,
didn't you even verify their identity?
Commissioner Di,
it was our first time
doing something like this.
We were too panicked at the time.
The fire in that room
shot up so high all of a sudden.
I was too scared.
I didn't dare look.
The fire in the room?
Think again.
Is there anything else you left out?
The fire
even burned onto him.
He seemed not to have
moved at all
right from the start.
He never moved?
(Laifu said)
(that a huge fire broke out
in the room instantly.)
It's flint.
Just as I thought.
(I thought this fire
looked strange at first glance.)
(The night the fire started,
there was a southeast wind.)
(The flames rushed southeast.)
(Therefore, the wood there)
(should be the place
that burned the fiercest.)
(The scorched wood
should be grayish-white.)
(Why is it that burnt wood
around the bed)
(also grayish-white?)
(So the root cause was here.)
Light it up.
You do it.
(Du Ruo claimed)
Qi Feng!
(she witnessed Qi Feng
struggling in the fire,)
(- but was hit by a beam when escaping.)
- Ruo!
Qi Feng!
(But Laifu said)
(the burning man didn't move at all.)
(Who's lying?)
(Or...)
(Are neither of them lying?)
Master!
Bad news!
Did you find Xian?
No. It's not about the Young Master.
It's Qi Feng.
Qi Feng?
Qi Feng is the water ghost.
He killed Sun Qi and the other two.
And he also knows
that the Young Master
had his ship scuttled.
Even Di Renjie and his people know now.
What proof does he have
that it was my son?
The Young Master was drunk.
He told Lady Du Ruo
everything he did!
If Di Renjie wants to find evidence,
it'll only take him the blink of an eye.
You have to think of something!
The most important thing now
is saving the Young Master's life!
Think of something?
What else can I possibly do?
Then...
This...
The prefectural office...
Right.
Go to the prefectural office.
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
These are Qi Feng's bills,
along with the dispatches and letters
he personally signed.
(Qi Feng)
Du Ruo brought us Qi Feng's corpse,
yet I completely overlooked
the authenticity of Qi Feng's letter.
Who wrote that letter?
It was Du Ruo.
She's skilled
in calligraphy and painting.
Forging this handwriting
would've been effortless for her.
Without a careful comparison,
it's incredibly hard
to spot the difference.
(Ship)
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
Please announce me.
Du Ruo is here to take her husband home.
Why would she forge the letters?
We let the shipwreck
cloud our judgment.
If we had just believed from the start
that Wang Xian really went missing...
The answer
lies with that charred corpse.
Lady Du,
what brings you here?
Official,
the killer has been caught,
and Qi Feng's case is solved.
I'm here to take him home.
Where's Du Ruo?
She left.
What about the corpse?
It's right here.
That was close.
The case isn't fully closed.
I'd never
let anything happen to the body.
Qinglan,
do another autopsy.
Magistrate Cao.
Sir,
look here.
A massive amount of soot
in his windpipe and lungs.
His lungs are a purplish-black.
It seems there are traces of drugs.
He must have
lost consciousness from the drugs
and unknowingly inhaled all that soot.
That makes sense.
I was careless.
Judging by his bone structure,
it's a perfect match.
This is Wang Xian?
Then where is Qi Feng?
There is no Qi Feng.
(Preview of Next Episode)
I'm sorry.
I...
I didn't mean to.
Ruo,
I couldn't help myself.
Forget about him.
Start over with me.
Let's start over.
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪