Please.
Uncle Min.
Among my father's belongings,
I found an ancient scroll about Mengna Valley.
It says
the map of the heart of Mengna Valley
is hidden in the Silver Eye at Juedabu City Ruins.
What Silver Eye?
To an outsider,
the Silver Eye looks like a giant relief.
But to those in the know,
what is it?
It's a coordinate map!
This ancient scroll states
that at its center is drawn
a territorial map of Mengna Valley.
By following this map,
the location of Mengna Valley
can definitely be found within the Silver Eye.
So you mean
we first need to go to Juedabu City Ruins
and find the Silver Eye.
Exactly!
Then we should get He Shutong.
Brother Chen really gets me!
I won't lie to you,
I've thoroughly studied every paper
Miss He wrote about Mengna Valley.
So Miss He
is an indispensable member
of this trip to Mengna Valley.
Brother Chen,
I can only turn to you for this.
Please help me persuade Miss He.
Put down those walnuts.
Stop fiddling with them.
This is a fantastic opportunity.
Here's the deal, Old Lu.
Come back with me now to draw up the contract.
Four people.
Two thousand per person, per day.
That's not bad.
Nobody turns down money.
But still,
won't this go against our principles?
We have to notify the organization.
At the very least, Curator Zhu needs to know.
Fine, fine, here's what we do.
We'll draw up the contract, no delay.
Let Old Chen report to the organization and Curator Zhu.
Just give them a heads-up.
And give him a day off while he's at it.
Let him win over Advisor He.
First thing tomorrow, I'll go get my visa.
If nothing unexpected comes up,
I'm going abroad next week.
When did you decide this?
Just now.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let me tell you, I...
I could slap myself right now.
You know that?
I really regret it.
I shouldn't have
urged you and Advisor He to go together.
At least I'm going abroad for treatment.
Brother,
can your illness even be cured abroad?
Don't you know that deep down?
I know what Advisor He is thinking.
She's a woman in a tough spot, so she's emotional.
How did you get brainwashed too?
Why do you keep pushing me to go to Mengna Valley?
What's your angle?
My life is on the line.
You think I care about his lousy money?
Brother,
I went to all that trouble setting this up.
Do you think it was for the money?
That's a question I should be asking you.
Stop, stop.
Why am I telling you to go to Mengna Valley?
Because I know
Uncle Min has the same illness as you.
He's going to Mengna Valley
to save his own life.
You actually have the nerve to make up this nonsense?
Fatty, you can't joke about stuff like this.
Get lost.
Who's joking?
How many years have you known me?
Am I the kind of guy who'd joke
about a brother's life?
Boss, with your current condition,
I think this trip to Mengna Valley,
let me go in your place.
No way you can take my place.
Where this illness really comes from,
and whether it can be cured,
that's something I need to go and find out myself.
This is seriously bizarre.
Uncle Min,
how does he have this same scar too?
Commander Chen,
I promised to help you break the curse on you,
and I never thought of quitting halfway.
But Commander Chen,
if you die in some hospital abroad
without ever knowing why,
I, Fatty,
will never forgive you, not in this lifetime.
Look at the mess we're in.
Visa denied.
Didn't I tell you to memorize the script?
I did memorize it.
I answered exactly as written.
You never wanted to go abroad, did you?
Just because the visa got denied,
you can't dismiss what I planned.
Then what about those adventure books by your bed?
How do you explain that?
If you didn't want to go abroad, you could've just told me.
If you want to go exploring, I'll come with you.
I just want to ask you,
before you make every decision,
did you ever think to discuss it with me?
Or at least let me know?
Shutong.
Shutong, let me explain.
I memorized the script word for word.
I answered seriously, I swear.
Shutong.
Good morning, sir.
What do you do for a living?
I work at a museum.
I'm an archaeologist.
What's your current salary?
One thousand a month.
Why are you going abroad?
Because I'm ill.
I need to try a new treatment.
How about
we consider a fake marriage?
Who'd ever fake-marry you?
Oh, right.
There's something important
I need to discuss with you.
It's about the Lingxiao Pearl.
Get lost.
Bodhisattva, please bless us.
Keep us guys safe and sound,
in harmony together,
and please don't let us fall apart.
Bless us, bless us, bless us.
Coming!
Where's Fatty?
Well, I called him.
Whether he shows up, who knows.
Fine, forget him then.
What's up?
I've worked things out with Uncle Min.
He's already in Chengdu.
We leave first thing tomorrow morning.
After we meet up, we head straight west.
That's what brothers are for.
What do you mean, "forget him"?
The ancestors' rule:
United we live, divided we die.
That rule can't be broken, you know that?
I won't waste any more words.
This time,
unlike any tomb expedition we've done before,
is completely different.
We're heading to the west.
The climate, altitude, terrain,
any single one of these factors
could get us killed.
None of us can let our guard down.
That's point one.
Point two,
and the most important one in my view,
I, Chen Youxi, may very well die out there.
Anytime, anywhere,
if I tell you to leave,
you must listen to me.
No hesitation whatsoever.
Rule two: you don't get the final say.
Brother Chen!
I've been waiting for you guys forever.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
And this must be
Miss He Shutong, am I right?
Yes.
I've read many of your papers.
A true honor to read them.
Meeting you today, you're as elegant as your writing.
A pleasure, truly.
You flatter me, I don't deserve it.
Come, come, come.
Please, come on in.
Come, come.
Take a seat anywhere.
Bi Huaqiang,
get everyone seated.
I'll go fetch some fine tea for you all.
Great, great, great.
Fatty,
Come here, come here, come here.
Look at this.
Pretty cool, huh?
Cock it.
What are you doing?
Don't touch it.
You could've just said so.
Who are you trying to scare with that crappy slingshot?
It's a crossbow.
Range of 100 meters.
Within 50 meters,
It's like a Type 54 pistol.
A pistol?
Look how cocky you are.
What gun hasn't Fatty seen?
Come on, shoot here.
Stop it!
Don't move.
What's going on? What's wrong?
What's happening here?
These are my guests.
What are you doing? Let go!
Drop it.
You.
These are all guests I invited.
Is this how you treat my guests?
Apologize.
My apologies.
Bi Huaqiang.
Let me tell you,
If it weren't out of respect for Uncle Min,
I'd teach you a lesson.
Alright, alright, alright.
Fatty, Fatty, please have a seat.
Don't be angry.
Brother Chen, I'm so sorry.
Come, take the seat of honor.
Come on, sit at the head.
Let's go.
Brother Chen, please sit down.
Ah Zhong is young and doesn't know better.
But let me tell you something,
His wilderness survival skills
Are truly extraordinary.
And this crossbow,
Don't underestimate it either.
He made it himself.
Now you've met,
Let me give you a proper introduction.
She's the head coach of the Krav Maga Association.
Thank you.
Teacher Lu,
We met on the train.
Teacher Li,
I caused trouble at your lecture.
Teacher Chen, we meet again.
I remember now, Fatty,
she's the girl you were hitting on, on the train!
I remember, I remember.
We meet again here.
You know Uncle Min too?
I'm Uncle Min's goddaughter.
My name is An Xiang.
I've long heard about your archaeology exploits.
You're all my idols.
Of course I had to come.
But with you wearing those sunglasses, beautiful,
I failed to recognize you.
An Xiang.
Take off the sunglasses.
Turn around.
An Xiang's eyes,
they're no ordinary eyes.
Any unclean things,
she can sense them all.
An Xiang, Ah Zhong, Bi Huaqiang,
each of the three has their own use.
On the road ahead,
we can look out for one another.
They're... they're all going?
As the ancients said,
too many cooks
spoil the broth, right?
Idiot.
Watch your mouth.
Who's here to cause trouble?
That remains to be seen.
This... this...
My wife, He Lingla,
this time,
will also be coming along with us.
Uncle Min,
the Jueda Ruins,
high altitude, freezing, low oxygen.
Bringing just you is already pushing it.
Dragging the whole family along isn't right.
Brother Chen,
how is this "dragging the family along"?
These are my right-hand people.
Old Chen, I don't think this is a good idea.
Guys, let's go get hotpot.
Let's go, let's go.
No,
nobody leaves.
We're showing plenty of sincerity,
but they're not buying it.
This trip is going to be brutal.
My team has no room for dead weight.
Brother Chen,
where's this "dead weight" talk coming from?
Don't forget, we have a signed contract.
We need to talk this through.
Just as Advisor He said,
this little girl is just a gimmick.
My Godfather said,
we leave in fifteen minutes.
Wait, when do we leave?
You shouldn't startle people like that.
You scared me half to death.
Just... just ignore him.
He's always startling people.
What's up, sis? Need something?
Can I ride in your car?
Sure.
What do you mean, sure?
Sis,
your Godfather treats you so well,
he dotes on you.
Wouldn't it be nice to ride with him?
The ride's too long, I'd be bored stiff.
Right, right, right.
The older folks should be together,
and us young people together.
Give me a break,
we're the young ones here, okay?
You find them boring,
but I'm worried we'll be too rowdy for you.
Not rowdy, not rowdy at all.
It'll be great.
Sis, ride in our car then.
Front seat or back seat?
Come on, come on.
Old Lian,
just let An Xiang ride with them.
They're young people,
it's more fun together.
Take your medicine first.
Give it to me.
Why is Commander Chen turning?