Hurry up
Go bring him to me
Whoa
You scared the life out of me
Do you have any idea
that you could scare someone to death?
How vulgar
Our master wants to see you
Follow me
Uncle is here too
Looks like today might pay off
If he truly has another identity
I'll have a powerful backer from now on
Uncle Tianxuan
Long time no see
I've missed you so much
You little rascal
Where the hell have you been?
Why is this old swindler here too?
So this is the Ning Chen praised by Imperial Father and Old General Chen?
He doesn't look like much
Sit down first, then we'll talk
Uncle
You know this old swindler?
Old General Chen
has rendered great service to our court
His might is known far and wide
Few people don't know who he is
You're a general?
What?
Don't I look the part?
Then why did you scam me that day
and got me beaten up for nothing?
I won't let you off today
A gentleman uses words, not fists.
Sit down, sit down.
Whatever it is, let's talk it out.
This man has some nerve.
In all the court, aside from Imperial Father,
no one dares treat the Old General this way.
The other day,
you chose to help that person yourself.
You did the good deed on your own.
And you took that beating willingly.
What does it have to do with me?
You old swindler, trying to play dirty, huh?
Fine.
Then you owe me damages for emotional distress.
That fee, whatever it is,
I will pay it for him.
Today, just for my sake,
let Old General Chen off the hook.
Spends so generously,
attended by a eunuch,
and knows the Old General as well.
Uncle, you must be royalty without a doubt.
Then I'll gladly accept.
That's our Uncle Tianxuan!
Having a friend like this
is truly your blessing.
This man is quite interesting.
You flatter me.
By the way, who are these two?
My humble son,
and my beloved daughter.
Uncle, you have both a son and a daughter,
and great wealth besides.
Your son is truly handsome and elegant.
Your daughter is truly as lovely as a flower.
And a virtuous and gentle
wife at home.
So,
Uncle, are you buying poems today?
No poems today.
I came today
to bring you some good news.
The strategies you proposed the other day
to Old General Chen regarding the Tuluo Kingdom,
His Majesty has learned of them.
And he was furious.
What?
I mean, greatly pleased.
His Majesty believes you are brilliantly talented
and exceptionally wise.
So he appointed you to the Imperial Inspectorate as a Silver Guard.
The Imperial Inspectorate?
The Inspectorate answers directly to Imperial Father.
Does Imperial Father intend to bring Ning Chen under his wing?
Then wouldn't I lose my chance?
It seems His Majesty truly appreciates talent
and plans to cultivate Ning Chen.
You little rascal,
thrilled, aren't you?
The Inspectorate answers directly to His Majesty.
It has the power to oversee all officials
and the entire realm.
If at the Ning residence
you suffer any unjust treatment,
a single petition can reach the Emperor directly.
You can pin on him charges of a lax household
and cruel treatment of his son.
Oh, Ning Ziming!
Really?
Of course.
Thank you, Uncle Tianxuan.
No need to thank me.
You should thank His Majesty instead.
His Majesty?
But I have never even met His Majesty.
I wonder if a nobody like me
will ever have the chance.
Don't worry.
You'll meet him sooner or later.
Ning Lanxing.
He actually knows my surname is Ning?
So Uncle Tianxuan already knew.
Lanxing is just my pen name.
The name I use when writing poetry.
In that case,
let me formally introduce myself.
I am Ning Chen.
A pleasure to meet you, Uncle Tianxuan.
Likewise.
So,
how much does a Silver Guard earn per month?
Are you that short on money?
Under the name Lanxing,
any poem you write sells for hundreds of taels.
Why bother joining the Inspectorate?
I am.
Of course I am.
Selling poems for money
isn't a long-term plan.
Besides,
I don't want to be just a scholar.
My true ambition
is to earn merit on the battlefield,
to win a title in the saddle.
After all, I'm a soldier.
It's pretty much my line of work.
Good lad!
You've got ambition.
Hey...
What... what's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
I'm still a bit weak.
Still recovering.
You look so frail, you little rascal.
Drop by Chen Manor when you can.
I'll teach you some martial arts.
It'll build up your strength.
Really?
Thank you, Old General.
Why not "old scammer" anymore?
That's a separate matter.
You shouldn't have hidden your identity.
Actually,
I grew up hearing tales of your heroics.
My admiration for you
flows like a mighty river,
endless and unceasing.
You little rascal.
When did you learn to flatter like that?
You've got quite the silver tongue.
But I don't mind hearing it.
All right, that's enough.
It's getting late today.
Stop your prattling.
The decree for your Inspectorate appointment
should be reaching Ning Manor soon.
Hurry back to receive it.
All right.
Then, Uncle Tianxuan,
Old General Chen,
brother,
sister,
cousin,
I'll see you all later.
You little rascal!
Don't forget to visit Chen Manor.
I won't forget.
Lao Quan.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It seems Ning Chen has suffered
quite a bit at home lately.
Drag Ning Ziming to the imperial study to see Us.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It seems if I want Ning Chen on my side,
I'll have to find another way.
What are you all doing here?
Ning Chen,
the manor's been overrun with rats lately.
For the safety of the household and its valuables,
we must search every room.
Guards!
Search this place thoroughly.
Your humble servant greets Your Majesty.
Ning Ziming, I ask you this.
What kind of emperor am I in your eyes?
Your Majesty,
You are unmatched in civil and military achievements,
and are a benevolent and righteous sovereign.
A benevolent sovereign?
So what you mean is,
I have been too benevolent,
so you may defy my decrees?
Your servant would never dare!
Please enlighten me, Your Majesty.
I ordered you to treat Ning Chen well,
yet what have you done?
How did he get those injuries?
Is your minister's manor a den of thieves,
or a bandit's lair?
His Majesty has seen Ning Chen?
How could that be?
Old General Chen always keeps his word.
Could someone have planted
a spy in my manor?
Forgive me, Your Majesty!
I beg Your Majesty's mercy!
Mercy, mercy, mercy!
Mercy, please, mercy!
Mercy, mercy!
Enough, enough, stop kowtowing!
You...
I know,
you want to kowtow yourself to death here,
to brand me as a cruel ruler, is that it?
Your servant would never dare!
I would never dare.
Mark my words clearly:
if there is a next time,
I will personally send you to the execution ground.
Your servant will keep it in mind.
In mind, in mind.
Get out.
Yes.
Your servant takes his leave.
Shipeng.
Go to the Ning Manor once more.
Deliver the decree summoning Ning Chen to the Imperial Inspectorate.
Yes.
Fourth brother,
Big brother was thinking of you.
Just think,
what if you got bitten by rats?
We could never face Father.
Exactly.
Big brother did it for your own good.
Big brother thinks of me,
so I shouldn't be ungrateful.
By the way,
I happen to have
a very precious gift here,
to present to you, big brother.
Fourth brother is being sensible.
What precious gift could he possibly have?
Hurry.
Big brother
Ning Chen
You beast
How dare you splash piss on me!
This boy's urine wards off rats
And it can also cure illness
You should count yourselves lucky
It's just that I've been running a bit hot lately
The smell
Might be a bit strong
I...
Big brother
Hurry, help me get this off
Ouch, ouch, ouch
Big brother, your head's too big
I can't get it off
You wretched scoundrel
I'm doing this for your own good
And yet you do something so disgusting
Guards!
Seize him!
Get him
Brothers, both of you
Think carefully
About how Lord Ning has treated me lately
If you injure me
Lord Ning will surely hold someone accountable
And by then, these two
Do you think they'll speak up for you?
A servant striking a master
How would the Ning house rules punish that?
I mean, you two
Earn so little each month
Why risk your lives?
Right?
So...
Brother, mind if I borrow this
What are you standing there for?
What are you going to do?
Take you down
Mother
You two, panicking again
What a disgrace.
Help, Mother!
Ning Chen
That bastard Ning Chen
His madness has flared up again
What is that smell?
Why does it reek so badly?
That beast Ning Chen
He splashed piss on me
What?
That bastard!
Today I'll teach you what discipline means
Guards!
Fifty strokes of the cane
Madam
Shouldn't we report this to the master first?
What?
My word doesn't count?
Of course it does, Madam
Then what are you waiting for?
Fine then
So you're rebelling, are you?
You won't even listen to me?
Get him, now
Stop!