Young Master
Brother
It's tough out here
We're all family here
Here
Take it
Don't be shy
It's fine, it's fine
This isn't my body anyway
I'm not embarrassed
It's the others
who'll be embarrassed.
Fourth Young Master
I bought these clothes for you
Please make do with them for now
Fourth Young Master
Your righteousness, brother,
I shall never forget
Until we meet again
Young Master
Why put yourself through all this?
You're a young master of Ning Manor
Just wait until you're of marrying age
Then you can get some silver from the manor
And live a comfortable life
Forget it
Give us one
The Imperial Examination just ended today
Scholars are gathering at Top Scholar Pavilion
To recite poems and compose couplets
And if you stand out from the rest
You can win a thousand taels of silver
A thousand taels of silver?
There's such a sweet deal?
Then I'd better hurry over
Writing poems for a thousand taels of silver?
Then I'd be unstoppable!
Young Master,
there's something you don't know
If among these poets
Someone actually becomes the Number One Scholar
That'd be Top Scholar Pavilion's
golden reputation
What a pity
Young Master, you are in Ning Manor
The Madam plays favorites
and won't let you study
Otherwise, in two years you could take
the Imperial Examination
And once you make the list
The Master would surely see you in a new light
By then
You'd be Your Excellency yourself
I couldn't care less
Where'd this old drunk come from?
Daring to dine and dash at our place!
Folks!
The workers at this tavern
Not only do they beat up an old man
They also sell fake wine!
Talk nonsense one more time
And I'll kick you to death
You!
Beggar, go beg somewhere else
Bullying an old man in broad daylight
Have you two no shame?
He dined and dashed
Is that supposed to be honorable?
You're standing up for him?
Then you pay up!
Fine, I'll pay
Pay up!
Hurry up!
I...
Next time...
What do you mean, next time?
I'll beat you too!
Why are you hitting people?
Help! Is anyone there?
I'm reporting this to the authorities!
Somebody, help!
They're beating someone in the street!
Get lost!
Don't ever come to our shop again!
Now scram!
Unbelievable.
Young Master.
Why put yourself through this?
Sir.
You saw that, didn't you?
These guys hit with no mercy.
Don't pull stunts like this anymore.
Xiao Mei, let's go.
Wait, no...
Oh, my dear son!
You can't abandon your father!
Sir, you're drunk.
Who's your son?
How could I be your son? Folks!
You be the judge here!
I struggled to raise him.
Now that I'm old,
he wants to abandon me.
You're trying to scam me!
Let go!
Young man,
you're in the wrong here.
No matter what a father does wrong,
he's still your father.
The laws of our dynasty state
that those who shun their elders
will face banishment to military service.
That's right.
You'll face banishment
to military service.
This...
Young Master,
what do we do?
What else can we do?
How about...
we take him to your home too.
Slow down, slow down.
Auntie!
Mei Shi!
Let Auntie have a look at you.
Did you miss Auntie?
Yes!
Brother.
Sister-in-law.
Sis.
I was just talking about you
with your sister-in-law.
Little sister.
So, who are these two?
This is the Fourth Young Master
of Ning Manor.
Ning Chen.
And this elderly gentleman is...
So you're the one
the Fourth Young Master
my sister always mentions.
Sorry to intrude.
This elderly gentleman
is someone I happened to meet on the road.
Once he sobers up,
I'll deal with him.
Sister-in-law, brother.
I need to discuss something with you.
From now on,
I may not be working
at Ning Manor anymore.
The Fourth Young Master
will also be staying with us for a while.
Little sister,
you know our family's situation.
Your nephew will start school soon,
and we really need money right now.
If you've lost your job,
your brother and I supporting you
is only right and proper.
But
if there's another mouth to feed,
how are we going to manage?
Watch your mouth.
Master Ning,
my wife doesn't know
how to speak properly.
Please don't take it to heart.
No,
Am I wrong?
He's just Lord Ning's bastard
from Ning Manor.
Don't talk nonsense!
I'll say it anyway!
Even Ning Manor doesn't want him.
What future could he possibly have?
Just look at him.
He can't do any heavy lifting.
If I let him stay here,
I'd have to wait on him hand and foot!
Shut up!
Brother!
Brother Mei! Mother!
What are you doing, mother?
Mei Jiu, how dare you hit me!
Get back inside the room!
I won't!
I'm staying right here.
Since when do you run this house?
Get back inside!
Sister-in-law.
Brother Mei.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
I've caused you trouble.
Master Ning, you overstate it.
Having you stay in our home
is an honor for my sister and me.
Rest assured,
I can't promise lavish meals,
but you'll have full meals every day.
Then I'll be imposing on you for a while.
No need to treat me differently.
I'll eat whatever you eat.
Sis.
Um,
go tidy up the side room.
I need to find a way
to earn silver and repay
Xiao Mei's family.
That's right.
Top Scholar Pavilion.