Don't think just because His Majesty favors you,
you can act without restraint.
If you hadn't reminded me,
I would've forgotten about it.
Imperial Inspectorate serves His Majesty.
Since Lord Geng won't let me go,
I'll go ask His Majesty directly.
Hold it right there.
Are you threatening me?
My lord,
how would I dare?
Compared to you,
I'm absolutely nothing.
We both serve His Majesty, after all.
How about this?
Once I return from Zhenyuan County,
all the credit will go to you.
And besides,
I also have 100 taels to show my respect.
That's bribery.
I simply admire your character, my lord.
It's just a normal exchange of courtesy.
How could that be considered bribery?
His Majesty truly didn't misjudge you.
Adaptable, upright, and kind.
Willing to stand up for the people.
Imperial Inspectorate needs men like you.
This is evidence.
You may leave now.
I'll think it over.
Lord Geng must think it over carefully.
The situation is urgent,
and the people are suffering greatly.
Get out!
Zhenyuan County belongs to Chongzhou,
the Left Chancellor's fiefdom.
Old Pan,
let's hear it.
What should we do?
Root out the corrupt.
Ease His Majesty's burden.
It's the Imperial Inspectorate's duty.
You'll lead the team again this time.
It's my duty, without question.
So,
should we bring this kid along?
Ning Chen's status is special.
I'll go ask His Majesty at the palace.
Even if His Majesty agrees,
you must keep him safe.
Old Geng,
Isn't he just the Ning family's bastard?
Is he really that important?
I suspect he's His Majesty's bastard.
What did you say?
His Majesty favors him like a prince.
Give it back to him.
If there's a next time,
you'll be punished without mercy.
That little rascal.
Let's go.
Come up and have a chat.
Uncle Tianxuan's son.
Isn't that a prince?
What does he want with me?
I'm in a hurry to get to work.
I'll be going now.
Just a few words.
These two siblings...
What are they up to?
Knowing you're heading out,
I came specially to see you.
Here.
My sister prepared this just for you.
They're trying to win me over.
Young Master.
I'm not going on a picnic.
You!
How dare you!
A gift bestowed by this princess,
and you dare refuse?
Watch me have you flogged thirty times!
I believe you.
Of course I do.
So rude.
Ning Chen seems afraid of Huai'an.
Well, if there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave now.
Young Master Ning,
be very careful in Zhenyuan County.
You're brilliantly talented.
Father wants me to learn from you.
When you return,
I'll treat you at Zhuangyuan Tower.
Here.
Testing officials with this, are we?
Is this His Majesty's idea,
or his?
Young Master,
I'm an Imperial Inspectorate Silver Guard.
How could I accept a bribe?
Young Master Ning, you misunderstand.
Zhenyuan County is remote.
Unlike the capital.
With some funds for the case,
you can grease the wheels, right?
Well...
Is this appropriate?
Of course, of course.
If it's appropriate,
then I suppose it's fine.
Taking my goodwill for malice.
Very well, then.
Since it's all for the case,
I'll respectfully oblige.
I'll be taking off then.
Why do I get the feeling
you don't really like him?
He thinks he's so talented,
and acts so arrogant.
Talks like a stuffy old man, too.
He's just so annoying.
Is this woman out of her mind?
What's that supposed to mean?
One team will investigate openly.
The other will go undercover.
Before departure,
everyone prepare accordingly.
This mission
is far from ordinary.
Everyone on this trip
must proceed in secret.
Don't hit me, don't hit me!
It's me!
Stop!
You... you...
You...
You scared me half to death!
A-Are you okay?
You're too brutal!
You hit him till his nose bled!
It was just a reflex, I...
You're such a coward.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I-I didn't mean to do it!
Anyway, pack your things.
Pack up!
T-The four of us should head out.
Just the four of us?
This time we're going undercover.
Too many people will blow our cover.
Enough.
You two, go pack your things first.
Right, let's go.
This is evidence of your bribery.
Keep it safe yourself.
From now on, at the Imperial Inspectorate,
don't pull this stunt.
Hurry up and pack.
What a piece of junk.
Farewell, my lords.
Move out!
Look here.
Zhenyuan County is just ahead.
You two will sneak in disguised later.
Ning Chen and I
will enter from the front.
Got it.
Chen.
What are you doing?
What's going on with you?
Nothing.
I...
Golden Guard Pan.
Maybe I should ride with Old Gao
and Old Feng instead.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm not arguing with you, Golden Guard.
It's just...
What? What are you doing?
Golden Guard Pan, no, no.
You don't like men, do you?
I don't like men either.
Get lost.
But the thing is...
the horse...
I can't ride anymore.
If I keep riding like this,
not only will everything get wrecked,
my prostate will be ruined.
Qianlie County? Where's that?
Aren't we headed to Zhenyuan County?
There's no Qianlie County.
Wait...
So you can't even ride a horse?
I can.
Just a little.
This kid really sucked it up.
Didn't say a word the whole way.
Brother,
you're a real man.
Come on.
Let Old Gao take a look at you.
See if anything got worn down.
No, no, no need.
Really, no need.
Old Gao,
don't try to take his length
to make up for your shortage.
Hey, you...
It's all right, brother.
If it really got worn off,
we'll send you to the palace as a eunuch.
That works too.
Even if mine got worn off,
it'd still be longer than both of yours.
Longer than his, longer than his.
Longer than yours too.
Enough, stop bickering.
Since you can't ride,
you three sneak in disguised.
I'll go in from the front alone.
Better than dragging dead weight along.
Dead weight?
Golden Guard Pan is wise.
A Zheng,
get him some medicine.
Keep a close eye on him.
Got it.
Come on, dead weight.
Let me apply some medicine on you.
Old Gao,
With that stance of yours,
people might think you were ambushed.
I sense killing intent.
Someone really is attacking.
Where's the killing intent?
Right there.
Thirty-six thousand catties.
What an extraordinary gift.
You flatter me.
Damn.
Wait, hold on.
Is this really the right path?
Li Si described this route himself.
He's a local.
The route shouldn't be wrong.
But there's no way through here.
Have you ever heard the saying...
"There were no paths in the world,
but as more people walked,
paths were formed."
Who said that?
I did.
Today, I'll set a precedent.
And take the road less traveled.
Ning Chen.
Stop joking around.
These are sheer cliffs.
What, are you going to fly?
Brother, no offense, but...
a cliff this high...
if you happen to fall,
that extraordinary gift of yours
won't be of any use.
Then you two watch closely.
It's time to witness a miracle.
You're about to see...
Spider-Man.
Nonsense.
So his name is Miracle.
His name is Spider-Man.
Right.
Spider-Man.
Old Gao,
I think I underestimated him.
Thought he was just a pampered noble.
He's got some real skills.
That lean frame of his...
Agile and clean moves.
That slim build,
incredibly strong waist,
truly an extraordinary gift.
Ning Chen!
Ning Chen! Chen!
He's ambushed! Save him!
He fell into a trap.