Old Lu.
You okay?
No, my butt hurts.
Something jabbed me.
So this is that "studio apartment" you mentioned?
Cut the nonsense.
Just pull me up already.
Why are there so many bones in this cave too?
Look at these bones.
Looks like they were just gnawed on.
This... isn't a wolf den, is it?
It's just a wolf cub.
Is this really necessary?
There's another one.
Such a tiny little life.
It didn't do anything to you.
Why insist on killing it?
Uncle Min.
Keep your men in line.
We're here for archaeology,
not hunting.
Wolf cubs grow up to eat people too.
We're in the middle of nowhere anyway.
You...
"You" what?
Shut your mouth.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
What kind of mess is this?
Look at this.
What is this?
An eyeball pattern.
There's more here.
You see it?
Commander Chen.
The style of these murals
is similar to the ones in Rahu Hall.
Is this depicting some kind of ritual?
Seems this was where the Jueda people
once held some kind of ritual.
After the ritual was finished,
they would take some
symbolic stone statues
and transport them into the snowy mountains.
Isn't that basically a sacred sealing rite?
Look here.
There's a pagoda here too.
Who would build a pagoda in the snowy mountains?
One level,
two levels,
three levels,
four levels,
five levels,
six levels,
seven levels,
eight levels,
nine levels.
The Nine-Tiered Pagoda.
Are the wolves coming?
We need to leave before the wolves return.
Don't go scaring yourselves.
Even if the wolves do come back,
they won't be that fast, right?
Brother Chen.
Enough talk.
Let's get out of here, fast.
Alright.
You lead the way, I'll cover the rear.
Remember,
do not shoot unless the wolves attack us.
Got it?
Let's go!
Move!
They're really here.
We're done for. We're surrounded.
Everyone, get your weapons out, quick!
Fatty!
Hurry!
Remember,
only wound them, don't kill the wolves.
Old Chen, here.
These wolves come in packs.
These few arrows...
These few arrows won't even scratch them.
If worse comes to worst, use the homemade explosives.
Once the pack closes in, we shoot.
They'll fall back temporarily.
At that moment,
throw the explosives behind you.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hurry up!
You're killing me here!
Hurry up, Old Lian!
As long as the wind doesn't pick up,
we'll get through tonight.
The wind's coming!
Wolf packs have one trait:
they all follow the alpha's command.
The alpha wolf.
But how do we know
which one's the alpha?
The alpha usually stays at the back of the pack.
Take that!
Wolf pack brothers!
Right, like father and son in battle.
Wolf packs operate with strict order.
The alpha must be in a spot
where it can survey everything.
That should be this hilltop.
Look, that should be the alpha.
Why are the wolves moving forward again?
Weren't they supposed to be afraid of fire?
The alpha must have just
issued another attack command.
It's gotta be Old Chen.
His negotiations with the alpha broke down.
Careful!
Stop, stop blowing!
We're done for. The fire's out.
It's out, it's out!
Fatty!
Give me the rope!
Catch!
Fatty!
You...
No, no, no.
I, I, I...
It's me.
Brother Xiao Qi.
What... what happened?
They... they retreated.
The wolves just ran off like that.
Old Chen and the others succeeded.
It's the final step.
It all comes down to this.
Are you nervous?
I'm about to wet myself.
I am a little, too.
It's all up to you.
Leave it to me.
One.
Two.
Three.
Officer He!
Come quick! Old Chen fought the alpha
and fell from up there!
What?
Hurry up!
What happened? Go check on him, quick!
Chen Youxi, are you okay?
Old Chen!
Old Chen, I'm coming!
What's wrong?
I, I, I...
Enough.
The wolves are gone already.
Can't you give those two some space?
Stop butting in.
You're so bad.
Where are you hurt? Let me see.
Is it serious?
My ribs...
Listen to me.
I might...
not make it through tonight.
What nonsense are you talking?
Listen to me.
I have only one wish.
Could you...
give me a kiss?
You're tricking me, aren't you?
What are you all staring at?
What are you looking at?
Well... uh... we'll get going first.
Yeah, take good care of Old Chen's wounds.
We'll wait for you up ahead.
What's the big idea?
At a time like this?
So this last wish of mine,
can it be granted?
Commander Chen, we finally got out.
On our way to Xiaduo Yuzhang,
is there any hidden spot
where we can set up camp?
Once we enter Shenluo Gorge,
we're basically inside Xiaduo Yuzhang.
We'll rest in that grove of trees,
then head toward Shenluo Gorge.
Brother Xiao Qi, didn't you say before
we were going to Xiaduo Yuzhang?
Where did this Shenluo Gorge come from?
After I entered that cave earlier,
the murals on the walls showed me the way.
The murals clearly depict
the Nine-Tiered Pagoda located
among four surrounding snow mountains.
In the Xiaduo Yuzhang range,
I've only seen one place
surrounded by four snow peaks,
just like in the mural.
Shenluo Gorge.
Keep up at the back!
That right there is Shenluo Gorge.
Once inside Shenluo Gorge,
we'll reach the snow peaks from the mural.
We need to lighten our gear.
The mule team won't be able to keep up.
We have to go down from here.
This looks fun!
Just like a giant slide.
Easy to slide down this ice, hard to climb back up.
So we need to find an anchor point
and leave the rope here.
That way, when we come back,
we can use it to climb back up.
Be careful!
When everyone goes down,
copy Duji's movements.
Slow down.
Commander Chen!
Look!
Hey, buddy.
Move aside, would you?
Step aside, pal.
Take a hint, will you?
Just keep moving.
What a waste of a brain.
Fatty!
Fat...
Grab on!
Why weren't you more careful?
You stupid woman!
Did you just trip me?
Stop talking nonsense!
White-hair, mind your own business.
Let me tell you.
If it wasn't her, it was you.
You shameless pair!
Neither of you is any good.
I'm saying, with your weight,
altitude sickness comes easily.
Who knows if you just lost your footing
and lost face
and now you're blaming us.
No.
What's that got to do with my weight?
You're twisting the facts.
All right, all right.
This is no place for arguing.
If an avalanche hits,
we'll all die here.
Let's move.
These four snow-capped peaks
look exactly the same.
How can we tell them apart?
Where's the Nine-Tiered Pagoda?
The place we're standing now
is right where these four snow peaks'
glaciers converge.
The terrain is rough and uneven,
crisscrossed with ice trenches and crevasses.
So when this pagoda was built,
the Jueda people
hadn't yet developed a mature construction system.
Look at these four snow mountains.
Don't they seem to be guarding
or paying homage to the Nine-Tiered Pagoda?
So if you ask me,
once we find
the cave with the stone statue,
we should get a clue to the exact
location of the Nine-Tiered Pagoda.
Look here.
Surrounded by four snow mountains.
So this stone statue
must be beneath these glaciers.
Everyone knows it's down there.
But where do we look?
Old Lu.
Come, come, come.
Look beneath that glacier.
Brother Chen,
Did you find something?
What is it?