This looks exactly like
the photo Advisor He had.
According to Advisor He,
we should head to the highest Royal Palace
for the Silver Eye.
Right.
After we get inside,
we'll head straight for the highest
Royal Palace.
I bet the Silver Eye
is hidden right inside the King's Bedchamber.
Uncle Min,
how are you holding up? Can you make it?
I... I can make it, of course.
I've already made it this far.
Even if it kills me,
I have to go in and find the Silver Eye.
He Lingla isn't doing well.
Bi Huaqiang,
you stay here with Lingla so she can rest.
We'll go in first.
Got it.
N-No way.
I... I need to go up and find the Silver Eye.
Oh, give it a rest.
You're suffering from altitude sickness.
You could die here if you're not careful.
Old Lu!
Old Lu, are you okay?
I...
I... I'm just...
going up...
See?
You'll die trying to get a free ride.
Are you okay?
This... this statue looks familiar.
Curly hair, deep-set eyes,
high nose bridge, thin lips,
muscular and well-built.
This must be the Haixi Fanxiang style.
Look at this.
Every stone pillar
has a similar pattern.
All these circles...
What... what does it mean?
This is probably
their record of the sun.
Different forms at different times.
Now isn't the time to chat
about Mengna Valley.
We should be looking for the Silver Eye right now.
Brother Chen,
all the palaces here combined
make a total of nine buildings.
Let's think logically based on the layout.
These stone pillars are all carved with the sun.
So if we assume the Royal Palace
represents the sun,
the eight palaces in the middle
should correspond to other
celestial bodies.
The question is,
where exactly would the Silver Eye be?
Based on our previous deduction,
it should be in the most prominent place.
And the most prominent place
is definitely the Royal Palace.
Isn't the Royal Palace right here?
Exactly.
Not necessarily.
I think it could be
for the city of Juedabu,
the most highly valued star.
The question is,
which one did they value the most?
I... I was just wondering about something.
You said there... there are nine.
I've been counting and only found seven.
Sun, Moon,
Venus, Jupiter, Mercury, Mars, and Saturn.
Then... what are the other two?
The orbits of the sun and the moon
intersect in the zodiac,
creating a north and a south node.
The South Node and North Node.
In the traditional astronomical system,
the point of intersection
during a solar eclipse
is also called Rahu.
It's considered an existence
higher than the sun.
That means
the palace corresponding to Rahu
should be higher than this Royal Palace.
I think
it is the most likely place
for the Silver Eye to be kept.
I just don't get it.
After all this talk,
the question is,
which is the Rahu Palace?
When this royal city was first built,
each palace corresponded to
a celestial body.
If we look at this
from the king's perspective...
Over there.
So this really is the dragon
devouring the sun.
Brother Chen.
Are you sure this place is Rahu?
From the Royal Palace's observatory,
the eight palaces and the Royal Palace
are arranged
according to the traditional
astronomical system,
based on the positions of
the nine celestial bodies.
The Royal Palace corresponds to the sun,
so this place must be Rahu.
What are you doing, Fatty?
You know, in here,
every plant and tree in these ruins
needs to be carefully protected.
If you break it,
a lifetime's wages couldn't pay for it.
Help, give me a hand here.
Let's fix it.
What's this?
Let's check over there.
Uncle Min, you said before
that the Silver Eye is essentially
a coordinate map, right?
That's right.
Then this must be it.
All these pieces...
What on earth is this?
Are you sure this thing is the Silver Eye?
Look.
On these fragments,
there are beasts and deities.
These are all elements representing coordinates.
So what you mean is
these also represent
real geographical locations?
Exactly.
On my map of the Mengna Valley territory,
it's explained very clearly.
All the mountains and rivers are labeled
with the names of deities
and sacred beasts.
You two keep going on and on,
you're not thinking of
piecing it together, are you?
Don't just stand there. Let's get to it.
Come on, come on.
What's that sound?
Look over there.
Brother Chen.
It's both an eyeball and coordinates.
There's no mistake about it, Brother Chen.
This is the Silver Eye!
This pattern seems drawn to you.
It follows you wherever you go.
Are you all right?
Godfather!
Godfather, what's wrong?
It's nothing, just my old condition.
My scripture mentioned that
the hierarchy of Mengna Valley,
including the Jueda people,
and the earliest origin
of their eye worship
came from Mengna Valley.
Now, this image can't be wrong.
This is what will lead us
to Mengna Valley—the Silver Eye!
Miss He.
I'm handing this map over to you now.
Compare it with the Silver Eye,
and we'll see where we should head next.
It'll all be visible, you see.
Old Lu, hurry up!
Godfather, slow down.
Talk about shoddy construction.
The Silver Eye!
These Jueda ruins
are over a thousand years old.
It's a miracle they've survived this long.
This
might also have to do with us
removing the fragment.
The main beam collapsed!
What if the roof comes down too?
We can't stay here for long.
Quick, run!
Everyone, get out of here now!
We can't leave!
We have to find the Silver Eye.
Godfather, listen to Brother Chen.
Let's get to safety first and talk later.
Anxiang.
Just listen to me.
Look out!
Godfather!
My Silver Eye! Godfather!
What happened? Are you okay?
Beneath this Rahu Hall,
there's a cave this deep?
There were indeed records before
that a foreigner
discovered many caves in these ruins.
The most famous among them
is the Headless Mummy Cave.
There's also a weapons cave
filled with a huge amount of weapons.
But they're all far from this Rahu Hall.
What's that thing? It's pitch black.
Look, look, look!
This must be the golden statue
of the Silver Eye.
The Hell's Calamity Mural.
We've really found something good this time.
Forget the murals for a moment.
Just this statue alone,
made of five fused metals,
cast in one piece.
Even with today's craftsmanship,
no one could replicate it.
All right, everyone get out of here, quick.
Right, right, before the roof collapses.
Let's go, let's go, Old Lu!
My Silver Eye!
A Zhong, my cane and gloves,
bring them to me!