♪Life is a dream♪
♪A dream like chasing the wind♪
♪Yet he is lost within it,
refusing to wake♪
(Wenbo, Puppeteer)
♪The so-called Golden Millet Dream♪
♪Severed between clouds and water♪
(Xuansi Drama Troupe)
♪Looking back once more♪
- Only...
- Bravo!
Since ancient times, it's been said
that when Nuo opera begins,
a hundred disasters vanish.
Even though the gods
might look like demons,
they are actually the ones
who drive away plagues and disasters.
The show is starting!
Look!
(Xuansi Drama Troupe)
The Nuo opera is starting!
- Let's go!
- Go, go, go!
Today is the God-Welcoming Dance.
- We get to see Master Zhuang Luobai!
- Yeah!
We get to see Zhuang Luobai today!
Right! Let's go see Zhuang Luobai!
Come on, hurry!
If the God-Welcoming Dance
is this grand today,
imagine what
the Winter Festival in seven days
will be like.
I know, right?
I'm looking forward to the full show
at the Winter Festival.
That lady has such a beautiful figure.
Nuo opera has its taboos.
Ladies
are forbidden to touch the masks,
let alone dance.
Is he a man?
A man?
How can a man perform Nuo opera
with such grace and beauty?
That's Zhuang Luobai.
He's the only one
playing female roles in the troupe.
He's a true master.
Something seems a bit off.
Looking at his movements today,
he seems to have lost his usual flair.
He fell!
Look! Look!
He's not Zhuang Luobai!
That's not Zhuang Luobai.
He's not Zhuang Luobai.
Who is this?
- We want to see Zhuang Luobai!
- That's not Master Zhuang!
- Yeah!
- Is he performing or not?
(Ming Yu)
Isn't that Zhuang Luobai's apprentice,
(Nuo Opera Apprentice)
Ming Yu?
Get off! Bring Master Zhuang out!
This dance is nothing
without Master Zhuang.
Ming Yu...
(Zhuang Luobai, Nuo Opera Master)
Master...
What are you doing?
For today's God-Welcoming Dance,
you will lead.
Lead the God-Welcoming Dance,
and then the Winter Festival.
Dance well today,
and you will always be the lead dancer
for the Winter Festival.
Master.
Can I really do this?
Don't betray the Troupe Master's trust.
Yes.
Master,
I will do my best.
It's freezing out here.
How much longer do we have to wait?
- It's so cold!
- Are they still dancing?
We want to see the dance!
Exactly!
- We want to see Zhuang Luobai!
- Are they dancing or not?
Where is Zhuang Luobai?
Someone's dead! Someone's dead!
There's a dead body backstage!
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 7=
Sir, follow me.
Right over there.
It's her.
Why is it her?
Divine punishment.
It's divine punishment!
She broke the rules!
The gods have punished her!
Do you know the deceased?
She's Master's lover.
Don't talk nonsense.
Who might you be?
Imperial Commissioner of Jiangnan,
Di Renjie.
Oh.
I am the Troupe Master.
Greetings, Commissioner Di.
Just now,
why did you call this divine punishment?
What else do you know?
Ming Yu,
you tell him.
Her name is Gu Pan'er.
(Gu Pan'er)
She was Master's
close friend.
How do I look, Master Zhuang?
Don't I look
better than you?
You do.
Master...
Master!
What has gotten into you?
Has this woman bewitched you?
What nonsense are you spouting?
Master,
you've broken the rules
of the Nuo opera.
Women cannot perform Nuo opera.
Much less touch the masks.
Since when
is it your place to meddle?
Give the mask back to me.
Give it back!
You will be punished by the gods.
It was this woman.
I saw her wearing the costume
with my own eyes.
She even wore the mask.
This must be divine punishment.
Exactly.
It's divine punishment.
She broke the rules.
The gods have passed judgment.
She deserves her death.
Her tongue has blackened.
Light red lividity has
appeared on the body.
Complete rigor mortis has set in.
The eyes have clouded over.
Given the snowy weather
and the cold temperature,
she has been dead for fourteen hours.
It should be
late You hour last night.
A person died backstage,
and none of you noticed a thing?
Commissioner Di,
our theater is divided
into the front, middle,
and back courtyards.
We live in the front,
practice in the middle,
and store our props in the back.
It snowed heavily last night,
so we didn't perform.
We all stayed in the front.
We didn't notice.
Yes.
None of us was here last night.
Commissioner Di,
it was not poison.
There are strangulation marks
on the victim's neck.
Narrow on the left,
and wide on the right.
It indicates the use of the right hand.
On the left side of the neck,
there is a circular puncture wound.
The murder weapon appears
to be a woman's hairpin.
This is the fatal wound.
Based on the footprint,
the foot length is 27.33 cm.
What?
That is Master's exact foot size.
A mere coincidence.
How could Master be a murderer?
Commissioner Di,
it's the work of the Red-Faced Guardian!
Ming Yu,
someone has died!
Tell them the truth.
Remember how Master
has been acting weird lately?
Stop talking!
What is going on?
Get out!
Get out of my body!
(Over a month ago,)
(Master was like a changed person.)
(He started berating and hitting me.)
(But he was even more cruel to himself.)
(In the dead of winter,)
(he would dance barefoot endlessly)
(despite the frostbite)
(on his feet.)
(It was as if his body wasn't his own.)
(As if the Red-Faced Guardian)
(possessed him.)
Master has indeed
been acting strangely,
but he could never be the murderer.
This must be divine punishment,
Commissioner Di.
Commissioner Di!
(Gongsun Heng, Prefect of Raozhou)
Gongsun Heng, Prefect of Raozhou.
Greetings, Imperial Commissioner.
Some members of the troupe
went to the Bureau to report the crime.
They said a commissioner was present,
so I guessed
it must be you, Commissioner Di.
I just wanted
to catch a Nuo opera performance
and enjoy the festivities,
but I didn't expect
to run into a homicide.
That's my oversight.
With the holidays approaching,
we should be much more vigilant.
Please, Prefect Gongsun,
seal off the news of the deceased
and have your men
transport the body to the Bureau.
Yes.
However,
I heard
that Master Zhuang is a suspect.
Prefect,
why are you reacting like that?
It's nothing.
Zhuang Luobai
is the top
Nuo opera master in Raozhou.
I've heard that
he usually dislikes socializing
and is only obsessed with Nuo opera.
I never would've imagined
he was hiding a secret.
Where is Zhuang Luobai?
Our men are looking for him.
Once he's found,
bring him in for questioning.
Yes.
Whether this footprint is a coincidence
or the truth
remains unclear.
We need more evidence.
Just make sure
he doesn't leave Wangnian County.
Yes, Commissioner Di.
(Based on the footprint,)
(the foot length is 27.33 cm.)
(What?)
(That is Master's exact foot size.)
Commissioner Di,
the victim's family is here.
Pan'er!
(Gu Qi, Father of Gu Pan'er)
(Hou Guangming, Vice Director)
My Pan'er!
With you gone,
- what am I supposed to do?
- Sir, please accept my condolences.
Sir,
yesterday morning,
I couldn't find Pan'er.
I thought
she'd gone to visit her in-laws,
so I didn't think much of it.
But who would've thought...
Her in-laws?
They didn't look down on me,
and let me
marry Pan'er.
Did Pan'er have any close friends?
Has she seen anyone lately?
Sir,
Pan'er didn't really
have any close friends.
I...
I know who killed Pan'er!
It must be Zhuang Luobai!
What makes you say that?
Before Pan'er was married,
she and Zhuang Luobai
already knew each other.
Back then,
he relentlessly tried
to seduce Pan'er.
He acts like a man of high morals,
but who knew he's actually
a heartless beast?
Even after Pan'er got married,
he kept pestering her.
She must have rejected him,
and he held a grudge,
which led him to kill her.
Please, justice must be served!
If there is concrete evidence,
the Bureau will
ensure justice is served.
Thank you, sir.
Guards,
send him out.
This case is interesting.
Everyone is adamant
that Zhuang Luobai is the killer.
You mean to say
someone else is the killer?
If this were a crime of passion,
why would Zhuang Luobai drag the body
back to the theater?
Everyone there knows
he and Gu Pan'er had a past.
Isn't that just
asking to be caught?
This has to be a set-up.
But according to Prefect Gongsun,
Zhuang Luobai stays inside all day,
obsessed with his dancing.
How could he have enemies?
Why would anyone bother framing him?
Duan,
dig deeper into Gu Pan'er.
Understood.
Again.
Master,
I've been watching.
Nothing unusual so far.
It's not as sinister as they say.
He just has a bit of a temper.
- Again.
- Zhuang Luobai
is a man obsessed.
Sir,
do you think he's the killer?
An obsessed man can become a saint,
or he can become a devil.
If you don't practice hard,
you'll embarrass yourself on stage.
If you perform
the God-Welcoming Dance this way,
how can you be the lead dancer
for the Winter Festival?
You useless fool!
Are you out of your mind?
You could've beaten him to death.
My business
is none of your concern.
Sir,
if you have evidence,
then send men to arrest me.
If you don't,
then stop interfering.
Gu Pan'er was innocent.
You and Gu Pan'er were friends.
Please, enlighten me.
Why is Master so polite to him?
They're all too high-minded.
Too refined for the common folk.
Too what?
Talk less, and read more.
But I can't read.
When was the last time
you saw her?
Over a month ago.
How did you and Gu Pan'er
meet each other?
This time, a year ago,
it was snowing just like this.
(Back then, Pan'er)
(was still an innocent girl.)
(Just like this white snow,)
(untouched by the world.)
Come in.
Are you
really Zhuang Luobai?
You're actually so handsome.
I've only ever seen you wearing a mask.
I've never seen the real you.
Whether I'm wearing a mask or not,
I'm still the real me.
Do you like this?
Yes.
Women can't touch the mask.
It offends the Red-Faced Guardian.
If you truly hold it dear,
how could it
be offensive?
(Since then,)
(we've become good friends.)
(She often came backstage)
(and had me teach her Nuo dancing.)
(Many are obsessed with Nuo opera,)
(but she was the first woman)
(brave enough)
(to step into the backstage.)
(I'd never seen the purity and beauty)
(in her eyes before.)
This year's Winter Festival performance
was inspired by her.
The Winter Festival?
For a Nuo performer,
the culmination of my life
is this grand performance of the year.
May I hear about this dance,
Master Zhuang?
She was pure radiance,
untainted by the world,
yet the world
trapped her in a cage.
She fought back.
She couldn't break free in the end,
but she still
managed to bloom for a while.
The bond between you two
wasn't about the dance,
was it?
Pan'er
and I
were trapped by these shackles.
Just two miserable souls
who could never break free from them.
My dear,
please, just have a bite.
Pan'er is already gone.
Do you really
intend to follow her to death?
Zhuang Luobai
brought the Red-Faced Guardian's curse.
None of us can escape it.
My dear!
(Preview of Next Episode)
Help!
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪