Sun,
new brew today?
I've already eaten.
Good grief.
You never hear a word I say.
Have you eaten too?
Steamed buns for sale!
Fresh out of the steamer!
Coming through.
(Wanyue Pavilion)
Come on in, sir.
Come upstairs.
(Flower Lanterns)
Sun.
Yes?
This batch...
It's freshly brewed.
It's so strong.
Oh.
Unload the liquor.
(Fuxian Restaurant)
Shopkeeper!
Four barrels of osmanthus liquor!
Good food and drink.
- There are exciting stories too!
- Sir.
- Keep eating.
- Inside, please.
(Drunken Moon Paradise)
Drink up.
Bring the liquor already!
Why is it taking so long?
Sorry to keep you waiting, sir.
Coming right up.
Fine brew is worth the wait.
I've waited so long.
There's still no liquor?
Go on drinking.
Hurry and bring the liquor.
This is heavy.
There should be more.
Darned Sun.
He never rinses his barrels properly.
What is this?
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 12=
(Changsha)
Sir,
it's noon.
(Zhou Quan, Prefect of Tanzhou)
(Cui Junmao,
Magistrate of Changsha County)
Should've arrived by now.
What's going on?
No signs of struggle
inside the barrel.
No abdominal fill.
The body was placed in the barrel
after death.
There are cuts all over the body.
I'm still searching for the fatal wound.
These scraps of flesh
were left behind after soaking.
Oh, sir.
Great Lord of Justice!
This has nothing to do with us.
The liquor
was delivered by Sun earlier today.
Lady Yue.
Sir,
I'm innocent!
It must be
the fox demon again.
A fox demon?
Move aside!
Who has such audacity
to barge into a crime scene?
Take them all away!
Hush.
Quiet down.
We're examining the body. Keep it down.
Who are you?
Who are you people?
Do you have no regard for the law?
- Do you have no...
- Shut your mouth!
This is Imperial Commissioner
of Jiangnan,
Di Renjie.
Well...
Di Renjie
is sent by the Heavenly Empress.
We can't afford to slight him.
We'll wait
until he arrives.
But another fox demon murder happened
in the county this morning.
The victim was a bureau runner.
How about...
Which do you think takes priority?
Wait.
Wait until he arrives.
Sir!
Di Renjie is at Fuxian Restaurant now!
Captain Cai almost
got into a fight with him.
What?
Magistrate Cui,
what's your problem?
Buyan,
sketch the wounds.
Yes, Master.
We waited at the city gate
since dawn
for your arrival, Commissioner Di.
But we didn't catch sight of you.
Turns out
you'd already entered the city.
No wonder.
You didn't show up
at the crime scene.
I almost thought
there were no officials of Tang here.
I'm Cui Junmao, sir.
Multiple murders have occurred
under my jurisdiction.
I've failed in my duty.
Please forgive me, Commissioner Di.
Take those who drank the blood liquor
to get treated.
The bureau will cover
all the medical expenses.
Yes, sir.
Hurry.
Get them all out of here.
I failed
to discipline my subordinate.
Please forgive me, Commissioner Di.
Perhaps you should eat first
and rest from your travels.
The Great Tang
is a land governed by the law,
yet a bureau runner
was brazenly murdered
in broad daylight,
while the rumor of a fox demon killing
is making the rounds among the people.
What do you make of this,
Prefect?
Commissioner Di,
I'm aware of that.
It really was a fox demon.
The previous victim was Pisi.
He was a broker.
A few days ago,
Pisi was traveling on business.
On his way down the mountain,
he passed an abandoned house
in the woods.
Young Lady,
I'm thirsty.
Could I ask for a bowl of water?
Not long after,
a terrible stench
came from inside the house.
A passing beggar
reported it to the authorities.
Captain,
over there.
Pisi died horribly.
His face was clawed open.
Those were clearly beast marks.
And his heart was ripped out.
If that wasn't a fox demon,
what else could it be, sir?
Enough.
Stop talking now.
The body is stiff.
Lividity has formed.
The eyes are slightly clouded.
The time of death
was around twelve hours ago.
Late Hai hour last night.
Sir, the corpse bears
eleven major wounds.
At the preliminary examination,
they resemble claw marks
of beasts.
The cuts are deep,
but none of them are fatal.
Chest.
He died
because his heart was dug out.
Again?
This is terrifying.
It has to be a fox demon.
Magistrate Cui,
within two hours, investigate
the movements of Xu Da and Pisi
over the past month.
Find the witnesses.
Verify the times and locations
of the murders.
Yes, sir.
Captain,
tighten security at all city gates.
All ingress and egress
must be recorded.
Yes, sir.
Qinglan,
reexamine both bodies thoroughly.
Yes, sir.
Whose mongrel is barking
on my turf?
(Li Qian, Lord Xunjiang)
Are you blind...
Hush.
This isn't someone you can mess with.
I, Di Renjie, greet Lord Xunjiang.
Commissioner Di,
you wave the Heavenly Empress's decree
around on my land
like your own place.
I almost thought
you had forgotten
there's a Lord Xunjiang in Tanzhou.
Your Lordship,
I certainly am aware of that.
But court affairs are piling up,
and now Tanzhou has been plagued
by the fox demon killings.
The murders are gruesome.
I imagine
Your Lordship must be concerned
for the people
and unable to sleep at night.
I merely wish to ease your worries
and restore peace to Tanzhou
as soon as possible.
That is why
I neglected property courtesy
and failed to pay my respects first.
Smooth talker.
What a loyal mutt
of the Heavenly Empress.
I've underestimated you.
Di Renjie,
I give you
three days
to solve the fox demon case.
If not,
get out of Tanzhou.
Yes, Your Lordship.
If the Li imperial family
had fewer fools like him,
things would never have come to this.
(Fuxian Restaurant)
The liquor
was freshly brewed.
Commissioner Di asks
when the liquor was loaded
into the barrels.
Ah!
Commissioner Di,
it was filled around noon
before moving to the backyard.
We loaded them onto the donkey cart
this morning
(Fuxian Restaurant)
and sent them to Fuxian Restaurant.
Did you stop anywhere along the way?
Commissioner Di is asking
if you made any stops.
Commissioner Di,
I came straight there.
None of you noticed
there was a body inside?
Uh...
Commissioner Di,
the two of us loaded the cart that day.
I did notice
one of the barrels
felt heavier than usual.
Oh, right!
I thought
he was slacking off,
so I argued with him over it.
Right!
Master was rushing us that day,
so we didn't think much of it.
Commissioner Di,
we honestly didn't kill anyone.
That's right!
This has nothing to do with us.
- We swear it!
- We didn't kill him!
The killer must've known
Su was hard of hearing,
which is why the victim was lured there.
Um...
Pisi died five days ago.
His heart was missing as well.
The body had been boiled
beyond recognition.
The murder weapon can't be determined.
There are no other useful clues for now.
Master,
look at their scarred faces.
Foxes love to eat hearts.
Could there really be a fox demon?
Young lad,
you've studied under your master
for years,
and you're still so clueless?
Demons do not exist.
Sir, don't dismiss it so quickly.
There was a fox demon
in Ji'an Village two years ago.
Several people
were eaten back then.
Two years ago?
Did you see it with your own eyes?
No, we didn't.
Someone did.
Who?
Magistrate Cui.
(Two Years Ago)
Two years ago,
I had just taken office
in Huarong County.
While passing near Ji'an Village,
I came across a run-down temple.
It was bitterly cold,
so I sought shelter inside
from the storm.
You're a skilled painter.
I wonder if
I'm worthy of a painting from you.
To paint such beauty
is my great fortune.
Receiving a painting from you
on a snowy night
truly delights me.
It's only a painting.
You needn't take it to heart.
And if
I asked for
your heart,
would you grant my wish?
I witnessed that with my own eyes.
After that, the fox demon began
killing people in the village.
It was too bizarre,
so I never dared tell anyone
about finding the painting.
Magistrate Cui,
are you telling me a ghost story?
Every word is true.
I would never dare deceive you.
Is there a case file on it?
There is, Commissioner Di.
(Case Record)
(According to the files,)
(Two years ago, a fox demon
caused havoc in Ji'an Village.)
(Chen Sheng)
(Chen Sheng, a passing scholar)
(died tragically.)
(This incident was witnessed by
Magistrate Cui.)
(Later, a traveling physician
named Zhuo Ji)
(was killed.)
(It cemented the belief
that the fox demon was killing people.)
(Villagers of Ji'an fled in fear)
(and abandoned the village.)
(From then on, Ji'an Village)
(was left deserted.)
Mother!
Mother, save me!
- Mother!
- Fu'an!
Master, the bureau just sent word.
The fox demon has killed again.
The victim is a newlywed bride.
It's Old Madam Jiang from South Alley!
(The wounds on the victim's body)
(do resemble beast claws.)
(But the marks on the wooden chair)
(and the scratches on the barrel)
(were made by sharp edges.)
(The cuts are clean)
(and even.)
(These were man-made.)
Did you find anything?
Flesh craps.
Why were these found under
all three victims' fingernails?
Could they have struggled
with the killer?
No.
Look, these wounds match
the width of their own fingernails.
It's more like
they scratched themselves.
Let's go and see Commissioner Di.
Compare the wounds.
They match the cuts exactly.
Sir,
Xu Da's body was soaked in liquor.
The smell changed
and cannot be confirmed.
But shaqianzi were found
in the wounds on Pisi's face
and Old Madam Jiang's skin.
Shaqianzi?
It's known as a medicinal herb,
but it's rarely used in medicine.
It's more like a poison.
Colorless and odorless.
But once heavily applied to the skin,
body heat melts it
and releases a sweet fragrance.
That scent attracts swarms of insects,
making the victim slowly suffocate
and unable to cry out.
We also found
fresh scraps under
all three victims' fingernails.
I doubt they scratched themselves.
(Pisi)
(Xu Da)
First, the victims were drugged,
causing them to scratch themselves.
Then one body was soaked in liquor,
the other boiled,
while the rainstorm helped cover up
the scent of the poison.
Finally, razor cuts were added
to fake claw wounds,
and the hearts were removed.
So this is the true color
of the so-called fox demon.
The murderer went to great lengths
to imitate fox demon killings.
But why?
If we want to find out the motive,
we must first uncover the connection
between the three victims.
Sir,
Pisi and Xu Da had no family.
Only Old Madam Jiang
and her foolish son, Fu'an,
depended on each other to survive.
(Old Madam Jiang's House)
Examine the scene carefully.
Leave no stone unturned.
Bad man.
Fu'an, don't run around.
You're all bad people.
It was raining yesterday.
The ground was muddy.
If Old Madam Jiang were taken by force,
at her age,
there would be signs of struggle.
There are only footprints here,
and no signs of resistance at all.
You're all bad people.
That means the victim
was either taken unconscious.
Or taken away by someone she knew.
Master.
We've questioned the neighbors.
No one heard anything unusual.
But someone said
they heard
Fu'an frantically shaking
his rattle drum.
Go away!
Bad man!
He's a bad man!
An official uniform...
Xu Da.
Buyan.
Is this the bad man?
Bad man!
Go away!
What did this bad man do?
I can't say.
Tell us.
Stop pushing him.
What did Xu Da do
in this woodshed?
Di, this is
the detailed record of Xu Da's
movements over the past month.
(Shen hour, money house)
(13th, Shen hour, He Pawnshop)
Why would a bureau runner
frequent a pawnshop?
Look into it.
Yes.
Sir,
I've reexamined all three corpses.
No traces of sedatives.
No knockout powder
was found in their stomach either.
The most likely possibility is
that the killer was someone they knew.
No one heard anything unusual.
But someone said
they heard
Fu'an frantically shaking
his rattle drum.
On the night Old Madam Jiang died,
Fu'an probably saw
the killer.
(Preview of Next Episode)
Finish this.
Grow up big and strong,
so you can give me a strong grandson.
I said eat!
You won't eat?
Eat!
Eat it!
Hurry up and eat!
Easy.
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪