What are you spacing out for?
Don't tell me every time I pass out,
that's when it's the real deal?
Well, you can't really say that.
But you did pass out back in Yunling.
Every time you held this pearl,
your face would twist up,
all kinds of messed up.
This time you're so calm,
means this divine pearl has no real magic.
Bro,
how about we take this pearl abroad?
The archaeology department at my school
has a team studying mysterious antiques like this.
No way.
This belongs to China.
How can it go abroad?
That'd be smuggling national treasures.
We're so busy celebrating,
we forgot
we're sitting on a volcano!
We've got the pearl anyway,
so let's get out of here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh no.
Look at that.
This...
What is it? What's wrong?
What are you looking at?
The tree sap melted and sealed the exit.
Run!
Go, go, go! Hurry!
Quick, quick, quick!
Move it!
Come on!
You go first.
Okay, okay, okay.
Fatty!
What is it?
Nothing.
Quit freaking me out.
Hey,
did you know I'd step right into this?
It's so sticky.
Let's get out first. Move!
So weird.
Old Lu!
Bro!
The ground's splitting open!
I can see the lava!
Fatty,
get everyone out first.
Got it.
Stay behind me.
A brush with death.
You can say that again.
I just don't know
if this Lingxiao Pearl
can lift the curse on Old Chen.
Do you still remember
the murals in the tomb passage?
Are you saying the dates on the murals
match the dates of crustal movement?
Exactly.
The Dian King was waiting for his chance to Become immortal,
but for the Sacrificial Ritual,
besides the Lingxiao Pearl,
he also needed a Natural Portent.
In modern terms,
that means a volcanic eruption.
Gu Valley recorded several times before,
but they were just tectonic shifts.
The lava never erupted.
That's why they
kept passing this message down,
until the day the volcano truly erupts,
so descendants could use the Lingxiao Pearl
to complete the Sacrificial Ritual.
Then isn't this the perfect timing?
If by any chance
it can lift the curse on Old Chen,
wouldn't that be a win-win?
Exactly.
Wait, isn't that...
Isn't that the altar right there?
Let's go check it out.
Got eagle eyes, huh?
Let's go.
We need to pick up the pace.
This ground's about to crack open.
What?
Hurry!
You're just being alarmist. Where's the...
Commander Chen,
you've got the gift of foresight!
Enough, quit yapping.
There'll be bigger cracks up ahead soon.
Get moving.
Quick! Listen to Commander Chen!
Move, move!
Fatty,
have I ever told you
you're the most agile fat guy I've ever seen?
Do you even need to ask?
Fatty has always been.
Old Chen, hurry over!
Fatty,
catch my bag!
Bro, wait a sec.
What's wrong?
If you throw this bag over,
what if it accidentally falls down?
You care that much about my bag?
The Lingxiao Pearl is in the bag!
Haven't we come all this way for it?
If it falls down,
wouldn't all our efforts be wasted?
Right, right, that makes sense.
I forgot to ask you,
didn't you come to catch butterflies?
Not fulfilling your dad's last wish,
isn't it a big regret?
Although I didn't find
the Kashenfu Ghost Beauty Butterfly,
I photographed many other butterflies.
After I go back and develop them,
I'll mail them to you right away.
Old Chen, come on over!
Ding Dawei.
Your dad passed away, right?
What about your mom?
My mom passed away too.
Why are you still walking in circles?
Hurry up, or you'll get burned soon.
Everyone,
I've made a decision.
This Lingxiao Pearl,
I don't want it anymore.
Don't say that.
Old Chen, are you crazy?
This is a cultural relic!
Haven't you been guarding it with your life?
Exactly.
Hey, Commander Chen,
don't you want to lift that curse of yours?
This Lingxiao Pearl
has nothing to do with my curse.
You haven't even tried.
How do you know it's unrelated?
Shutong, I promise you.
Please trust me.
Once we get out of here,
I'll go abroad with you for treatment.
When I touched the Lingxiao Pearl just now,
I got a really bad feeling.
It's going to bring us danger.
It's not dangerous.
Chen Youxi,
what did you feel when you touched the Lingxiao Pearl?
From the moment I got this Lingxiao Pearl
until we walked out of the tree,
I had already walked this entire path once.
Are you serious?
Didn't you say I had opened my third eye
Weren't you curious why I didn't turn around
and knew your foot would sink into the tree sap?
I also knew when this ground crack would split open.
I've already been through all of this once.
So, whatever we're about to say,
you already know in advance.
I just can't be sure
whether all this is real or a premonition.
So it seems
the function of the Lingxiao Pearl
isn't to help people Become immortal,
but to cause one's consciousness to travel.
Then...
what does this have to do with Dawei?
Want to know what he did to you?
Me?
What could this kid possibly do?
He wouldn't push all three of us into the lava, right?
Who did he push?
The three of you.
He even pushed me in.
What were you trying to get?
The Lingxiao Pearl?
He doesn't even have a curse.
What would you want it for?
Because our friend Ding Dawei
is in cahoots with Bai Lingling.
They work for the same boss.
They want to use us
to find the Lingxiao Pearl, right?
Is what Old Chen said true?
Of course it isn't.
I think, Bro,
touching the Pearl messed with your mind.
The one you should be worried about right now isn't me. It's him.
Shut up!
Fatty's gonna ask you one question.
Do you know Bai Lingling or not?
I don't.
Fatty,
you've been suspicious of me the whole way.
We've been through so much together.
Don't you know what kind of person I am?
How can you doubt my character
based on one thing Bro said?
Ding Dawei, we really don't know you.
We know nothing about your past.
And the reason you came here,
we know even less about.
You suspect me too?
Just because
he says he saw me kill you?
That was just his hallucination.
Aren't you afraid
he'll take the Lingxiao Pearl for himself?
You may not realize this,
but among all of us,
the one who cares least about the Pearl
is Chen Youxi.
Bro,
didn't you see the photo of me and my dad?
What's there to doubt?
How do you know I saw the photo?
My father spent his whole life searching
for the Kashenfu Ghost Beauty Butterfly.
I want to fulfill his last wish.
Dawei,
so this really was your setup, huh?
Fine, just great.
And here I thought
I'd made some true friends.
Turns out
it was all for nothing in the end.
In that case,
no need to talk about friendship.
This Lingxiao Pearl,
I'm taking it.
Take it, my ass!
Fatty's coming over to deal with you!
Run back, head up!
Looking for this?
Stay behind me.
No way.
I gotta find a way over to help Old Chen.
Wait.
Going now will just add weight to the ground.
You'll fall down together.
What do we do?
Old Chen!
Bro,
Just let me go.
There's no point in me living anymore.
And in your eyes,
someone like me doesn't deserve to live.
Dawei, it's okay to be selfish,
but you can't be ruthless.
What do you know?
I was raised by the organization as a machine
just to find the Lingxiao Pearl.
I only learned how to deceive,
never how to be a person.
Sometimes, I really envy you.
At least you have
people around you who truly care.
The days I spent with you all
were the most thrilling,
most exciting,
and the happiest,
warmest days of my life.
That's the truth.
I'm not lying to you.
Dawei!
Old Chen, forget about him!
Get over here!
Hurry, the volcano's about to erupt!
The volcano's erupting!
Old Chen, be careful!
The rope's about to burn through!
Grab my leg!
Old Chen,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
That was close.
Such a shame about the Lingxiao Pearl.
Nothing to be sorry about.
It can't break my curse anyway.
Let's hurry up before the volcano erupts
and get out of here!
Move, move!
Go, hurry, go!
Look at that.
I gotta say, it's pretty spectacular.
Just like a giant sparkler.
What a dramatic change.
The Dian King's dream to Become immortal
was just a misunderstanding.
Whether he misunderstood or not isn't our business.
The point is, we got it pretty wrong ourselves.
Another wasted trip.
Chen Youxi,
for the Lingxiao Pearl to have such an impact
and stimulation on your consciousness,
that doesn't seem like Earth civilization.
I think it's just the human brain
operating at high speed,
predicting all the possibilities.
It's just that my deductions
are a little more advanced,
a little more accurate,
a little clearer,
a little more refined.
And his ego? More than a little inflated.
Let's get a little farther away from him.
This Earth can barely contain him.
Let's go, let's go.
Move.
Hey, Old Chen,
If you've got this skill,
I'll invite you to play cards next time.
Maybe we'd actually win.
That skill of his,
who knows if it can be sustained.
No worries. When it runs out,
we'll have him touch a live wire to recharge.
The Lingxiao Pearl isn't with them.