=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 15=
You're awake.
Why aren't you sleeping a little longer?
I was worried you'd be too tired,
so I wanted to make you something to eat.
Worried I'd be too tired?
Mm.
If you hadn't begged
for mercy last night,
would you still
be cooking here right now?
What are you doing?
This is the kitchen.
What's wrong with the kitchen?
Then aren't you going to eat anymore?
That's not important.
You are here.
Have some fruit.
Thank you.
Have you been sleeping here
this whole time?
You've really suffered.
What are you doing?
I haven't suffered at all.
How is it?
Is it sweet?
Want to know?
Try it yourself.
Let's go back to the bedroom.
There's no time.
Darling.
Darling, it's me.
I'm your husband, Gu Nianchi.
Did you discover he's fake?
I'm the real Commander.
You came to save me,
didn't you?
Save you?
I wish I could tear you to pieces.
Gu Shaoyan.
My name is Gu Nianchi,
not Gu Shaoyan.
Have you been working with my brother
behind my back all along?
You've both been waiting
for today, haven't you?
He really has always desired you.
Desired his own sister in law!
This has nothing to do with him.
Everything I've done,
from the very beginning,
was to take your life.
Why?
I liked you so much.
Back at Paramount,
the way you looked
while playing the piano
was truly beautiful.
That was when
I fell in love with you at first sight.
That's right.
I even killed Lily myself
for bullying you.
Are you happy now?
I was wondering why
no one could find Lily anywhere.
So it was you.
Yes, it was me.
I've treated you so well.
Why did you betray me?
Do you really not remember?
Then let me help you remember.
Three years ago,
you
killed my entire family.
You shot me here,
made me misunderstand the person
I loved most for three whole years.
Do you remember now?
The person you loved most?
Three years?
Didn't you once say
you wanted to marry me?
What a pity.
You're the reason I was separated
from the person I loved most
for three whole years.
I remember now.
You're the daughter of the Zhuang family
from three years ago,
Zhuang Yun...
You finally remembered.
Gu Shaoyan.
So it really was you.
You carefully plotted your way
into the Commander's Residence.
From the very beginning,
you came to kill me, didn't you?
Not just kill you.
I want to carve you into pieces.
Let me tell you.
All these years,
not a single moment has passed
without me thinking about
how to use your blood
to honor the souls of the Zhuang family.
But I never could have imagined
that you'd be this deceitful.
Using Lu Shaoyuan as your stand in.
If your Zhuang family hadn't hidden
that shipment of opium back then,
your entire family wouldn't
have been wiped out.
You only brought this upon yourselves.
What does it have to do with me?
Shut up!
It was because our Zhuang family
refused to join your filthy dealings
that you framed us.
And even now,
you still refuse to admit your crimes?
What are you trying to do?
Are you going to kill me?
My brother won't let you kill me.
He'll never agree to it.
You really think
he doesn't want you dead?
I'm his brother.
You stole his name
and took his place as Commander.
Now you remember you're his brother?
Zhuang Yunqiu,
Lu Shaoyuan looks exactly like me.
What makes you so certain
that I committed those crimes?
You...
You're not even worthy
of being compared to him.
Lu Shaoyuan has always carried warmth
and light within him.
And you...
You're just a rat
hiding in the darkness.
Your life
will never see the light of day.
Shut up.
Shut up!
When you harmed
all those innocent people,
did you ever think
you'd end up like this one day?
What do those people's lives or deaths
have to do with me?
This stab
is for my father,
and for the fifteen lives
of everyone in the Zhuang family!
Your father sold opium.
I executed him in the name of justice!
This stab
is for Lu Shaoyuan.
You ignored the bond between brothers
and broke his heart.
I generously offered to share
the Commander's position with him,
yet he repaid kindness with betrayal
and stole what belonged to me.
The one who deserves to die is him!
The third stab
is for the innocent people
of all Yancheng!
♪What is there to seek or desire,
trapped in worldly sorrow?♪
♪Entangled through lifetimes,
drawn into chaos and schemes♪
♪Your silhouette♪
♪Carved through endless hardship♪
You're awake.
How long was I asleep?
A full day and night.
I didn't kill him.
I know.
He's committed every evil imaginable
and lost every shred of conscience.
I truly wanted to take his life.
But the reason I didn't kill him
wasn't because he's your brother.
It was because
I wanted justice to be upheld
through the fairness of the law.
I want him despised by everyone,
repenting every single day.
We're thinking the same thing.
But fortunately,
heaven is still fair.
You reclaimed your place
as the Commander,
and your own name as well.
I don't care about that anymore.
The name Gu Nianchi
stopped being my name long ago.
Ever since my mother passed away,
I've been called Lu Shaoyuan.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪