=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 23=
Lieutenant Cheng,
do you think these flowers look nice?
They do.
They're especially beautiful.
Lieutenant Cheng.
Let go of me!
Let go!
I heard the guns have arrived.
- Tell them to be extra careful.
- Alright.
Why is one of your buttons missing?
Are you blind or what?
Sorry.
It's fine. Go get back to work.
It's just a pair of shoes.
Since when did you become
so careful with your things?
Well,
you gave them to me.
Of course I'd treasure them.
It's nothing.
I can always buy you another pair.
You're the Commander now.
I have to pay attention
to these things too.
Can't let you lose face because of me.
What are you talking about?
No matter who I am,
you'll always be my best brother.
Mm.
Best brother.
I'm leaving.
(Divorce Agreement)
A divorce agreement?
How...
How was everything fine yesterday?
Xinran.
Where did she go
so early in the morning?
She didn't even tidy up the room.
Zhuang Yunqiu.
Xue Wan.
These past two days,
the Commander and I have been discussing
what gift to buy for you.
We were planning
to go apologize in person.
Zhuang Yunqiu,
drop the act.
Where did you hide Gu Nianchi?
Give him back to me.
Gu Nianchi?
What are you talking about?
You locked him up
and turned him into that state.
You vicious woman.
Why would you do this to my husband?
So you knew I locked him up.
You're the one who let him go?
That's right.
I saved him.
But now he's gone.
I've searched everywhere
and still can't find him.
You must've locked him up again.
Zhuang Yunqiu,
he doesn't love you.
The one he loves is me.
And I love him too.
Stop wasting your efforts.
He told you he loves you?
That's right.
We're already husband and wife,
and we've already
consummated the marriage.
I know.
Back then,
because I didn't want to marry him,
I agreed to let you marry him instead.
But at the time, I didn't know
Gu Nianchi was the one
fate had chosen for me.
Only now do I realize that I love him.
In this Commander's Residence,
it's all about fame and fortune.
As long as you're willing
to leave the Commander,
the Xue family can give you
anything you want.
Xue Wan,
I'm truly sorry about this matter.
I should've told you sooner.
Gu Nianchi is already dead.
The current Commander isn't Gu Nianchi,
but his twin brother, Lu Shaoyuan.
Zhuang Yunqiu,
you'll really make up
any lie now just to fool me.
I know it's hard for you
to accept right away,
but this is the truth.
If you think about it carefully,
the former Commander had
a terrible reputation in Yancheng.
He oppressed the people.
But the current Commander
is completely different.
So...
So what?
You were the one saying before
that he committed every evil imaginable.
And now you're the one saying
he serves the city and its people.
Which of your words are true,
and which are lies?
Xue Wan, I'm not lying to you.
They're two different people.
Fine.
You said he's dead.
If he's alive, I want to see the person.
If he's dead, I want to see the body.
Take me to his corpse.
I...
Can't answer that, can you?
Looks to me like you just want to keep
the title of Commander's wife for yourself
and don't want to give
it back to me, right?
Xue Wan,
I never thought
you'd distrust me this much.
But everything I said is true.
If that's the case,
then I'll go ask Xinran.
You say there are two Commanders.
Even if you won't tell me,
someone else eventually will.
This matter
absolutely cannot be made public.
It's a secret.
Fine.
Even if what you said is true,
I don't care which Commander it is now.
That position was originally mine.
I want it back.
Xue Wan,
I'm truly sorry about this.
But what I want to say is,
I've never wanted
to be the Commander's wife.
I only want to be his wife.
You can make me do anything,
but I have to stay by his side.
He's the most
important person in my life.
No matter what,
I will never leave him.
Zhuang Yunqiu, you're shameless.
I know you won't believe
anything I say anymore.
But this is the truth.
Since that's the case,
take out your anger however you want.
I won't fight back.
Don't think I wouldn't dare hit you.
Nianchi.
Shaoyuan.
She may have agreed to it,
but she's my woman.
And I won't allow it.
Miss Xue, be careful.
Nianchi.
Why were you
so affectionate toward me before,
but treating me like this now?
Did you forget
how she locked you up before?
I'm telling you...
Forget it. Stop talking.
Xue Wan,
this is all my fault.
I'll keep begging for your forgiveness
until the day you truly forgive me.
Xue Wan,
whatever grievance you have,
take it out on me.
Please,
don't make things difficult
for her anymore.
Nianchi.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪