=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 12=
(Kasili)
The Fragrance Gala?
What's the Fragrance Gala?
It may look like
they're selling perfume and spices,
but behind the scenes,
they're dealing opium.
Just like those people.
Nothing but hypocrisy.
Yunqiu.
Are you sure?
But I think the Commander
is actually a good person.
He even takes care of orphans.
I almost got fooled by him too.
If that's the case,
then we have to expose him.
Yunqiu.
Be careful no matter what.
Wait for my message.
The moment I get the evidence,
I'll call the newspaper office immediately.
Alright.
Then I'll tell my coworkers
to stay late and get ready.
As soon as we get your evidence,
we'll prepare the papers for print.
Then I should get going.
Wait for my message tomorrow.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
This way, please.
Why did you come back?
I didn't really feel like
going to the concert anymore.
I wanted to stay home with you.
Last night, it was because
I was worried about your condition.
You've only just recovered.
And as your wife,
shouldn't I be helping you receive guests?
Alright.
I'd like that too.
Welcome, everyone,
to the Commander's Residence
for this year's Fragrance Gala.
My wife and I
have specially gathered
rare perfumes and spices
from both home and abroad.
We hope you'll all enjoy
a truly unforgettable evening.
- This one isn't bad either.
- Indeed.
Understood.
You prefer lighter scents.
Right.
Then let's head over there.
Every perfume here
has such a unique fragrance.
No perfume here
could ever compare to your scent.
Perfume is actually
a very special kind of gift.
How so?
For example,
you could give me a bottle of perfume.
If I wear it every day,
then whenever you
catch that scent again,
you'll naturally think of me.
You're right.
It's citrus, isn't it?
Too sweet.
Looks like I should learn
a thing or two today.
That's true.
What do you think of this one?
A pure sweetness
with a mysterious allure.
It suits you perfectly.
Then let's take this one.
Thank you.
I really like it.
Commander,
commander-in-Chief Li has arrived.
Wait here for me a moment.
I'll go greet Commander-in-Chief Li.
Alright. I'll go touch up my makeup first.
(This is the perfect chance
to look for evidence.)
Commander-in-Chief, this way please.
Commander-in-Chief.
This way please.
Mm.
The opium is in Warehouse No. 2.
Right.
Tonight, this shipment must
be sent out no matter what.
Handle it the usual way.
Naturally.
Keep this safe.
This is...
These are the names
of the merchants selling our goods.
Tonight,
that shipment from Warehouse No. 2
must be delivered.
This shipment is extremely important.
There can't be any mistakes.
Understood.
Nianchi.
This is a special opportunity
I've given you.
Don't repeat
what happened three years ago.
Back then, the Zhuang family
secretly held back the shipment.
Of course,
I was also at fault
for misjudging people.
That won't happen again,
Commander-in-Chief.
Have you found the opium
the Zhuang family hid?
We're still searching.
You'd better move faster.
My patience is limited.
I'm sorry, Commander-in-Chief.
Nianchi.
Three years ago,
you followed me into battle.
Back then,
you were full of spirit
and undefeated in every fight.
You even saved my life during a crisis.
That's why
I promoted you
to Commander of Yancheng.
You and I are on the same boat.
Don't disappoint me.
Rest assured, Commander-in-Chief.
I'll handle it immediately.
Good.
This way please, Commander-in-Chief.
Cheng Yi.
(The opium is in Warehouse No. 2)
Stop right there.
(Investigation into Yancheng
Opium Addiction Groups)
Why do you have
the document I gave the Commander?
(Investigation into Yancheng
Opium Addiction Groups)
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪