=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 11=
(Ten days later)
Your wound has only just healed.
You need to get more rest lately.
I'm fine.
I'm not that fragile.
Come back early tonight.
I'm planning
to make roast chicken for you.
How did you know
I like roast chicken?
Oh.
I only made it because I like it myself.
I'll prepare a gift for you too.
Shaoyuan.
You're really lucky.
Do you know how hard
Miss Xue has been taking care
of you these past few days?
She's injured herself,
yet she still put you first.
If I were you,
I'd completely forget about Miss Zhuang.
After all, she's been gone for so long.
Pretend I never said anything.
What if I told you
they're the same person?
The same person?
So when you said before
their voices
and appearances were alike...
Could it be...
Then has she recognized you?
She thinks I'm Gu Nianchi.
Once I help her seek justice,
it won't be too late
to tell her the truth.
By the way,
have you found Lily yet?
We've searched everywhere
and still haven't found her.
No one knows
if she already escaped Yancheng.
Keep looking.
After what she did,
she has to pay the price herself.
Yes.
Let's go.
Come somewhere with me.
Where?
You'll find out when we get there.
The flowers at this shop
are so fresh today.
But I think pink might look nicer.
Red looks nice.
Wouldn't that be a little plain?
Maybe add a bit of pink
or white
to brighten it up.
Stop overthinking it.
- Your wife will definitely love it.
- You really think so?
She'll definitely love it.
Maybe we should go back
and take another look.
Come on, Shaoyuan.
(Lao Fengxiang Jewelry Store)
Make way.
Are you alright?
Thank you.
Commander, you're here.
So that's the Commander?
Commander.
Have you eaten today?
No.
I'm giving you money.
Here.
One coin each.
Thank you, Commander.
Your hair's gotten longer.
Commander.
When did you get back?
The roast chicken is ready.
Come downstairs and eat.
I don't want that.
I want you.
Commander.
I'm not feeling very well today.
Maybe next time.
Next time?
You're my wife.
If I want you,
I'll have you whenever I please.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Still so fiery.
Sooner or later, you'll be mine.
Darling.
You're back.
Why are you here?
I came to talk to my dear brother.
Perfect timing.
I have something
to discuss with you too.
What is it? Go ahead.
You've been sick for quite a while now.
As your brother,
I haven't properly checked in on you.
I just wanted to see
how well your sister-in-law
has been taking care of you.
What a coincidence.
I was about to say the same thing.
Oh?
From today onward, she belongs to me.
Didn't you say before,
you weren't interested in her?
That was before.
Now that I've saved her,
she's mine.
You risked your life
to save my wife.
With that...
As your older brother,
I really should thank you properly.
Looks like I haven't
done enough as your brother.
Another day,
I'll punish myself with three drinks
and thank you properly.
No need.
I only want her.
Then let's make a bet.
We'll see who she chooses.
I'm telling you,
she belongs to me alone.
Fine.
Since you like her that much,
you can have her.
Alright.
Let's talk business.
Tomorrow, stay hidden.
Don't show yourself.
What could possibly require you
to appear in person?
Tomorrow, the Commander's Residence
is hosting the annual Fragrance Gala.
You won't be able to handle it.
You even needed me to stand in
for your wedding night.
Could a Fragrance Gala
really matter more
than your own wedding?
Isn't Li Shuche coming tomorrow?
I know.
You don't like him.
That's true.
I don't want to see him.
The flowers look nice.
How did he suddenly
become like a different person?
Xue Wan, I'm back.
Go away. I don't want to see you.
No...
Xue Wan.
What happened?
Open the door, Xue Wan.
Didn't you hear me talking to you?
I don't want to see you.
Xue Wan.
Open the door, Xue Wan.
Get lost!
(Gu Nianchi...)
(What exactly did you do?)
You've worked hard these past few days.
Tomorrow's Fragrance Gala
won't require your help anymore.
I bought concert tickets for you.
Tomorrow, go relax and enjoy yourself.
The Fragrance Gala...
I'll leave the tickets by the door.
Tomorrow, I'll
have someone escort you there.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
♪Falling into your smile before my eyes♪
(Yunqiu...)
(I became his stand in)
(all to wait
for tomorrow's Fragrance Gala.)
(As long as everything
goes smoothly tomorrow...)
(we'll finally be reunited.)
♪Love is so strange,
the way it entangles me♪
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪