=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 20=
Looks like fate is still on our side.
It didn't let us miss each other.
Commander.
What are you doing?
From now on,
I'll never let go of your hand again.
Do you really mean it?
Every word is sincere.
I swear it with all my heart.
(My little brother
really is lucky in love.)
(The cause he created back then)
(has now)
(become the result paving the way for me.)
(Shaoyuan,)
(this is what you owe me.)
Have some fruit and rest for a while.
Commander.
A letter from Lieutenant Cheng
has arrived.
(Gu Nianchi escaped. I killed him.
I was injured and will return after I recover. Cheng Yi)
How is it?
What did Cheng Yi say?
Cheng Yi said
he killed Gu Nianchi.
Are you sure?
This was written by Cheng Yi.
It's definitely him.
He never liked studying
when we were young.
I was the one who forced him
to practice writing for a few days.
He always liked to flick up
the last stroke of his characters.
Look at these.
This one.
This one too.
And this.
He also liked drawing a little orange
beside the character "Cheng."
(Cheng Yi)
If you're sure,
then it should be true.
This is...
Gu Nianchi's glasses.
Looks like
he really is dead.
What about Cheng Yi?
Did he say when he'll be back?
He said he was injured
and would return after recovering.
He told us not to worry.
He must be badly hurt.
His handwriting is all crooked.
It barely looks like his anymore.
That child...
Always trying to act tough.
Even when he's injured, he insists on
recovering before coming back.
Don't worry too much.
Since he doesn't want to return yet,
he's probably afraid you'll nag him.
Now that we've confirmed he's safe,
let's just wait for him to come back.
Now that I know Cheng Yi is safe,
I can finally stop worrying.
Next, it's time for me to meet
that Commander-in-Chief Li,
the one I once saved,
yet who now acts
without conscience or mercy.
My brother is leaving for another city.
I need to see him off at the station.
It's a shame I still haven't
dealt with Zhuang Yunqiu.
Otherwise, I'd be able to properly
visit my future brother in law.
Once I return
to my position as Commander,
we'll surely spend our lives together.
When that day comes,
I'll personally bring generous gifts
to thank the Xue family.
I believe in you.
And I'll do
everything I can to help you.
Darling.
Mm?
In the next few days,
I need to make a trip to Hengcheng.
Your injuries haven't even healed yet.
Why are you traveling so far?
I want to regain my position
as Commander as soon as possible.
Only then
can I protect you.
But right now,
I need some help from you.
Could you lend me some money?
Of course.
I'll give it to you when I get back.
I should get going now.
All right.
As instructed by you,
the letter has already been delivered
to the Commander's Residence.
The people sent out
by the Commander's Residence
to search have also been withdrawn.
Lu Shaoyuan...
Your soft heart will always
be your deadliest weakness.
I grew up with Cheng Yi too.
How could I not recognize
his handwriting?
The Xue family is wealthy and powerful.
We'll never have to worry
about money again.
That's right.
What's important isn't her.
It's everything the Xue family owns.
Sooner or later, it'll all belong to me.
With the Commander's charm,
I'm sure Miss Xue
will willingly fall for you.
(Golden Love Song)
Commander-in-Chief.
Long time no see.
Gu Nianchi.
So you still remember
I am your Commander-in-Chief.
I failed in my duty.
I've specially prepared a song for you,
Commander-in-Chief.
I don't think it's a matter
of failing your duty.
You're getting bolder and bolder.
You even dared touch my goods.
You've misunderstood me,
Commander-in-Chief.
Everything I've done
was for your sake.
Oh?
For my sake?
Then I'd like to hear this.
You stole my goods
and cut off my source of income.
How exactly was that for me?
I've already found
the Zhuang family's daughter.
I promised her that as long
as she handed over the opium,
I would destroy it myself.
What?
You found the goods?
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪