=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 24=
Xue Wan,
whatever grievance you have,
take it out on me.
Please, don't make things difficult
for her anymore.
Nianchi.
You've been deceived by her.
You'll regret this.
Xue Wan.
Commander,
I'll go after her.
Shaoyuan.
I can't leave you.
But I truly feel sorry for her.
What should I do?
This isn't your fault.
The man she was supposed
to marry wasn't me either.
Maybe
this was fate's arrangement all along.
How could you be so careless?
I'm telling you,
my heart has been feeling uneasy
these past two days.
You,
you're always overthinking things.
I think
you should just spend more time admiring
your beautiful flower room every day.
You'll feel much better.
Alright.
Report.
A female corpse has been discovered
behind the Commander's Residence.
What?
Alright, I understand.
Darling, I'll go take a look.
Wait.
This is the jade pendant you gave me.
It once blocked a bullet for me.
I've had it repaired.
You should wear it with you.
May it keep you safe and sound too.
My Darling,
I'm only going to the back courtyard.
Don't worry.
Go on then.
Commander,
Xinran's estimated time of death
was around two days ago.
And it appears she suffered abuse
before her death.
Have you found anyone suspicious?
To avoid alerting the enemy,
I've already had people quietly investigate.
But no suspicious individuals
have been found.
Who would dare
commit murder right under my nose?
Shaoyuan.
Didn't you just go out?
Tell them to be extra careful.
Alright.
Yi?
It's me, Yunqiu.
Cheng Yi, why are you here?
Why do you have
so many fresh knife wounds on you?
Yunqiu,
are you that interested in my body?
These knife wounds...
Do they look familiar to you?
Answer me.
(Land Ownership Certificate)
Thank you, Commander.
Why call me Commander all of a sudden?
You...
Since when did you start
putting sugar in your coffee?
Just felt like
trying something different.
Could it really be him?
Yunqiu.
Yunqiu!
Shaoyuan.
Gu Shaoyan.
Looks like nothing can escape your eyes.
Was my disguise really that poor?
Where's Yunqiu?
This way, please.
Gu Shaoyan.
I already told you,
my name isn't Gu Shaoyan.
I'm Cheng Yi now.
Cheng Yi.
Do you understand?
Where's Yunqiu?
Where's the real Cheng Yi?
Want to know?
Beg me.
Maybe if you beg me, I'll tell you.
I'll ask one more time.
Where is Cheng Yi?
Cheng Yi?
Cheng Yi
is dead.
You killed him?
I
strangled him to death.
I watched the Gu Nianchi in his eyes
fade away little by little.
And then I gave you
a brand new Cheng Yi.
So?
Satisfied now?
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪