=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 16=
The name Gu Nianchi
stopped being my name long ago.
Ever since my mother passed away,
I've been called Lu Shaoyuan.
It's really hard for me to imagine
that you and he are brothers
born of the same mother.
How could he possibly replace you?
And how could he bear
to let your mother die?
We were originally born
into a fairly decent family.
But after our father passed away,
our family fell into ruin.
Mother took us
and wandered into a village.
From then on,
Mother's health worsened day by day.
To earn money for Mother's treatment,
I enlisted in the army.
Because of my military achievements,
and because I
accidentally saved Li Shuche,
I was promoted to Commander.
But I never expected that
on my way home,
I'd be ambushed by attackers,
nearly lose my life,
and temporarily lose my sight.
That was when
Gu Shaoyan replaced me.
It's him.
It must be him.
Quick.
Bring him to me.
Yes.
Gu Nianchi.
Gu Nianchi. The Commander-in-Chief
is looking for you.
Please.
Nianchi.
So it really is you.
You are...
I've finally found you.
Nianchi,
because of your
outstanding military achievements,
I've personally come to promote you
to Commander of Yancheng.
Thanks, Commander-in-Chief.
What are you thanking me for?
You saved my life.
I haven't even thanked you properly yet.
Oh, right.
Who else is left in your family?
Bring all of them here.
My whole family is dead.
I'm the only one left.
So that's how it is.
Nianchi,
would you be willing
to become my adopted son?
Father.
Come.
Get up.
All right, let's go.
Shaoyan.
Where's Godmother's medicine?
This...
He's just some street punk.
Let's go, Father.
All right.
Yes.
Shaoyan.
Godmother's medicine. Don't go!
After Gu Shaoyan used your name
to become Commander,
because my father refused to help
Commander-in-Chief Li traffic opium,
he secretly withheld
one of his opium shipments.
So he joined forces
with Zhuang Xun and Lily
to frame my family together.
He executed my whole family.
He shot me once too.
But heaven had other plans.
The jade pendant you gave me
blocked that bullet for me.
I had someone repair it afterward.
So the person who sent me the letter
saying Zhuang Xun
was at Golden Melody Love Songs
really was you.
That's right.
At the time,
I wanted to use Gu Shaoyan's hand
to kill the traitor
of the Zhuang family.
After you left that day,
Cheng Yi found me
and told me my mother had passed away.
So I had no choice but to leave
without saying goodbye.
If he hadn't replaced me back then,
your family wouldn't have suffered.
How can you blame yourself for that?
You're kind by nature.
With you as the Commander
of Yancheng from now on,
you'll definitely protect Yancheng well.
By the way, Darling,
Cheng Yi and I previously discovered
that the clue about the Zhuang family
hiding that shipment of opium
was connected to a flower.
Do you know what flower it was?
Look.
So this was it.
I thought of it before too.
But I just couldn't figure out
what secret was hidden here.
The scar really is still here.
But back at Paramount,
why didn't I notice it?
That day at Paramount,
it was because
of the special angle and lighting.
How is my wife so smart?
Back then,
my father hid that harmful shipment
in an extremely secret place.
Then he hid the location
inside this flower.
The secret lies in
the varying flower petals
and dotted stamens.
This is Morse code.
That's right.
Before my father died,
I got the pattern
of the red spider lily.
But I was worried it might fall
into the wrong hands again.
After thinking it over,
I tattooed it onto my body.
I planned that
once everything settled down,
I'd find that shipment of opium
and destroy it
when the time came.
Shaoyuan.
Yunqiu is awake?
Hello, Yunqiu.
Shaoyuan,
that military seal
has already been hidden
where you instructed.
I guarantee that besides you and me,
no one else will find it.
Good.
Can you tie your tie properly?
You're already serving as an adjutant.
Pay more attention to your image.
Haven't I always been like this?
What?
Now that you have Yunqiu,
you find me annoying?
What nonsense are you talking about?
You'll always be my little brother.
All right.
Where did this sachet come from?
Xinran just gave it to me.
She said it was to congratulate me
on becoming an adjutant.
If you like it,
I'll give it to you.
No.
You really haven't figured
women out at all.
Anything else?
Nothing.
I'm leaving.
Goodbye, Yunqiu.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Something as important
as the military seal,
is it really okay
to leave it to him?
Don't worry.
He's my brother who's gone through
life and death with me.
Other than you,
he's the only family
I have left in this world.
Tonight I'll take Yunqiu out first.
Go make the arrangements now.
Don't worry.
I couldn't tell
you were actually this romantic.
Keep your voice down.
But let's agree on this first.
I'm reserving the position
of your future child's godfather.
I'll teach the kid how to shoot too,
just like you taught me.
You should find my child
a godmother first.
Don't worry.
In the future, I'll learn from you too.
I'll do something romantic for her
so my future wife
will never forget it.
All right.
Once you find someone you like,
I will arrange something
even grander than this for you.
Forget it.
I'd rather save up some money first,
buy a big house,
and then get married.
I'm leaving.
Yi.
What's wrong?
Be careful on the road.
Come back early.
Got it.
I'm not a child anymore.
No matter how old you are,
you'll always be my little brother.
Got it.
Mission guaranteed.
Darling,
I know
you're still worried about Xue Wan.
Once I finish dealing with the opium matter,
we'll go apologize to her properly,
all right?
Mm.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪