=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 17=
Go.
Commander.
Madam is here too.
Xue Wan?
So you're Xue Wan.
Looks like the Commander
already knows everything.
That saves me a lot of trouble.
Xinran.
We have guests here.
Why wasn't I informed?
I...
I'm sorry, Commander.
Gu Nianchi.
Didn't you already know I was Xue Wan?
She...
Zhuang Yunqiu.
She's just my dowry maid.
I'm the true daughter of the Xue family.
I think you've misunderstood, Miss Xue.
The person I want
to marry is Zhuang Yunqiu.
Whether she's a maid or a young lady,
she's the only woman
who'll stay by my side.
Shaoyuan.
What are you saying?
I believe I've made myself very clear.
Miss Xue.
My wife and I still
have matters to discuss.
We won't keep you any longer.
Xinran.
See Miss Xue out.
Xue Wan.
I'll explain everything
to you properly someday.
Zhuang Yunqiu.
You...
You want me to leave?
Well, I'm not leaving.
Miss.
Why don't I take you home first?
Xinran.
Even you're siding
with that Zhuang Yunqiu now?
Of course not, Miss.
You must've been tricked
by Zhuang Yunqiu.
That's why you
let her marry in your place.
She's been throwing her weight around
inside the Commander's Residence.
Even the Commander listens to her.
Just because I know who she really is,
she keeps threatening me,
saying she'll slash my face
and make the Commander
wipe out my whole family.
Zhuang Yunqiu.
I really misjudged you.
Xinran.
Come back with me. We don't need to
stay here and suffer this humiliation.
Thank you for your kindness, Miss.
Young Master has never liked me.
I'd better not go back
and make myself unwelcome.
I'll stay here and help you
keep an eye on Zhuang Yunqiu.
All right?
Okay.
Just wait. I'll make sure
you get your revenge.
Mm.
I'm leaving first.
(I won't become the young madam
even if I go back.)
(But if I stay here, I might still have
a chance with Deputy Commander Cheng.)
(I'm not going back just to be a maid.)
(I want to be just like Zhuang Yunqiu.)
Let me go.
(That voice...)
(It sounds like the Commander.)
(What's going on?)
Stay here and keep watch.
I'm going to relieve myself.
I'm leaving now.
Commander.
What took you so long?
Hurry up.
Gu Nianchi?
Who are you?
What happened to you?
Why are you bleeding so badly?
You're...
I'm Xue Wan.
We just met a moment ago.
Xue Wan...
My injuries are too severe.
I didn't recognize you.
What happened to you?
How did you end up so badly hurt?
Commander.
There's no time to lose.
I'll go bring the car over first.
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
Lieutenant Li?
What happened?
It's nothing.
They're all Zhuang Yunqiu's people.
Zhuang Yunqiu?
Weren't you two just fine a moment ago?
She forced me to do it.
When I refused,
she treated me like this.
Xue Wan.
Help me.
All right.
Gu Nianchi.
(Yancheng Freed from the Scourge of Opium)
This poison should've been destroyed long ago.
It's ruined countless lives.
Commander.
This is...
These were seized
from the dock warehouse.
And we also found them
using the coordinates of the Red Spider Lily
you gave us.
These are the ones mentioned
at the Fragrance Gala.
So you were the one
who confiscated them.
These drugs have destroyed the people.
They've ruined bodies, torn families apart,
and left homes shattered.
Shaoyuan.
You did well.
Today,
I'm going to destroy
all this opium in public.
Wonderful.
Then let's
destroy all these poisonous things
together.
Prepare to burn the opium.
Yes, Commander.
Well done, Commander!
From this day forward,
- no one is allowed to sell opium in Yancheng.
- Well done, Commander!
All right!
Well done, Commander!
- Why haven't I seen
- All right!
the man who's always by your side today?
His name is Cheng Yi, right?
He's handling something else for me.
Destroy every last bit of it.
- Yancheng is only getting better and better.
- Well done!
The people will live happier lives too.
I'll protect Yancheng.
Including you.
Don't leave a single bit behind.
- This poison ruins lives.
- Pour it in.
Then...
may I have the honor
of inviting Miss Zhuang
to come somewhere with me?
All right.
I accept your invitation.
Thank you.
Don't open your eyes.
Okay.
The walk is a bit long.
Watch the steps.
When can I open my eyes?
Why are you being so mysterious?
We're almost there.
Come on.
Don't open your eyes yet.
Don't move.
All right.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪