=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 26=
Yunqiu.
Yunqiu, are you alright?
I'll be fine once you're dead.
Yunqiu.
Did he force you to do something?
I didn't force her.
She brought it up herself.
Look at you now,
pathetic like a stray dog.
Who would still want someone like you?
Isn't that right?
Impossible.
Impossible...
Nothing is impossible.
I saved you before
because I heard you'd
been appointed Commander.
I even gave you my address
so you could come marry me.
But now it seems
there's no chance for you to rise again.
Please stop dragging me down.
Alright?
♪What is there to seek or desire,
trapped in worldly sorrow?♪
The lieutenant's aim is very accurate.
Better be careful when firing.
Yunqiu, don't listen to him.
There's only one bullet in the gun.
You only get one chance.
Gu Shaoyan.
What are you saying to her?
Yunqiu.
Yunqiu, don't believe a word he says.
Don't listen to him, Yunqiu!
♪Even fleeting happiness is enough♪
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
♪What kind of ending
will this fate bring?♪
♪Crossing through
the barriers of dreams♪
♪Burning away all my devotion♪
This is the jade pendant you gave me.
It once blocked a bullet for me.
I should put it on you too.
May it keep you safe as well.
(Shaoyuan,)
(there's no other choice now.)
(This is the only gamble left.)
(I just hope you'll be as lucky
as I once was.)
(If it can stop the bullet,)
(you'll fall into
a state of fake death,)
(and briefly stop breathing.)
(If it works,)
(live on well.)
(We'll meet again in the next life.)
Since childhood,
he was always the one praised,
while I was the one blamed.
Never thought that today,
you'd finally get a taste
of being trampled underfoot.
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
♪What kind of ending
will this fate bring?♪
You really killed him.
♪Crossing through
the barriers of dreams♪
You really killed Lu Shaoyuan.
My dear sister in law
killed her own husband.
You killed him
so you could be with me, didn't you?
For the sake of the dead,
could Xue Wan come collect his body?
She always said I stole her husband.
Now that he's dead,
I'll return him to her.
Xue Wan?
That foolish rich girl?
Fine.
I'd love to see
what kind of reaction she'll have
when she sees this.
Have Xue Wan come collect the body.
Yes.
Zhuang Yunqiu!
Wake up, Zhuang Yunqiu!
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
Madam is awake!
You've been unconscious
for over half a month.
If you're feeling any discomfort,
you must tell me right away.
Go get the Commander.
Yes.
Wait.
During these past two weeks,
have there been any updates
from the Xue family?
The day you collapsed,
many doctors were called to the Xue residence
for emergency treatment.
Was that person saved?
I'm not sure about that.
But I heard
those doctors treated him
for days without success.
Later, the Xue family sent people out
of town to bring back famous physicians.
They're still trying to save him.
That means there's still hope.
You're awake.
I've taken care of you for half a month,
yet you still wanted to kill me.
But I do have good news for you.
You're going to be a mother.
From now on, even if you
don't care about yourself,
you should think about the child.
What did you say?
Don't believe it?
Ask the doctor then.
Yes, Madam.
Your body is weak.
During this period, you must do everything
you can to protect the pregnancy.
Otherwise,
the child could be
in danger at any time.
You may leave.
Yes.
Did you hear what the doctor said?
Whether this child lives safely or not
depends on
your behavior.
Nianchi...
You're awake.
Here.
Where am I?
This is my home.
Why am I here?
You were unconscious for three months.
I saved you.
Where's Zhuang Yunqiu?
You're still asking about her?
She was the one who shot you.
Have you forgotten?
How is she now?
Her?
She's living quite comfortably now.
She's the Commander's wife now.
Commander Cheng's wife.
Don't believe it?
Look for yourself.
It's in the newspaper.
Look.
(Cheng Yi and Zhuang Yunqiu
Wedding Announcement)
Nianchi,
pull yourself together, alright?
Miss Xue,
I'm not Gu Nianchi.
I know.
You two are twins.
But whether you believe it or not,
our fate was tied together long ago.
You don't want to remain
a discarded pawn either, do you?
So pull yourself together.
Take back everything
that belongs to you.
Don't let those who care for you suffer
while your enemies celebrate.
(Cheng Yi and Zhuang Yunqiu
Wedding Announcement)
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪