=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 19=
(Shaoyuan.)
(I can't stay by your side any longer.)
Cheng Yi.
Cheng Yi!
What's wrong?
I dreamed about Cheng Yi.
He was saying goodbye to me.
Do you think something
might've happened to Cheng Yi
while he was chasing Gu Nianchi?
Dreams are usually the opposite.
Don't worry too much.
After my father passed away,
we moved around a lot
before settling in Cheng Yi's village.
At that time, his parents had just died,
so my mother took him in.
He called my mother his godmother,
and I've always treated him
like my own younger brother.
When Gu Nianchi burned down the village,
Cheng Yi survived too
because he had gone out looking for me.
Then that means
he's someone blessed with good fortune.
So don't worry.
How about this?
Tomorrow morning,
I'll go look for him with you.
He'll be fine.
Get some rest.
Let's sleep.
Do you know
where the military seal is now?
Gu Shaoyan.
I'd rather die than tell you.
You've committed countless evil deeds.
Your hands are stained
with so many lives.
You'll go to hell for this.
Shaoyuan will avenge me.
Just you wait.
Little brother.
Your tie is crooked.
You...
Why don't you
take better care of yourself?
I really don't want to kill people.
But every time, you force me into it.
Don't be upset.
Isn't she just a girl?
Come on.
I earned some money today.
I'll take you out for a drink.
Here.
Okay.
Remember this.
No matter what happens,
I will always stand by your side.
(I'll always be your younger brother.)
(And you'll always be my big brother.)
At least I've done something
for Shaoyuan's happiness.
Godmother,
you can rest easy now too.
Shaoyuan doesn't just have me anymore.
He has a wife now too.
Things will only get better from now on.
What are you talking about?
You'll always be my younger brother.
Got it.
Yi.
What is it?
Be careful on the way.
Come back early.
Got it.
I'm not a child anymore.
No matter how old you get,
you'll always be my younger brother.
Commander.
If he won't tell us
where the military seal is,
how are we supposed
to take back the position of Commander?
Do you think he'll still talk
after being tortured like this?
It's fine.
I still have another way.
Take care of him.
Yes, Commander.
Miss Xue.
Could you help me?
Lieutenant Li isn't here,
and it's really
inconvenient for me alone.
Sorry.
Did I hurt you?
All done.
Then I'll be leaving now.
Will you stay with me?
You want me to stay with you?
You refused to marry me before.
And now that I'm like this,
I can't give you anything anymore.
Not fame,
or status.
Do you think those
are the only things I care about?
I've studied abroad for many years.
What I learned there
was to bravely pursue what I truly want.
Back then,
I had someone marry in my place
because I refused to accept
a love and marriage arranged for me.
The moment I met you on the street,
I realized
I'd already fallen for you.
And when I found out
you were the Commander,
I admired you even more
for everything you've done for Yancheng.
I thought we were
going to miss our chance.
My heart was filled with mixed emotions.
I never expected
that even now, we still could...
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪