=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 22=
Didn't expect your taste in shoes
to be this good.
But my taste in people is even better.
I'm back.
Yi.
Cheng Yi, you are back.
What took you so long?
How are your injuries?
They healed a long time ago.
Wasn't this
to give you two some alone time?
You're the thoughtful one.
What happened to your voice?
Just a minor throat injury.
It's nothing serious. It'll heal soon.
By the way,
I brought some wine.
Let's have a drink.
Alright.
Why don't you join us too, Yunqiu?
I'll pass. I'll go prepare something
for you two to eat.
Sit.
Do they look nice, Shaoyuan?
They do.
But I'm not talking about the flowers.
I'm talking about
the person holding them.
You're teasing me again.
I'm serious.
Alright, smooth talker.
Then do you want a taste?
Taste it.
Commander, didn't you say you
needed me for something?
Wasn't I told to come later?
Then I'll leave.
Hey.
If you two have serious business,
hurry up and talk.
(Land Ownership Certificate)
This house and land
were prepared for you.
Now all that's left
is for you to marry
a good wife and settle down.
What, lost for words?
Thank you, Commander.
Why call me Commander all of a sudden?
That's too formal.
Got nervous for a second.
Besides, your status is different now.
Calling you that
also helps build your authority.
My little brother's all grown up now.
Much more sensible too.
Darling, see if there are any good girls,
and introduce one to A'Yi.
Alright. Leave it to me.
I'll make sure to choose carefully for you.
Then I want someone
just as wonderful as you.
That's right.
If you're getting married, it should
be to someone like your sister-in-law.
Enough.
I'm right, aren't I?
Of course.
You are the best.
Alright already, are you two done yet?
You two keep chatting.
I'll go make you something to eat.
Thank you.
Come, sit.
Alright.
You...
Since when
did you start
putting sugar in your coffee?
Just felt like
trying something different.
I heard she studied abroad too.
A double major
in journalism and the arts.
But she's nothing
more than a pretty face.
If you ask me,
she just loves being in the spotlight.
Always trying to stir up some big story.
Going on and on about justice,
morality, and protecting Yancheng.
And dragging
all of us into overtime with her.
Well now she learned her lesson.
How can someone
like her even be a reporter?
She might as well
just go home and get married.
Alright, break it up.
Let's go.
(Darling,)
(I miss you very much.)
(But if I want
to make something of myself soon)
(and marry you properly,)
(I have to leave
and make my way in the world.)
(But lately I've been short on money.)
(I still need your help for now.)
(In the future, I promise
to devote myself to you)
(and treat you even better.)
Gu Nianchi, just you wait.
I'll send the money right away.
Commander,
Xue Wan has already
transferred the money.
Ten thousand silver dollars.
Your side?
Not the slightest suspicion.
He's still treating me very well.
Shaoyuan,
you're really generous
with someone else's money.
Using my money
to support that brat.
I'm your big brother,
yet you've never treated me this well.
Please calm down, Commander.
Lu Shaoyuan is cunning.
We need to plan this carefully.
We absolutely
can't let him discover anything.
The Commander's Residence
is heavily guarded by soldiers.
I have to get the military seal back
and reclaim control of the troops.
Spread your fingers a little more.
Raise the web between
your thumb and index finger.
I already learned this before.
Back then, I specially learned it
just to get close to you.
You learned before?
Mm.
You're that good?
Couldn't tell at all.
Come.
One.
Two.
Three.
That's not my fault.
How is it not your fault?
It's because you distracted me.
When did I distract you?
You're obviously
just too good at this yourself.
I remember when we first met.
- You were lying there.
- Don't say it.
And your leg was like this...
No,
that never happened.
You forgot already?
Then let me help refresh your memory.
That day wasn't like this at all.
- Then what was it like that day?
- That day...
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪