=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 21=
The Zhuang family's daughter
has already been found.
She was promised that as long as
the shipment of opium was handed over,
it would be destroyed.
But it was only for show.
The location of the opium
has already been revealed.
What?
The opium was found?
Commander-in-Chief,
please dismiss everyone else.
All of you wait downstairs
in the main hall.
Now we can talk.
Come in.
Why do you look so familiar to me?
Li Shuche.
I look familiar to you?
I'm the Zhuang family's daughter
you've been searching for all along.
This...
This can't be.
I remember now.
You're Xue Wan.
How could you be Zhuang Yunqiu?
Nianchi,
what exactly is going on?
Let me introduce myself again.
My name is Lu Shaoyuan.
And this is
Zhuang Yunqiu.
What did you say?
Gu Nianchi,
what kind of game are you playing?
Don't forget,
I'm the one who promoted you.
How could I not know who you are?
What did you just say?
Lu Shaoyuan?
Your benefactor.
Wasn't I promoted
to Commander of Yancheng
because of the military merit
I earned back then?
If anything, I was the one
who saved your life.
Commander-in-Chief.
That's true.
If you hadn't earned
great military merit back then,
you wouldn't be where you are today.
But that also became my greatest regret.
If not for that,
my brother would've
never taken my place,
and sided with you,
then none of this would've happened.
Your brother?
Are you twins?
No...
What are you trying to do?
To seek justice.
Commander-in-Chief,
shouldn't you
answer for the mistakes
you've made
and the lives you've taken?
No.
You've got it all wrong.
None of that was done by me.
You're the mighty Commander-in-Chief.
Was someone forcing you to do it?
Exactly.
As the Commander-in-Chief,
why would I do something like that?
Yes,
Gu Nianchi was ordered
to help gather wealth,
but how it was done,
I knew nothing about it.
Do you think saying that
lets you escape responsibility?
It was your indulgence and inaction
that ruined countless innocent lives.
Do you even know
that the wealth and luxury you enjoy
came at the cost of countless lives?
No.
I was wrong.
How about this?
I'll give up my position
as Commander-in-Chief.
I'll donate every bit
of wealth I've accumulated to the people.
Oh,
and the Zhuang family as well.
And everyone harmed by Gu Nianchi,
I'll clear their names one by one.
As long as you
spare my life,
I'll do anything.
Darling,
you decide.
Miss Zhuang,
please spare me.
A man like him
dying won't change anything.
Better to do as he said.
Have all his wealth donated
to help the people,
clear the names of everyone
who was wronged,
and make every guilty person
face justice.
(Lao Fengxiang Jewelry Store)
Extra!
The Zhuang family's smuggling case
has been overturned.
Li Shuche has been removed from office
and will stand trial immediately.
Give me a copy.
I want one too.
One for me too.
(The Zhuang family's smuggling case
has been overturned.)
(Li Shuche has been removed from office
and will stand trial immediately.)
Commander,
are you alright?
Lu Shaoyuan.
(Li Shuche has been removed from office
and will stand trial immediately.)
You got rid of Li Shuche
and turned me into a discarded pawn.
But don't get too comfortable.
We'll be seeing
each other again very soon.
Is the surgery ready?
Everything is prepared.
(Shaoyuan,)
(you'll soon get to see
your brother, Cheng Yi again.)
What a pity.
(Commander Gu Nianchi achieves
great success in the opium ban.)
What are you laughing about?
I was just thinking,
back when I read the newspapers,
they were always full
of criticism toward the Commander.
But now everything has changed.
All they're writing
are praises about you.
It's just a shame
they still think the Commander
is that Gu Shaoyan.
It's alright.
Even if no one else knows,
as long as you do, that's enough.
You've really worked hard these days.
You've been searching for
both Cheng Yi and Gu Shaoyan,
while still handling official duties.
Now that you've
received Cheng Yi's letter,
you must feel much more relieved.
You've been through a lot
staying by my side lately.
A gift was prepared for you.
When did you buy it?
That's a secret.
Try it on.
Do you like it?
I do.
Then is there a reward for me?
(I'm back.)
Didn't expect your taste in shoes
to be this good.
But my taste in people is even better.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪