=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 25=
What?
Don't want to know
where Zhuang Yunqiu is?
The biggest weakness here
is a soft heart.
If there was really intent to kill,
it would've happened long ago.
It would've never come to the point
where the closest brother
ended up dead.
It was that mercy
that killed him.
Why?
Why hurt
everyone close to me?
Why?
That's exactly what I want to ask.
Why did we grow up together,
yet Cheng Yi was always by your side?
Why was I the older brother
and you the younger?
You went off to war and earned glory.
Why did we clearly look alike,
yet Mother always favored you?
Here.
Eat.
Thanks, Mom.
It's really sweet.
Mom, have some too.
Cheng Yi, you're here.
Shaoyuan, this is for you.
I want one too.
Can I give it to my brother?
No, there's only one.
I only wanted to give it to you.
Where did this come from?
You brat, stealing my things now?
Where else could it come from?
Stole it from me.
Who told you to steal?
I'm sorry. He's just a child
and doesn't understand.
Why steal someone else's things?
Because I really
wanted to give this to Mom.
Stealing at such a young age?
What will become of Gu Shaoyan later on?
Mom doesn't need any gift.
Mom only wants you to be obedient
like your brother.
As long as you stop causing trouble.
I did nothing wrong.
Only stole a little money.
There used to be plenty of money at home.
Now there's none.
What's wrong with taking some from them?
You...
Let's see if I beat you today.
- Still talking back after stealing?
- I did nothing wrong!
I'll beat you to death!
Admit the mistake or not?
I did nothing wrong.
- Still daring to argue? Today I will...
- Mom, you're unfair!
You only love him, not me!
You...
- I did nothing wrong!
- Let's see if I beat you!
I did nothing wrong!
This is all my fault.
If there's anger, take it out on me.
Don't drag innocent people into this.
Innocent?
As if you're the only one with feelings.
Feelings exist here too.
That's why a gift was prepared.
Yunqiu.
Put the gun down.
If you don't want her dead,
hand over the military seal.
Let her go.
Then I'll say where the seal is.
Tell me.
The military seal
is beneath the pocket at the twelve
o'clock direction on the billiard table.
If Lieutenant Li can't find it,
she'll be in danger.
Commander,
it's been found.
Excellent.
Now Commander Cheng Yi is back again.
Although it doesn't sound
as nice as Gu Nianchi,
Commander Cheng sounds pretty good too.
The thing you wanted is yours now.
Release her.
Shaoyuan,
such a beauty...
Don't touch her!
How could I bear to let go?
Don't worry.
She'll be cherished properly.
Gu Shaoyan!
You're shameless!
How many times does it need to be said?
My name isn't Gu Shaoyan.
My name is Cheng Yi!
You don't deserve that name!
What?
Let him go! You're insane!
Feeling sorry for him?
Compared to the pain of being
stabbed again and again by you,
what does this knife count for?
Gu Shaoyan.
If you want to kill or torture someone,
come at me!
Don't touch her.
Then that wish will be granted first.
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
Why treat Cheng Yi so well?
Stop!
Stop it!
Why?
Stop!
Why did Mother always favor you?
Lu Shaoyuan.
Lu Shaoyuan...
What will it take to let him go?
Does it hurt?
Does it feel painful?
Fine.
Then I'll start by tormenting your body,
then the heart.
Let him taste it too,
the feeling of having
the most beloved thing stolen away.
(I need to find a way out.)
(If this keeps going,)
(even if Gu Shaoyan
doesn't beat him to death,)
(he'll be tortured to death by him.)
I have something to say.
♪Carved through endless hardship♪
What is it?
I know you hate him.
But he's still your brother.
There's no point
in torturing him like this.
How about this?
Kill me instead.
I'm the person he cares
about most in this world.
After I die, make him live
the rest of his life alone.
Let him suffer for the rest of his life.
Wouldn't that be better?
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
Darling, that does
remind me of something.
You kill him.
That way, not only will he die,
it'll hurt him even more.
Then why not just kill both of us?
Why go through all this trouble?
Of course it's different.
One of you kills the other,
and the other dies by the hand
of the person they love most.
Wouldn't that make the pain even worse?
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
I don't want to die.
If I kill him,
will you let me go?
Don't try anything funny.
If you can't kill him,
then I'll slowly torture him.
I'll gouge out his eyes.
I'll make him wish he were dead.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪