=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 18=
All right.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
We're already husband and wife.
Why go through all this?
It may seem a little old fashioned,
but...
Back then, it was Gu Shaoyan
marrying Xue Wan.
But now,
it's me, Lu Shaoyuan,
who wants to marry Zhuang Yunqiu.
So...
Miss Zhuang Yunqiu,
would you be willing
to marry Mr. Lu Shaoyuan?
♪A happy game that began within a dream♪
I do.
♪Can you still see it within the night?♪
♪The life I long for
is tangled within it♪
♪Forcing me to trade pain for the past♪
Beautiful.
♪In this world♪
♪Love is a beautiful exchange♪
♪In that moment, our hearts became one♪
♪Breaking through
what reality could never allow♪
♪Casting aside everything meaningless♪
Something terrible has happened.
The soldiers guarding the prisoners are dead.
The prisoners were taken too.
- What?
- Have they been found?
- Not yet.
Keep searching.
How is it?
Any news?
We've searched the entire city.
There's still no sign of them.
There's something else
that's been bothering me.
Cheng Yi hasn't returned in a long time.
Could something have happened to him?
Cheng Yi...
Last night, I sent him
to prepare the church.
By now, he should've returned already.
But it's also possible
that he discovered Gu Shaoyan escaping
and went after him before we did.
Let's wait a little longer.
All right.
Commander. There are large numbers
of soldiers searching outside.
My dear brother
would never imagine
that I'm hiding
in my real wife's family home.
Everything was arranged by fate.
Heaven truly hasn't abandoned me.
And now we still have him.
Commander. What should we do with him?
Keep a close eye on him for now.
Yes, Commander.
Move.
Commander.
I made this medicinal soup for you.
It'll help your recovery.
Thank you, Miss Xue.
And thank you for taking me in.
May I ask...
Who was the man in the sack just now?
And what exactly is going on here?
This whole thing
was all because
I failed to see the truth.
I mistook Zhuang Yunqiu for you
and believed all her sweet lies.
I truly never expected
her to be so manipulative,
so skilled at winning people over.
By the time
I realized it,
she had already slowly taken
all my power into her own hands.
Zhuang Yunqiu
is really that calculating?
But you trusted her so much before.
When I went to tell you
who I really was,
you believed her completely.
She forced me to do all of it.
She said I wasn't convincing enough,
that I wasn't close enough to her
or distant enough from you.
That's why
she locked me up.
What did you say?
Now that I think about it,
it's truly hard to speak of.
I'm the Commander of an entire city,
yet I was manipulated by a woman.
But you're the Commander of Yancheng.
How could Zhuang Yunqiu,
a woman on her own,
possibly do anything to you?
That's because
you don't know her methods.
You saw the man
tied up today too.
He used to be my adjutant,
yet he betrayed me
and became her lackey.
How could Zhuang Yunqiu
become like this?
Miss Xue has been overseas all this time,
so there are things you don't know.
Back then,
under Commander-in-Chief's orders,
I executed the Zhuang family
for trafficking opium.
Zhuang Yunqiu
has held a grudge ever since.
She carefully planned her marriage to me
for the sake of revenge.
But I've heard about that matter too.
She told me you framed her family.
What she's best at
is twisting right and wrong.
When she stayed at your house,
she often insulted the Xue family too,
saying Xue Tian treated her poorly
and that the Xue family
ignored her completely.
How unreasonable.
I even let her stay in my home
out of respect for old ties,
yet she spoke of my brother like that.
Before she got married,
I even embroidered
a Red Spider Lily on her.
I never expected her
to deceive me like this.
We're both victims.
I understand that feeling.
I doubted her before too,
but she was too cunning.
I also doubted the things she said.
One moment she'd say
you were a good person,
and the next
she'd call you hypocritical.
I truly couldn't tell which of her words
were true and which were false.
This is all my fault.
And now,
she's even found a puppet to replace me.
The fact that I'm still alive
is already a blessing.
This isn't your fault.
If anyone's to blame,
it's me for believing her
and letting her marry you in my place.
But don't worry.
Stay at my house and recover in peace.
I'll help you take back
your position as Commander.
Then thank you, Miss Xue.
Gu Shaoyan.
My name is Gu Nianchi.
My sworn younger brother.
Who is your younger brother?
The lives in that poor village
can't be saved anymore,
but you can still save your own life.
Tell me.
Where did Lu Shaoyuan
hide the military seal?
And I'll let you go.
Keep dreaming.
I'm not telling you.
I'll never betray Shaoyuan.
So you really do know.
If you don't want to suffer,
then you'd better talk.
I do know.
But I'll never tell you.
What a nuisance.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪