Once the transfer order was official,
the preparations went smoothly.
Seeing everything in boxes
makes it feel real all of a sudden.
I haven't spoken to Fukami since then.
I just don't have the confidence.
Being long-distance and unable to meet...
Once that connection is gone,
there's no way it'll work out.
Someone like me, who wasn't
even loved by his parents...
"There's no such thing as a parent
who doesn't love their child."
Looking at you and your sister,
it's obvious you were raised
with love in a good home.
It's like a constant reminder
that I'm not like you guys.
I'm the one who hurt you.
No.
I don't want this.
I don't want to be apart from you.
Don't abandon me.
I've had enough of this.
I'm tired of being jerked around by you.
Let's just...
end it.
Someone who says they aren't confident
they can make you happy...
would never be chosen anyway.
There's nothing left for me to do.
Is the pollen already acting up?
Ah.
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
(Episode 9)
Bro, are you going to invite
Kaji-san to the wedding?
Why would I?
Because he's one of your few friends.
By the time the wedding rolls around,
he won't be here anymore.
Huh?
He's transferring.
I heard he's going to Hokkaido.
So, what are you going to do about it?
What do you mean?
He's just a colleague.
There's nothing to do.
You're lying.
You've never introduced
a friend to me before.
He's someone important to you, isn't he?
He doesn't seem to smile much around me.
He's always got a scowl on his face.
Maybe things have been hard for him.
So, it's better this way.
Well, of course it is. That's what love is.
Falling for someone
isn't always about being happy.
There's pain, sadness,
and plenty of embarrassing moments.
That's just part of being in love.
Not everyone can do "fast-food" romance,
switching partners like they're
turning a page! Some people can't!
Don't lecture me based on your standards.
We all die in the end anyway.
At Mom's funeral,
didn't you say you can't take
anything with you when you die?
You shouldn't choose to be alone.
I know it's easier that way,
and you don't get hurt as much.
It's not like I'm choosing
to be alone on purpose.
It's just...
if he can't be happy with me...
Bro.
Thank you for everything.
I'll still be back every now and then.
I look forward to seeing you all then.
Kaji-san,
thank you for all your hard work here.
- Thank you.
- Don't catch a cold in Hokkaido!
- I won't.
- When you come back,
don't forget to bring some crab!
Crab, right. You got it.
Good luck out there!
I'll do my best.
We'll work hard enough
for you too, Kaji-san.
- I'm counting on you.
- Please don't forget about us!
I won't.
Hey, don't cry.
Oh, good.
I made it in time.
- Manager Tokura.
- This is a farewell gift from Engineering.
Oh?
Are you sure?
Of course. You've really looked out for us.
No, it was nothing.
Thank you so much.
Can I open it now?
Go right ahead.
It's a scarf.
Since I'm going somewhere cold,
this will really come in handy.
Fukami has better taste than I thought.
Huh?
I heard you and Fukami were close,
so I figured he'd know your style.
I left the choice up to him.
You know how Fukami usually dresses...
I was a little worried after I asked him.
But he actually has great taste.
Good work today.
You too.
I heard you picked out the scarf for me.
It was nothing. I just bought
what the clerk recommended.
Hey.
Wait for me behind the station after work.
I have overtime.
I'll wait until you show up.
Are you looking for one last hookup?
Idiot.
What are you saying in a place like this?
If that's what it is, I'll go.
But...
if it's not,
then I'm not going.
Huh?
What?
If you come, I'm fine with doing it.
But if I go, does that mean
this is the last time?
Because if you don't show up,
we might never get to talk again.
I only barely brushed his shoulder...
Hey.
I'm about to lose it.
Fukami.
You're the type who
really would wait forever.
It's scary.
Two grown men running
through a crowd hand-in-hand...
People are going to stare.
I can feel people turning to look.
We might even run into someone we know.
But I don't care about any of that anymore.
Sorry.
Wait.
I'm not ready yet.
I want to clean myself out properly.
Since it's the last time.
Is this really the last time?
Checking in on how the other person
feeling,
showing respect...
Fukami taught me all of that.
Ah.
So beautiful.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Forget about that.
If we're doing this, let's go.
Fukami.
Can we be friends forever?
Sorry.
I'm being so inconsistent.
But you know,
my life has always been full of lies.
Being with someone as genuine as you
makes me feel like I can finally breathe.
So,
staying in touch with
you is important to me.
We can meet up and
sleep together sometimes.
I don't care if you see other people.
If it makes things too complicated,
we don't even have to have sex.
So, please, just stay in my life...
Let's not be friends.
Sorry.
I'm being annoying, aren't I?
Our final night
is about to begin.
(Next Episode Preview)
Is this what love is?
Is it always this messy and confusing?
So, did you find your answer?