I want to talk to her in private.
Nun!
He's not my brother.
He's just the troublemaker of our family.
Khanin is one of Fire Phoenix's members,
just like Naruban.
The one who has to die…
…is Taiga.
Death is so close to us.
So close that sometimes,
we forget to watch out
which direction
we're getting stabbed from.
Mr. Taiga.
Do you like it?
It's quite good.
I thought you'd say you like it.
You have no business here.
Mom,
this is Ratee. She's a friend of mine.
She owns the café on the first floor.
Good afternoon.
I'd like to treat you all to a coffee.
I'll have a server come
and take your orders.
Thank you.
Oh.
Then, may I order for Ms. Nun first?
One salted caramel affogato, please.
Rin,
go make me a coffee.
I said go.
Prepare the data
of our clients on every platform.
I'm going downstairs
to talk to the IT team.
Why are you here?
I'm here to support you, Taiga.
Ratee, please.
I know.
Don't worry. Just go back to work.
Ms. Nun, it's your turn.
Was it good?
Why'd you come out here, sir?
I'm going to talk to the IT team. Why?
You should go back to your office,
or go home.
Why?
Uncle Punlop,
what are you doing here?
Mr. Naruban is being targeted.
I had your driver come pick you up.
Please go home.
Please go now. I told your driver
to wait at the entrance.
PLEASE DO NOT LEAN ON ELEVATOR BUTTONS
Ugh.
Where's Rin?
Why's she taking so long? I need a coffee.
Ms. Nun,
would you like to try our coffee?
- Ms. Nun!
- Are you alright?
Ms. Nun, are you alright?
Are you alright?
- Are you hurt?
- You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Did you? Huh?
I didn't mean it.
What happened, honey?
She tripped me on purpose, Mom.
I didn't mean it!
Please excuse us.
Are you hurt?
- My dress got a little stained.
- Was it hot?
Rin!
Are you okay?
Don't get up yet. You're hurt, right?
Damn it!
So close. That Naruban,
that Fire Phoenix guy would've been dead!
Taiga!
Taiga! Taiga!
I just wanted to see you while you work.
Nunnapat isn't a good model
for your clothes anyway.
But this is my work!
Why are you so childish, Ratee?
Fine,
I admit it. I hate her guts.
That's why I had Techut take me there.
Well, if Nannapat
didn't get so close to you…
I'm sorry.
You have to know
I hate those people at 3C.
This has got to end someday.
You have to think about our future too.
You don't care
about my love for you at all, do you?
Do you love for your own happiness
or for your partner's happiness?
- Stay out of this.
- I can't.
Taiga's doing everything
to find someone to pay
for his dad's death.
You love him, yet you never understood
or stayed patient
for the sake of his wish.
Only moody, self-centered, worthless girls
would use love as an excuse
to get what they want.
Ratee.
You have no right to criticize me.
Taiga's a good guy, but I'm not.
I just say it as I see it.
Plus, I don't need to be polite
with selfish girls like you.
Stop using true love
as an excuse
to control someone else's life, okay?
Don't worry about her.
You've got bigger things
to worry about than her.
Today, while you were at work,
I hacked the cameras at 3C.
Khanin.
And who's this?
No idea.
I tried other angles,
but I couldn't find his face.
It's as if he knew
how to avoid all the cameras,
and all the footage during that time
got wiped clean.
Someone must've ordered it
to be deleted for sure.
Someone who could do that…
Naruban.
Here, let me help you.
How'd the uniform shoot go?
It's still not quite done.
How long will that designer
keep working for us?
You don't seem to like Mr. Taiga.
Tell your daughter to end it.
Pay him and get rid of him.
But the project isn't done yet.
Or should I fire him myself?
What's the cause, then?
If you fire him without cause,
it can damage our company.
Well, a good cause
is that I hate his work.
Pay him and fire him.
I don't want him to show up at 3C again,
no matter what the reason.
If no one gives orders,
I'll handle it myself.
Sit.
It's nice to sit outside sometimes.
TAIGA - INCOMING CALL
Mr. Taiga?
Mr. Taiga again!
He must be worried about you.
There's no need to be.
Please leave a message after the tone…
I need your help.
I want to know Rin's friend,
the one she's closest to.
BANGPAKOK 3 HOSPITAL
BREATHING AS ONE
Are you okay?
Here.
Relax.
By the time those two finish talking,
we'll have finished both cups.
Rin's going to kill me.
If I didn't see
that Mr. Taiga kept calling,
I would've kept quiet.
Ah.
Here,
go ahead.
Ow!
How'd you end up here?
I fell down the stairs
and sprained my ankle.
How'd you get here?
Must've been Aru.
Are you badly hurt?
I'm okay.
Huh.
Nno broken limbs.
Now I believe that you're okay.
You still hit just as hard as ever.
Are you cold?
Nun, trust me.
Your dad has reason
for not wanting Taiga to work at 3C.
Is hatred
a reason that makes sense?
No one can be good at everything
or win every time.
Sometimes,
silence is the best solution.
Don't do anything.
I'll take care of Taiga's situation.
Here.
You can be on your way now.
Mr. Taiga, why don't you come upstairs
and have something to drink?
Let's go.
My place isn't so big, but it's still
a "home sweet home".
Whoa, your light.
You use that for your livestreams?
If you use two more of those,
you'll glow up so hard,
- and your sales will go way up.
- Whoa!
Do you have one? Can you give me one?
Thank you for the ride.
I'll stop bothering you now.
I'm free today.
I'm also super free.
Then, can you go buy me a light?
Ow!
Mr. Taiga,
would you like to try designing
a new collection that's more street style?
We don't need to use your brand.
We can sell it under my brand.
We could try and sell it
on my livestreams.
Want to give it a try?
That's some good marketing.
No wonder you invited us in.
I'm a fan of his brand too, you know?
Sure.
But
I can't really afford it,
so I can only shop with my eyes.
- Should I try creating a few designs?
- You don't need to.
Yes, please! That'd be perfect.
We could make it a limited edition.
Maybe sell only ten.
Surely, everyone will want it,
and the price will skyrocket!
Let me see.
- What?!
- Your brain is amazing.
Amazing. What a great seller.
Well, it's hard to make money.
I see an opportunity right in front of me,
so, of course, I have to seize it.
Actually, it's an interesting idea.
I'll design for you.
Whoa!
For free, right?
Honestly, I can't afford to hire
someone on your level like 3C can.
- It's free.
- Don't!
And feel free to sell it under your brand.
Can I hold your hand, please?
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Leave him alone, Aru.
It's fine. It'll be fun.
See?
Well, aren't you sweet?
- Let me thank you again.
- Hey, thank me instead.
You've thanked him enough.
- Please?
- What?
Do you even know how to design?
No, not at all.
Model for me, then.
- How about this dress!
- Model?
Yas, sis!
You need a new model?
Yeah?
Please don't forget our promise.
I won't. I'll send you a design tonight.
He's making me fall again.
Hey, don't fall for me.
I don't want to carry your stuff.
Not you!
Leave already. Go!
- I'm such a big fan!
- I'm going now. Bye.
Bye-bye.
What do you think we'll gain
from those two?
I want to know more about Rin.
But if she finds the bug, we're screwed.
She's smart. She'll surely
be able to tell it's us.
I'll take my chances.
Rin's the closest person to Naruban.
We might find a link
between Khanin and Fire Phoenix.
Khanin wants revenge
on the Fire Phoenix guys,
yet he never told you
he's also one of them.
He claimed he knew your mom
and told you he got framed, forced off
the police force, and also hunted.
Now I don't even know
what to believe from Khanin anymore.
Oh well,
at least you two share the same goals.
Get close to Naruban
and destroy Fire Phoenix.
The only problem is…
Rin.
They released a new music video!
It's from Ryu Dragon!
Here we go!
Here we go.
Look, look!
Isn't he cute?
Is he as cute in person?
Right? I knew it.
Look!
They filmed it on a beach.
We use 3C-Coin to make huge profits,
then we spend those huge profits
so we can have the world
in the palm of our hands.
I hope you don't think
Nun's stupid "new uniform" project
can ever help us grow bigger.
I never agreed with it. You know that.
Then you should fire Taiga.
Trust me. I'll use my power
to build our empire.
I hope you don't think I'm intruding.
I see you really gave your all for 3C.
But it seems like 3C
doesn't welcome me anymore.
I apologize on everyone's behalf.
I hope all the chaos here
didn't make you want to leave us.
I'll make sure my work's finished.
Don't worry.
Now we just need the uniform
to be finished,
and as for the small tasks,
like promoting the videos,
you don't need to do that.
Let's leave it to an ad agency.
So you're here to fire me.
To be honest,
I don't want any more trouble
like yesterday.
The woman who came with my son, Techut,
is she your friend?
Ratee won't be here again.
Please let me finish my work.
You want to handle the filming, don't you?
Yes.
Ms. Nun doesn't have
to model in it either.
We can have someone else do it.
I want Rin to model for me.
I don't know about that.
She's just an employee.
The clothes I design
must be worn by someone
who can present them best.
Mr. Taiga wants Rin to model
for 3C's uniform?
That way, we can get it over with.
You're not the loser here.
Your tears from today
will become a fire
that'll burn your enemies to the ground
until even their souls are gone.
Are you sure you're fine?
Yes, I'm okay.
And you?
I'm fine.
I’ve had more guards brought in.
Can I see all the cameras' footage?
I need to find that guy.
I ordered all of it to be deleted.
If it got out,
it'll be bad for 3C's reputation.
Taiga will be out of here soon.
Until then, watch his every move.
Don't let Taiga damage 3C again.
Yes, sir.
Taiga will be out of here soon.
Watch his every move.
Don't let Taiga damage 3C again.
I just told Mrs. Giranun
that I want you to model for my clothes.
- Well, I--
- Don't want to?
Please don't refuse, Rin.
I'll show everyone
that no one should look down on others.
Taiga's trying to turn
the spotlight on me.
Try to earn his trust for now, Rin.
Pretend you're a decoy.
Squeeze everything you can out of Taiga
before you deal with him.
You had Rin monitor Taiga?
Aren't you afraid
they'll team up and betray us?
Do you know
what traitors are afraid of the most?
Traitors
are afraid of other traitors.
I need to get away from 3C.
Naruban found out about you?
They're suspecting me,
so they're using my work as an excuse.
- We need to hurry and finish the job.
- No.
I'll handle it.
Naruban's life is mine to take.
You?
You had so many chances, but never did it.
What are you waiting for?
I want to destroy them completely.
Fire Phoenix will have nothing left
but its name.
Here.
It's Mr. Taiga's design!
Hold it for a sec.
Can… Can I scream?
He really gave me all these?
And he won't charge me?
All of those are free.
Wow!
I'm so freaking happy!
All my superstitions paid off.
They're so, so pretty!
You'll be selling like crazy, Aru.
Can you tell Mr. Taiga
that I want to pay for his designs?
I don't accept freebies.
How will you pay him?
How about
a huge set of barbecue or hot pot?
I can be free any day. Let me know.
- Totally worth it.
- Yeah.
Sure, sure. Gotta go.
- Tell him for me.
- Okay.
That scumbag of a husband. So ungrateful.
So untameable!
I treat your mom and sister so well,
yet you betrayed me
and went to see your ex!
Why'd you go see her?
She's poorer than me.
Why?!
What's wrong?
You've been frowning for an hour now.
I don't want to model.
Really, Rin?
If I were you, I'd set off firecrackers
at ten temples to celebrate.
I'd offer a dance,
a pig's head, Thai clothing,
zebras, or anything to the gods.
I'd even run naked.
Rin,
you think Taiga's
asking you to do it just for fun
or just because he's bored?
You know it's a big deal, right?
You'll be the face of 3C, for God's sake!
You'll get to wear a pretty outfit
Mr. Taiga designed too.
Do you know how lucky you are?
Do you want to do it instead?
What?
Can I really do that?
As if Mr. Taiga would be okay with that.
Hey,
this is your chance.
Don't let it get away.
Think of it as a nice life experience.
How about you ask them
if I can be there at the shoot,
so you'll be more relaxed?
Perfect.
Then, you need to practice your walk.
- Get up, get up!
- Ugh!
As a top supermodel
and the queen of the runway,
I'll train you myself.
Hey! Get up, will you?
I'm going to sleep.
- You're sleeping?
- I'm so sleepy.
You need to practice your walk,
so you'll really shine.
- Don't sleep yet!
- Let me sleep!
No! Come on.
Don't fake sleep now. Get up!
- No.
- Come on!
Done!
You're done? Let me see.
You're so pretty!
You have to smile, okay?
Smile a lot,
like you're lighting up the world,
like you're proud of working at 3C.
Smile. Come on.
Go on. Do your hair.
Smile.
Don't you want to go down there?
Then, I'll go and keep you updated
in real-time.
So pretty!
Looking fabulous as the face of 3C!
Everyone at 3C is pretty.
Give me a confident smile,
like you know you're the prettiest.
Okay? Walk to the center there,
then look straight into the camera.
Okay? Ready?
Let's go. Please, take her.
You got this! Come on.
Beautiful! Just like that, Rin.
You look so pretty!
Yeah, just like that.
Aru.
Sun?
How'd you get here?
They're shooting her?
Beautiful.
Keep walking.
Okay. Side angle, please.
I got it. Okay.
Now give us your right side.
Beautiful!
Just like that. Be confident.
Can we do one more?
Give me more confidence.
Now pose.
Beautiful.
Hold on.
Turn around.
You look pretty.
What?
Taiga.
Taiga!
Huh?
We need to leave.
Are you okay?
Get out of the way.
I told you, get out of the way!
- Move!
- Pat!
You love her so much, don't you?
You love each other so much, huh? Die!
- No!
- Hey!
Pat!
Sun.
It hurts.
Aru, gorgeous!
I can do a lot worse than that.
The bullets were directed at me only.
Who do you think did it?
I don't know. Do you?
My dad died because of Fire Phoenix.
Then why aren’t you searching
for the truth?
The mask contains
the code to all the information
of every member.
If we can steal Naruban's mask,
then we can get
to the core of Fire Phoenix.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya