I want you to be my model.
The tears today, they'll turn into a fire
that will burn the enemy
until not even a soul remains.
Buy his trust first, Rin.
Act like bait,
draw everything out of him,
then deal with him.
You love each other, right? You're dead!
- Oh!
- Whoa!
Hey!
Pat!
Sun.
Pat, are you okay?
It hurts.
Stop! One more move and you're dead!
Didn't I teach you, Khanin?
Shoot first, talk later.
Why are you trying to kill Taiga again?
Fire Phoenix already ruined his life,
destroyed his family once.
I know you're a good subordinate.
But I didn't expect
you'd be loyal to every boss.
Even a dog's ashamed.
And you? Why do you help Taiga?
Have you ever asked yourself?
Are you helping because you really care
or just taking one man's revenge
and twisting it
for your own gain?
You want revenge for your family, right?
If you fail, you'll never face
your parents in the grave.
Stop talking about my family like that!
Your stupid grief
is dragging Taiga straight to hell,
with your dad, mom, and sister!
Punlop!
Ugh!
Geez!
Damn it!
The media won't cover us.
They'll focus on jealousy instead.
And the others?
Police are clearing the area.
But I think you should leave
the building first.
The security team is ready outside.
The other four units
are checking every corner for the shooter.
Let's go home. It's not safe here.
Where the hell did the files go?
The footage from the building cameras
during the incident is gone.
What about the street cameras?
None.
Someone ordered them deleted.
Who has that kind of power?
The bullets were aimed at me alone.
Who do you think did it?
I don't know.
Or you do?
Did they catch the guy who shot Taiga?
Not yet.
Police are gathering all the evidence.
Mr. Naruban hasn't left the house.
A security team is on duty all the time.
What about Taiga?
At the hospital, checking on the injured.
Don't let him slip out of sight.
And Mr. Naruban?
It's fine. He's in a safe place
and already guarded.
Rin, go focus on Taiga.
The shooting news made 3C's stock drop.
Should we do something?
Since when do you care about the company?
I care about my husband.
Don't worry. PR will make sure
we're not tied to the shooting.
Who's that woman a victim for?
Who were they really trying to shoot?
I already sent flowers
and compensation money to the injured.
Sun.
How are you feeling?
These are flowers from 3C Corp.
Does it hurt much?
It hurts.
I'll tell the police
not to ask you anything yet.
Pat.
I'm sorry.
You're not the one who shot me.
Why apologize?
Because I've wronged you.
I've made you hurt in every way.
What if I don't forgive you?
I have to accept it because I was wrong.
I just want you to know,
Aru and I, we are nothing more
than old friends,
absolutely nothing else.
Hello, everyone!
Today,
if it's not on sale,
I'll just slash the price myself!
We're breaking the price on swimsuits!
Here it is. Summer's here.
Who's ready to hit the beach
looking hot and gorgeous?
Only 99 baht! Wow, crazy cheap!
Add to cart and grab yours, everyone!
While you're shopping,
I'll be reading your comments too!
"Really shipping, exactly like the pics!"
Someone already confirmed.
Grab yours, everyone!
"Ex-con seller."
I'm not ex…
I'm not exaggerating.
I'm not lying to you.
Seriously, our stuff is top quality,
every single piece!
Okay, let's keep reading.
SHE KILLED SOMEONE
WHY ONLY A SHORT TIME IN JAIL?
Whoa.
My throat's super dry.
I'm gonna take a quick break
and grab a drink.
We'll be back soon!
Alright, let's shut it down for now.
All the comments are insults.
It's like the IPs
were made just to attack you.
"Ex-con seller. Go to hell."
Then, let someone else
take over the livestream for now.
Got it.
Take it slow.
Even if you two have nothing going on,
I won't forgive you.
I'll drag her to hell
because you love her.
Pat!
What are you going to do to Aru?
Thank you.
Aru, gorgeous!
I can do even more than this.
I thought we didn't need to be involved.
Aru, please.
Please what, Sun?
I'm minding my own business.
Yet she hired people to trash me online
and even threw paint at me.
Serves you right.
I was gonna trash-talk you myself.
Too bad I'm stuck hurt in bed.
Do you even realize what you've done?
What? I just removed
the thorn from my heart,
ripped it out of my life,
out of society.
You have no place in this world.
IN CASE OF FIRE, DO NOT USE THE ELEVATOR
You said you care about me,
that you worry about me.
Then kick her out! Get her out!
How could I even stand
being with a cruel woman like you?
Because you're a money-grubbing man!
My money didn't just buy you,
it bought your mom
and sister as well!.
- Pat!
- Go ahead!
If you're going to team up on me, do it!
Yeah, we didn't start out with love.
But I've been trying every day to build it
to make it what you wanted.
But making others suffer
doesn't heal the wounds of the past.
It only opens our wounds wider.
In the end, some things can't be fixed.
If you think you can buy me with money,
with no real connection,
today, your money means nothing to me.
Sun!
Sun. No, Sun!
I'm sorry for everything.
- Sun! Don't go, Sun!
- Miss Pat.
Sun!
Take care of yourself first.
Pat, that's enough, dear.
Mom.
Sun, get out
of my daughter's life already.
How much money do you want? Tell me!
I've had enough.
The only one who still needs me is Pat.
Mom, don't interfere.
I'll handle this myself.
I won't wait until things go too far,
until my daughter dies first.
That's good.
You love your daughter as you should.
Because a child grows on love,
not money, like you've been doing.
Even animals love their young.
A mother like you should understand that.
I've been suffering.
I've had to live
like no one else exists in this world.
Every day, I feel more worthless.
I know how much I owe you.
But I've lost
the most important thing in my life.
From now on,
I just want to live like a normal person.
Just go!
Don't cling to him.
I'll find someone better for you.
No, Mom. I want Sun! Mom, don't!
Mom, hold him back!
Why are you sending him away?
- Pat!
- Sun!
- No! Sun!
- Pat.
- Calm down, dear.
- Mom! Sun!
Let's end everything here.
If Mr. Sun still has anything pending,
send the list to my assistant.
Mr. Sun is someone I know.
Sun. Sun!
- Sun! You can't go!
- Pat!
- No!
- Pat! My dear!
- No way!
- Pat!
I love you, Pat.
- From now on, I won't leave you alone.
- No!
Go after Sun! Sun belongs to me!
Sun is mine! Sun!
- Sun!
- Pat!
Sun isn't yours.
He has his own life.
Sun is mine!
I want him!
- Sun is my toy!
- Pat.
- I'll play with him!
- Sit down, Pat.
- Calm down, Pat.
- Sun, come back right now!
- Sun!
- Pat!
It's my fault.
You can start over anytime, Sun.
Even when I was in prison,
behind those walls,
I never lost hope.
You had to go to jail
taking the blame for me.
I'm sorry.
I don't dwell on the past.
I've moved on from the times
I was really hurting.
These days, I'm just Aru,
the online seller, selling stuff,
working every day,
earning my own money,
not relying on anyone.
This is my life
and my pride.
Thank you.
My adoptive father, Mr. Kenji,
he died because he refused
to live under the rule of evil people.
My father was killed by Fire Phoenix.
I don't even know what Fire Phoenix is
and why they wanted my father dead.
Why didn't you try to find the truth?
There's no information
on what Fire Phoenix is.
All I know
is Fire Phoenix killed my father.
He was just a designer.
After the funeral, 3C Corp. contacted me.
I thought work
would make me forget the pain.
Want to try?
Welcome to the voicemail service.
If you ever want to paint,
you can come here anytime.
Are you opening an art school?
I can be a lot of things
if you want.
I'll take it.
I'll frame it for you.
No need. Thank you so much, Taiga.
My pleasure, student.
Hey, Rin. Today,
someone was lurking around
the front of the house.
I even took pictures.
Do you recognize whose car this is?
Whose car?
Huh?
I'll go take a shower first.
Sorry I didn't answer.
I was at Taiga's house.
He invited me, so I went.
It was an opportunity for us.
Did you find anything?
No. He was completely normal.
I didn't see anything.
I'll find out what he's hiding.
I trust you, Rin.
Don't forget how your father died.
Don't forget who brought you back to life.
I'm not trying to demand gratitude,
but I don't want my only niece
going down the wrong path.
Don't let anyone see your weakness, Rin.
Even matters of the heart
must be handled with your head.
Until now, we've got nothing.
Rin's just like any normal girl.
Normal? Is it because you
never really paid attention?
I know, but I have to find a way
to connect Rin to Fire Phoenix.
And you let yourself be an easy target,
almost getting shot.
Lucky you survived.
At this rate, next time,
they'll come at you harder.
Until Fire Phoenix gets my body,
I don't want anyone else
getting hurt because of me.
That's gonna be tough.
Instead of running,
we have to lure them out.
Hunt them down every way we can.
Everyone's here.
So let's get started. Please.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you for taking the time
to join today's press conference.
Our Cosmic Central Corporation Group
is honored to welcome Mr. Taiga,
the designer behind
the globally famous Kenji clothing brand,
as our signature designer
to create uniforms
for our employees.
We are also launching
the smart application, Hi,
a hub for shopping, talking,
and entertainment, bringing happiness
and prosperity to everyone.
The design concept
reflects the organization's identity.
Sleek, elegant,
leading in every investment,
with the vision
of being intelligent, powerful,
and confident.
Next, please welcome Mr. Taiga.
Hello.
The heart of this clothing design
is classic style,
to emphasize the stability of 3C Corp.
May I invite all executives
to take a group photo together?
Thank you very much.
Dad!
Cheers!
Dad's press conference
didn't even last half an hour,
and our 3C stock shot up 30%,
hitting the ceiling price.
The profits are obvious.
Without the ceiling,
it would've gone over 100%.
Today's press conference went really well.
The media interviewed Dad
for over an hour.
The uniform change was Nun's idea.
Keep going, dear.
Yes, thank you.
I'll get back to work.
From now on, 3C-Coin
will make you a future world leader.
Alright.
Make it happen, Te.
Dad and I are waiting to celebrate.
I will, for sure. When it comes
to money, you can trust me.
I'll use every coin
to build our 3C empire.
Thanks. You're the one
who planned the press conference.
I had to do it for you.
Go serve the room inside as well.
Okay.
Alright. Prep these for me.
You know, my next project will let
everyone farm their way to wealth.
- Sorry.
- Yes?
Could you take this inside to serve?
My stomach hurts.
Sure.
My 3C-Coin will soar,
generating the highest profits.
You can use it to buy anything,
even a human's breath.
That's really interesting.
Right?
Hey, aren't you going to the bathroom?
Oh, I'm going!
Techut was talking about 3C-Coin,
but it didn't sound
like it's just an investment.
What does he mean by human breath?
To survive, humans need the basics,
food, clothes, shelter, and…
- Medicine!
That's what I think.
Especially now, with pandemics,
vaccines, serums, and medicine
are insanely valuable.
But 3C Corp. doesn't make medicine.
Doesn't make it or you just don't know?
Rin, try to investigate.
Anything that comes out of Techut's mind,
it's bound to be evil,
corrupt, and disastrous.
Mr. Naruban wouldn't just let his son
do whatever he wants like that.
Don't underestimate a madman, Rin.
Okay, I get that you have faith
in Mr. Naruban.
But his son's definitely something else.
Anything we can stop,
we need to act before it's too late.
Do you trust an ex-con like me?
The prison isn't for rich people.
I graduated in medical science.
We're not hiring for this department.
I can actually do a lot of different jobs,
even outside my degree.
You have a conviction for murder.
Yes.
We'll get back to you.
Thank you.
Can I see that application?
Yes?
You want me to come back
for another interview?
Okay, sure!
Looking at your application,
I was surprised.
Surprised by what?
Everything.
You're full of surprises.
We're not that close.
Even if we were,
you have no right to touch me
without my permission.
You want the job, don't you?
I want it based on my skills,
not anything else.
Don't do anything
that could count as sexual harassment.
I could have you arrested.
Mr. Naruban's looking for you.
Mr. Te.
He said no need to meet anymore.
He's doing an online call to Europe now.
Online call?
Then why drag me here?
Stop meddling in everything
and messing up the timing.
Mr. Te.
I really want to thank you, Mr. Taiga.
I do what I'm supposed to.
It's no trouble.
My mother
would like to host a meal for you.
No need, Ms. Nun.
I have to do my best, anyway.
Please let me host you at my home.
Don't refuse me, okay?
Please.
- Please, Taiga. I want to go too.
- Madam.
Taiga.
- Stop throwing! That hurts!
I want to go with you.
You need someone with you
in case something happens.
Something will go wrong
because you are coming.
With your stubbornness, Taiga won't get
anything from Naruban's house.
Shut up, you bear!
Opportunities like this don't come easily.
You get to go into a tiger's den.
Just let Taiga do his job, Madam.
Please, madam.
Please, Ratee.
I'll handle this myself.
I'm tracking Punlop.
If we find a connection between these two,
Punlop and Rin,
we can be sure
she serves Fire Phoenix.
That's why Naruban sent her to shadow you,
ready to kill you at any moment.
Stay strong, Taiga.
A woman like Rin has no heart.
She'll do anything because it's an order.
I'm going to Naruban's house.
Good. Then we can find a way
to confirm Naruban's identity.
Fire Phoenix members
must wear masks at every meeting.
Each mask
contains the code
for all of a member's information.
I mean everything.
Even things the member has forgotten,
Fire Phoenix still keeps.
If we can get Naruban's mask,
we'll be able to access
the heart of Fire Phoenix for sure.
Who's going somewhere?
It's Dad.
He's got urgent investment business.
He has to go handle it.
Is something wrong, dear?
I invited Mr. Taiga over today,
so I thought
we could have a relaxed chat with him.
I'm still here.
Shall we give Mr. Taiga
a very special welcome?
Yes.
They cut the building's power
without telling us, causing a surge
that knocked out several CCTV servers.
The backup power isn't enough.
Let's go.
Thanks.
Mr. Taiga is here, Mom.
Flowers for you.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Naruban had to fly to Europe
on urgent business.
Understood.
We're so glad to have
the chance to welcome you.
I heard Nun invited some friends over,
so I invited Miss Ratee to join.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Your house is beautiful.
My mom has great style.
She decorated all of this herself.
This is why they say a man's power
comes from the woman behind him.
A happy family is the greatest thing.
Just seeing Mr. Naruban
and the kids smile,
that's enough to make my life complete.
I'm so envious.
Mr. Techut's family is so warm.
I hear you're a great cook too.
Oh.
Good grief, are you gossiping
about me too?
- Huh?
- Just a little.
I'll excuse myself to the bathroom.
This way, please.
This is the information Dad kept.
The Blazing Tiger gang in Japan,
they oppose Fire Phoenix.
They killed our people.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn