With a pretty face and figure like yours,
you'd be better at something fun.
Please me properly, and I'll promote you.
Everything about Taiga, report only to me.
Yes, sir.
Come here.
I want some new designs
for the next collection.
You draw really well.
Want to try?
I can't draw.
Stand still while you draw here,
so the wound doesn't tear.
There's no right or wrong in art.
Beauty comes from the heart, not the eyes.
I don't get it.
Use your heart. Use your feelings.
That's all you need.
I took my medicine, and I'm sleepy.
I think I'll go lie down.
Taiga, Madam Ratee
is in front of your house.
Where have you been?
I've missed you so much.
Since when did you start resenting me?
I could never resent someone
who once risked her life to save mine.
Stop talking about debts of gratitude.
Our relationship is only about love
and marriage.
Please, Ratee.
Sometimes I have work, I have business.
You make it sound
like I'm invading your personal space.
I'm willing to be second.
Because your father
comes first in your heart.
But after him, it must be me.
You're not allowed to let
any other woman come between us.
I won't accept it.
You know that, Taiga?
Why are you pretending to sleep?
I'm not pretending.
I actually fell asleep.
Go ahead and keep sleeping.
I can sit here and work.
I want to be alone.
Te, I'll go upstairs first.
There's a meeting.
- Sorry.
Don't look!
My wound still hurts.
Why are you forcing me to draw?
If you want to know what's in my heart,
the distance between us is too far.
But the distance between us
shouldn't be this close.
STAFF ONLY
Greeting me with a gun, Khanin?
It's been a long time
since I saw my old boss.
The one who loves his team
more than anything.
You've got a new boss now.
Ever since I was pressured
and kicked out
of the police force, which I loved,
I promised myself
I'd never be anyone's subordinate again
until I've avenged everyone.
You're as determined as ever.
But nothing's the same anymore.
Right. Nothing is the same.
You survived,
kept working, while the rest
of your subordinates died,
disappeared, lost their futures.
You survived alone, living comfortably!
I have to fight for myself first.
For yourself.
It's a shame I ever had faith in you.
It's time
that you take responsibility
for everything, Punlop.
Damn it!
Your made-to-order meal.
Just how you like it.
You're good at a lot of things.
Pink mochi with pickled sakura leaves,
only available this season.
Food makes us feel like we're with family.
I'm alone. I don't have a family.
My dad died long ago.
Did I say something wrong?
Because I mentioned my dad?
I'm fine.
You should eat.
Any info yet?
Not yet. Rin's being careful. How's Ratee?
A mess, totally wasted.
But don't worry. I'm watching her.
Thanks a lot.
Dhammatat, you went too hard on Rin.
It had to be that rough.
Only then can you get Rin.
Make every second count.
Being this close to her,
something's bound to slip.
Thank you.
Is everything done?
You're as determined as ever.
But nothing's the same anymore.
It's a shame I ever had faith in you.
I have to fight for myself first.
Is this the reward for dedication?
Right now,
the arrest team is under investigation,
accused of misconduct.
The media's criticizing us,
saying we overstepped our duties
and abused our power against civilians.
They're not civilians!
They're human traffickers.
Backed by higher-ups
protecting the gang from the top.
Sir.
Do we really have to be the scapegoats?
I'll protect our team to the end.
Truth never dies.
You have to fight, sir.
We won't abandon you.
If we take them on, everyone will see
that you dared to challenge injustice.
We can uproot them.
Only if the higher-ups
give the green light
and ignore the bribes
those scoundrels throw at them.
Let's fight together, Khanin.
Yes.
Can't you drop this case, son?
The more you pursue it,
the less safe you'll be.
Now we're close to the gang's boss, Mom.
Our lives won't have anything left either.
You know, they're trying
to seize our land.
The witness told the police I cheated.
And the police believe them,
without investigating further?
Please stop. I'm scared.
Even with you being a cop,
they're doing this.
I'm sorry. I can't stop.
I won't back down.
Right now, I'm under investigation
for corruption.
I have to fight.
People need to see what I'm doing.
I ran into someone I shouldn't have.
A villain from the past.
Someone I trusted.
Someone who betrayed his own team.
He was my boss. A boss I respected.
A boss I devoted my life to. He taught me
to fight for justice,
to stand up for those who were oppressed,
so they wouldn't be alone.
I've faced a lot of terrible things
in my life.
But in the end,
I haven't even been able
to protect my family.
Rescue team, spread out! Search quickly!
Report to headquarters. We found a body.
My father, mother, and sister
were staged as suicides because of debts.
As for me,
I was fired for crimes I never committed.
Every piece of evidence was fabricated
to eliminate our whole team, except him.
Only he survived!
He lives comfortably atop the corpses
of our team and my family.
His name is Punlop.
He disappeared for years.
But today,
he showed up at the 3C building.
- Could it be related to Naruban?
- Someone like Punlop…
He's a cop who can be bought with money.
He might be protecting Naruban.
What about you?
Did you get anything else from Rin?
I'm working on a way for Rin
to open Inspector Phumin's box.
Are you sure it'll work?
You're close to Rin. You won't get killed
or let your guard down with her, right?
What's Taiga hiding?
There are security cameras everywhere.
Except in the bedroom and the art room.
If you can't find anything,
pull out immediately. Don't get caught.
Yes.
‪It's so pretty, Sun.
Do you like it?
The most! I love everything you buy me.
Hug me.
Not close enough.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Where did you buy this outfit?
I don't remember. But you like it, right?
I'll get you another one.
I love it! The cut is perfect.
Thank you.
But a beautiful girl
would look good in anything.
Hey, you really have a sweet mouth.
The other side too.
Has your hubby been spoiling you lately?
You're all smiles!
Of course!
You've really got him well-behaved.
Pure charm, that's all.
Always showing off
your wealth and your hubby!
Hey, Pat, this outfit is gorgeous.
Looks familiar. Where did you get it?
- My boyfriend--
- Hey!
- Here, this page is famous..
- Hello, guys!
- Good stuff, cheap, exactly like the pics.
- Aru's Back.
- The seller's amazing.
- This is the first dress
- Let me see.
- I'm going to show you.
It's super cute!
If you already have a boyfriend,
wear this to dinner.
He'll adore you, I promise.
And if you don't have a boyfriend yet,
wear this, and I guarantee you'll get one!
- Alright then…
- Here you go.
Okay.
Do you guys want
something to drink? My treat.
- Sure.
- Anything's fine.
Okay.
You disgusting, awful boyfriend!
Screw you!
Are you seriously making me wear
your ex-wife's outfit?
Pat, calm down!
Get out of my house! Out!
- Get out!
- Pat!
Pat, listen to me.
It's just a similar outfit, that's all.
No! You bought your ex-wife's outfit
for me to wear.
You want her to laugh
at me behind my back, don't you?
Now that I'm with her husband
and wearing her clothes!
Pat, Aru was just a girlfriend.
She's not my wife.
The only one who's my wife is you.
The only one who's my wife is you, Pat.
You haven't done anything
with that salesgirl, right?
No.
- Swear it.
- I swear.
You won't leave me
like my parents left me, right?
I won't.
I'll stay with you.
I thought you hated drawing already.
I had some free time, so I tried again.
Come on. Keep drawing. Don't stop yet.
My wound's healed.
I won't bother you anymore.
Is this a farewell meal?
Warabi mochi, sprinkled with kinako
and drizzled with kuromitsu.
Enjoy.
Ten kilos of warabi roots
yield only 70 grams of starch.
Warabi made from real warabi starch,
not tapioca,
is rare and expensive.
My dad and I, we love eating
warabi mochi in the summer.
Our 3C Corp. needs more investment.
We could sell shares to outsiders.
That'll give us more capital.
Do whatever you think is best, my friend.
Chanchai.
Go ahead and expand the factory.
Reach out to every country
that can help develop our technology.
Sure. That's my specialty.
Our 3C Corp. will be number one.
Our profit this year has exceeded 200%.
Our satellite is about to go online.
What else are you worried about, Prin?
Someone wants our customer data.
Are you crazy?
Customer data is top secret.
Who would want it?
Fire Phoenix.
I can't let my family die
the way yours did, Prin.
HUMAN TRAFFICKING
Pok, Prab, Pun.
You know this family?
That child is me.
I'm the only surviving child.
I got a new life
thanks to Mr. Kenji's care.
Rin, this box means a lot to me.
It's yours, isn't it?
No.
My friend left it with me.
My friend's parent is a police officer.
INSEETHONG FARM
Inseethong Farm?
Two more wrong tries,
and we won't be able to open it.
Maybe the answer's here.
Walk carefully. Don't tear the wound.
Mr. Taiga went for inspiration?
Yes. The team called,
said Mr. Taiga sent word to notify us.
Rin isn't here either.
He's probably really looking
for inspiration.
Thailand is stunning.
As for Rin,
the CEO must've given her some task.
She's been gone for several days.
I guarantee she's got
the CEO's approval for sure.
Two rooms, please.
Only one left.
All others are fully booked.
Are you sure?
Here it is.
- Which way do we go?
- This way, please.
I'm at Inseethong Farm.
How's everything over there?
Madam Ratee's losing it,
questioning me like I'm a criminal. If she
tracked you with her dad's satellite,
she'd already be on your tail.
But no rush to come back.
I've reserved everything there.
Only the suite is left.
Now, how you squeeze out the secret,
that's all on you.
Rin, be careful, okay?
Share your location with me.
Why's your boss giving you so much work?
Heavy tasks and sending you out of town…
They better pay you extra.
Don't just accept it.
You silly bear! What are you doing
in the bathroom so long?
What are you doing?
Peeking? Did you see anything?
Or did you sneak your phone in
to film a clip to sell?
Hey, what are you doing?
Your creepy bear clips are lame!
Who would want to watch that stuff?
- Wanna see?
- You silly!
Hey, just a peek. Come on.
- Just a peek first.
- Use the bathroom quickly!
- I'm next! Hurry up!
- Check it out. Maybe I can sell it, madam.
Come here. I'll help.
It's done.
If it gets infected, it'll be trouble.
The hospital can handle it.
I'll buy it, all of 3C's stuff!
I'll kick Nunnapat out.
Wherever she goes to work,
I'll push her out, kick her out,
and buy everything up.
I'll pour it for you.
Thanks.
Does it make you happy?
Of course! Haven't you ever held a grudge?
I have.
My grudge was so strong, I wanted to kill.
But then I calmed down and laughed
at myself for thinking such stupid things.
Stop pretending to be good.
I'm just a normal person,
not good or anything.
I just know what my flaws are,
and I try not to trigger
the worst in myself.
I don't want to be so bad,
to the point
that there's no turning back.
If it's necessary,
do it.
Go all the way.
Don't look back, and don't regret it.
Every one of us
can close their eyes and shut our minds.
But right here…
Inside here…
Every feeling…
No one sees it.
But you always know…
what you're feeling
inside.
Don't!
I order you.
You're not allowed to feel anything.
Don't.
Did your father ever tell you
about the cases,
like the family
that was murdered ten years ago?
Taiga, Mr. Naruban was poisoned.
You've been through a lot, Naruban.
Soon you'll be off duty.
You'll finally get a long rest.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn