Finish this drink first, then you can go.
You're getting close to the target.
You don't believe
that Lirin, the inspector's youngest,
is dead, do you?
Taiga, did you see the board this morning?
Stocks and 3C-Coin got smashed.
Do you know who did it?
Ratee's father.
You know,
if Taiga just says the word,
I can even buy this entire building.
I bet Mr. Taiga doesn't know
this is what you think.
It's true that
I haven't known him for long,
but you can't understand
the heart of an artist as well as I do.
Then just you wait.
Very soon, I'll take over Cosmic Central
as my wedding gift to him.
No way!
Yeah?
What could someone like you
possibly maintain?
You keep walking tall,
but your role is meaningless.
You contribute nothing
to the company's profit.
You're an outsider.
Don't act like you know everything.
I've done my research.
If I'm going to put my dog on a leash,
I'll make sure its leash and collar
are pretty and perfect for it.
Don't worry, I've chosen a collar
that's perfect for Cosmic Central Group.
You won't be embarrassed.
Hey, man. I need your help.
I want to know about the company
who tanked 3C-Coin.
I'm going to deal with them, of course.
But not to their faces.
You can let me go now.
Wait.
Move a muscle, and I'll do it for real.
You sure are worth what you're paid.
I don't work for you. Stay away from me.
Hey!
Madam,
you're using your dad's company
to attack 3C-Coin and 3C Group.
Taiga's got nothing to do with this.
This one was all you, madam.
Love and jealousy sure beat all.
Cornball.
So it's true. I was spot on, right?
You could tell it was me?
Who am I?
I'm an unemployed drifter.
I day trade just to get by
and be able to afford coffee.
Taiga should really choose his friends.
He did.
He chooses based on looks.
So,
what do I get from talking to you?
Nothing! What a waste of time.
Just listen for once.
What I'm trying to say
is even I could find out it was you
who intentionally tanked 3C,
so, of course, the experts
could find that out too.
But isn't it normal?
It's just a part of investment.
Are you sure about making 3C your enemy?
Just worry about
your own future, you giant bear.
If I didn't ask, stay out of it.
What a cute nickname.
"You giant bear."
Well, suit yourself then,
Madam Problematic.
Put away her stuff
and get her something to drink.
Understood.
Go get some rest.
Yes, sir.
You're Naruban's driver?
Yes, ma'am.
How strange. He's never hired
a female driver before.
I used to work at the office.
I was also a security guard.
Really? A pretty face like you
as security?
You look like you're around Nun's age.
Oh, Rin. What are you doing here?
I'm Mr. Naruban's driver.
You can go get some rest.
Understood.
I beg you, Techut. She works for your dad.
Don't worry, Mom.
I know a snack when I see one.
Have a seat, Mr. Taiga.
If Cosmic Central
would invest in fashion products,
would the Kenji brand
be interested in partnering with us?
I appreciate the offer,
but we like to keep it simple
and only work with familiar faces.
He turned us down, Nun.
May I use your restroom?
Of course.
Come on. Come here. Up, up.
Eat.
Eat it. Aren't you hungry?
Eat it. Come on. Here.
Meow, meow, meow.
Eat your food, kitty.
Eat and then sleep,
so you won't roam around
flirting with guys.
- Hey.
- Okay? You're so cute.
- Hey!
- Ow!
Madam!
You're always hurting me and violating me.
Hey, let me tell you something.
Your love and jealousy for him
are like bag holding.
You don't want to regret a loss,
but you also don't know how long
you'll have to wait to make a profit.
If you just sell it
and invest in a different crypto,
I assure you it'll be way more exciting.
Why don't you try a new crypto like me?
Wanna try?
I wouldn't choose you
even if you were on discount.
When will Taiga be back?
I didn't ask him.
Where'd he go?
I'm not his wife. I didn't question him.
- You!
- Hey!
There you go again.
- Begging for more?
- Again and again, always hitting me.
You silly bear. Why didn't you ask him?
Don't you have a phone, madam?
He turned off his phone.
Taiga turned off his phone
to ignore Madam Problematic.
For sure, 100%.
Oh my gosh.
Hey, you!
Madam!
Enough, enough! Man!
Watch your mouth!
The restroom's this way, Mr. Taiga.
Why are you scared of me?
There's a fine line
between "scared" and "hate".
Sorry,
I don't quite understand Thai.
You should learn the insults
before the compliments.
Then, I should let you teach me.
Do I look like a thief to you?
This is not your home.
Even if you're a guest, have some manners.
I bet a host like Mrs. Giranun
is well-mannered enough
not to tell her bodyguard
to follow my every step
and stare me down like this.
I'm just doing my job.
Treating a guest this way is your job?
My job is to check up on everyone
who acts suspicious.
You know, I'm starting to wonder.
Since when did you start monitoring me…
and knowing me so well?
Hey. Look a little lively, won't you?
I asked my dad to bring you along.
I'm here to drive you, aren't I?
You aren't driving now, are you?
Has anyone ever told you
you're not meant for fighting?
With a pretty face and body like yours,
you should be doing something
nice and fun.
Nun!
Nun is the type of girl
who always gets what she wants.
Mr. Taiga, listen to this seashell.
Come on, Mr. Taiga.
There's a sound!
How funny.
Listen.
How is it? Is it good?
Are you sick?
Let me give you a pelvic exam.
Get rid of Rin,
then I'll do whatever you ask.
Don't struggle.
Please me.
I'll give you a promotion.
I'll promote you faster
than my dad ever did.
Got it?
Okay.
Ms. Nun,
my online team wants to talk.
There's an issue with our prototype.
Sure, I'll be waiting here.
Thank you.
Tell the designer I want the outfit's
details to look more realistic.
Hey!
Techut!
Damn it, Techut.
Damn it, Techut!
Get changed. Don't go anywhere.
Do you understand, Rin?
What do you want me to do with Techut?
He'll never admit to it
unless there's proof.
Your body is proof.
I don't want to lose my job.
I can hire you.
Don't put up with harassment.
Thank you, but let me make
my own decision on this.
I handed her to you on a silver platter,
yet you let her get away.
You suck.
I'll make her mine today, no matter what.
Where are you going?
Rin already checked out last night.
Dumbass.
Mr. Taiga!
Why'd you come without inviting me?
I'm ready. Should we practice surfing now?
Ms. Nun, I have to go back to Bangkok.
But you said you'd be free.
I have to edit the design
with our pattern designer right away.
I'm sorry, Ms. Nun.
Someone came to Inspector Phumin's house.
Yeah.
Mom's birthday.
YOUNG EXECUTIVES CO-FOUND CCC
COSMIC CENTRAL CORPORATION
Someone took the box
with the files on your family's case
I almost had them.
But luckily, you can still go
in and out of Naruban's house freely.
Naruban doesn't trust me.
Rin's always monitoring me.
I trust that you can do this.
Who would also want
the Fire Phoenix case files?
But my dad's dead.
He spent his life working for others.
But the law can't protect
every good person.
Fire Phoenix
is a secret organization that works
to eliminate injustice in society.
That means Fire Phoenix
can find who killed my father.
Uncle, where is Fire Phoenix?
POL.LT.COL. PHUMIN PHONGRIT
BORN: NOVEMBER 11, 1972
DIED: NOVEMBER 1, 2018
Inspector Phumin?
Rin knows him too?
SLOW DOWN
Get in!
Quick!
Your fever's gone down.
Where are you, Rin?
I'm sure you don't want the cops to know.
That's why I brought you here.
Does your wound hurt?
I'm okay.
You still look pale, though.
You need to rest.
Eat up.
The bodyguard Dad hired called in sick.
She turned off her phone.
We can't contact her.
And the designer's gone too.
They're both gone.
Taiga's working on a design for me.
If believing that
makes you feel better, then sure.
Can you contact her yet?
She turned off her phone.
Turned off her phone?
What about her home?
At the address she gave us, her apartment,
I got no response.
And her parents' home?
Also no response.
Both the designer
and the bodyguard are gone.
I bet they've been boning
so many times they lost count.
You can't go to work yet.
I don't want to bother you.
This house is large enough
that you can avoid me all day.
I've arranged for a doctor.
He'll check on your wound every day.
Thank you.
Get well first. Don't come in to work yet.
I'll count it as if
you're still working for me.
If anything related to Taiga comes up,
you report it to me only.
Yes, sir.
Greeting me with a bullet, huh, Khanin?
It's the best way to greet an old boss.
It's about damn time
you took responsibility
for everything, Punlop.
Pok, Prab, Pun.
You know this family?
This kid is me.
I'm the only son who survived.
If we get it wrong two more times,
we're locked out for good.
Maybe the answer lies in there.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya